"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138948","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many planning applications on Green Belt land in (a) Walsall South constituency and (b) England were called in by the Secretary of State in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277186","277186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138949","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department last (a) undertook a review and (b) updated the National Policy Statement for National Networks; and whether he plans undertake a (i) review of and (ii) public consultation on the National Policy Statement for National Networks in the next parliamentary session.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277192","277192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138950","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many planning applications on the Green Belt in (a) Walsall South constituency and (b) England were approved after referral to the National Planning Unit in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277187","277187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138951","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives from mobile phone operating companies on establishing a roaming system in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277107","277107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138952","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on trends in the level of Tazir laws in Iran in relation to the (a) arbitrary punishment, (b) imprisonment and (c) internal exile of members of the Baha’i community in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277106","277106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138953","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has undertaken a recent assessment of the potential effects on businesses in the UK of leaving the EU VAT area.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277127","277127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138954","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether men ordained as deacons in the Roman Catholic Church are Ministers of Religion for the purpose of applications under Tier 2 and Tier 5 of the immigration rules.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277208","277208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138955","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the criteria are for an investigation of an asylum seeker by Immigration Enforcement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277290","277290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138956","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how his Department plans to evaluate the effectiveness of its specialist training on faith or belief-based asylum claims.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277291","277291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138957","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how his Department determines whether the treatment of non-religious people and other religious minorities in Egypt amounts to persecution.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277292","277292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138958","2019-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the public consultation on proposals for the regulation of district heating networks.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277236","277236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138959","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 May 2019 to Question 257548, what further collaboration his Department is planning with (a) the Animal and Plant Health Agency and (b) Border Force following that meeting with the Immigration Minister.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277278","277278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138960","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the prevalence of the use of e-scooters; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277108","277108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138961","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many calls were made to the pension credit claim line in each of the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277103","277103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138962","2019-07-17","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the equity of means-testing for child benefit in relation to couples in which one parent is entitled to child benefit and the other is not.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277264","277264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138963","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals for amending the regulation advertising for (a) aesthetic and (b) cosmetic treatments.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277124","277124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138964","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Probate Service in processing applications for probate in 2019; how he measures that performance; and how long it took on average to process a probate application in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277181","277181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138965","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he is taking steps to reduce the time taken to process applications for probate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277182","277182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138966","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on the application-processing performance of the Probate Service of changes to the fees structure in 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277183","277183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138967","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to make a decision on Housing Infrastructure Fund bids relating to Essex.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277184","277184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138968","2019-07-18","Women and Equalities","2019-07-15","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to respond to Question 267246 on Employment: Disability, tabled by the hon. Member for Warwick and Leamington on 20 June 2019.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277263","277263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138969","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether Homes England has made an assessment of the Housing Infrastructure Fund bids relating to Essex; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277185","277185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138970","2019-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to her oral contribution of 8 July 2019, Official Report, column 19, when she plans to announce the change of policy in relation to guidance on sharing and receiving intelligence.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277216","277216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138971","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2019 to Question 273806 on Prisoners: Training, what courses are listed on that HMPPS Management Information System for each prison.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277220","277220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138972","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the of Answer 9 July 2019 to Question 273431 on Courts: Sales, which organisation was responsible for providing each of the valuations.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277221","277221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138973","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of hours per week was that a (a) child and (b) young adult aged 19 to 21 in custody spent playing sport in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277222","277222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138974","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful prosecutions following a request made under the European Arrest Warrant there have been in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277223","277223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138975","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of children in custody were held in (a) Secure Children's Homes, (b) Secure Training Centres and (c) Young Offenders Institutions in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277224","277224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138976","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of places available in Secure Children's Home was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277225","277225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138977","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prisoners are housed in resettlement units in the area that they will be released  into within three months of their release date.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277226","277226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138978","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) exclusions for violence against an adult and (b) exclusions for verbal abuse or threatening behaviour against an adult there have been in each of the last 20 years for which data available.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277298","277298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138979","2019-07-17","Church Commissioners","2019-07-15","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what discussions the (a) Church of England and (b) Church in Wales have had with (i) other religious and faith bodies, (ii) the Government and (iii) the Equality and Human Rights Commission on the exemption of those bodies from equality legislation for appointments and provision of services.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277265","277265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138980","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on reports of Eritrean soldiers on Yemeni islands in the Red sea.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277115","277115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138981","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the 2020-21 Local Government Finance Settlement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277135","277135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138982","2019-07-17","Women and Equalities","2019-07-15","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions the Government has had with the (a) Church of England, (b) Church in Wales and (c) Church of Scotland on those bodies' exemption from equality legislation in terms of (i) appointments and (ii) provision of services.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277266","277266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138983","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the 2020-21 Local Government Finance Settlement will form part of a multi-year financial settlement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277136","277136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138984","2019-07-17","Women and Equalities","2019-07-15","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions her Department has has with the Equality and Human Rights Commission on the exemptions from equality legislation applied to the (a) Church in England, (b) Church in Wales and (c) Church of Scotland.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277267","277267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138985","2019-07-17","Women and Equalities","2019-07-15","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government has taken to monitor Church of England compliance with equality legislation.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277268","277268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138986","2019-07-17","Church Commissioners","2019-07-15","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, pursuant to Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 269594 on Churches, which dioceses keep records of (a) thefts and (b) attempted thefts of metal.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277093","277093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138987","2019-07-17","Church Commissioners","2019-07-15","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 269594, whether the Diocese of St Albums holds any records of the type of metal stolen.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277094","277094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138988","2019-07-17","Church Commissioners","2019-07-15","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Commissioners plan to investigate which roofing material is (a) least likely to be stolen and (b) best value; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277095","277095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138989","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by what proportion, compared to current figures, will carbon emissions from aviation at Heathrow change following the completion of a third runway.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277099","277099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138990","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to include emissions from international aviation in the Government's climate targets.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277100","277100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138991","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he will take to offset the carbon emissions from increased aviation into and out of Heathrow following its proposed expansion.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277101","277101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138992","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the viability of deploying sustainable alternative aviation fuels.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277102","277102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138993","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many licences his Department has issued to kill (a) cormorants and (b) goosanders in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277096","277096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138994","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) cormorants and (b) herons on immature fish in English river systems.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277097","277097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138995","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of salmon stocks in English rivers.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277098","277098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138996","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for treating anorexia of the research published in July 2019 in the journal Nature Genetics entitled genome-wide association study identifies eight risk loci and implicates metabo-psychiatric origins for anorexia nervosa.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277123","277123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138997","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Women of 11 July 2019, Official Report column 439, what forms of documentation have been provided to each of the more than 6,400 applicants to the Windrush scheme.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277132","277132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138998","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many outstanding Windrush scheme applications there are.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277133","277133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138999","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will provide a breakdown of the type of documentation received by the 4,200 successful applications through the Windrush Scheme.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277134","277134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139000","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the per capita funding for St Helens Council is in the current financial year.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277214","277214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139001","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the availability of refuges for victims of domestic violence in (a) St Helens borough and (b) the North West.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277215","277215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139002","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to extend the soft drinks industry levy to milk replacement drinks containing sugar; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277130","277130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139003","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to (a) extend the scope of the soft drinks industry levy to other products containing free sugars and (b) increase the rate of the levy.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277131","277131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139004","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to enable the identification of the age of ovine animals other than by the eruption of the permanent incisor under the Transmissible Spongiform Encephalopathies Regulations (2018).","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277203","277203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139005","2019-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State in Westminster Hall on 3 July, column 584WH, if he will provide a reference to the section of the award of March 2015 of the UN Convention on the Law of the Sea Tribunal which concluded that the Agreement in 1965 to the detachment of the Chagos Archipelago was legally binding.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277209","277209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139006","2019-07-17","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether part-time students studying undergraduate courses using distance learning will be eligible to apply for maintenance loans for the 2019-20 academic year.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277277","277277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139007","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of supply of the drug Actavis Propranolol in pharmacies in (a) North East Somerset and (b) Somerset.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277188","277188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139008","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish draft guidance on the use of Knife Crime Prevention Orders; when the consultation process on that guidance will begin; and for how long it will run.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277272","277272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139009","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which stakeholders his Department is engaging to develop guidance on the proposed knife crime prevention orders.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277273","277273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139010","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the knife crime prevention order pilots will begin; how many pilots will be run; and in which local authorities those pilots will run.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277274","277274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139011","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the knife crime prevention order pilots will include orders on people under 18 years of age; and what criteria will be used to assess the success of those pilots.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277275","277275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139026","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure the immediate release of Roadchef pension fund monies to Christine Slack and other former Roadchef employees; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277311","277311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139027","2019-07-18","Department for International Development","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what policies his Department has on the provision of funding for the low income indigenous peoples of the Amazon basin in Brazil.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277312","277312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139028","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many background checks on foreign offenders were requested by police, broken down by police force, in the most recent year for which information is available .","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277301","277301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139029","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign offenders were prosecuted by each police force, in the most recent year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277302","277302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139030","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he has taken as a result of the HM Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire and Rescue Services report on police effectiveness in March 2018 which concluded that background checks were being missed on foreign national offenders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277303","277303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139031","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2019 to Question 273758 on Courts, what the average length of time was between first court appearance and trial in Bradford Crown Court in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277304","277304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139032","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 272804 on Court: Sales, if he will place a copy of the valuation report relating to Lambeth County Court in the Library.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277305","277305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139033","2019-07-17","Cabinet Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he had made of the number of (a) male and (b) female perpetrators of domestic violence who have also been victims of domestic violence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277306","277306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139034","2019-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much coal was imported for use in (a) UK coal fired power stations (b) UK steel works and (c) other industrial processes in 2018.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277307","277307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139035","2019-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much coal the UK has stockpiled.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277308","277308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139036","2019-07-18","Department for International Development","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what policies her Department has on the provision of funding for impoverished indigenous people of the Amazon basin in Brazil.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277313","277313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139037","2019-07-17","Cabinet Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the prevalence of domestic violence within (a) gay, (b) lesbian and (c) bisexual couple relationships.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277309","277309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139038","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if HMRC will ensure the immediate release of Roadchef pension fund monies to Christine Slack and other former Roadchef employees; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277314","277314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139039","2019-07-17","Cabinet Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the prevalence of partner domestic violence perpetrated by each sex by (a) ethnicity and (b) nationality.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277310","277310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138443","2019-07-15","Department for Education","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships were created in the construction sector in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276218","276218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138607","2019-07-17","Department for Education","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to help ensure that schools take the leading role in deciding whether to (a) form and (b) join a multi-academy trust.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276587","276587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138608","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Indian counterpart on the time taken to conduct the trial of Jagtar Singh Johal in that country.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276588","276588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138609","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan Implementation Framework: system support offer, what his timescale is for completing the national review of Care Treatment Review policies.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276531","276531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138610","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan Implementation Framework: system support offer, whether the quality assurance framework to strengthen existing oversight arrangements for autistic people and people with learning disabilities will be mandatory; and what funding local authorities and CCGs will receive to ensure they can follow that framework.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276532","276532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138611","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan Implementation Framework, what targets his Department has set for increased access to specialist community perinatal mental health services in 2019-20.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276533","276533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138612","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan Implementation Framework, what the timeframe is for meeting the target of 345,000 additional children and young people being able to access NHS-funded mental health services.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276534","276534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138613","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan Implementation Framework, how much additional funding he plans to allocate to support the development of school or college-based Mental Health Support Teams.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276535","276535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138614","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a return scheme for plastic bottles of all sizes for the economy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276508","276508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138615","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of freedom of information requests received by HS2 Limited were resolvable requests withheld in full for (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018 and (e) the first quarter of 2019.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276515","276515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138616","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on encouraging schools to expand vegetarian options for school meals.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276580","276580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138617","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2019 to Question 267262 on Police: Disciplinary Proceedings, what information a written explanation is required to include in the event of an investigation going beyond 12 months.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276577","276577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138618","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2019 to Question 267262 on Police: Disciplinary Proceedings, what plans he has to ensure the (a) police and (b) Independent Office for Police Conduct take forward the next steps identified in the event of an investigation going beyond 12 months.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276578","276578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138619","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2019 to Question 267262 on Police: Disciplinary Proceedings, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of requiring a written explanation in the event of an investigation going beyond 12 months times on lowering investigation times; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276579","276579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138620","2019-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to work towards finding a political solution to the conflict in Libya.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276558","276558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138621","2019-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the assault on the UN-backed Government of National Accord in Libya.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276559","276559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138622","2019-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will support calls for a UN Investigation into the recent airstrike on a migrant detention centre in Tripoli.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276560","276560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138623","2019-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his French counterpart on arms sales to combatants in the conflict in Libya.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276561","276561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138624","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will allocate more funding to the fire service in the 2019-20 financial year.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276608","276608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138625","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Russian counterpart on the role the Russian military in Ukraine.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276524","276524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138626","2019-07-16","Department for International Trade","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to comply with the recommendation of the UN Special Rapporteur on freedom of opinion and expression to impose an immediate moratorium on the export, sale, transfer, use or servicing of privately developed surveillance tools until a human rights-compliant safeguards regime is in place.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276582","276582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138627","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Ukrainian counterpart on the involvement of the Russian military in Ukraine.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276525","276525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138628","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Sri Lankan counterpart on the implementation of UN Human Rights Council resolutions regarding the aftermath of the Sri Lankan civil war.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276526","276526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138629","2019-07-16","Department for International Trade","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the UK exported surveillance equipment to the Philippines in 2019.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276583","276583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138630","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to (a) promote and (b) fund local welfare assistance.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276564","276564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138631","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will allocate additional funding for local welfare assistance.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276565","276565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138632","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of  change the level of tax for NHS consultants working overtime.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276566","276566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138633","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Government's announcement that NHS health information will be made available through Amazon’s Alexa, what steps he plans to take to ensure the privacy of patient data.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276567","276567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138634","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking reduce waiting times for routine operations.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276568","276568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138635","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made representations to the US Administration for the release of Abdullatif Nasser after Mr Nasser was cleared for transfer in 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276505","276505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138636","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the US Administration on releasing Guantanamo Bay inmates who have been cleared for release by the Periodic Review Board.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276506","276506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138639","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to reduce waiting times for autism assessments for adults.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276605","276605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138640","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps with NHS England to implement a waiting time standard for autism diagnosis in the CCG Improvement and Assessment Framework in order to tackle regional differences.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276606","276606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138641","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to work with NHS England to establish autism diagnosis waiting times standards for each (a) sustainability and transformation partnership and (b) integrated care system.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276607","276607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138642","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Wales and (d) England (i) made new applications for personal independence payments and (ii) were reassessed from disability living allowance to personal independence payments in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276584","276584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138643","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Wales and (d) England that were in receipt of disability living allowance and underwent a reassessment for personal independence payments applied for mandatory reconsideration of the decision in each year since 2013; and how many of those people (i) had their decision overturned and (ii) had their decision upheld.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276585","276585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138644","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Wales and (d) England that made a new application for personal independence payment applied for mandatory reconsideration of the decision in each year since 2013, and how many of those people had had their decision (i)  overturned and (ii) upheld.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276586","276586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138645","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of Local Plans which include a requirement for new homes to be accessible and adaptable.","Biography information for Julia Lopez","Julia Lopez","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276602","276602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138646","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that more homes are built to accessible and adaptable standards for older and disabled people; and what steps his Department is taking to assess progress on such building standards.","Biography information for Julia Lopez","Julia Lopez","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276603","276603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138647","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2019 to Question 269620 on Hearing Impairment, what steps his Department has taken to (a) issue and (b) promote commissioning guidance to clinical commissioning groups in relation to people with hearing loss.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276507","276507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138648","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are employed (a) full time and (b) part-time by the Royal Mint.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276575","276575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138649","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 252658 on Youth Offending Teams: Grants, what the real terms change was in the value of Youth justice grants allocated to each local authority to fund Youth Offending Teams between 2010-11 and 2019-20.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276569","276569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138650","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 252658 on Youth Offending Teams: Grants, what the value was of youth justice grants allocated to each local authority to fund Youth Offending Teams in 2010-11.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276570","276570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138651","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 252658 on Youth Offending Teams: Grants and with reference to allocation of funding for 2019-20, what the value was of youth justice grants allocated to each local authority to fund Youth Offending Teams in 2010-11.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276571","276571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138652","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time was for a not guilty plea trial for an alleged sexual offence in each court in (a) 2011 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276572","276572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138653","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Recorders sat in each court that was open on the 1 May 2019.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276573","276573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138654","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions prison staff in each prison had their pay deducted for not being able to complete a shift as a result of an assault in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276574","276574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138655","2019-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) level of demand for electricity and (b) electricity generation capacity there will be in the UK in the next five years.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276589","276589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138656","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue (a) capital gains tax and (b) stamp duty have raised for the Exchequer (i) in total quantum terms and (ii) as a proportion of total UK revenue in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276590","276590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138657","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money from the public purse has been spent on infrastructure in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276591","276591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138658","2019-07-16","Department for Transport","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's news story, Competition opens to create community facilities as Pacer trains retire from passenger service, published on 11 July 2019, how much that competition has cost; and how many of his Department's staff have worked on that competition to date.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276541","276541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138659","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many mediators there are in England; and how many mediations by subject have taken place in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276592","276592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138660","2019-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the amount of woodland there was in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276593","276593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138661","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for visitor visas from (a) US, (b) Russian, (c) Indian and (d) Chinese citizens were (i) granted and (ii) declined in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276516","276516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138662","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time was for a decision on visitor visa application from  (a) US, (b) Russian, (c) Indian and (d) Chinese citizens in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276517","276517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138663","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what performance targets his Department has put in place for the time taken to make a decision on a visitor visa application form (a) US, (b) Russian, (c) Indian and (d) Chinese citizens.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276518","276518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138664","2019-07-16","Department for Transport","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2019 to Question 273804 on Freight, what assessment he has made of the value for money of the freight network capacity plans that he announced in December 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276542","276542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138665","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what (a) quantum and (b) proportion of greenbelt land in England has been built on in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276594","276594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138666","2019-07-16","Department for Transport","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2019 to Question 273804 on Freight, what comparative assessment he has made of the value for money of the plans for new freight network capacity made in (a) December 2018 and (b) June 2019.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276543","276543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138667","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of houses that have been built in (a) Hertfordshire, (b) Bedfordshire, (c) Surrey, (d) Northamptonshire and (e) Berkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276595","276595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138668","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of UK children that have attended fee paying schools in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276596","276596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138669","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference the report entitled, Asbestos-related diseases in Great Britain, 2018, published in October 2018, how many deaths from mesothelioma there were in each (a) region and (b) local authority area.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276514","276514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138670","2019-07-16","Department for Transport","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress Highways England have made towards its target of ensuring that the majority of roads with a (a) 1* and (b) 2* safety rating under the EuroRAP3* assessment programme have improved to a 3* rating; and what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the conclusion of the Highways England Strategic Road Network Star Rating Report published on 4 July 2019 that for the funding period 2015-2020 60 per cent of journeys on Highways England’s single carriageways are forecast to be below the three-star road safety benchmark under the EuroRAP/iRAP rating system for the safety of road infrastructure.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276544","276544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138671","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much money has been spent in each English local authority area on (a) social care, and (b) transport in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276597","276597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138672","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money has been spent by each school in England on children with special educational needs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276598","276598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138673","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of not-for-profit legal aid providers that have closed in each year for the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276509","276509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138674","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of guides for teaching relationships and sex education in schools for the 2020 school year.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276599","276599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138675","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the introduction of compulsory relationships and sex education in schools in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276600","276600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138676","2019-07-16","Cabinet Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect on public sector contracts at the (a) NHS, (b) Passport Office, (c) Department for Work and Pensions and (d) Metropolitan Police of redundancies at DXC Technology.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276536","276536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138677","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the (a) cost, (b) environmental and (c) build-time benefits of modular housing build.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276545","276545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138678","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to encourage (a) supermarkets, (b) restaurant chains and (c) hotel groups to sign up to the European chicken commitment.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276519","276519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138679","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals to the tribunal service in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in relation to (i) personal independence payment, (ii) employment and support allowance, (iii) income support, (iv) jobseeker's allowance, (v) tax credits, (vi) universal credit were successful in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276546","276546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138680","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was for the Tribunals Service to administer a First-Tier Social Security and Child Support appeal in relation to (a) personal independence payment, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) jobseeker's allowance, (e) tax credits, (f) universal credit in (i) Coventry, (ii) the West Midlands and (iii) England in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276547","276547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138681","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appellants are waiting for the Tribunals Service to list their First Tier Tribunal Social Security and Child Support appeal in relation to personal independence payment in (a) Coventry, (b) West Midlands and (c) England.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276548","276548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138682","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support (a) architects, (b) engineers, (c) approved Inspectors, (d) quantity surveyors and (e) fire engineers in renewing their professional indemnity insurance.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276601","276601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138683","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of families with children living in temporary accommodation in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midland and (c) England in (i) each of the last two years and (ii) the latest month for which information is available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276549","276549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138684","2019-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what funding his Department allocated to projects to support grassroots sports facilities in Coventry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276550","276550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138685","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the (a) financial, (b) emotional and (c) medical implications for couples experiencing infertility problems of IVF services being decommissioned by clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276551","276551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138686","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has take to ensure equity of access to IVF treatment throughout England.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276552","276552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138687","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help fill vacancies for medical staff in the NHS.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276553","276553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138688","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in the Emirati Government to allow Ahmed Mansoor access (a) to an independent lawyer of his choice and (b) regular family visitation rights.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276520","276520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138689","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children aged 4 and under were admitted to hospital for a tooth extraction as a result of decay in (a) Coventry North East constituency and (b) Coventry local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276554","276554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138690","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of NHS hospitals have had vacancies for medical staff unfilled for more than (a) one, (b) two, (c) three and (d) four years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276555","276555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138691","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to prevent clinical commissioning groups from decommissioning IVF services.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276556","276556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138692","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department has spent on administering reviews and appeals against disability benefits in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276510","276510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138693","2019-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps he is taking to tackle universal credit fraud.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276511","276511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138694","2019-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure accurate verification of universal credit claimants who request an advance.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276512","276512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138695","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the decision of the European Court of Justice to annul sanctions on members of Ukraine's Yanukovych regime; and whether the Government remains committed to recovering those assets in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276521","276521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138696","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that homeowners are aware of Japanese knotweed, and what guidance his Department provides to homeowners who are affected by that invasive species.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276522","276522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138697","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of supplementing the Local Welfare Assistance Scheme with a centrally allocated fund.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276576","276576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138698","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to use pharmacists to help improve care for people with type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276523","276523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138699","2019-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to support victims of universal credit scams.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276513","276513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138700","2019-07-16","Wales Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on social media advertising in each month since July 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276557","276557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138701","2019-07-17","Department for Education","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in what circumstances the dismissal of a teacher must be reported to his Department.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276604","276604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138702","2019-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of pubs to (a) local economies, (b) local employment and (c) the Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276539","276539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138703","2019-07-16","Department for Transport","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal for the aviation industry on (a) the passage of flights across EU countries and the UK, (b) air services agreements, (c) aviation safety and security, (d) border management and (e) the environment.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276540","276540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138704","2019-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to her oral contribution of 8 July 2019, Official Report, column 19, if she will publish the review by the Investigatory Powers Commissioner on guidance on sharing and receiving intelligence.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276562","276562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138705","2019-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to her oral contribution of 8 July 2019, Official Report, column 19, when she plans to announce the change of policy in relation to guidance on sharing and receiving intelligence.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276563","276563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138706","2019-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what additional funding has been (a) required and (b) allocated to the Military Afloat Reach and Sustainability programme for the Royal Fleet Auxiliary’s (RFA) Tide-Class tankers (a) Tidesurge, (b) Tidespring, (c) Tidewave and (d) Tideforce since each of those vessels was delivered to the RFA.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276527","276527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138707","2019-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date the Royal Fleet Auxiliary’s Tide-Class tankers (a) Tidesurge, (b) Tidespring, (c) Tidewave and (d) Tideforce completed their first Replenishment At Sea exercise.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276528","276528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138708","2019-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much money the Royal Fleet Auxiliary spent on vessel maintenance in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276529","276529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138709","2019-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, under which statutory provisions his Department is able to direct Basildon Council and Essex County Council to reduce the speed limit on the A127.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276530","276530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138710","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff are employed in the processing asylum applications in the UK Visa and Immigration team.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276581","276581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138711","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the long-term workforce plan for the NHS will consider how many diagnostic professionals are needed to meet the ambition to diagnose three out of every four cancers in the next 10 years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276504","276504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137585","2019-07-10","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of ECMT permits (a) required by UK haulier operations and (b) that will be made available in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 274651","274651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138376","2019-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2019 to Question 242198 on Horse Racing: Animal Welfare, what the timescale is for improving the design of starting stalls.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276229","276229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138377","2019-07-15","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the average nursery costs for children under two years old in (a) the UK, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) York in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276230","276230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138378","2019-07-15","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many babies under six weeks old were placed for adoption in Yorkshire and the Humber by local authority area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276231","276231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138379","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has been made of the number of children living in poverty that have at least one parent in work.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276232","276232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138380","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the increase in the gig economy on levels of child poverty.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276233","276233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138381","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his announcement, Government review confirms local authorities will continue to commission public health services, published on 7 June 2019 and paragraph 2.4 of the NHS Long Term Plan, whether he plans to publish the proposals that formed as part of his Department’s review of the commissioning arrangements for sexual and reproductive health.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276234","276234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138382","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement, Government review confirms local authorities will continue to commission public health services, published by his Department on 7 June 2019 and paragraph 2.4 of the NHS Long Term Plan, whether he plans to hold a consultation on proposals to improve co-commissioning developed as part of his Department’s review of the commissioning arrangements for sexual and reproductive health.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276235","276235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138383","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 2.4 of the NHS Long-Term plan, what consultation took place with the sexual and reproductive health sector with regard to his Department’s review of the commissioning arrangements for sexual and reproductive health.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276236","276236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138384","2019-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, to which nation the road named national highway on Diego Garcia in the British Indian Ocean Territory refers.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276225","276225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138385","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of claims that the Universities Superannuation Scheme exaggerated its budget deficit in November 2017.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276269","276269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138386","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 271500, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the changes to electric vehicle plug-in grants announced in November 2018 on the uptake of electric vehicles after 2021.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276195","276195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138387","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan implementation framework, how many people have carer passports; and what targets have been set to increase the adoption of those passports.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276173","276173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138388","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan implementation framework system support offer, how many of the 75,000 staff to be trained on personalised care approaches will work in (a) autism and learning disability and (b) mental health services.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276174","276174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138389","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan implementation framework system support offer, whether the Institute for Personalised Care will deliver support to staff working in social care.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276175","276175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138390","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan implementation framework system support offer, what criteria will be used to determine which areas receive transformation funding to develop, test and deliver new approaches to care.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276176","276176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138392","2019-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to ban the import of beef from South America if it does not meet UK standards for sustainable farming after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276166","276166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138393","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the article in the Guardian entitled A demeaning environment: stories of racism in UK universities, published 5 July 2019, if he will hold discussions with the Office for Students on their assessment of the scale and nature of racism in UK universities.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276161","276161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138394","2019-07-15","Department for International Development","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many aid trucks have been prevented from accessing areas in need of humanitarian assistance in Yemen since 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276145","276145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138395","2019-07-15","Department for International Development","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the number of aid workers operating on (a) on UK funded and (b) non-UK funded missions in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276146","276146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138396","2019-07-15","Department for International Development","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of demurrage and related operational expenses in Yemen since 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276147","276147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138397","2019-07-15","Department for International Development","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of food consumed in Yemen has been imported in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276148","276148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138398","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many migrant detainees were referred to the National Referral Mechanism in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276155","276155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138399","2019-07-15","Department for International Development","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of UK aid to Yemen has been spent on imports of food in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276149","276149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138400","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of migrant detainees referred to the National Referral Mechanism were subsequently given positive decisions by the Home Office that there were reasonable grounds to believe they were trafficked to the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276156","276156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138401","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in what languages he plans to display electronic road signs on road closures on A-roads and motorways.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276150","276150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138402","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department plans to spend on displaying electronic road signs in foreign languages on A-roads and motorways.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276151","276151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138403","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in which parts of the UK his Department plans to install road signs on road closures in foreign languages.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276152","276152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138404","2019-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Black Hornet drones the British Army (a) possesses and (b) has deployed in active service.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276153","276153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138405","2019-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much her Department has spent on the acquisition of Black Hornet drones.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276154","276154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138406","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants over the age of 60 in receipt of universal credit have been sanctioned in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276287","276287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138407","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that the provision of free school meals to all infant school aged children does not adversely affect (a) the allocation of and (b) level of registration for pupil premium funding.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276288","276288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138408","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan implementation framework system support offer, how his Department will monitor growth in the independent and voluntary sector care and support market for autistic people and people with learning disabilities with more complex needs.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276177","276177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138409","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the locations are of the Emergency Service Network sites that are planned to be deployed in Angus; when those masts will become operational; and which of those sites will enable mobile network operators other than EE to make use of those new sites.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276286","276286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138410","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the increases in state pension for 2019-20 were calculated; and for what reasons pensioners reaching the age of 80 are awarded an increase of 25 pence in 2019-20.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276270","276270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138411","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Economic Operator Registration and Identification numbers were held by UK firms in (a) December 2018 and (b) 23 June 2019.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276289","276289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138412","2019-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257528 on Telecommunications: Infrastructure, whether the supply chain review is planned to be released before summer recess 2019; and what assessment he has made of the effect of a delay in publication on cyber-security.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276280","276280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138413","2019-07-16","Cabinet Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 272302 on Huawei: 5G, whether he has met with the operators that are known not to follow Huawei Cyber Security Evaluation Centre advice and guidance.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276281","276281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138414","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints to the Independent Complaints Commissioner are (a) allocated to a caseworker and (b) awaiting allocation to a caseworker as at 11 July 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276137","276137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138415","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is between a case being accepted by the Independent Complaints Commissioner and being allocated to a caseworker in the most recent period for which figures are available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276138","276138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138416","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of school uniforms being gender neutral.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276261","276261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138417","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the availability of diet apps on the mental health of school-aged girls; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276262","276262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138418","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints for the Independent Complaints Commissioner were received in 2018; and how many of those complaints have been allocated to a caseworker.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276139","276139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138419","2019-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support businesses to develop new and more sustainable vegetation oils as a replacement for palm oil.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276167","276167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138420","2019-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who currently fulfils the responsibilities of the position of Minister for Asia and the Pacific.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276282","276282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138421","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue his Department has raised from VAT on e-publications in (a) 2016, (b) 2017, (c) 2018 and (d) 2019 to 11 July 2019.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Sir George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276162","276162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138422","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to improve access to benefits for all people who have been diagnosed as terminally ill.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276141","276141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138423","2019-07-16","Women and Equalities","2019-07-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to increase diversity across all levels of FTSE 100 companies.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276168","276168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138424","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the prevalence of verbal and physical harassment of non-UK EU citizens in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276220","276220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138425","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary for of State for the Home Department, what information he holds on the number of people who used the National Domestic Violence helpline in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276221","276221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138426","2019-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the role of free to air sport on public participation in sport.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276222","276222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138427","2019-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to announce the new ambassador to the United States.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276223","276223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138428","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children applied for asylum in 2018 whose age was disputed.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276224","276224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138429","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that banks provide sufficient support to elderly and vulnerable customers to access their services.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276248","276248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138430","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that banking services are accessible to (a) elderly customers, (b) vulnerable customers and (c) customers without internet access.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276249","276249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138431","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many late filing penalties HMRC collected from large companies in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276208","276208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138432","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of dementia diagnosis in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276142","276142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138433","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax avoidance schemes related to the use of personal service companies HMRC successfully challenged in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276209","276209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138434","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have been challenged by HMRC for promoting or facilitating tax avoidance schemes since 2017.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276210","276210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138435","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received an end of year tax summary from HMRC in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276211","276211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138436","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people are employed at Companies House.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276212","276212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138437","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of avoidable hospital admissions of people with dementia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276143","276143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138438","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many capital infrastructure projects have been completed as part of the Government’s National Infrastructure and Construction Pipeline.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276213","276213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138439","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships were created in 2018 as a result of capital infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276214","276214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138440","2019-07-15","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships were created in the manufacturing sector in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276215","276215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138441","2019-07-15","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships were created in the energy sector in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276216","276216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138442","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many apprenticeships were created in the transport sector in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276217","276217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138444","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax experts HMRC's Tax Capacity Building Unit and Tax Expert Unit has trained since 2017.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276219","276219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138445","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of care companies operating in the UK that have collapsed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276144","276144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138446","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who has responsibility for developing resources to teach pupils about HIV within Relationships and Sex Education.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276243","276243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138447","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which providers are creating resources to teach pupils about Sexually Transmitted Infections in Relationships and Sex Education.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276244","276244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138448","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding will be provided to local authorities for public health in 2020-2021 if the Government’s spending review is postponed.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276265","276265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138449","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will increase funding for sexual health services to tackle the increases in cases of syphilis and gonorrhoea in England.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276266","276266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138450","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to find a long-term and sustainable funding package to ensure PrEP is available to all who require it.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276267","276267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138451","2019-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the contribution that (a) rooftop solar, (b) solar farms and (c) onshore wind can make to delivering the 2050 net-zero emissions target; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276250","276250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138452","2019-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what was the capacity of (a) onshore wind and (b) solar PV installed in the UK in (i) 2015, (ii) 2016, (iii) 2017, (iv) 2018, and (v) 2019 to 11 July 2019.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276251","276251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138453","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has a target for the time taken to make a decision on a claim submitted to the Windrush compensation scheme.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276274","276274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138454","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he will publish data on the time taken between someone submitting a claim to the Windrush compensation scheme and a decision being made on that claim.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276275","276275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138455","2019-07-16","Department for International Development","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the UK meets its ODA obligations in the event that the UK leave the European Union without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276180","276180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138456","2019-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to respond to the letter of 18 June 2019 from the hon. Member for Bishop Auckland requesting a meeting with the Minister of State for the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276170","276170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138457","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many requests for spilt payments of universal credit have been (a) made and (b) accepted in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276271","276271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138458","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many requests for alternative payment arrangements of universal credit have been (a) made and (b) accepted for (i) twice monthly payments and (b) four twice monthly payments in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276272","276272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138459","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claims for universal credit were made using the bank account details of the main carer in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276273","276273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138460","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of Clinical Commissioning Groups do not allow varenicline and other stop smoking treatments to be prescribed to patients in primary care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276206","276206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138461","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department is aware of buildings for which cladding has needed to be remediated on more than one occasion since June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276196","276196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138462","2019-07-16","Department for International Development","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps he is taking to help ensure that (a) health workers in the Occupied Palestinian Territories are protected from attack and (b) perpetrators of such attacks are held accountable.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276132","276132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138463","2019-07-16","Department for International Development","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of permit restrictions imposed by the Government of Israel on (a) medical patients and (b) companions of those medical patients seeking to exit Gaza.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276133","276133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138464","2019-07-16","Department for International Trade","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will place in the Library a copy of the witness statement of the Head of the Export Control Joint Unit dated 27 June 2019 in his Department's application to appeal the Court of Appeal judgment of 20 June 2019.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276268","276268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138465","2019-07-16","Cabinet Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2019 to Question 274634, what cost/benefit analyses have been conducted for each of the catalyst challenges; and if he will publish those analyses.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276283","276283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138466","2019-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 10 of the Government Transformation Strategy, how many of the 10 commitments the Government intended to complete before 2020 are on track to be completed.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276284","276284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138467","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the National Literacy Trust's report Children, young people and digital reading, published by the  on 30 April 2019, on the literacy benefits of children reading both digital and print formats.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276252","276252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138468","2019-07-16","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what percentage of freedom of information requests received by HS2 Limited were fulfilled within the 20-day deadline in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018 and (e) the first quarter of 2019.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276157","276157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138469","2019-07-16","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many freedom of information requests were received by HS2 Limited in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018 and (e) the first quarter of 2019.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276158","276158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138470","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether people applying to the Windrush compensation scheme who request a Tier 1 or Tier 2 review will have access to the evidence or data upon which an initial or review decision has been made.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276276","276276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138471","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether people applying to the Windrush compensation scheme will be subject to the immigration exemption to the Data Protection Act 2018.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276277","276277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138472","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what central Government funding Newcastle Local Authority will be allocated for its 2020-21 budget.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276189","276189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138473","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons his Department is not providing funds for the remediation of non-Aluminium composite cladding where it is found to be unsafe.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276197","276197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138474","2019-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons 31.2 per cent of freedom of information requests received by his Department were not fulfilled within the 20-day deadline in 2018.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276159","276159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138475","2019-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reason only 55.4 per cent of FOI requests received by his Department in the first quarter of 2019 were met within the 20-day deadline.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276160","276160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138476","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference the article in the Oxford Mail entitled, Hockmore Tower among five Oxford blocks facing post Grenfell scrutiny, published 11 July 2019, what information his Department has provided to local authorities in July 2019 on the need to remediate high-pressure laminate cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276198","276198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138477","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the National Fire Chiefs Council or his Department's Independent Expert Panel have been invited to witness the large-scale fire safety tests commissioned by his Department in July 2019.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276199","276199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138478","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Windrush compensation scheme, what the average offer has been to an applicant and what criteria his Department uses to calculate loss of income in such awards.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276278","276278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138479","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor for the Exchequer on increasing funding for early years education in the forthcoming spending review.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276255","276255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138480","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which (a) persons and (b) organisations the Anti-Muslim Hatred Working Group has met with in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276245","276245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138481","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will maintain Government funding for the 30-hours childcare policy.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276256","276256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138482","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the terms of reference of the Anti-Muslim Hatred Working Group (a) were last and (b) are next due to be reviewed.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276246","276246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138483","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether compensation awarded from the Windrush compensation scheme is taken into account in an assessment for an application for (a) universal credit, (b) tax credits and (c) other benefits.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276279","276279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138484","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what engagement the Anti-Muslim Hatred Working Group has had with the (a) Attorney General’s Office, (b) Cabinet Office, (c) Crown Prosecution Service, (d) Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, (e) Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government, (f) Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport; (g) Department for Education, (h) Foreign and Commonwealth Office, (i) Home Office, (j) Ministry of Justice, and (k) Department for Transport in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276247","276247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138485","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the APPG for Childcare and Early Education July 2019 report entitled Steps to Sustainability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276257","276257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138486","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2019 to Question 259958 on Channel Ferries: Freight, if he publish the existing planning assumptions; and when he plans to announce a decision on a revision of those assumptions.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276181","276181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138487","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of levels of (a) recruitment and (b) retention in the childcare sector in the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276258","276258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138488","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2019 to Question 259958 on Channel Ferries: Freight, which (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department are working on the existing planning assumptions; and what deadline he has set for revised assumptions to be reported to him.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276182","276182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138489","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what contingency preparations he is making at the Port of Dover for (a) passengers, (b) hauliers and (c) seafarers in the event that the UK leaves the EU on 31 October 2019 without a deal.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276183","276183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138490","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff in his Department are working on preparations at major ports for the UK leaving the EU on 31 October 2019 without a deal.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276184","276184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138491","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of implications for his policies of the recent study published in the journal, Nicotine & Tobacco Research entitled, Prescribing prevalence, effectiveness, and mental health safety of smoking cessation medicines in patients with mental disorders.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276169","276169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138492","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of the (a) opening and (b) closure of childcare settings in (a) affluent and (b) disadvantaged areas.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276259","276259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138493","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on the (a) consultation on, (b) preparation for and (c) introduction of the National Assessment and Accreditation Systems for (i) social workers, (ii) social work supervisors and (iii) leaders.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276201","276201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138494","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial support Partners in Practice has provided to each local authority to help establish (a) Trust models and (b) Community Interest Companies in relation to local authority children's services departments.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276202","276202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138495","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of funding allocated to the consultation on the National Assessment and Accreditation System for social workers was spent on (a) private sector consultants and (b) local authorities in 2018-19.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276203","276203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138496","2019-07-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what role the government Chief Data Officer will have in the implementation of the National Data Strategy.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276285","276285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138497","2019-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when she plans to publish the Defence Arctic Strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276171","276171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138498","2019-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when she plans to publish the Defence Space Strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276172","276172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138499","2019-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the size of the (a) regular armed forces community and (b) reserve armed forces community including the partners, spouses and children of people serving in the armed forces.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276190","276190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138500","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to appoint a national active travel commissioner.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276191","276191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138501","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257559, when he plans to publish further details on the operation and allocation of the Stronger Towns Fund.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276192","276192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138502","2019-07-15","Cabinet Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2019 to Question 249954, if the Government will publish the recommendations of the Joint Funds Unit audit of Overseas Security and Justice Assistance; what steps have been taken in response to the recommendations of that audit; who was responsible for conducting that audit; and what the cost was to the public purse of that audit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276193","276193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138503","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many former armed service personnel who have declared their membership of those services are serving a sentence in each prison in Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276194","276194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138504","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that local authorities provide adequate leisure and recreational facilities for people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276263","276263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138505","2019-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2019 to Question 274551 on Buildings: Fire Prevention, what steps leaseholders are able to take in the event of being presented with high charges for non-cladding fire safety remedial work.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276200","276200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138506","2019-07-16","Treasury","2019-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequacy of checks undertaken to guarantee the accuracy of the payment of monies greater than £10,000 by HMRC to private citizens.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276131","276131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138507","2019-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) the Post Office Ltd and (b) sub-Postmasters for collecting parcels in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276226","276226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138508","2019-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of Royal Mail's parcel postbox expansion on the income of (a) the Post Office Ltd and (b) sub-Postmasters.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276227","276227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138509","2019-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of Royal Mail's parcel postbox expansion on the sustainability of Post Office branches.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276228","276228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138510","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) NHS Trusts and (b) Care Commissioning Groups are able to deliver the objectives of the Long-Term Plan in the absence of the NHS People Plan.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276253","276253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138511","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of the cessation of freedom of movement on the NHS workforce.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276254","276254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138512","2019-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 273334, if she will make it her Department's policy to mandate her Department's assessors to record instances in which they have formally questioned a prognosis given by health professionals in DS1500 forms.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276163","276163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138513","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to ensure that new bypasses funded through the Major Roads Network programme are safe for cyclists.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276207","276207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138514","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 272159, what assessment he has made of the merits of the recommendations made in the Birth Companions Report entitled Birth Charter for women in prisons in England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276164","276164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138515","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 273333 on Stem cells: donors, what the targets are for the proportion of donors that must be from BAME backgrounds.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276165","276165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138516","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 272279, how many people (a) are entitled to be  and (b) have been reimbursed for employment tribunal fees.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276237","276237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138517","2019-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 270773 on Addiction Services, what plans has he to increase the availability of medically-staffed detoxification beds in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276179","276179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138518","2019-07-16","Department for International Trade","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2019 to Question 267763 on Standard Individual Export Licences: Saudi Arabia, what the estimated value is of the 57 export licences for Saudi Arabia under consideration on 20 June 2019.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276260","276260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138519","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) titles, (b) amount awarded and (c) reasons for decisions were for the (i) unsuccessful and (ii) successful bids for grant funding from the Holiday Activities and Food Programme for the summer holidays in (A) 2018 and (B) 2019.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276204","276204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138520","2019-07-16","Department for Education","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to launch a Holiday Activities and Food Programme for 2020.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276205","276205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138521","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will establish a nationally funded local welfare assistance scheme similar to the former Discretionary Social Fund; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276140","276140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138522","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the disparity in discounts on properties offered to (a) council tenants and (b) right to buy schemes.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276185","276185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138523","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage recycling of electronic waste throughout the UK.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276186","276186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138524","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to prevent the procurement of personal information by criminal organisations.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276187","276187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138525","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average time taken by the Probate Service to complete a grant of probate application in each in of the last four quarters.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276238","276238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138526","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by the Probate Service in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276239","276239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138527","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff have left the Probate Service in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276240","276240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138528","2019-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many agency staff have been employed by the Probate Service in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276241","276241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138529","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of service for a member of staff at the Probate Service was in each of the last four quarters.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276242","276242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138530","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number of child asylum seekers living in adult accommodation.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276134","276134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138531","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many successful appeals on grounds of age were made by asylum seekers who were found to be juveniles in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276135","276135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138532","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the need for safeguarding policies to support child asylum seekers erroneously placed in adult removal centres.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276136","276136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138533","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to allow the use of electronic scooters on roads and cycle paths.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276188","276188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138534","2019-07-15","Department for International Trade","2019-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether representatives from Saudi Arabia (a) have been or (b) will be invited by the Government to send a delegation to the Defence and Security Equipment International exhibition taking place at the Excel Centre in London 10-13 September 2019.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276264","276264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138046","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons claimants of personal independence payments who have received a tribunal decision since the Upper Tribunal’s judgments on MH and RJ have been excluded from the administrative review.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275788","275788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138047","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what account he has taken of  his Department's report entitled What is the relationship between public and private investment in R&D published July 2015 which stated  that an extra £1 of public funding would give rise to an increase in private funding of between £1.13 and £1.60 in setting policy on the relationship between public and private investment in R&D.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275748","275748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138048","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential increase in the number of Export Health Certificate that will be required in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275832","275832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138049","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much per capita funding has been allocated from the public purse to cycling in Central Bedfordshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275708","275708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138050","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's consultation, Energy performance certificate in buildings: call for evidence, published in October 2018, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of off-grid properties switching from lower carbon to higher carbon forms of heating in order to obtain a higher energy performance certificate rating.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275644","275644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138051","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2019 to Question 263146 on Visas: Applications, if he will ensure that the processing of in-country visa services by Sopra Steria will not result in increased prices for visa services for (a) international students and staff at UK universities and (b) universities.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275742","275742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138052","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential environmental benefits of permitting use of light electric vehicles on (a) roads and (b) public paths.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275806","275806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138053","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the projected change in smoking rates among pregnant women is over the next two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275697","275697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138054","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who have previously received (a) 25 or more and (b) 50 or more convictions or cautions, have been convicted of an offence and not been given a custodial sentence in each year since 2007; and how many of those people have previously been convicted of (i) possession of a blade or point, (ii) possession of an offensive weapon, (iii) common assault, (iv) assaulting a police officer, (v) sexual assault, (vi) public order, (vii) theft, (viii) robbery, (ix) burglary, (x) drugs, (xi) criminal damage, (xii) breach of anti social behaviour order, (xiii) fraud and (xiv) vehicle taking.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275833","275833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138055","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people sentenced to an immediate custodial sentence for the first time for (a) possession of a blade or point, (b) possession of an offensive weapon, (c) common assault, (d) assaulting a police officer, (e) sexual assault, (f) public order, (g) theft, (h) robbery, (i) burglary, (j) drugs, (k) criminal damage, (l) breach of and anti-social behaviour order, (m) fraud and (n) vehicle taking had (i) no, (ii) between one and four, (iii) between five and nine, (iv) between 10 and 15, (v) between 16 and 25, (vi) between 26 and 50, (vii) between 51 and 75, (viii) between 76 and 100 and (ix) 101 or more convictions and cautions for previous offences of any type in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275834","275834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138056","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of previous (a) cautions and (b) convictions offenders had before being sentenced to an immediate custodial sentence for the first time for (i) possession of a blade or point, (ii) possession of an offensive weapon, (iii) common assault, (iv) assaulting a police officer, (v) sexual assault, (vi) public order, (vii) theft, (viii) robbery, (ix) burglary, (x) drugs, (xi) criminal damage, (xii) breach of anti social behaviour order, (xiii) fraud and (xiv) vehicle taking in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275835","275835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138057","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the largest number of community sentences previously received by an offender who was (a) convicted of a crime and (b) convicted of a crime and sentenced to a community sentence in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275836","275836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138058","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people sentenced for domestic burglary for (a) the third time and (b) more than three times received an immediate custodial sentence of (i) less than three years, (ii) exactly three years and (iii) more than three years in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275837","275837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138059","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) his Hungarian counterpart and (b) other EU counterparts on (i) the closure of the Central European University and (ii) restrictions on academic freedom in Hungary.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275713","275713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138060","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is providing to the Somali Government to counter the proliferation of weapons within Somalia and prevent access to weapons by terrorists.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275714","275714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138062","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to A connected society: A Strategy for tackling loneliness – laying the foundations for change, published 15 October 2018, what progress has been made on his Department's commitment to fund research into the impact of community-led housing and cohousing solutions on loneliness.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275810","275810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138063","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to A connected society: A Strategy for tackling loneliness – laying the foundations for change, published 15 October 2018, what progress has been made on his Department’s commitment to work with external stakeholders such as the UK Cohousing Network to build a database of case studies of innovative housing developments that promote social cohesion.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275811","275811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138064","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to A connected society: A Strategy for tackling loneliness – laying the foundations for change, published 15 October 2018, what progress has been made on his Department’s commitment to run a series of industry events, conferences and seminars to promote the role of design in wellbeing, including tackling loneliness and to publish case studies and evidence.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275812","275812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138065","2019-07-15","Women and Equalities","2019-07-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of obligating all major employers in the UK to publish their gender and ethnicity pay gap data.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275700","275700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138066","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much HM Courts and Tribunals Service has spent on (a) courts translation services and (b) Capita Translation Services in each of the last 10 financial years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275723","275723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138067","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the evidential basis was for the downgrading of the impact of persecution of Christians in the Middle East between the the Bishop of Truro’s Independent Review for the Foreign Secretary of FCO Support for Persecuted Christians and (a) Interim and (b) Final Report.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275654","275654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138068","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been (a) charged and (b) convicted as a result of Operation Gull in Northern Ireland in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275698","275698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138069","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on reports of the closure of a Baha’i-run elder care centre in Karaj, Iran.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275646","275646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138070","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on (a) reports that the Public Places Supervision Office is seeking to close Baha’i-owned businesses in Iran and (b) the targeting of other minority communities in that country.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275647","275647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138071","2019-07-15","Department for International Development","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Millennium Development Goal targets on access to clean water by 2020 will be met in sub-Saharan Africa.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275699","275699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138072","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what outcomes NHS England plans to achieve for children and young people with special educational needs and disabilities during the lifespan of the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275749","275749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138073","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding NHS England has allocated to improving outcomes for children and young people with special educational needs and disabilities during the lifespan of the NHS Long-Term Plan.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275750","275750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138074","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for the publication of its final report on the effectiveness of programmes to protect former SSI steelworkers from long-term unemployment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275684","275684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138075","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Questions 272897 and 272898, what assessment she has made of whether the feedback of Presenting Officers has led to (a) an increase in successful mandatory reconsiderations for claimants, (b) more correct decisions resulting in fewer successful appeals and (c) fewer claims reaching appeal stage.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275796","275796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138076","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report of the Committee on Climate Change entitled,  Progress in preparing for climate change, published on 10 July, for what reasons good progress was not made in any of the 33 sectors assessed by that Committee on actions needed to manage climate change risks.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275655","275655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138077","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to implement the recommendations of the final report of the Bishop of Truro’s Independent Review for the Foreign Secretary of FCO Support for Persecuted Christians.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275685","275685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138078","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve the mental health of prisoners.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275743","275743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138079","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the prison population with mental health problems.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275744","275744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138080","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase awareness of the Help to Save scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275728","275728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138081","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have invested in a Lifetime ISA since its introduction.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275729","275729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138082","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to improve the infrastructure for electric vehicles.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275730","275730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138083","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many electric vehicle charge points there are in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275731","275731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138084","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what financial incentives the Government is offering to increase the uptake of electric vehicles.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275732","275732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138085","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average age is of people who have taken up a Help to Buy ISA.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275733","275733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138086","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 11 of the report entitled, Net Zero, published by the Committee on Climate Change in May 2019 on setting a target of net zero emissions by 2050 and if he will make it his policy to set an earlier target date for reaching net zero.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275656","275656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138087","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to put in place year-long environmental campaigns in 2020 similar to the Year of Green Action in 2019.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275734","275734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138088","2019-07-15","Cabinet Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to tackle postal vote fraud.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275735","275735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138089","2019-07-15","Cabinet Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to tackle bribery during elections.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275736","275736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138090","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the most popular models of (a) electricity and (b) heat microgeneration in buildings throughout the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275753","275753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138091","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of using medicinal cannabis for pain relief.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275737","275737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138092","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential for microgeneration of electricity and heat to contribute to the goals of (a) decarbonisation and (b) net zero emissions by 2050.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275754","275754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138093","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support the incorporation of infrastructure for microgeneration in housing developments throughout the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275755","275755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138094","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using medicinal cannabis to treat Irritable Bowel Syndrome.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275738","275738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138095","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the financial contribution of the oil and gas sector to the economy of (a) each region of the UK and (b) the UK; and how many jobs the oil and gas sector supports in each region of UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275756","275756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138096","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy,  how many new models of boilers introduced since October 2017 have been tested and submitted to the BRE to comply with the new Boiler Plus regulations.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275657","275657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138097","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to end the requirement for the consent of a spouse when entering into a change of name deed to be enrolled at the Royal Courts of Justice using form LOC020.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275802","275802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138098","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a green tax on air travel which would be invested in environmentally-friendly transport infrastructure.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275701","275701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138099","2019-07-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of employment tribunal decision, Ms A Braine and others v The National Gallery: 2201625/2018.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275798","275798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138100","2019-07-15","Attorney General","2019-07-10","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) legal advice and (b) representation at inquests for Government Departments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275781","275781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138101","2019-07-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the extent of (a) poor employment practice and (b) insecure work at publicly funded cultural institutions.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275799","275799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138102","2019-07-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the employment tribunal decision, Ms A Braine and others v The National Gallery: 2201625/2018 on other publicly-funded cultural institutions.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275800","275800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138103","2019-07-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to tackle (a) reports of poor employment practices, (b) insecure work and (c) the gig economy within publicly-funded cultural institutions.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275801","275801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138104","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much was spent from the public purse on (a) security, (b) accommodation and (c) transport for family members of President Trump during his visit to the UK in June 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275782","275782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138105","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the reform of legal aid on average annual earnings of legal aid solicitors.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275783","275783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138106","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the financial impact on defendants of the introduction of an upper limit on disposable income for people claiming legal aid for Crown Court representation.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275784","275784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138107","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when details of the funding arrangements for the planned pilots of four week waiting time standards to access adult community eating disorder services will be made available.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275724","275724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138108","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he will announce the (a) scope and (b) timelines of the pilots of four week waiting time standards for adult and older adult community mental health teams, including for adult community eating disorder services.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275725","275725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138109","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to improve the level of household food waste recycling.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275803","275803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138110","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of measles cases in England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275669","275669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138111","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on steps to improve local authorities' food waste collection services.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275804","275804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138112","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on vaccine research to tackle antimicrobial resistance.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275670","275670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138113","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much food waste went to landfill sites in 2018.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275805","275805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138114","2019-07-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold further discussions with the BBC to ensure that free TV licences are provided to all people over the age of 75; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275659","275659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138115","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of trends in the level of religious violence directed against Muslims in India in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275716","275716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138116","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Lords Economic Affairs Sub-Committee report, The Powers of HMRC: Treating Taxpayers Fairly, HL Paper 242, published on 4 December 2018, for what reason the Government’s response did not answer paragraph 70 on the Loan Charge; when he plans respond to the points raised in that paragraph on the culpability of employers who directed people to use Disguised Remuneration schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275726","275726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138117","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of Hindu nationalist rhetoric publicly used by members of the ruling Bharatiya Janata Party in inciting violence against Indian Muslims.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275717","275717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138118","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of learner motorcyclists have taken up one-to-one motorcycle skills lessons after completion of the compulsory basic training course in London in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275648","275648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138119","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of delivery company learner motorcyclists have not undertaken free one-to-one motorcycle skills sessions in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275649","275649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138120","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road accidents have been recorded in London involving learner motorcyclists in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275650","275650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138121","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that housebuilders take account of (a) heatwaves, (b) flash flooding and (c) other effects of climate change in building new homes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275671","275671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138122","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of staffing levels in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275807","275807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138123","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Government's announcement that NHS health information will be made available through Amazon’s Alexa,  who will have ownership of data generated through that collaboration; what estimate he has made of the financial value of that collaboration to (a) the NHS and (b) Amazon; and for what reasons that collaboration is exclusively with Amazon and not other providers of voice-activated searches.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275751","275751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138124","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement that NHS health information will be available through Amazon’s Alexa, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of Alexa for identifying health information; what safeguards for patient safety are in place to monitor the effectiveness of Alexa; whether the information provided by Alexa that originates from NHS-verified health information be clearly differentiated from information that originates from other non-verified sources; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275752","275752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138125","2019-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on parliamentary accountability of the EU defence structures that the UK has joined since the EU referendum in 2016.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275696","275696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138126","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of Parkinson's disease nurse specialists employed by the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275660","275660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138127","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the three planning decisions announced on 8 July 2019 for two sites in Hatfield Peverel, for what reasons (a) the decision was made to remove 10 sites from the Braintree District Council five-year supply position and (b) there was no consultation with interested parties on those planning applications prior to removing those 10 sites; and if he will publish all relevant correspondence and representations he received regarding those 10 sites.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275745","275745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138128","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the three planning decisions he announced on 8 July 2019 for the sites Gleneagles Way and Stone Path Drive in Hatfield Peverel, if he will make an assessment of the availability of public transport in Hatfield Peverel.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275746","275746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138129","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on future co-operation over shared environmental resources with neighbouring countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Dame Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275674","275674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138130","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to employ more staff working on cancer (a) prevention, (b) diagnosis and (c) treatment in the NHS after 2021; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275661","275661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138131","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the three planning decisions announced on 8 July 2019 for two sites in Hatfield Peverel, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequate provision of (a) school places and (b) health services at those sites.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275747","275747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138132","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for funding from the Flexible Support Fund have been received for up-front childcare costs in each of the last 12 months; and how many of those applications have been (a) paid in full, (b) paid in part and (c) refused.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275816","275816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138133","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have people on universal credit who have turned down a job offer in the last 12 months have cited lack of affordable childcare as the reason; and how many of those people received (a) a civil penalty and (b) a sanction.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275817","275817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138134","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the merits of increasing green spaces in the UK to reduce the effect of flash flooding.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275672","275672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138135","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Office of Environmental Protection will take account of Northern Ireland’s specific environmental requirements should its jurisdiction apply there.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275765","275765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138136","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Office of Environmental Protection will have a physical presence in Northern Ireland should it have jurisdiction there.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275766","275766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138137","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of computers in the NHS that use the Windows XP operating system.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275828","275828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138138","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he will take to ensure that (a) Northern Ireland is represented on the Office of Environmental Protection’s (OEP’s) Board and (b) that the specific needs of Northern Ireland are taken into account when the OEP’s budget and strategy is agreed.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275767","275767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138139","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he will take to ensure Office of Environmental Protection staff have adequate knowledge and experience of Northern Ireland’s legislation and practices.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275768","275768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138140","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to add additional principles to those included in the Draft Environment (Principles and Governance) Bill 2018.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275769","275769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138141","2019-07-15","Cabinet Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Minister or official is responsible for ensuring cross-governmental compliance with the Minimum Cyber Security Standard.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275829","275829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138142","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's policy is on making the environmental principle of avoiding trans-boundary environmental damage applicable in both England and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275770","275770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138143","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to start the consultation on Healthy Start vouchers.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275808","275808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138144","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made by each nation of the UK on developing common frameworks for environmental policy, legislation and regulation to (a) manage shared environmental assets and (b) meet environmental challenges after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275771","275771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138145","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of local authority areas that do not have a housing legal aid provider in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275673","275673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138146","2019-07-15","Department for Education","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the provision of professional training for people who work therapeutically with children and young people on mental health issues; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275818","275818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138147","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether postgraduate training level seven will be fully funded and mandatory for people working therapeutically with children and young people on mental health issues.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275819","275819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138148","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions have taken place between (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have held with (i) TfL and (ii) the Mayor of London on plans to build on land around High Barnet, Cockfosters and Finchley Central underground stations within the last 12 months.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275710","275710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138149","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether training programmes designed to equip people working therapeutically with children and young people on mental health will have a set of learning objectives derived from practice-based evidence.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275820","275820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138150","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish correspondence between his Department and (a) TfL and (b) the Mayor of London on plans to build on land around High Barnet, Cockfosters and Finchley Central underground stations.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275711","275711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138151","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which areas of land around (a) High Barnet, (b) Cockfosters and (c) Finchley Central underground stations are classed as operational land by Transport for London.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275712","275712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138152","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to protect the rights and identities of benefit claimants from people making fraudulent claims using other people's identities.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275683","275683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138153","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the public purse was of the Smile4life Starting well pilot project in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275778","275778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138154","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children aged five to nine have had to go to hospital for an emergency dental extraction in each of the last three years; and what the cost has been to the public purse.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275779","275779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138155","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department will update the National Rail Travel Overview Survey Report.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275643","275643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138156","2019-07-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to Question 268565 on buildings: insulation, tabled by the hon Member for Croydon North on 24 June 2019.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275759","275759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138157","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to monitor antibiotic resistant bugs in seagull faeces in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275689","275689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138158","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he has taken to ensure that overseas domestic workers are informed of their rights as workers in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275676","275676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138159","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timeframe is for the planned information sessions on the employment rights of overseas domestic workers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275677","275677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138160","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many EU member states apply a reduced rate of VAT to e-publications.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275786","275786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138161","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the adoption of the amendment to Directive 2006/112/EC on rates of value added tax for books, newspapers and periodicals by the EU Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275787","275787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138162","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made on filling the 480 child refugee places in the Immigration Act 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275678","275678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138163","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the political situation in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275838","275838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138164","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs,  what recent assessment his Department has made of the political situation in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275839","275839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138165","2019-07-15","Cabinet Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what preparations his Department has made for holding a second referendum on UK membership of the European Union.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275840","275840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138166","2019-07-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what preparations his Department has made for holding of a second referendum on UK membership of the EU.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275841","275841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138167","2019-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to penalise (a) local authorities and (b) companies found to be illegally exporting refuse and recycling abroad.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275789","275789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138168","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2019 to Question 263677, for what reason the letter sent to a universal credit claimant’s journal to confirm an advance payment does not specify the (a) amount to be repaid each month or (b) number of months that the repayments will last; and if he will add that information to that letter.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275662","275662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138169","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish a response to EDM 2164 on visa costs for Commonwealth service personnel.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275663","275663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138170","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made on ensuring that (a) people who purchased a defective Whirlpool tumble driers are compensated and (b) those dryers are made safe.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275664","275664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138171","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons the Dean Street Clinic, GUM, is not permitting gay and bisexual men to take part in the PrEP impact trial.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275772","275772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138172","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the extent to which fraudulent claims for universal credit have been made by people using a loophole in the online application process to make an application and claim an advance using another person’s information.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275665","275665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138173","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that gay and bisexual men using Dean Street Clinic (GUM) have access to PrEP as part of the PrEP Impact trial.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275773","275773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138174","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reducing child citizenship fees for children born or raised in the UK to avoid any future immigration complications.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275702","275702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138175","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to advertise extra places on the PrEP Impact trial to people who are at risk of HIV.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275774","275774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138176","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he is having with local authorities in London on increasing access to the PrEP Impact trial.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275775","275775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138177","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on how much has been spent on investigating fraudulent universal credit claims that have been made by people using a loophole in the online application process to make an application and claim an advance using another person’s information.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275666","275666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138178","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the proportion of successful universal credit claims which are fraudulent; and how that figure compares to legacy benefits.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275667","275667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138179","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it is policy to introduce a dedicated dementia fund as recommended by the Alzheimer's Society.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275693","275693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138180","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 272738, what recourse is available to a member of a joint claim whose partner has deliberately prevented them from being made aware of a universal credit advance; and in what circumstances a member of a joint claim who was unaware of an advance of universal credit is no longer liable for repaying that advance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275668","275668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138181","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve (a) awareness and (b) diagnosis of dementia.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275694","275694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138182","2019-07-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much was spent on dementia care in (a) Bexley, (b) London and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275695","275695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138183","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the US Administration on the treatment of (a) child and (b) other refugees and migrants being held at detention centres on the US-Mexico border.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275797","275797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138184","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the (a) finding in the July 2019 Highways England Strategic Road Network Star Rating Report that for the funding period 2015-2020 60 per cent of journeys on Highways England’s single carriageways are forecast to be below the three-star road safety benchmark under the EuroRAP/iRAP rating system for the safety of road infrastructure and (b) statement in the March 2015 Highways England 2015-2020 delivery plan that the organisation will ensure that by the end of 2020 more than 90 per cent of travel on the strategic road network will be on roads with a safety rating of EuroRAP3* (or equivalent).","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275760","275760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138185","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding has been allocated to the optoelectronics industry in the UK in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275690","275690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138186","2019-07-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport what recent assessment he has made of the size of the optoelectronics industry in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275691","275691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138187","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications of the purchase of Manston airport site by Riveroak Strategic Partners from Stone Hill Park in July 2019 for (a) his freight network capacity plan in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal and (b) the provisions of the Town and Country Planning (Manston Airport) Special Development Order 2019.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275761","275761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138188","2019-07-15","Department for Education","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has received the 29th report of the School Teachers’ Review Body.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275813","275813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138189","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what due diligence his Department undertook on Riveroak Strategic Partners before that company's purchase of Manston Airport in July 2019.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275762","275762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138190","2019-07-15","Treasury","2019-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to use Manston airport as an inland, pre-customs clearing port for outward freight in relation to his Department's freight network capacity plans in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275763","275763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138191","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Annual Report of the Independent Monitoring Board at HMP Lincoln for reporting Year 1 February 2018 to 31 January 2019, published on 8 July 2019, what plans his Department has to reduce the 30 per cent of prisoners that leave HMP Lincoln to homelessness or to no fixed abode.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275821","275821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138192","2019-07-15","Department for Transport","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what role he played in Riveroak Strategic Partners' application for a Development Consent Order on the site of Manston Airport; and what the (a) process and (b) timeframe is for his granting of consent after the Planning Inspectorate’s examination has concluded.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275764","275764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138193","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Annual Report of the Independent Monitoring Board at HMP Lincoln for reporting Year 1 February 2018 to 31 January 2019, what plans his Department has to tackle the 49 per cent increase in incidents of self-harm recorded at HMP Lincoln between 2017 and 2019.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275822","275822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138194","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Annual Report of the Independent Monitoring Board at HMP Lincoln for reporting Year 1 February 2018 to 31 January 2019, what representations has he made to that Board on its statement that there was an extremely tardy manner in which the numerous repair and maintenance jobs across the establishment were dealt with.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275823","275823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138195","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the  Annual Report of the Independent Monitoring Board at HMP Lincoln for	reporting Year 1 February 2018 to 31 January 2019, what assessment has he made of the adequacy of the provision of rehabilitative programmes and courses offered to prisoners upon their release by HMP Lincoln.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275824","275824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138196","2019-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the United Nations Security Council letter dated 26 January 2018 from the Panel of Experts on Yemen mandated by Security Council resolution 2342 (2017) addressed to the President of the Security Council, what steps he took following publication of (a) footnotes 19 and 20 on page 267 and (b) footnote 39 page on 272 recording that components of missiles used by the Saudi-led Coalition in Yemen were manufactured by EDO MBM Technology Limited, UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275727","275727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138197","2019-07-15","Department for Education","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the correlation between the number of students studying (a) design and technology and (b) the English Baccalaureate.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275703","275703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138198","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Annual Report of the Independent Monitoring Board at HMP Lincoln for reporting Year 1 February 2018 to 31 January 2019, published on 8 July 2019, what representations has he made to that Board on its statement that there was an apparent lack of co-ordination across government departments to tackle the high level of homelessness of discharged prisoners.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275825","275825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138199","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of support provided to disabled prisoners at HMP Lincoln.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275826","275826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138200","2019-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the stay of six weeks or less for 60 per cent of prisoners in HMP Lincoln on the ability of that prison to provide adequate rehabilitative services.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275827","275827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138201","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2019 to Question 263224 on Asylum: Detainees, what estimate he has made of the number of people detained at Dungavel immigration removal centre.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275814","275814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138202","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the former places of residence of detainees at Dungavel detention centre.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275815","275815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138203","2019-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the accuracy of the findings of the End Child Poverty Group's report, Local indicators of child poverty, 2017-18, published in May 2019 on child poverty levels in (a) Kettering constituency and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275715","275715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138204","2019-07-15","Cabinet Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants working for central Government departments in each pay band were based in each (a) nation and (b) region of the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275692","275692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138205","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July to Question 269826, what data his Department collects on the number of sexually exploited people supported by his Department to exit prostitution.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275757","275757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138206","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July to Question 269825, what steps she has taken to implement recommendation 36 (e) of the UN Convention on the Elimination of all Forms of Discrimination Against Women to create educational and employment opportunities for women who wish to exit prostitution.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275758","275758"
