"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36806","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many large commercial solar applications have been approved by Ofgem to date.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186465","186465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36807","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to simplify and speed up the applications process for commercial solar schemes.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186466","186466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36808","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average time taken by Ofgem to complete large solar commercial applications is.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186467","186467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36809","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many applications Ofgem has received for large commercial solar schemes.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186463","186463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36810","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what definition his Department uses for a Lower Super Output Area.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186516","186516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36811","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many power outages that were in (a) Wolverhampton and (b) Wolverhampton North East constituency in (i) 2011, (ii) 2012 and (iii) 2013.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186554","186554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36812","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, column 21W, on bovine tuberculosis and with reference to the response to request number RFI 2218 made by Natural England on 15 November 2013, if he will review his policy on parliamentary information to written parliamentary questions to ensure that the standards of openness applied under parliamentary proceedings are no less favourable than those applied under statutory requirements.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186517","186517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36813","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to require the Environment Agency to dredge the Aldingbourne Rife in West Sussex.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186520","186520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36814","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Secretary of State for the Home Department on charges for firearm licences.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186462","186462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36815","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC) when making new policy and legislation, if he will place in the Library all assessments of how new policy and legislation from his Department since January 2013 has given due consideration to the UNCRC.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186585","186585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36816","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assets his Department has sold in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and what the value of each such sale was.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186571","186571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36817","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will place the most recent version of the draft Morecambe Bay Hybrid Fisheries Order in the Library.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186668","186668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36818","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the rise of the pheasant population and its impact on other wildlife.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186618","186618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36819","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what costs savings he expects to make at the Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew, over the next 12 months; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of such changes on the services provided to the public by the gardens.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186736","186736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36820","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of costs savings at the Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew, on the scientific research and conservation work carried out at the gardens.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186737","186737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36821","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on maintenance of buildings within the    Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew, in 2012-13; and if he will list each such building and the cost of repairs to it during that period.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186738","186738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36822","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which organisation his Department and its subsidiary bodies use to tackle internal instances of crime, including corruption and fraud; and whether he has designated this organisation or any individual within it to grant authorisation for carrying out directed surveillance under section 28 of the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186710","186710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36823","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which organisation his Department and its subsidiary bodies use to tackle internal instances of crime, including corruption and fraud; and whether he has designated this organisation or any individual within it to grant authorisation for carrying out directed surveillance under section 28 of the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186711","186711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36824","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British nationals live in (a) China, (b) South Korea, (c) Japan and (d) Singapore.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186729","186729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36825","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British nationals live in other EU member states (a) in total and (b) by member state.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186728","186728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36826","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on bloc voting by EU member states on the Committee of Ministers of the Council of Europe when the EU accedes to the ECHR; whether the Government has taken any steps to prevent bloc voting (a) generally and (b) in respect of future matters to which the European Union is itself a party; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186595","186595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36827","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of (a) permanent, (b) temporary and (c) contract staff in his Department are paid the living wage or above.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186682","186682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36828","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assets his Department has sold in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and what the value of each such sale was.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186572","186572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36829","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC) when making new policy and legislation, if he will place in the Library all assessments of how new policy and legislation from his Department since January 2013 has given due consideration to the UNCRC.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186586","186586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36830","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to view the restitution of, or compensation for, property seized in Montenegro and in which UK citizens have an interest as one of the benchmarks in determining his support for Montenegro's application to join the EU.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186495","186495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36831","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the implementation of relevant UN Security Council resolution on the return of the Cypriot city of Famagusta to its lawful inhabitants under UN administration.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186519","186519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36832","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the threat of Hezbollah to the UK's national interests.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186505","186505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36833","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of Hezbollah fundraising activities in the (a) UK, (b) EU and (c) rest of the world.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186507","186507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36834","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will proscribe the whole of Hezbollah as a terrorist organisation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186497","186497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36835","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the level of the gender pay gap at senior grades in his Department.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186524","186524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36836","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Israel and (b) the Gulf States on Iran's nuclear programme.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186515","186515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36837","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure continued enforcement of economic sanctions against Iran during the six months interim agreement period in respect of that country's nuclear programme.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186514","186514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36838","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Home Office on better addressing issues in the criminal justice system raised during the recent listening exercise on the review of the adult autism strategy.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186556","186556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36839","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Education on better ensuring that it addresses issues on transition raised during the recent listening exercise on the review of the adult autism strategy.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186557","186557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36840","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what systems are in place to monitor the proportion of leaflets advertising the Care.Data scheme that are successfully delivered.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186539","186539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36841","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Ministry of Justice on better addressing issues in the criminal justice system raised during the recent listening exercise on the review of the adult autism strategy.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186558","186558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36842","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2014, Official Report, columns 65-6W, on abortion, if his Department will review data collection protocols in order to record how many doctors have been challenged to defend their decision to refer for an abortion and how many such challenges have been overturned.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186549","186549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36843","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy and effectiveness of current models of care and treatment for people with autism in the NHS.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186482","186482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36844","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish a list of meetings he has attended in which the issue of sugar consumption was discussed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186500","186500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36845","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on the availability of legal highs on the high street.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186501","186501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36846","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England waited for more than a year for treatment in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186490","186490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36847","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that health professionals with expertise in spinal cord injury are included in multidisciplinary teams for continuing health care.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186522","186522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36848","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the process for monitoring the level of care that individuals with severe spinal cord injuries are receiving from their immediate provider.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186523","186523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36849","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research he has commissioned on the effect of sugar consumption on heart disease.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186475","186475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36850","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of sugar on obesity levels.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186476","186476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36851","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of daily calorie intake was provided by added sugar for a (a) male child, (b) female child, (c) male adult and (d) female adult in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186477","186477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36852","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC) when making new policy and legislation, if he will place in the Library all assessments of how new policy and legislation from his Department since January 2013 has given due consideration to the UNCRC.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186587","186587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36853","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assets his Department has sold in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and what the value of each such sale was.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186573","186573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36854","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have opted out of the care.data scheme; and how many people he expects to opt-out overall.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186662","186662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36855","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that spinal cord injured people have access to NHS continuing health care and that the ruling on the case of Pamela Coughlan 1999 is adhered to.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186675","186675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36856","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure all patients are aware of changes to the use of their data.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186674","186674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36857","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether someone who is sanctioned while a mother in receipt of jobseeker's allowance remains eligible for healthy start vouchers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186692","186692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36858","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of (a) permanent, (b) temporary and (c) contract staff in his Department are paid the living wage or above.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186690","186690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36859","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of (a) permanent, (b) temporary and (c) contract staff in her Department are paid the Living Wage or above.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186671","186671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36860","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assets her Department has sold in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and what the value of each such sale was.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186574","186574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36861","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC) when making new policy and legislation, if she will place in the Library all assessments of how new policy and legislation from her Department since January 2013 has given due consideration to the UNCRC.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186588","186588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36862","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost of (a) administering firearms licenses and (b) income from firearms licenses was in each police force in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186652","186652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36863","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list all the people who have been deprived of British citizenship since 2010.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186564","186564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36864","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what payments have been made to (a) Serco and (b) Tascor in respect of the transfer of immigration detainees from Colnbrook Immigration Removal Centre to Harmondsworth Immigration Removal Centre in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186548","186548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36865","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the escorting arrangements are for immigration detainees who are transferred from Harmondsworth Immigration Removal Centre to Colnbrook Immigration Removal Centre.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186546","186546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36866","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what payments have been made to (a) GEO and (b) Tascor in respect of the transfer of immigration detainees from Harmondsworth Immigration Removal Centre to Colnbrook Immigration Removal Centre in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186547","186547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36867","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times she has met the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland (a) in total and (b) specifically to discuss security in Northern Ireland in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186457","186457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36868","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received from the Association of Chief Police Officers on the cost of licensing firearms.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186478","186478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36869","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effects on incidence of (a) antisocial behaviour and (b) domestic violence of extensions to pub opening hours.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186480","186480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36870","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes to Criminal Records Bureau checks on taxi drivers.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186491","186491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36871","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of police cars are equipped with defibrillators.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186492","186492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36872","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people aged 14 to 24 years classified as having complex needs have been arrested in (a) total and (b) each region since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Alan Meale","Sir Alan Meale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186496","186496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36873","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to page 18 of her Department's Evaluation Framework for the UK Drug Strategy, what assessment she has made of (a) the Impact Analysis project of New Drugs Legislation in the Czech Republic, (b) the paper, What can we learn from the Portuguese decriminalization of illicit drugs in the British Journal of Criminology, (c) the King's College London Randomised Injecting Opioid Treatment Trial report, (d) the report by the National Treatment Outcome Research Study, After Five Years, the Department of Health and (e) the No. 10 Strategy Unit Drugs Project Phase 1 report, Understanding the issues; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186538","186538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36874","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national prisoners, who were given temporary release to attend interviews with the immigration service at immigration detention centres operated under contract to the UK Border Agency, were transported to and from their interviews in each month of the last three years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186541","186541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36875","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost has been of escorting foreign national prisoners, who were given temporary release to attend interviews with the immigration service at immigration detention centres operated under contract to the UK Border Agency in each month of the last three years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186542","186542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36876","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration detainees have been transferred from Colbrook Immigration Removal Centre to Harmondsworth Immigration Removal Centre in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186543","186543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36877","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration detainees have been transferred from Harmondsworth Immigration Removal Centre to Colnbrook Immigration Removal Centre in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186544","186544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36878","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether contracted companies receive a payment for each reception and discharge of an immigration detainee.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186545","186545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36879","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will assess the effectiveness of the use of the Royal Prerogative to remove passports from British nationals whom her Department want to prevent from travelling abroad to take part in extremist activity, terrorism training or other fighting.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186537","186537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36880","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which organisation her Department and its subsidiary bodies use to tackle internal instances of crime, including corruption and fraud; and whether she has designated this organisation or any individual within it to grant authorisation for carrying out directed surveillance under section 28 of the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186712","186712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36881","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many work visas have been issued to Chinese nationals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186730","186730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36882","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Chinese nationals are currently residing and working in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186731","186731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36883","2014-02-06","Department for International Development","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which organisation her Department and its subsidiary body use to tackle internal instances of crime, including corruption and fraud; and whether she has designated this organisation or any individual within it to grant authorisation for carrying out directed surveillance under section 28 of the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186713","186713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36884","2014-02-06","Department for International Development","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC) when making new policy and legislation, if she will place in the Library all assessments of how new policy and legislation from her Department since January 2013 has given due consideration to the UNCRC.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186589","186589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36885","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC) when making new policy and legislation, if he will place in the Library all assessments of how new policy and legislation from his Department since January 2013 has given due consideration to the UNCRC.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186590","186590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36886","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) permanent, (b) temporary and (c) contract staff in his Department are paid the Living Wage or above.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186673","186673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36887","2014-02-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assets his Department has sold in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and what the value of each such sale was.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186636","186636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36888","2014-02-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons have gone through his Department's benchmarking process to date; and which prisons are due to be benchmarked under that process during 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186639","186639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36889","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will amend the terms of his contract with the Salvation Army to require that body to record information on the location of victims of human trafficking once they have exited its shelters; and if his Department will make an assessment of the ways in which human trafficking victims are recorded in this country.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186626","186626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36890","2014-02-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how each prison that has gone through his Department's benchmarking process scored against each of the criteria in that process.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186640","186640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36891","2014-02-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the comparator benchmarking scores used in his Department's benchmarking scheme are; and how those scores are calculated.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186642","186642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36892","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of a possible in-house bid for shared services contracts within his Department.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186632","186632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36893","2014-02-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been received on Community Payback since Serco was awarded the contract for that scheme in London; and on what date that contract commenced.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186641","186641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36894","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders released on licence have been returned to prison on fixed term recall basis on more than one occasion in each year since 2008 under (a) the same sentence and (b) a different sentence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186605","186605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36895","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list the outcomes of sentences for convictions of domestic violence offences in 2009 by local criminal justice boards.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186661","186661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36896","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders released on licence were returned to prison on a fixed term recall in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186603","186603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36897","2014-02-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, under payment of results schemes for the provision of offenders services, what proportion of the contract will be subjected to this scheme.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186655","186655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36898","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women have been convicted of murdering one or more of their children in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186599","186599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36899","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were imprisoned in each division in each month since May 2013 for contempt of court.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186598","186598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36900","2014-02-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Magistrates' Association has raised any concerns in respect of the probation change programme.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186656","186656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36901","2014-02-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects that his proposed round-table meeting with groups representing survivors of childhood sexual abuse will take place; and when he expects that invitations to participate in that meeting will be issued.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186553","186553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36902","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners have been given temporary release to attend interviews at immigration detention centres operated under contract to the UK Border Agency in each month of the last three years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186540","186540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36903","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any individuals in England or Wales have been found guilty of fundraising for Hezbollah's proscribed military wing to date.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186506","186506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36904","2014-02-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new matter starts there have been in (a) welfare benefits, (b) family and mediation, (c) debt, (d) employment and (e) housing since April 2013.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186512","186512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36905","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-molestation orders were issued by Horsham County Court in West Sussex in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186458","186458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36906","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which organisation his Department and its subsidiary bodies use to tackle internal instances of crime, including corruption and fraud; and whether he has designated this organisation or any individual within it to grant authorisation for carrying out directed surveillance under section 28 of the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186714","186714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36907","2014-02-06","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the dates and duration were of each conversation she had with Dr Richard Haass between 25 December 2013 and 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186471","186471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36908","2014-02-06","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the dates and duration were of each meeting she has held with the Chief Constable of Northern Ireland since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186472","186472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36909","2014-02-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assets her Department has sold in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and what the value of each such sale was.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186637","186637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36910","2014-02-06","Prime Minister","2014-02-04","To ask the Prime Minister, what the dates and duration of his meetings with the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland have been in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186473","186473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36911","2014-02-10","Prime Minister","2014-02-04","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he had with the (a) Secretary of State for the Home Department and (b) Minister for Crime Prevention before stating on social media on 3 February 2014 that the Government would consult with the pub trade, police and councils on having extended pub opening hours on 14 June 2014.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186479","186479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36913","2014-02-10","Scotland Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent assessment he has made of the level of private sector job creation in Scotland.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186555","186555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36914","2014-02-10","Scotland Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent assessment he has made of the level of child poverty in Scotland.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186695","186695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36915","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC) when making new policy and legislation, if he will place in the Library all assessments of how new policy and legislation from his Department since January 2013 has given due consideration to the UNCRC.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186591","186591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36916","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assets his Department has sold in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and what the value of each such sale was.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186575","186575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36917","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Livingston of 16 January 2014, Official Report, column 646W, on East Coast Railway Line, if he will publish the minutes and any papers from his Department's meetings monitoring train operator performance.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186565","186565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36918","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what impact London Gateway will have on rail freight interchanges in London and the South East.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186627","186627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36919","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, into which budgets the 16 million removed from the accounting category Transport Security in his Department's 2013-14 budget was moved; and what guarantees are in place to ensure the same provision of security is maintained under the new budget allocation.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186647","186647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36920","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the 30-year life expectancy of the proposed Strategic Rail Freight Interchange at Radlett.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186628","186628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36921","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what evaluation he has made of the proposed Strategic Rail Freight Interchange at Sundon with the newly-created passing loop.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186629","186629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36922","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will detail the 70 million liability attached to the International Maritime Organisation building.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186649","186649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36923","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will give the reasons for the growth in the cost of central administration in his Department between the 2012-13 and 2013-14 financial years.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186650","186650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36924","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will detail the sources of revenue within the sales of assets accounting category for the Marine and Coastguard Agency in the financial years 2012-13 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186648","186648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36925","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2014, Official Report, column 655W, on unmanned air vehicles, which Government departments have used unmanned systems to collect data; which unmanned systems are used; and which policies are so supported.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186609","186609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36926","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure alternative strategic rail freight interchange sites to Radlett are fully explored.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186594","186594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36927","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will detail the components of income via interest and dividends in the accounting category K: Aviation, Maritime, Security and Safety in the financial years 2011-12, 2012-13 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186651","186651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36928","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people prosecuted under the Road Traffic Act 1988 were prosecuted for an offence while they were participating in authorised off-road motor events in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186510","186510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36929","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to launch road safety educational programmes to prevent death and injury for motorcyclists in the next year.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186503","186503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36930","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of requiring new drivers to display a probationary plate on the vehicle they are driving for three years after qualification.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186526","186526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36931","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which organisation his Department and its subsidiary bodies use to tackle internal instances of crime, including corruption and fraud; and whether he has designated this organisation or any individual within it to grant authorisation for carrying out directed surveillance under section 28 of the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186715","186715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36932","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish a redacted version of the Major Projects Report excluding any content detrimental to the developer of the High Speed 2 project.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186739","186739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36933","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the UK's Representation to the EU's negotiating mandate is regarding the proposed EU port services regulation.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186733","186733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36934","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date the European Council will next discuss the proposed EU port services regulation.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186734","186734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36935","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of the EU port services regulation on UK ports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186732","186732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36936","2014-02-06","Women and Equalities","2014-02-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many and what proportion of businesses participating in the Government's Think Act Report scheme have (a) conducted a gender pay audit, (b) are publicly reporting the pay of all employees by gender and (c) adopted any other measures under the Think Act Report scheme.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186620","186620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36937","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his letter of 8 January 2014 to the hon. Member for Bishop Auckland on the performance of Atos, when he will publish the results of his Department's monitoring of the delivery and quality of service provided by Atos.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186619","186619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36938","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the benefit to the economy of mothers in work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186621","186621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36939","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assets his Department has sold in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and what the value of each such sale was.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186638","186638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36940","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the statement by the Minister of State for Employment in European Committee B on 16 December 2013, Official Report, column 5, in relation to Youth Contract wage incentives, that more than 20,000 have been paid out so far, whether this refers to youth contract wage incentive job starts, or to wage incentives paid out; and to what date the figure refers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186676","186676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36941","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC) when making new policy and legislation, if he will place in the Library all assessments of how new policy and legislation from his Department since January 2013 has given due consideration to the UNCRC.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186593","186593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36942","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what benefits are available to people appealing an Employment and Support Allowance decision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186683","186683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36943","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of (a) permanent, (b) temporary and (c) contract staff in his Department are paid the living wage or above.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186681","186681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36944","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken following the conviction of A4E employees for fraud; and what steps he has taken to prevent similar abuse in other companies which are contracted to provide services by his Department.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186725","186725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36945","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2013, Official Report, column 669W, on employment and support allowance, if he will set out (a) what medical conditions those transferred from incapacity benefit to jobseeker's allowance after having being seen by an assessor have been diagnosed with and how many such people have been diagnosed with each such condition and (b) how many people put in the work related activity group without having been seen by an assessor have been in contact with the work programme; how many such people have achieved employment outcomes; how many people put in the work related activity group after having been seen by an assessor have been in contact with the work programme; how many such people have achieved employment outcomes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186702","186702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36946","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the change in the number of jobs in Wales and in other regions in the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186726","186726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36947","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which Work Programme providers are using an IPS intervention to assist clients with mental health problems into work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186693","186693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36948","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2013, Official Report, column 669W, on employment and support allowance, if he will set out (a) the age of those with a mental health condition who were transferred from incapacity benefit to an employment and support allowance work-related activity group without being seen by an assessor, (b) what medical conditions those on incapacity benefit had been diagnosed with for the period September 2011 to November 2012 and how many such people have been diagnosed with each such condition and (c) what medical conditions those transferred from incapacity benefit to the employment and support allowance support group without being seen by an assessor have been diagnosed; and how many such people have been diagnosed with each such condition.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186700","186700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36949","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the performance of Work Programme drug and alcohol pilots.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186691","186691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36950","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Jobcentre Plus is funding employment support through Community Drug and Alcohol services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186696","186696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36951","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) evaluated on fraud rates among (i) EEA and (ii) EU migrants claiming UK benefits; and what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the Exchequer of such fraud.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186481","186481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36952","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children living in households where one or both parents are (a) working part-time because they are unable to find full-time work and (b) employed on a zero hours contract.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186513","186513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36953","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Coventry have undergone a work capability assessment in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186489","186489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36954","2014-02-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children living in poverty with at least one working parent; and what recent estimate he has made of such figures in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186487","186487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36955","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time is for applicants for personal independence payments to be seen by Atos Healthcare for an assessment in each region.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186721","186721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36956","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what target his Department has set Atos Healthcare for the length of time taken to complete assessments for personal independence payments; and what steps his Department takes when that target is not met.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186722","186722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36957","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has imposed any penalties on Atos Healthcare for delays that personal independence payment applicants have experienced in waiting for an assessment since April 2013.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186723","186723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36958","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which organisation his Department and its subsidiary bodies use to tackle internal instances of crime, including corruption and fraud; and whether he has designated this organisation or any individual within it to grant authorisation for carrying out directed surveillance under section 28 of the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186717","186717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36959","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2013, Official Report, column 669W, on employment and support allowance, if he will set out (a) what medical conditions those transferred from incapacity benefit to jobseeker's allowance without being seen by an assessor have been diagnosed with and how many such people have been diagnosed with each such condition, (b) what medical conditions those transferred from incapacity benefit to the employment and support allowance support group after having being seen by an assessor have been diagnosed with and how many such people have been diagnosed with each such condition and (c) what medical conditions those transferred from incapacity benefit to the employment and support allowance work-related activity group after having being seen by an assessor have been diagnosed with; and how many such people have been diagnosed with each such condition.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186701","186701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37038","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to increase the participation of older people in further education.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902478","902478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37053","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of the Government's policy on tax-free childcare on low income households.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902490","902490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36421","2014-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to prevent reforms of HM Land Registry leading to the off-shoring of jobs.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186216","186216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36422","2014-02-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish a list of the illiquid assets that became available from the transfer of the Royal Mail pension fund in March 2012.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186229","186229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36423","2014-02-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the illiquid assets acquired by the Government following the transfer of the Royal Mail pension fund in March 2012 have been; to which buyers; and at what price to date.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186276","186276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36424","2014-02-06","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, under which terms and conditions John Manzoni has been appointed Chief Executive of the Major Projects Authority; when he commences this position; what his annual salary and any bonus scheme is; and if he will place in the Library a copy of his contract of employment.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186232","186232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36425","2014-02-06","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what payments were made to David Pitchford, the former Executive of the Major Projects Authority, during the term of his appointment; what his (a) annual salary, (b) claimed bonuses, payoffs or other lump sums and (c) any other remuneration were; and if he will place in the Library a copy of his contract of employment.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186233","186233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36426","2014-02-06","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which projects and accompanying report have been examined by the Major Projects Authority since that body was established; and what traffic-light classification was given to each such project and report.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186234","186234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36427","2014-02-06","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recruitment or executive search process was used to recruit the new Chief Executive of the Major Projects Authority; what the total cost of the recruitment process was; which individuals acting on behalf of the Government interviewed the candidates; and what recruitment or executive search companies were employed for this purpose; at what cost; and under which terms and conditions.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186235","186235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36428","2014-02-05","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to ensure that charities do not act in a politically partisan way.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186213","186213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36429","2014-02-05","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent representations his Department has received about charities acting in a politically partisan way.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186214","186214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36430","2014-02-06","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many honours were awarded in each year since 1995.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186277","186277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36431","2014-02-13","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change there has been in median gross weekly pay for (a) men and (b) women in Houghton and Sunderland South constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186264","186264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36432","2014-02-13","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of providing companies investing in the exploitation of onshore oil and gas and including shale gas an allowance equal to 75 per cent of their capital spend on such projects.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186263","186263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36433","2014-02-13","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the recently announced tax allowance for the exploitation of onshore oil and gas and shale gas will cost the public purse in tax year (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18; and how such figures have been calculated.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186265","186265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36434","2014-02-05","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what amount of quoted Eurobonds were issued by companies within the charge to UK corporation tax or income tax in circumstances where there is only one noteholder; what total interest was paid on those Eurobonds; and how much such interest was (a) allowed as a deduction against such companies' corporation tax or income tax profits, (b) disallowed pursuant to self-assessed transfer pricing returns or advance in capitalisation agreements and (c) disallowed following enquiries by HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186301","186301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36435","2014-02-05","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the workings of the Barnett Formula.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186215","186215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36436","2014-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new homes were built in London last year; and what the target for such building was.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186204","186204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36437","2014-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to tackle rising rents in London.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186205","186205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36438","2014-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the council tax freeze grant will be; and whether this sum will be built in to the council base settlement for future years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186230","186230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36439","2014-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to announce the capping limit on council tax for the coming financial year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186231","186231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36440","2014-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what financial support his Department provided to the Hindu community in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186227","186227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36441","2014-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 489W, on William Hill, if he will place in the Library a copy of the letter received in November 2011 and the response from his Department.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186335","186335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36442","2014-02-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the future sporting and cultural expansion of Lilleshall National Sports Centre; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186266","186266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36443","2014-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress was made at the recent Franco-British summit in relation to defence equipment collaboration; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186324","186324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36444","2014-02-06","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will be accompanied by (a) a human rights adviser and (b) an expert on the Government's Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative on his forthcoming visit to Colombia.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186250","186250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36445","2014-02-06","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will meet trades unionists during his forthcoming visit to Colombia.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186248","186248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36446","2014-02-06","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether all organisations and individuals accompanying him on his forthcoming visit to Colombia have been briefed on the UK Action Plan on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186249","186249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36447","2014-02-06","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with which outside academic bodies the Democratic Engagement Project is now working.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186254","186254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36448","2014-02-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the implications of UK policy on changes in Northern Ireland voter registration statistics in the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186302","186302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36449","2014-02-05","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary schools offer female pupils access to cricket teaching.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186312","186312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36450","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will bring forward proposals to ratify the Optional Protocol to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child on a Communications Procedure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186274","186274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36451","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has reviewed the use of radio frequency identification technology with a real-time location system at UK West Cheshire College in Chester; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186331","186331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36452","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the contribution of school support staff to educational attainment at schools in England.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186236","186236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36453","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of support staff working in schools in (a) England, (b) the West Midlands, (c) Dudley Metropolitan Borough and (d) Dudley North constituency.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186237","186237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36454","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the elevated levels of radiation detected at Sellafield on 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186256","186256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36455","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the economic cost was of running Sellafield with only essential staff on 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186257","186257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36456","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the noise maps created for the second round of strategic noise mapping as part of the Noise Action Plan will be published.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186255","186255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36457","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the government of Montenegro settles all outstanding compensation or restitution claims for illegally seized property in that country as part of the pre-qualifying criteria for admission into the EU.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186218","186218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36458","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold discussions with his EU partners on introducing (a) a visa ban and (b) steps to freeze assets held within the EU on individuals involved in human rights abuses in Ukraine.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186219","186219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36459","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 23 December 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Elizabeth Wheelan.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186221","186221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36460","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce political corruption in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186293","186293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36461","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of financial sanctions on members of the government of Zimbabwe and associated individuals.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186295","186295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36462","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of resources possessed by the International Atomic Energy Agency and its ability to enforce the terms agreed with Iran in November 2013.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186296","186296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36463","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of unrest in the Central African Republic on neighbouring countries.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186297","186297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36464","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reach a comprehensive final settlement on Iran's nuclear programme.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186298","186298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36465","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department has provided to the Crown Dependencies and Overseas Territories to implement the Financial Action Task Force Standards.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186299","186299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36466","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with its Nigerian counterpart on improvements aimed at increasing transparency and visibility in the oil and gas sector.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186300","186300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36467","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence on the ongoing technology appraisal of ipilimumab for the treatment of advanced melanoma.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186281","186281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36468","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS staff are on long-term registered sick leave.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186342","186342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36469","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been transferred to an NHS hospital following complications in their treatment at a private hospital in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186278","186278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36470","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of households have not yet received a Better data means better care leaflet; and when he expects the leaflet drop to be completed.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186267","186267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36471","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of HIV have been identified in (a) St Albans constituency, (b) Hertfordshire, (c) the East of England and (d) the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186223","186223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36472","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish an analysis of the cases of HIV identified in (a) St Albans constituency, (b) Hertfordshire, (c) the East of England and (d) the UK among people of each (i) gender, (ii) age group and (iii) ethnicity group.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186224","186224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36473","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department provides for the treatment of HIV in (a) St Albans constituency, (b) Hertfordshire, (c) the East of England and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186225","186225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36474","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the HPV vaccination among young women since 2008.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186226","186226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36475","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training health professionals receive on engaging with new fathers.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186202","186202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36476","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that maternity services acknowledge and provide support to new fathers.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186203","186203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36477","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent meetings (a) Ministers in his Department and (b) NHS England National Directors have held with representatives of private healthcare providers; and what the (i) dates, (ii) attendees and (iii) subject matter were of any such meetings.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186258","186258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36478","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many diabetes-related amputations were carried out in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186282","186282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36479","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of diabetic retinopathy have been diagnosed in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186283","186283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36480","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many forced marriages have been recorded in the UK in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186217","186217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36481","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration dated 23 December 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mrs Elizabeth Adejoke Omitola.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186220","186220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36482","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of moving the firearms licensing system online.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186289","186289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36483","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the introduction of online visa applications and booking systems.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186294","186294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36484","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent work has been undertaken by the taskforce on tackling extremism.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186290","186290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36485","2014-02-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the role played by civil society organisations in Bangladesh's democracy.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186292","186292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36486","2014-02-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to end aid dependency through the creation of jobs in Gaza.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186291","186291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36487","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have been incorrectly assigned places as part of Community Payback in London since Serco was awarded the contract for the delivery of that programme.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186340","186340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36488","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what targets are included in Serco's contract for Community Payback in London.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186280","186280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36489","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average time is taken to answer telephone calls by Serco with regards to placements for offenders as part of the London Community Payback contract.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186279","186279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36490","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork in young offender institutions.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186343","186343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36491","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many unpaid penalty notice orders were cancelled in (a) England and Wales and (b) each police authority area in each year from 2010 to 2013; and what the value was of those cancelled orders in each such year.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186341","186341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36492","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of all cases heard in family courts where both the mother and father sought custody of their children the residence order was awarded to (a) the mother, (b) the father and (c) jointly to both the mother and father in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186222","186222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36493","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to protect grandparents' access rights.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186275","186275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36494","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of grandparents' right of access to their grandchildren in the event of family breakdown.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186325","186325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36495","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women serving a custodial sentence in prison in England and Wales gave birth in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186252","186252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36496","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women served a custodial sentence while pregnant in England and Wales in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186253","186253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36497","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women serving a custodial sentence in prison in England and Wales had a miscarriage in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186251","186251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36498","2014-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many penalty notice orders were (a) issued, (b) not paid within a 21-day payment window and (c) never paid in (i) England and Wales and (ii) each police authority area in each year from 2010 to 2013; and how many outstanding fines there were of what monetary value on 31 December (A) 2010, (B) 2011, (C) 2012 and (D) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186228","186228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36499","2014-02-05","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with (a) ministerial colleagues and (b) Transport for London on Crossrail Two.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186206","186206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36500","2014-02-05","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate HS2 Ltd has made of the number of classic compatible services originating at stations north of Wigan which will (a) call at and (b) terminate at Manchester Piccadilly once phase 2 of High Speed 2 is complete.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186303","186303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36501","2014-02-05","Women and Equalities","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether it is her policy to support cricket teaching at secondary school level for girls and young women.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186313","186313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36502","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the content and purpose are of performance improvement plans for jobcentre staff; how many staff have a performance improvement plan at each jobcentre; how such plans relate to staff disciplinary procedures and performance assessment; and for what purpose statistics relating to such plans are reported to and maintained by his Department.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186288","186288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36503","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of the discretionary housing payment allocation for 2013-14 has been targeted at people who have wheelchair-standard properties.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186336","186336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36504","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the recommendations of the Jobseeker's Allowance Skills Conditionality Pilot evaluation report published in August 2011.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186333","186333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36505","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of claimants of employment and support allowance/incapacity benefit since August 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186332","186332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36506","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the backlog is of personal independence payment and disability living allowance claims at each regional disability benefit centre.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186284","186284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36507","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the backlog is of employment and support allowance and jobseeker's allowance claims at each jobcentre.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186285","186285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36508","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what changes in the number of staff are proposed for each (a) regional disability benefit centre and (b) jobcentre.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186286","186286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36509","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the probability of meeting the commitment to eradicate child poverty by 2020.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186337","186337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36510","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what procedures have been put in place in jobcentres to deal with the consequences of the removal of warm phones from jobcentres.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186287","186287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36511","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to amend or replace the Child Poverty Act 2010 as a result of his Department's consultation on measuring child poverty.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186338","186338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36512","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measure he will assess on whether the Government has met the commitment to eradicate child poverty by 2020.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186339","186339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36513","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to prevent applicants for employment and support allowance suffering financial hardship while awaiting a work capability assessment.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186207","186207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36514","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to fast track claims for employment and support allowance where the claimant is identified as being at risk of financial hardship; what definition of financial hardship his Department applies; and what role (a) his Department's decision-maker and (b) medical assessors play in making a decision to fast track.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186208","186208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36515","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are currently awaiting work capability assessments.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186209","186209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36516","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that applications from claimants of employment and support allowance suffering financial hardship are dealt with as a priority.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186210","186210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36517","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of applicants for employment and support allowance who do not receive a decision within the target waiting time of 35 days; and what steps he is taking to expedite such applications.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186211","186211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36518","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time for applicants for employment and support allowance is between submission of the ESA50 form and the date of the work capability assessment.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186212","186212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36519","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has plans to alter the indexation used to uprate pensions credit.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186326","186326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36520","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of the Jobcentre Plus Flexible Support Fund budget for 2012-13 was spent on (a) transport, (b) childcare, (c) training and (d) other costs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186330","186330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36521","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which of the 12 policy recommendations in DWP Research report 768, The Jobseeker's Allowance Skills Conditionality Pilot evaluation report, published in August 2011, have been implemented; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186334","186334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36522","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pensioners were living in poverty in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK in each financial year since 1996-97; and what estimate he has made of the number of such pensioners in the current financial year.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186328","186328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36523","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made with transitional arrangements to allow people who will receive the new single-tier state pension to receive passported benefits from April 2016.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186327","186327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36524","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the performance and effect of the Jobcentre Plus Flexible Support Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186329","186329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36525","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2013, Official Report, columns 759-60W, on poverty, on what date he expects to publish the Government's response to the consultation on measuring child poverty.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186273","186273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36526","2014-02-05","Attorney General","2014-02-03","To ask the Attorney General, how many public appointments the Law Officers' Departments made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of  such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186390","186390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36527","2014-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186389","186389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36528","2014-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to allow sub post offices to trial new technologies such as scanning of ID pictures and other procedures in order to supply front office counter services to boost future footfall and business to benefit all of the Post Office network.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186422","186422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36529","2014-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support the Government is giving to business growth opportunities in Greater London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186423","186423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36530","2014-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many injuries have been caused by electrical products either (a) then subject to or (b) subsequently subject to a product recall action in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186430","186430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36531","2014-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many dwelling fires have been caused by electrical products either (a) then subject to or (b) subsequently subject to a product recall action in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186431","186431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36532","2014-02-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received on extending the remit of the Gangmasters Licensing Authority to cover additional sectors of the economy.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186442","186442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36533","2014-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what timetable or deadline he has for the completion of the sale of illiquid assets acquired following the transfer of the Royal Mail pension fund.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186268","186268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36534","2014-02-05","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186391","186391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36535","2014-02-05","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the (a) cost to the Exchequer and (b) effects on vehicle uptake of reducing the duty differential for liquid petroleum gas by one pence per litre per year in each year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186382","186382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36536","2014-02-05","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.92 of the Autumn Statement 2013, what assessment he has made of the (a) fiscal effects and (b) effects on vehicle uptake of his plans to continue reducing the duty differential for liquid petroleum gas by one pence per litre per year in each year up to 2024-25.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186383","186383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36537","2014-02-05","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186407","186407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36538","2014-02-06","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many house sales have been completed in Barrow and Furness constituency using the Help-to-Buy scheme since that scheme's introduction.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186439","186439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36539","2014-02-06","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the additional revenue accruing in the form of (a) income tax and (b) national insurance contributions as a result of people moving off benefits and into employment in each of the last four quarters.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186346","186346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36540","2014-02-05","HM Treasury","2014-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made as part of his continuing review of all taxes of the environmental impact of liquid petroleum gas in comparison with other road fuel gases.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186311","186311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36541","2014-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with local authorities about the safety effect of dimming street lighting.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186310","186310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36542","2014-02-05","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to encourage the adoption of unadopted roads where there is a dispute over responsibility for paying for essential maintenance.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186272","186272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36543","2014-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that local authorities are able to build or purchase properties for social housing.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186377","186377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36544","2014-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the Government has set aside for local authorities to build or purchase properties for social housing in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186378","186378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36545","2014-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186392","186392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36546","2014-02-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many public appointments her Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186393","186393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36547","2014-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186394","186394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36548","2014-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to amend the D-Notice system.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186415","186415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36549","2014-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps were taken in respect of recommendation 95 in the Tornado Airworthiness Review Team Report Table of Recommendations, Action Officers and Status Notes dated 5 February 1998.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186448","186448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36550","2014-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what safety issues were identified in recommendation 95 of the Tornado Airworthiness Review Team Report Table of Recommendations, Action Officers and Status Notes dated 5 February 1998 regarding the Tornado's ejection seat.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186449","186449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36551","2014-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the net book value is of a single Trident warhead.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186450","186450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36552","2014-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to ensure the participation in commemorations of the First World War of RAF squadrons whose formation can be traced to that war.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186271","186271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36553","2014-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many incidents have been reported of (a) civilian staff and (b) military personnel using illegal drugs at UK nuclear bases in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186243","186243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36554","2014-02-06","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what discussions he has had regarding the human rights and labour standards clauses in the EU Free Trade Agreement with Peru and Colombia ahead of his visit to South America.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186246","186246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36555","2014-02-06","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on the UK Action Plan on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186247","186247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36556","2014-02-05","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent meetings he has had with representatives of (a) Facebook, (b) Ask FM and (c) other social media; and what was discussed at each such meeting.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186349","186349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36557","2014-02-05","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to assist schools in educating young people on the dangers of using hazardous substances.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186350","186350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36558","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) junior and (b) middle schools were in the lowest 268 for value-added progress for key stage one to key stage two for disadvantaged pupils in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186370","186370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36559","2014-02-05","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to permit the Independent Schools Inspectorate to undertake inspections of state-funded academies which are sponsored by schools or foundations within the independent sector.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186351","186351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36560","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to train new teaching assistants.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186239","186239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36561","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to recruit teaching assistants.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186240","186240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36562","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will place in the Library copies of all correspondence his Department holds on the use of radio-frequency identification technology with a real-time location system in schools produced in the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186344","186344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36563","2014-02-06","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support teaching assistants.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186238","186238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36564","2014-02-05","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils in England achieved no GCSEs at A* to C grade in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Jeremy Browne","Mr Jeremy Browne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186306","186306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36565","2014-02-05","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools were rated (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) satisfactory or requires improvement and (d) special measures by Ofsted in each parliamentary constituency and local authority in England in (i) May 2010 and (ii) January 2014.","Biography information for George Freeman","George Freeman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186388","186388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36566","2014-02-05","Department for Education","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186395","186395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36567","2014-02-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186396","186396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36568","2014-02-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will publish forward projections of electricity generation by type for the next 15 years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186356","186356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36569","2014-02-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of water meters in reducing housing water bills.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186320","186320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36570","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many incidents there have been of staff of nuclear power facilities being (a) disciplined and (b) dismissed for inappropriate behaviour in each of the last three years; and what the nature of each such incident was.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186244","186244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36571","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many incidents there have been of staff at nuclear facilities using illegal drugs in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186245","186245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36572","2014-02-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what research has been undertaken (a) by his Department or (b) on behalf of his Department on the adequacy of sea defences to protect the (i) Sellafield nuclear site and (ii) low level waste repository at Drigg.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186354","186354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36573","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of any duplication between accreditation that applies to installers of renewable technology under the Micro Generation certification scheme and installation of technology under the Green Deal; and if he will estimate the cost to businesses of any such duplication.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186372","186372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36574","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many green deal assessments have been completed to date; and how many such assessments were for heat pumps as qualifying technology that had already been installed.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186371","186371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36575","2014-02-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) UK, (b) European and (c) other international energy companies have applied for licences to explore for shale gas in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186361","186361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36576","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans he has to provide assistance to dementia patients who are living in fuel poverty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186369","186369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36577","2014-02-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people with dementia living in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186366","186366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36578","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on flood defences in Chatham and Aylesford constituency in (a) 2007-8, (b) 2008-09, (c) 2009-10, (d) 2010-11, (e) 2011-12 and (f) 2012-13; and how much has been allocated by his Department for flood defences in that constituency in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186365","186365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36579","2014-02-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs entered the UK from each country for (a) non-commercial purposes uinder the Pet Travel Scheme and (b) commercial purposes under the Balai Directive 92/45/EEC in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186362","186362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36580","2014-02-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research has been carried out by (a) his Department, (b) consultants for his Department and (c) agencies for which he is responsible on the effects on the release of methane gas from rotted grass and other vegetation inundated by the recent floods.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186352","186352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36581","2014-02-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consideration he has given to building wind-powered pumps to assist water management on the Somerset levels; and whether he has had discussions with his Dutch counterpart on the use of such pumps in the Netherlands.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186353","186353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36582","2014-02-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to encourage greater use of carbon dioxide-based methods of male chick disposal at UK hatcheries.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186323","186323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36583","2014-02-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the prevalence of maceration in UK hatcheries.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186322","186322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36584","2014-02-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures are in place to promote the use of water meters.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186384","186384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36585","2014-02-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186397","186397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36586","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many successful prosecutions have been brought by the Gangmasters Licensing Authority in each year since it was established.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186433","186433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36587","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what level of resources he has made available to the Gangmasters Licensing Authority (GLA) in each of the last three years; and what resources he plans to make available to the GLA in 2014-15.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186436","186436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36588","2014-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the likelihood of increased marine flooding on the Furness peninsular as a result of changing climate patterns.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186438","186438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36589","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 472W, on Iran, whether Iran has clarified how it would use plutonium produced at the Arak Heavy Water Research Reactor.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186434","186434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36590","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 472W, on Iran, whether the Joint Plan of Action allows Iran to manufacture components off-site for the Arak Heavy Water Research Reactor.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186437","186437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36591","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 472W, on Iran, whether the Joint Plan of Action requires Iran to provide detailed information to the International Atomic Energy Agency on all undeclared nuclear facilities.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186435","186435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36592","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the US authorities on having the label "specially designated global terrorist entity" lifted from the charity organisation Interpal.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186432","186432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36593","2014-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186398","186398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36594","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to encourage reconciliation between the conflicting sides in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186379","186379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36595","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the outcome of the negotiations on Iran's nuclear programme at the Geneva Summit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186380","186380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36596","2014-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress of negotiations on settlements in the West Bank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186381","186381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36597","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people from black, Asian and minority ethnic backgrounds were diagnosed with type 2 diabetes in England in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186358","186358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36598","2014-02-05","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people from Black, Asian and minority ethnic backgrounds died from type 2 diabetes in England in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186357","186357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36599","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with type 2 diabetes in England in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186359","186359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36600","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of midwives are on long-term registered sick leave.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186375","186375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36601","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) job title and (b) pay grade is of each member of staff in his private office; and when each member of staff was appointed.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186241","186241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36602","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many non-permanent civil servants work in his private office.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186242","186242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36603","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) evaluated on possible links between paracetamol and Alzheimer's Disease; and what discussions he has had with regulatory bodies on such links.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186270","186270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36604","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether patient data extracted through the care.data programme will be used to facilitate direct care for individual patients.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186315","186315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36605","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2014, Official Report, column 227W, on abortion, under what conditions and what other factors may influence gender being considered a relevant criterion for an abortion under the Abortion Act 1967 (as amended); and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186308","186308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36606","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the accuracy of the Information Governance Assessment on care.data  published by the Health and Social Care Information Centre on 29 August 2013.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186316","186316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36607","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what use his Department makes of information governance assessments on care.data by the Health and Social Care Information Centre; and which is the most recent such assessment used by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186317","186317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36608","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2014, Official Report, column 227W, on abortion, what measures are in place to prevent a registered medical practitioner forming an opinion in good faith that the baby's gender would cause a greater risk to the physical or mental health of the pregnant woman than if the pregnancy were terminated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186309","186309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36609","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186399","186399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36610","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to remove geographic inequalities in the dispensing of the Humira form of the drug adalimumab; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186385","186385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36611","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that there should not be an upper age limit for gastric bypass operations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186386","186386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36612","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will create a Food Crime Unit within the Food Standards Agency.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186446","186446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36613","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the public health impact of the recent flooding in South West England; and what steps he is taking to address this issue.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186447","186447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36614","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to stop abortions due to the gender of the foetus being female.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186454","186454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36615","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what cross-departmental meetings on food crime have been attended by (a) Minsters and (b) civil servants.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186445","186445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36616","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GPs who have received mental health training.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186443","186443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36617","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) staff and (b) budgetary resources have been allocated to the Chief Inspector of Hospitals.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186429","186429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36618","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of mental health training currently given to GPs.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186444","186444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36619","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) male and (b) female foetuses were aborted in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186455","186455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36620","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with health bodies on development of medication to prevent nut allergy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186456","186456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36621","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many elderly people have had post-operative problems with a joint replacement in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186453","186453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36622","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with (a) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) and (b) NHS England on the potential effect of NICE's proposals for value-based assessment on (i) access to cancer medicines and (ii) expenditure on the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186440","186440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36623","2014-02-06","Department of Health","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE's) proposals to value-based assessment on patient's access to cancer medicines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186441","186441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36624","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure the preservation of religious liberty within the guidance on her planned Injunction to Prevent Nuisance or Annoyance orders.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186451","186451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36625","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has had from local and community bodies on her plans to replace anti-social behaviour orders with Injunction to Prevent Nuisance or Annoyance orders.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186452","186452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36626","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Republic of Ireland on the prevention of human trafficking between jurisdictions.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186424","186424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36627","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her Swedish counterpart on steps that the Swedish government has taken to tackle human trafficking.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186425","186425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36628","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were convicted of human trafficking offences in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186426","186426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36629","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people trafficked into the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186427","186427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36630","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of those trafficked into the UK for the purposes of (a) domestic servitude, (b) forced labour and (c) prostitution.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186428","186428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36631","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many investigations the Independent Police Complaints Commission has abandoned due to the officer or officers under investigation leaving the police force in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186412","186412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36632","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the Independent Police Complaints Commission defines restraint-related deaths involving police officers that occur outside the physical premises of a police station.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186413","186413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36633","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many investigations into individual complaints of excessive use of force have been undertaken by the Independent Police Complaints Commission in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186411","186411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36634","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officers are currently being investigated by the Independent Police Complaints Commission in relation to complaints of excessive use of force.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186410","186410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36635","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many public appointments her Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186400","186400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36636","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Independent Police Complaints Commission definition of a death in custody is for statistical purposes.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186414","186414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36637","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received on the charges levied by local police authorities for policing of commercial public events; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186261","186261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36638","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received on the different level of charges levied by local police authorities for policing of commercial public events; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186262","186262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36639","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths were attributable to legal highs in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Julian Brazier","Mr Julian Brazier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186259","186259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36640","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to secure the long-term future of the National Wildlife Crime Unit.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186305","186305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36641","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received on establishing a national pricing scale for charges by local police authorities for policing of commercial public events; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186260","186260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36642","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa applications were refused due to applicant error in the last 12 months; and how many such decisions were subsequently overturned at appeal.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186360","186360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36643","2014-02-06","Home Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the time limit will be for requesting an administrative review under the provisions of Clause 11 of the Immigration Bill currently before Parliament; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186364","186364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36644","2014-02-05","House of Commons Commission","2014-02-03","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, whether Palace of Westminster guides are contractors or employees of the House of Commons Commission.","Biography information for John Cryer","John Cryer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186345","186345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36645","2014-02-05","House of Commons Commission","2014-02-03","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, whether full-time employees of the House Service are required to have a separate contract if they are also employed by the House on a zero hours contract.","Biography information for John Cryer","John Cryer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186421","186421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36646","2014-02-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many public appointments her Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186401","186401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36647","2014-02-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the announcement made during her visit to the Philippines on 24 November 2013, whether the 5 million investment in resilience will be used to rebuild destroyed evacuation centres and storm shelters; and what plans she has to make further funding available for this purpose.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186319","186319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36648","2014-02-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the announcement made during her visit to the Philippines on 24 November 2013, which cities will be allocated the 5 million investment in resilience; and how these cities were selected.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186318","186318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36649","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young people in custody are subject to Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork to minimise the risk of self-harm and suicide.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186321","186321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36650","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if the Government will bring forward amendments to the Human Rights Act 1998 to ensure that the Act applies in situations where people receive care arranged by a public body from a private provider.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186348","186348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36651","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186402","186402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36652","2014-02-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many public appointments her Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186403","186403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36653","2014-02-05","Prime Minister","2014-02-03","To ask the Prime Minister, how many public appointments No. 10 Downing Street made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186404","186404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36654","2014-02-05","Scotland Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186405","186405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36655","2014-02-05","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-03","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what research the Electoral Commission has conducted on its standing amongst hon. Members.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186387","186387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36656","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the (a) public and (b) private bodies to which the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency, Swansea is authorised to release the (i) identities and (ii) home addresses of car registration numbers.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186416","186416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36657","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the Information Commissioner's Office on the propriety of the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency, Swansea releasing personal data of car registration number owners to private companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186417","186417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36658","2014-02-05","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186406","186406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36659","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to ensure that the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency, Swansea shall not in future supply private car parking companies with the personal data of car registration number owners; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186420","186420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36660","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library a copy of the guidance under which the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency, Swansea has been providing personal data of car registration number owners to private parking companies.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186419","186419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36661","2014-02-10","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what checks the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency, Swansea carries out on the (a) bona fides and (b) operating standards of private parking companies before releasing personal data to such companies about the owners of car registration numbers.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186418","186418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36662","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the performance of London Midland and of the future of their franchise; and whether the performance of London Midland from Watford continues to be monitored daily.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186368","186368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36663","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what weight his Department will give to performance on the Abbey Flier train line and investment in that route as a factor in the negotiations for the next operator of the West Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186367","186367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36664","2014-02-05","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what improvements will be required to the existing West Coast Main Line north of Wigan to allow classic compatible services to run to stations beyond Preston; and what estimate HS2 Ltd has made of the cost of such improvements.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186304","186304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36665","2014-02-05","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 771W, on High Speed 2 Railway Line, which individual upgrades HS2 Ltd believes are required to the existing West Coast Main Line between Crewe and Wigan to enable classic compatible services to Preston and beyond without the Winterbottom to Bamfurlong spur; and what the cost estimate of each individual upgrade is.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186314","186314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36666","2014-02-05","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which other sites were considered as potential locations for the rolling stock maintenance depot currently planned for Bamfurlong.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186307","186307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36667","2014-02-05","Wales Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Welsh Government on lessons learned from water management in the Gwent Levels for other flood prone areas in Wales.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186355","186355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36668","2014-02-05","Wales Office","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186408","186408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36669","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on using EU resources to help fund foodbanks.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186269","186269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36670","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2014, Official Report, column 583W, on housing benefit: social rented housing, for what reasons the Government's contribution to the overall discretionary housing payments allocation reduced from 180 million in 2013-14 to 165 million in 2014-15 and is planned to increase to 205 million in 2015-16.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186373","186373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36671","2014-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how his Deparment expects the cost of installing, maintaining and repairing special equipment and adaptations for housing will be met after universal credit replaces housing benefit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186376","186376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36672","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total housing benefit bill was for England in each year since 2002-03.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186363","186363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36673","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many workers made redundant as a result of the closure of Remploy in South Gyle, Edinburgh are (a) seeking work, (b) no longer seeking work and (c) in employment.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186347","186347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36674","2014-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was for the Pensions Regulator to complete an investigation into allegations of pension abandonment in the most recent period for which information is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186374","186374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36675","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many public appointments his Department made in the last 12 months; how many such appointments are remunerated posts; what the level of such remuneration is; and how many people so appointed are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186409","186409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37246","2014-02-06","Leader of the House","2014-02-03","To ask the Leader of the House, what the cost of repairs and maintenance of the Chevening Estate was in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902442","902442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37254","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of progress on the High Speed 2 Phase One environmental statement consultation.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902426","902426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37255","2014-02-06","Department for Transport","2014-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make a statement on his departmental responsibilities.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902446","902446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36291","2014-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in Mid Sussex constituency are enrolled in adult skills sessions.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186181","186181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36292","2014-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what use he has made of the powers granted to him by the Enterprise and Regulatory Reform Act 2013 with respect to property management agent redress schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186197","186197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36293","2014-02-05","Cabinet Office","2014-01-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women were classified as working part-time in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186196","186196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36294","2014-02-05","Cabinet Office","2014-01-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women have (a) entered and (b) left the labour market since 2004.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186199","186199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36295","2014-02-04","Cabinet Office","2014-01-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any official files contain a more accurate and precise time of death of the 7/7 victims than that given to their families.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186195","186195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36296","2014-02-04","HM Treasury","2014-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the number of (a) couples with children who are no longer eligible for working tax credits and (b) children now deemed to be in poverty as a result of the higher working hours threshold.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186154","186154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36297","2014-02-04","HM Treasury","2014-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the additional gaming duty raised by taxing at the point of consumption remote gambling operators based offshore.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186155","186155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36298","2014-02-04","HM Treasury","2014-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the revenue from remote gaming duty in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186156","186156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36299","2014-02-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-31","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what instructions or guidance his Department has given to local enterprise partnerships about High Speed 2 and the presentation of their strategic economic plans.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186201","186201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36300","2014-02-04","HM Treasury","2014-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what resources he will provide to enforce the wholesaler registration scheme when it comes into effect in 2017.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186176","186176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36301","2014-02-04","HM Treasury","2014-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the (a) per-container cost and (b) costs to industry of introducing a duty-paid tax stamp on all products liable to beer duty.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186173","186173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36302","2014-02-04","HM Treasury","2014-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consideration he has given to the reintroduction of fiscal stamps on alcohol products and their permissibility under the EU Treaty provisions on the freedom of movement of goods.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186174","186174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36303","2014-02-05","HM Treasury","2014-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) fiscal and (b) economic effects of postponing (i) the planned increases in the rates of duties on wines and spirits and (ii) the planned inflationary increase in beer duties for 2014-15.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186187","186187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36304","2014-02-04","HM Treasury","2014-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to tackle duty fraud before wholesale-registration comes into effect in 2017.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186175","186175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36305","2014-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the discussion paper for the review into housing conditions in privately rented homes will be published.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186178","186178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36306","2014-02-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the levels of retransmission fees for public service broadcasters paying to have their content carried; what plans she has for a review of retransmission fees; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186188","186188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36307","2014-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place a copy of his submission to the Stewart Review into Veterans in the Criminal Justice System in the Library.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186165","186165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36308","2014-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the (a) current value of the radar station in North Uist, (b) likely value of that station after its upgrade and (c) cost of the upgrade.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186179","186179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36309","2014-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what other (a) NATO or (b) non-NATO countries are investing or plan to invest in defence assets in the Hebrides.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186180","186180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36310","2014-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the rehabilitation periods for individuals with criminal records who wish to apply to join the Royal Navy are; and what plans he has to review them.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186168","186168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36311","2014-02-05","Department for Education","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 97W, on Kings Science Academy, on which grounds the decision was taken not to request and then publish a copy of the report made to Action Fraud on 25 April 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186158","186158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36312","2014-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many inspections have taken place by the Environment Agency and Health and Safety Executive of drill sites operated by Cuadrilla resources at (a) Preese Hall, (b) Balcombe and (c) Becconsall in each year of activity on each site.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186167","186167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36313","2014-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans his Department has to monitor methane emissions from shale gas extraction sites.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186166","186166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36314","2014-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what quantities of liquid and solid wastes were produced at drill sites operated by Cuadrilla Resources at (a) Preese Hall, (b) Balcombe and (c) Becconsall; what the composition of those wastes were; how and where those wastes were treated and disposed of; and what permits were issued for their storage, transport and disposal, for each year of activity on each site.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186169","186169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36315","2014-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of methane leakage from shale gas extraction on the UK's greenhouse gas inventory.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186170","186170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36316","2014-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, What estimate the Government has made of the costs of regulation of the shale gas industry during the (a) exploration and (b) commercial extraction stages.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186171","186171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36317","2014-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information is made available to members of the public about individual recipients of environmental stewardship grants from Natural England.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186177","186177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36318","2014-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people live within the 75 decibel noise contour of each motorway in Eastleigh constituency.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186172","186172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36319","2014-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to control the sale and use of chlorpyrifos.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186191","186191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36320","2014-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he will publish the results of the investigation into the pollution of 15km of the River Kennet following the release of chlorpyrifos into that river at Marlborough in 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186192","186192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36321","2014-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made in discussions with Thames Water on ending over-abstraction from the River Kennet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186193","186193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36322","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent by the South East Coast Ambulance Service NHS Trust on private ambulances in 2013; which providers were used; on how many occasions; and what amount was paid to each provider.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186184","186184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36323","2014-02-05","Department of Health","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many beds in the Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust have been occupied by patients affected by delays in discharge in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186182","186182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36324","2014-02-05","Home Office","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of crime in (a) Mid Sussex constituency and (b) West Sussex in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186183","186183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36325","2014-02-04","Department for International Development","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which projects funded by her Department have been (a) given an extension of or (b) started with a value of more than 50,000 in the current financial year.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186194","186194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36327","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value was of fines that were (a) issued and (b) uncollected in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186157","186157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36328","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value is of outstanding fines that were written off in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186159","186159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36329","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many outstanding fines were written off in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186160","186160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36330","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff worked on the collection of penalty notice orders in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186161","186161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36331","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many outstanding fines remained uncollected on 31 December in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186162","186162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36332","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims have (a) been offered and (b) taken part in restorative justice programmes since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186163","186163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36333","2014-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) female and (b) male offenders held in prisons have been included in restorative justice programmes since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186164","186164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36334","2014-02-04","Department for Transport","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the safety implications of quiet vehicles.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186189","186189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36335","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Oral Answer to the hon. Member for East Lothian of 14 October 2013, Official Report, column 429W, on Departmental Programmes (performance), to which budget he was referring in his Statement that universal credit would be on budget; and to which years that budget related.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186190","186190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36336","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total amount of benefit withheld as a result of benefit sanctions was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186198","186198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36337","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobs in the adult entertainment industry have been supported by Youth Contract wage incentives.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186185","186185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36338","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants have been sanctioned in each of the last three years for refusing to accept work in the adult entertainment industry.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186186","186186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36339","2014-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent estimate is of the number of households in each local authority area in London whose weekly income has been reduced by (a) less than 20, (b) between 20 and 39.99, (c) between 40 and 59.99, (d) between 60 and 79.99, (e) between 80 and 99.99 and (f) over 100 through the introduction of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186200","186200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35955","2014-02-04","Attorney General","2014-01-30","To ask the Attorney General, what the policy is of the Crown Prosecution Service and the Serious Fraud Office on whether to proceed with prosecutions of defendants who have not been able to find counsel to represent them under the new fee regime for very high-cost criminal cases.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185900","185900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35956","2014-02-03","Attorney General","2014-01-30","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 452W, on Crown Prosecution Service, if he will place the preliminary CPS review of R v Renate Andrews in the Library.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185974","185974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35957","2014-02-03","Attorney General","2014-01-30","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2013, Official Report, column 399W, on prosecutions, whether the National Scrutiny Panel has met.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185975","185975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35958","2014-02-04","Attorney General","2014-01-30","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the written ministerial statement of 30 January 2014, how much of the 19 million additional resources for the Serious Fraud Office has been ear-marked for specific investigations or prosecutions.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185994","185994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35959","2014-02-04","Attorney General","2014-01-30","To ask the Attorney General, whether he was consulted about the choice of Mr Stephen Wooler to head the investigation into the RSPCA's prosecution policy.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186016","186016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35960","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions Ministers in his Department have had with representatives of the Scottish Government on maritime apprenticeships; and if he will ensure that further such discussions take place in the near future.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185963","185963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35961","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on access to public funding for the Maritime Skills Alliance in designing apprenticeships in partnership with the maritime industry.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185962","185962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35962","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much (a) public and (b) private funding is provided to each sector skills council in the UK.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185964","185964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35963","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which sector skills council is responsible for the maritime industry.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186050","186050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35964","2014-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his strategy is for devolving skills funding in Wales and Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185917","185917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35965","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he last met the Chief Executive of Post Office Ltd to discuss initiatives and proven technologies to generate more footfall across the Post Office network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185940","185940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35966","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people are economically active in (a) Norwich North constituency, (b) the local authority area of Norwich and (c) Norfolk; and how many such people are paid (i) national minimum wage (NMW) and (ii) more than NMW but less that 7.65 per hour in each such area.","Biography information for Chloe Smith","Chloe Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185952","185952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35967","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials of his Department at (a) AA, (b) AO and LO2, (c) EO and LO1, (d) HEO, (e) SEO, (f) 7 and (g) SCS grades and equivalents since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186029","186029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35968","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward proposals to increase access for local brewers to the number of pubs owned by big pubcos.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185958","185958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35969","2014-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the sustainability of the universal postal service of the extension of end-to-end delivery services by providers other than the universal postal service provider.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185874","185874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35970","2014-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the universal postal service of operators other than the universal postal service provider extending end-to-end services in (a) Manchester, (b) Liverpool, (c) Edinburgh, (d) Glasgow and (e) Birmingham.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185875","185875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35971","2014-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will request Ofcom to expedite its review of the effect of end-to-end competition in the postal services market in order to ensure that the universal service obligation is protected.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185876","185876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35972","2014-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his most recent estimate is of the number of apprentices progressing to level 5 qualifications.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186132","186132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35973","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reduction in tax liabilities for shipping companies in the tonnage tax scheme was in each (a) calendar and (b) financial year since the scheme was introduced up to the latest estimates for (i) 2013 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185941","185941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35974","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect of the provisions of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2012 on the amount of VAT collected from the metal recycling industry.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185960","185960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35975","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will support real time data sharing for credit records.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185904","185904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35976","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of (a) the cost to the public purse and (b) the benefits of real time credit data sharing.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185905","185905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35977","2014-02-04","HM Treasury","2014-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency paid the top rate of tax in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186051","186051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35978","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue is lost annually as a result of the exemption of transfer passengers from air passenger duty.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185976","185976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35979","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue he expects air passenger duty to yield in the current and next year.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185977","185977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35980","2014-02-04","HM Treasury","2014-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the annual benefit to the public purse of reducing (a) the annual allowance for tax relief on pensions contributions to 30,000 and (b) the lifetime allowance to 1 million.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186010","186010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35981","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the implementation of the economic package announced for Northern Ireland in June 2013.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185951","185951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35982","2014-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much Natalie Elphicke and Councillor Keith House will be paid to lead the review of local authorities' role in housing supply.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186007","186007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35983","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support local planning authorities in (a) improving the viability of brownfield sites and (b) restarting stalled developments.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185957","185957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35984","2014-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, who will be on the panel of the review into local authorities' role in housing supply in addition to Natalie Elphicke and Councillor Keith House.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186000","186000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35985","2014-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that state-funded publications and literature by local authorities are politically impartial when communicating the scale of government funding reductions and budgeting.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186053","186053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35986","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of development schemes in England of over 100 units in the private rented sector which are either (a) seeking or (b) have secured planning permission.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186087","186087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35987","2014-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of progress on the (a) Build to Rent Fund, (b) Private Rented Sector Guarantee scheme and (c) Affordable Housing Guarantee scheme.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186141","186141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35988","2014-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many schemes under the Build to Rent Fund have (a) cleared due diligence and (b) started construction.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186142","186142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35989","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the 10 local authorities were with (a) highest and (b) lowest levels of funding reductions in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185896","185896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35990","2014-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what statistics the Government keeps on Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender homelessness.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185916","185916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35991","2014-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the total cost of the review into local authorities' role in housing supply.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186001","186001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35992","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials of his Department at (a) AA, (b) AO and LO2, (c) EO and LO1, (d) HEO, (e) SEO, (f) 7 and (g) SCS grades and equivalents since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186030","186030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35993","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of small retail businesses in the (a) administrative county of Essex and (b) Colchester constituency which will benefit in financial year 2014-15 from the Government's policy of reducing business rates by 1,000.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185927","185927"
