"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40383","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of each benefit type were referred to Work Choice in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189694","189694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40384","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of pensioners who switched annuities when they retired in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189703","189703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40385","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to (a) increase awareness of carers' allowance and (b) improve information on how to claim carers' allowance.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189701","189701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40386","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of carers that do not claim carers' allowance in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow City, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189700","189700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40387","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has for the future of the Independent Living Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189615","189615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40388","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish disaggregated data on new claims for personal independence payments between 8 April 2013 and 3 December 2013.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189632","189632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40389","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who indicated between April and December 2013 they had multiple sclerosis have (a) applied for personal independence payment and (b) received a decision about their claim.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189633","189633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40390","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what proportion of personal independence payment cases assessment providers are seeking additional evidence.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189630","189630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40391","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what proportion of personal independence payment cases evidence is returned in time to be used to (a) determine the nature and suitability of their assessment and (b) inform the assessor's picture of how a person's disability affects them.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189631","189631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40392","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will ensure that anyone with a prognosis of being unlikely to return to work in the longer term because of a progressive illness is placed into the support group rather than allocated to the work-related activity group.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189621","189621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40393","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who indicated they have Parkinson's (a) applied for personal independence payment and (b) received a decision about their claim between April and December 2013.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189550","189550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40394","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have indicated that they have a neurological condition have (a) applied for personal independence payment and (b) received a decision on their claim between April and December 2013.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189520","189520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40395","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average administrative cost to his Department was of imposing a sanction on a claimant of jobseeker's allowance in the most recent period for which data is available; and what the total cost of imposing all such sanctions was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189567","189567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40396","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings there have been between (a) officials and (b) Ministers in his Department and representatives of JD Wetherspoon plc in the last two years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189778","189778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40397","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Federation of Student Islamic Societies on interest-bearing student loan finance.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189832","189832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40398","2014-02-28","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times (a) the Cabinet Committee on improving the country ability to deal with flooding and (b) the National Resilience Forum has met in the last 12 months; and when each body will next meet.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189807","189807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40399","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the average change in the level of household (a) borrowing and (b) debt between 2008 and 2013 in Mid Sussex constituency.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189837","189837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40400","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings there have been between (a) officials and (b) Ministers in his Department and representatives of JD Wetherspoon plc in the last two years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189777","189777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40401","2014-02-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent progress has been made by local authorities in discharging their responsibilities under the Civil Contingencies Act 2004 to (a) promote business continuity, (b) encourage the take-up of property flood resistance and (c) increase resilience by businesses.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189801","189801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40402","2014-02-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent progress has been made by local authorities in extending eligibility for home improvement grants and loans to include flood resistance and resilience products for properties in high flood-risk areas.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189802","189802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40403","2014-03-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will discuss with her counterparts in the devolved administrations how best to co-ordinate approaches to the roll-out of superfast broadband in order to maximise benefits for rural communities across the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189742","189742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40404","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of ability of the Met Office to improve its forecasting and predicting methods to a level which meets the needs of emergency responders.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189788","189788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40405","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information and guidance is issued to service personnel in advance of a summary hearing relating to the implications of punishments issued under the National Police Records (Recordable Offences) Regulation 2000.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189806","189806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40406","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on improving NATO's cyber defence governance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189823","189823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40407","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the Queen's Regulations for the Army are not published online; and what plans he has to so publish those regulations.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189764","189764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40408","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, columns 821W, on students: Cumbria, how many of the individuals identified in Barrow and Furness and Cumbria were studying for (a) level 2, (b) level 3 and (c) vocational qualifications.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189827","189827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40409","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether (a) further education colleges and (b) sixth form colleges have access to the Online Free School Meal Eligibility Checking Service.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189839","189839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40410","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what sanctions his Department applies to energy companies which fail to comply with their targets for spending on energy conservation schemes.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189822","189822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40411","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of customers in (a) Glasgow North West, (b) Glasgow City, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK who will receive the refunds of direct debits announced by his Department on 18 February 2014.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189773","189773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40412","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department's calculation that 6.3 million tonnes of carbon dioxide were avoided in the UK in 2011 by onshore wind alone includes emissions from construction of turbines and backup technologies.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189817","189817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40413","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether there will be a reduction for further subsidies for onshore wind.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189814","189814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40414","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will take steps to give priority to both adaptation and mitigation in his Department's flood prevention programmes to help society cope with climate change.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189791","189791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40415","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress by the Environment Agency towards acheiving a national overview of all flood risk, including surface water and groundwater flood risk.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189790","189790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40416","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Environment Agency's annual regional revenue budget was in each year for which data is available; and what estimate he has made of such budgets in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189789","189789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40417","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress has been made on ensuring local authorities collate and map the main flood risk management and drainage assets including a record of their ownership and condition.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189800","189800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40418","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward building regulations to require that all new or refurbished buildings in high flood-risk areas are flood resistant or resilient.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189792","189792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40419","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress his Department has made with the Environment Agency and Natural England to establish a programme through catchment flood management plans and shoreline management plans to achieve greater working with natural processes.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189803","189803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40420","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance he has issued to local authorities and the public on the use and usefulness of sandbags and other alternatives in the event of flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189804","189804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40421","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on removing the automatic right to connect surface water drainage of new developments to the sewerage system.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189794","189794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40422","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made by the Environment Agency and the Met Office to improve their technical capability to forecast, model and warn against all sources of flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189781","189781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40423","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress has been made between his Department, Ofwat and the water industry on appropriate risk-based standards for public sewerage systems.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189795","189795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40424","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to develop a scheme which allows and encourages local communities to invest in flood risk management measures.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189805","189805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40425","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to develop a strategic long-term approach to investment in flood risk management.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189809","189809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40426","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many households were uninsurable against flooding in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189808","189808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40427","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many homes have been in danger of flood risk in each of the last 10 years; and what estimate he has made of the number that will be in danger of flood risk in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189786","189786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40428","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding for flood control measures has come from central government in each of the last six years; and what such central government funding will be in real terms in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189783","189783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40429","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of gross domestic product was spent on flood defences in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189784","189784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40430","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in local government funding on local authorities' ability to deal effectively with flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189785","189785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40431","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when preparation for and management of risk from flood ceased to be a key priority of his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189782","189782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40432","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress he has made on making property owners unable to lay impermeable surfaces as of right on (a) front gardens, (b) back gardens and (c) business premises.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189793","189793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40433","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of future flooding to the UK economy in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189810","189810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40434","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the operation and effectiveness of Planning Policy Statement 25 and the Environment Agency's consequent powers to challenge development.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189796","189796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40435","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much ancient woodland in England consists of areas of trees (a) larger and (b) smaller than two hectares; how many hectares of ancient woodland have been damaged or destroyed in the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189818","189818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40436","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what account the Flood Re scheme takes of increased risk of flooding as a result of climate change.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189772","189772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40437","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what projections his Department has made of the number of staff that will be employed by the Environment Agency in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189840","189840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40438","2014-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what action the Government is taking on human rights in Uganda.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189836","189836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40439","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England will start the Commissioning through Evaluation programme in April 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189813","189813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40440","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings there have been between (a) officials and (b) Ministers in his Department and representatives of JD Wetherspoon plc in the last two years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189819","189819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40441","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on NHS England's Commissioning through Evaluation programme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189812","189812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40442","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with NHS England on the Commissioning through Evaluation programme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189811","189811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40443","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS trusts are taking part in the Commissioning through Evaluation programme for each identified technology and service.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189821","189821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40444","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect in the UK of the vote of the European Parliament of 26 February 2014 on regulation and marketing of e-cigarettes.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189830","189830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40445","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the minutes of the monthly board meetings with G4S on the COMPASS contract.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189831","189831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40446","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to work with EU counterparts to promote an integrated approach to tackling female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189768","189768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40447","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of progress by (a) Bulgaria and (b) Romania against EU post-accession benchmarks.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189769","189769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40448","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what budgetary savings have been delivered by each planned reduction in the size of the youth secure estate over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189761","189761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40449","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many places have been (a) created and (b) decommissioned in (i) secure children's homes, (ii) secure training centres and (iii) young offender institutions in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189760","189760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40450","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much local authorities contributed towards the cost of places in the youth secure estate in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189759","189759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40451","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what offences were committed by those aged 18, 19 or 20 years old found guilty of criminal offences in 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189833","189833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40452","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of those aged 18, 19 or 20 years old found guilty of criminal offences in 2013 had committed a previous offence that resulted in a custodial sentence.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189834","189834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40453","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of those aged 18, 19 or 20 years old found guilty of criminal offences had (a) no previous convictions, (b) one to five previous convictions, (c) six to 10 previous convictions and (d) more than 10 previous convictions in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189835","189835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40454","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the independent review into the self-inflicted deaths of 18 to 24 year olds in custody will take into account the specific risks for young women in custody.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189776","189776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40455","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners on an Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork programme have been placed on a basic level of the Incentives and Earned Privileges scheme in each prison in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189820","189820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40456","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many temporary staff have been recruited by his Department and its agencies in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189838","189838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40457","2014-03-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will take steps to revoke the effects of the letter sent to John Downey on his alleged role in the Hyde Park bombing.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189828","189828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40458","2014-03-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether a letter in similar terms to that sent to John Downey was sent to (a) men alleged to be involved in the murder of Kenneth Smyth and Daniel McCormick, (b) men alleged to be involved in the murder of Lexie Cummins in Strabane and (c) the eight people questioned following the murder of four Ulster Defence Regiment members in Ballydougan, Downpatrick.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189829","189829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40459","2014-02-28","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits of displaying signage on overhead gantries reminding drivers about eyesight standards and eyesight testing.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189816","189816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40460","2014-02-28","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what data his Department holds on the effectiveness of signage on overhead gantries.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189815","189815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40461","2014-02-28","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the European Commission's publication COM (2013) 296, what representations he has received from British ports on the Commission's proposed regulation on ports; what representations he has made to the European Council on that proposed regulation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189770","189770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40462","2014-02-28","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings there have been between (a) officials and (b) Ministers in his Department and representatives of JD Wetherspoon plc in the last two years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189779","189779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40463","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new claims for (a) income-based incapacity benefit or employment and support allowance, (b) contributions-based incapacity benefit or employment and support allowance, (c) both income-based and contributions-based incapacity benefit or employment and support allowance were made in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189756","189756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40464","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to monitor the quality, reliability and accuracy of work capability assessments carried out by Atos.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189780","189780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40465","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason his Department has not published statistics on the number of people who have been declared fit to work and subsequently died; and whether his Department plans to publish such statistics in future.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189762","189762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40466","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will commence section 34 of the Child Maintenance and Other Payments Act 2008.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189767","189767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40467","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the recommendation made by the Independent Advisory Panel on Arrears of Child Maintenance, in its 2011 report, what work his Department has done to carry out a renewed soft market sounding or sampling exercise to test the sale potential of Secretary of State and arrears only cases.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189771","189771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40468","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Freedom of Information request 2014-19, answered by his Department on 13 February 2014, regarding work capability assessments carried out by Atos, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the difference in the proportion of cases in which Atos recommended an outcome of fit for work where claimants were found eligible for employment and support allowance by decision makers compared with the proportion of cases in which Atos recommended an outcome of not fit for work where claimants were refused employment and support allowance by decision makers.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189774","189774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40469","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make the mobility component of the disability living allowance available to children with life-limiting conditions under the age of three years old who are technology or ventilator-dependent.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189775","189775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40470","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have undergone a work capability assessment and have been declared (a) fit and (b) unfit to work who have died in each quarter since the first quarter of 2011.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189825","189825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40471","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to section 1c of the Report a benefit thief online form on the DWP website, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of asking whether suspected benefit thieves (a) are of a broad, heavy, medium, overweight, proportionate, short, slim, small, stocky, tall or thin build, (b) wear glasses or contact lenses, (c) have hair type of afro, bouffant, bald curly, dirty, dreadlocks, greasy, long, Mohican, permed, plaited, ponytailed, punk, quiffed, shaven, short, skinhead, spikey, spiked, straight, thinning, tidy, untidy, wavy or wig, (d) have distinguishing features such as facial hair, tattoos, scars or piercings and (e) always wears jeans or have distinctive jewellery to achieve the goal of tackling benefit fraud; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189824","189824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39866","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will arrange for the hon. Member for North Durham to receive a reply to his letter of 4 February 2014 to the Cabinet Secretary.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189300","189300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39867","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to protect those who are misled by claims management companies about how much they can claim in respect of PPI misselling.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189278","189278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39868","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether shortages of suitably experienced and qualified personnel will continue to be identified as his Department's top safety concern in the 2013-14 Safety and Environmental Protection Assurance Report.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189274","189274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39869","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will arrange for the hon. Member for North Durham to receive a reply to his letter of 18 December 2013 to the Permanent Secretary of his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189301","189301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39870","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost to his Department of the historical branches of each of the armed forces was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189280","189280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39871","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have had with European counterparts about the role of the UK's nuclear deterrent in European defence.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189281","189281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39872","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on the conservation of the environment and wildlife at its (a) military bases and (b) training centres in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189282","189282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39873","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost to his Department has been of the production, publication and distribution of (a) KiT!, (b) desider and (c) Defence Focus magazines in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189283","189283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39874","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many appeals were brought against his Department in (a) employment tribunals and (b) other courts in each year since 2010; and of these how many were granted.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189284","189284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39875","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel who successfully transferred to other branches of the armed forces were made redundant since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189285","189285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39876","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) national, (b) regional and (c) local businesses have signed up to the Defence Discount Service.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189286","189286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39877","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many individuals from the (a) regular serving armed forces, (b) reserve forces, (c) veterans from all branches, (d) MoD civil servants, (e) cadet forces, (f) NATO personnel, (g) spouses and partners, (h) war service widows and widowers and (i) bereaved family members have purchased or registered for a Defence Privilege Card.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189287","189287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39878","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which local authorities have not yet signed up to the Armed Forces Community Covenant.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189288","189288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39879","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many bids were submitted to the Community Covenant Grant Scheme in each region in each year since 2011; and how many such bids were successful in each region and in each year.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189289","189289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39880","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many bids were submitted to the Armed Forces Covenant (LIBOR) Fund in each year since 2012; and how many such bids were successful.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189290","189290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39881","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency and (b) Liverpool are eligible for but do not claim free school meals.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189298","189298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39884","2014-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take in the Council of Ministers to ensure protection for fragile deep-sea ecosystems and species from damaging forms of fishing.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189272","189272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39885","2014-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding the Government allocated to (a) help those affected by recent flooding to make their homes habitable and (b) dredge and drain rivers to prevent future flooding.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189275","189275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39886","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department provides for UK citizens extradited to the US who have no means to support themselves.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189299","189299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39887","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what value is applied to the fixed assets of GCHQ for resource accounting purposes.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189273","189273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39888","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to publicise the effects of smoking on health.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189276","189276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39889","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure a mandatory increase in sentence for prisoners who are found with contraband items in their cells.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189279","189279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39890","2014-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to help those with pensions which are worth significantly less than they anticipated when purchasing those pensions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189277","189277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39891","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the consequence for Liverpool's EU funding allocation of the decision in Rotherham Metropolitan Borough Council and Others v Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189350","189350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39892","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how his Department is helping small and medium-sized enterprises increase the number of countries to which they export.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189314","189314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39893","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the creation of industry councils based on the model of the Automotive Council for each of the industrial strategy sectors identified by his Department.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189315","189315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39894","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff in his Department have been part of an (a) inward and (b) outward secondment to businesses or other industry groups in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189316","189316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39895","2014-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the contribution to exports of One Direction.","Biography information for Dr Thrse  Coffey","Dr Thrse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189325","189325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39896","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consideration he has given to extending access to the Business Support Scheme to those coastal and fishing businesses affected by the winter storms.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189360","189360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39897","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in Corby and East Northamptonshire constituency are enrolled in adult skills sessions.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189419","189419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39898","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase the participation of older people in further education in Corby and East Northamptonshire constituency.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189420","189420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39899","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of adults in (a) Corby and East Northamptonshire constituency, (b) Northamptonshire and (c) the East Midlands who are unable to (i) read and (ii) write.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189421","189421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39900","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships were started in the Corby and East Northamptonshire constituency in each industrial sector in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189422","189422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39901","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many new apprenticeships were started in Corby and East Northamptonshire constituency in each of the last five years; and what the (a) age group and (b) gender of each such apprentice was.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189423","189423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39902","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of successful applicants to the start-up loans scheme in Essex are based in Chelmsford constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189509","189509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39903","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the report by the National Audit Office entitled Progress Report on the Regional Growth Fund, published on 25 February 2014, for what reason the majority of the Regional Growth Fund is unspent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189508","189508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39904","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what statistics his Department collects on instances of (a) cyber bullying and (b) children self-harming as a result of abuse or bullying.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189500","189500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39905","2014-02-27","Cabinet Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of working age adults are currently registered as disabled in (a) Corby and East Northamptonshire, (b) Northamptonshire, (c) the East Midlands and (d) England.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189424","189424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39906","2014-03-03","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which organisations received funding from the Innovations Fund as part of the Democratic Engagement Programme; how much each such organisation received; and what the time period is for their projects.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189479","189479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39907","2014-02-27","Cabinet Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children living in households where one or both parents are (a) working part-time because they are unable to find full-time work and (b) employed on a zero-hours contract in Corby and East Northamptonshire.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189426","189426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39908","2014-02-27","Cabinet Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Corby and East Northamptonshire, (b) Northamptonshire and (c) the East Midlands who have jobs which primarily require working (i) during the day and (ii) at night.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189427","189427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39909","2014-02-27","Cabinet Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Government contracts of what value have been awarded to companies or projects based in (a) Corby and East Northamptonshire and (b) Northamptonshire since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189425","189425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39910","2014-02-28","Cabinet Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the average change in the level of household (a) borrowing and (b) debt in Chelmsford constituency between 2008 and 2013.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189437","189437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39911","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has any sources other than PAYE RTI data for its estimates of employers' liability to income tax and national insurance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189432","189432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39912","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the likely cost to the public purse of raising the Rent a Room Scheme tax-free threshold from 4,250 a year to 7,500.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189462","189462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39913","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consideration he has given to creating opportunities for the establishment of new building societies.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189384","189384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39914","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that legislation is in place to enable small and medium-sized enterprises to attract funding from peer-to-peer lending and crowdfunding platforms.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189385","189385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39915","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the timescales in which the Financial Conduct Authority considers applications for potential new entrants to the UK banking sector.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189386","189386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39916","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with (a) peer-to-peer lenders and (b) crowdfunding platforms on the development of simpler products for potential investors.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189380","189380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39917","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of investment in small and medium-sized enterprises which has come from (a) peer-to-peer lending and (b) crowdfunding platforms in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189381","189381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39918","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on applications for challenger banks which are currently under consideration.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189382","189382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39919","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the Financial Conduct Authority to publish rules relating to peer-to-peer lending.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189388","189388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39920","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish proposals for consultation on bail-in orders in relation to building societies.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189389","189389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39921","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will propose changes to the taxation regime for individuals who wish to invest in peer-to-peer and crowdfunding schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189390","189390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39922","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with representatives of EU institutions on the cross-border implications of peer-to-peer lending and crowdfunding platforms.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189383","189383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39923","2014-02-27","Department for International Development","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2014 from the Department for International Development, Official Report, column 665W on European Investment Bank, when the EU funding guidelines, published on 19 July 2013, will be applied to loans to Israel from the European Investment Bank; and what recent discussions the UK representative on the European Investment Bank has had with him on this issue.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189307","189307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39924","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) peer-to-peer lending and (b) crowdfunding platforms on the availability of finance for small to medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189378","189378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39925","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the net effect in (a) cash terms and (b) as a proportion of the average annual income of the 2.5 per cent increase in the standard rate of value added tax to 20 per cent on (i) pensioner couples, (ii) single pensioners, (iii) couples with children and (iv) single parents with children.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189308","189308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39926","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate how much more value added tax a couple with two children, earning 20,000 a year, have paid in (a) cash terms and (b) as a proportion of their household income following the increase in the standard rate of value added tax to 20 per cent.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189309","189309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39927","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 441W, on working tax credit, what estimate he has made of the number of children who were living with couples who worked 16 to 24 hours per week who were eligible for child tax credit but were not eligible for working tax credit on 2 December 2013.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189353","189353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39928","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what resources HM Revenue and Customs has allocated to the Employee Shareholder Scheme since it was announced.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189347","189347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39929","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what response HM Revenue and Customs plans to make to the European Court of Justice judgment made in the case of the Bridport and West Dorset Golf Club on 19 December 2013 in relation to VAT refunds on green fees charged to non-members.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189449","189449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39930","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect on competition between proprietary and private members' golf clubs of being charged different rates of VAT as a result of the European Court of Justice judgment made in the case of the Bridport and West Dorset Golf Club on 19 December 2013 relating to VAT refunds on green fees charged to non-members.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189450","189450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39931","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much added income his Department estimates an EU/US free trade agreement would bring to the UK.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189492","189492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39932","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, in which months the Exchequer (a) was and (b) was not in surplus in each of the last 36 months.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189502","189502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39933","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total tax revenue for the Exchequer was in January of each year since 2001.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189503","189503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39934","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many public houses were built in (a) the UK, (b) Lancashire and (c) Preston in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (vi) 2013; and how many are projected to be built in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189490","189490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39935","2014-02-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to assign a proportion of all building permissions granted for developments of over 30 houses for self builds.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189445","189445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39936","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many called in planning applications for development on the green belt he has refused since the establishment of the National Planning Casework Unit.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189497","189497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39937","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of sites on the green belt in England which have been previously developed.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189498","189498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39938","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning applications for development on the green belt he has called in since the establishment of the National Planning Casework Unit.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189496","189496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39939","2014-02-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications were made across (a) West Yorkshire and (b) Leeds North West constituency to list (i) facilities and (ii) buildings as Assets of Community Value; and how many such applications were approved.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189366","189366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39940","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how often and for what reasons he has revoked planning permission he has allowed on appeal since May 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189304","189304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39941","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will ensure that any measures introduced as a result of the local authority parking review being undertaken by his Department will not have a detrimental impact on the safety of children.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189326","189326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39942","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 185266 tabled for ordinary answer on 27 January 2014.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189329","189329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39943","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning applications for development in the green belt have been referred to the National Planning Casework Unit since it was established.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189400","189400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39944","2014-02-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much arts funding (a) in total and (b) per head of population was allocated in (i) Essex and (ii) Chelmsford constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189436","189436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39945","2014-02-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she attends Cobra meetings on flooding in connection with her tourism responsibilities.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189379","189379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39946","2014-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Screen Yorkshire since the regional screen agencies were disbanded.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189319","189319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39947","2014-02-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she requires UK Sport to provide equality assessments of its funding decisions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189349","189349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39948","2014-02-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessments she has made of the proportion of food brands sold in the UK that have adver-gaming as part of their digital platforms.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189363","189363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39949","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what effect deployment of armed forces personnel to tackle flooding has had on current operational readiness; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189337","189337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39950","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what operational contingency plans he has made for future capability requirements in the event of further flooding.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189339","189339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39951","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to enable service personnel to vote in local, national and European elections and local referenda.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189291","189291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39952","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the companies with which his Department holds contracts have signed up to the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189292","189292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39953","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many email addresses were on the Community Covenant e-Newsletter distribution lists in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189293","189293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39954","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) human rights and (b) international humanitarian law training recruits of the Afghan National Army Officer Academy receive as part of their programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189294","189294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39955","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what requests NATO has received from the US government in relation to Alliance funding for the integration of the B-61 nuclear bomb onto the F-35.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189370","189370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39956","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK's F-35 Joint Strike Fighters will be equipped to carry the B-61 nuclear bomb.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189369","189369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39957","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the 270 members of the first kandak at the Afghan National Army Officer Academy are women.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189295","189295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39958","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers dropped out of Phase 2 training at the Infantry Training Centre (Catterick) in 2012-13; and how many of these had undertaken Phase 1 training at (a) the Army Foundation College (Harrogate) and (b) the Army Training Regiment (Winchester).","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189317","189317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39959","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers who dropped out of Phase 2 training at the Infantry Training Centre (Catterick) in 2012-13 had undertaken Phase 1 training at that Infantry Training Centre.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189318","189318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39960","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department was of promotional material for recruitment to each of the reserve forces in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189330","189330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39961","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel are currently stationed at the Afghan National Army Officer Academy as mentors.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189296","189296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39962","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings Ministers and officials in his Department have had with the NATO Nuclear Planning Group since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189331","189331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39963","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the statement of 23 January 2014, Official Report, column 461, on armed forces' restructuring, how many eligible Gurkhas have applied for compulsory redundancy under the fourth tranche of redundancies to date; what estimate he has made of the proportion of compulsory redundancies among Gurkhas which will be filled by voluntary applications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189357","189357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39964","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to retain the knowledge possessed by retiring military personnel and officials.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189398","189398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39965","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the 2010 Strategic Defence and Security Review on the number of people employed in the defence and aerospace industries in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189399","189399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39966","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets are available for Maritime Intra-Theatre lift to support the Joint Combat Aircraft aboard Queen Elizabeth class carriers when those aircraft enter service.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189507","189507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39967","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on the Cipher project to date.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189467","189467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39968","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what material support the UK army is offering under the Defence and Security Cooperation Treaty to French troops deployed in Mali and the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189487","189487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39969","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office's Major Project Report 2013 Appendices and project summary sheets, what steps he is taking to mitigate the risk posed by insufficient maritime intra-theatre lift assets to support the Joint Combat Aircraft operations aboard Queen Elizabeth class carriers identified in that report.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189471","189471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39970","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the ability of the V-22 Osprey to conduct maritime intra-theatre lift to support (a) routine operations aboard Queen Elizabeth class carriers and (b) Joint Combat Aircraft operations aboard Queen Elizabeth class carriers.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189472","189472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39971","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what air assets can carry an entire F135 jet engine and deliver it to the Queen Elizabeth class carrier.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189468","189468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39972","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of the refit of HMS Scott.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189469","189469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39973","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Tornado Airworthiness Review Team report.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189470","189470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39974","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made on the number of birds illegally killed on the British sovereign base area of Dhekelia in 2013.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189451","189451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39975","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what area of invasive acacia tree was removed from his Department's land at Cape Pyla in the Cyprus sovereign base area of Dhekelia in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189452","189452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39976","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the street value of the birds illegally killed on the British sovereign base area of Dhekelia in 2013.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189453","189453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39977","2014-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what turnover levels companies must meet under the Government Vehicle Lease framework.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189482","189482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39978","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office's Major Project Reports 2013, HC 817-i, published on 13 February 2014, Appendices and project summary sheets, what the contractual confusion was regarding the life support plan and integrated logistics support solution for the Military Afloat Reach and Sustainability Programme.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189506","189506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39979","2014-02-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2013, Official Report, column 392W on electoral register, when he will decide on the level of fine for not returning an electoral registration form; and when such fines will be able to be levied.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189413","189413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39980","2014-02-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when he will publish the full report on the data matching pilots for individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189412","189412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39981","2014-02-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the effect of comments by (a) Government Ministers, (b) hon. Members and (c) the media on public perception of electoral fraud.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189411","189411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39982","2014-02-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he is taking to advertise the availability of his Department's fund to increase voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189465","189465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39983","2014-02-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will introduce the Northern Ireland school registration programme to increase voter registration on the UK mainland.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189403","189403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39984","2014-02-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what organisations have applied to his Department for funding to improve voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189460","189460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39985","2014-02-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2012, Official Report, columns 54-5W, on electoral register, what assessment he has made of the reason for the disparity between (a) levels of proven instances of electoral fraud and (b) public perception of electoral fraud.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189405","189405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39986","2014-02-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2013, Official Report, column 971W, on Electoral Registration and Administration Act 2013, when he intends to lay an Order before Parliament under paragraph 28 of schedule 5 to the Electoral Registration and Administration Act 2013.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189418","189418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39987","2014-02-28","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what estimate he has made of how many and what proportion of UK second home owners who will register to vote online at an address at which they are not primarily resident under individual electoral registration proposals.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189342","189342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39988","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what basis he concluded that all the critical information regarding Kings Science Academy Bradford had been passed on to Action Fraud.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189348","189348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39989","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of additional early years education places in London resulting from the 8 million funding announced by his Department on 18 December 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189343","189343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39990","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to it of the 18 free schools cancelled or withdrawn during the pre-opening process.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189323","189323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39991","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will rank each primary school in each local authority area according to the percentage of children on free school meals; and what category each such school is.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189372","189372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39992","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the differences in the teaching of modern languages in state-funded comprehensive schools and in mainstream independent secondary schools. [R]","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189324","189324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39993","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what methodologies his Department uses to assess the value for money of each free school capital budget.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189320","189320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39994","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what difference in value for money of free school capital budgets there is between (a) London and (b) the rest of England.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189321","189321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39995","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many vacancies were identified in free schools in the school census in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189322","189322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39996","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what analysis his Department has carried out of the comparable value for money of (a) community schools other than academies and (b) free schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189394","189394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39997","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the 18 cancelled free school applications had a site purchased and assigned to the school.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189397","189397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39998","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received from each of the providers of the 18 free schools which had a scheme cancelled or withdrawn; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189395","189395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39999","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the 18 cancelled free school applications were in (a) Yorkshire and (b) London.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189396","189396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40000","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria he uses to decide whether to intervene in academies that are failing.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189429","189429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40001","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps parents can take to require action to tackle failing performance in (a) local authority schools, (b) academies and (c) free schools.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189428","189428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40002","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school places in non-free schools have been provided in the UK between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189377","189377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40003","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when officials in his Department have met counterparts in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills to discuss the Barnfield Federation since May 2010; and what the purpose was of each such meeting.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189455","189455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40004","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to expand the UK languages curriculum to encompass Mandarin.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189489","189489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40005","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who was responsible for the regulation of the Barnfield Federation.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189456","189456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40006","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the performance of schools sponsored by (a) AET and (b) Oasis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189444","189444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40007","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which academy chains have been restricted (a) in full and (b) in part from sponsoring new academies or free schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189443","189443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40008","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department gives to schools in assisting parents and pupils to tackle social media bullying which occurs outside of school time.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189501","189501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40009","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many responses to the consultation on the Education (Pupil Registration) (England) (Amendment) Regulations 2013 were made (a) nationally and (b) by private individuals; and how many such responses were (i) in favour of and (ii) opposed to the draft regulations.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189447","189447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40010","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will set out the reasons for the lower level of indemnity offered to bidders for the contracts for the parent body organisation (PBO) for (a) Magnox Ltd and (b) Research Sites Restoration Ltd compared with that offered to the successful PBO for Sellafield Ltd.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189473","189473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40011","2014-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what risk assessments he has made of the effect of fracking on water tables in Lancashire and East Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189495","189495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40012","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information Ofgem holds on the average call handling times for the energy customers of EDF, British Gas, Eon, NPower, SSE and Scottish Power.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189493","189493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40013","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to remove Government subsidies from renewable energy generating plants once the plant has achieved a reasonable return on investment.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189481","189481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40014","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) energy company obligation, (b) affordable warmth and (c) green deal grants have been accessed in (i) TR and (ii) PL postcode areas in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189391","189391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40015","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of individuals who have been removed from fuel poverty as a result of the Energy Companies Obligation in (a) Essex and (b) Chelmsford constituency.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189435","189435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40016","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the letter to the hon. Member for Newport West from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change of 24 February 2014, which companies or consortia have bid for the contracts for the parent body organisation (PBO) for (a) Magnox Ltd and (b) Research Sites Restoration Ltd; and when each meeting has been held with each bidding company or consortium since the competition for the PBO was opened to bidders.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189461","189461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40017","2014-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Livingston, of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 389W, on animal welfare: trapping, if he will consider bringing forward legislative proposals to put code of practice on the use of snares on a statutory basis or offer otherwise to amend it to improve compliance.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189354","189354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40018","2014-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consideration he has given to extending access to the (a) Farming Recovery Fund and (b) Repair and Renew scheme to those coastal and fishing businesses affected by the winter storms.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189359","189359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40019","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research his Department has commissioned into squirrel pox; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189446","189446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40020","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what direct or indirect bilateral funding arrangements his Department has with Argentina.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189499","189499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40021","2014-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress is being made on negotiations with the US on the establishment of an EU/US free trade agreement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189491","189491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40022","2014-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he is making on the reciept of compensation for damage done during the attack on HM Embassy in Tehran in 2011.","Biography information for Michael Ellis","Michael Ellis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189480","189480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40023","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his counterparts in the Pakistan government reports of the arrest and detention of Pakistani anti-drones campaigner Mr Kareem Khan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189441","189441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40024","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) homicides and (b) suspicious deaths of British nationals took place abroad in each country in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189438","189438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40025","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on the arrest and detention of Pakistani anti-drones campaigner Mr Kareem Khan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189439","189439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40026","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will investigate reports of the arrest and detention of Pakistani anti-drones campaigner Mr Kareem Khan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189440","189440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40027","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many incursions into British Gibraltar Territorial Waters by Spanish state vessels occurred in (a) December 2013 and (b) 2014 to date; and on which dates and by which Spanish Agency each of these incursions into British Gibraltar Territorial Waters took place.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189457","189457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40028","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times the Spanish Ambassador was summoned to his Department in 2013; on which dates the Ambassador was summoned; and what the subject of discussion was on each such occasion.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189458","189458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40029","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on the legitimacy of the recent Bangladesh general election results.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189311","189311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40030","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on the level of participation in the recent Bangladesh general election.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189312","189312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40031","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received on alleged human rights abuses in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189313","189313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40032","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what financial assistance his Department offers to relatives of British nationals killed abroad who are required to travel to foreign countries for criminal trials but are in financial hardship.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189334","189334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40033","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Uganda about the effect on the human rights of LGBT people of the new legislation to criminalise homosexuality.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189345","189345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40034","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the Burmese government's preparations for the census to ensure it is a complete, credible and peaceful process; what discussions he has had on the potential effect of the census on ethnic tensions in Burma; and what recent representations he has made to his Burmese counterpart on official recognition of the Royhingya under the census.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189340","189340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40035","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on the Strategy for the Abolition of the Death Penalty; and what recent assessment he has made of the prospects for global abolition of the death penalty.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189341","189341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40036","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the risk to LGBT people resident in or visiting Uganda following the introduction of legislation to criminalise homosexuality in that country.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189344","189344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40037","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Uganda authorities about the safety of LGBT citizens and visitors to Uganda following the publication of a list naming 200 people as homosexual by Red Pepper.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189346","189346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40038","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts have failed to reach their targets for reducing hospital acquired infections; and how many such trusts have been fined for such a failure in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189310","189310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40039","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that specialist autism training for community care assessors is addressed in the guidance and regulations arising from the Care Bill.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189327","189327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40040","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to further develop understanding and awareness of autism in local communities.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189328","189328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40041","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the clostridium-difficile targets for all hospital trusts and clinical commissioning groups will be published by the NHS Commissioning Board; and how his Department will enforce such targets.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189306","189306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40042","2014-03-11","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) district nurses, (b) health visitors, (c) community psychiatric nurses, (d) community matrons and (e) community learning disabilities nurses were employed by the NHS in each clinical commissioning group area in South Yorkshire in (i) the latest period for which figures are available and (ii) the previous 12 months from that date.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189376","189376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40043","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how Quality Premium funding agreements and the Outcomes Framework ensure a continued zero tolerance approach to hospital acquired infections.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189303","189303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40044","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what specialist services are currently available in hospitals to support patients diagnosed with cancers of unknown origin; and what plans he has to change the mandated minimum provision of such services.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189302","189302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40045","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the health needs (a) in relation to infectious diseases and (b) in general of people who have (i) migrated to the UK within the last two years and (ii) resided in the UK on visa for six months or more.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189448","189448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40046","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will institute a population-based assessment and bio-monitoring to establish any potential links between food-contact chemicals and chronic conditions such as cancer, diabetes and neurological disorders.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189362","189362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40047","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle rising rates of obesity amongst children in England.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189417","189417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40048","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the proportion of GPs who regularly prescribe mindfulness-based therapy for the treatment of repeat depression.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189356","189356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40049","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the health risks posed by synthetic chemicals used in the processing, packaging and storing of food.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189361","189361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40050","2014-03-11","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered nurses there were in each NHS trust in South Yorkshire in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189483","189483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40051","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff were assaulted in health centres and hospitals in Lancashire in 2013; in which locations each assault occurred; and what the role was of the member of staff assaulted in each case.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189485","189485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40052","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that NHS patients' details and medical records are safeguarded by insurance companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189409","189409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40053","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the British Academy for the Humanities and Social Sciences' recent report on local actions to reduce health inequalities, published in January 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189408","189408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40054","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP referrals have included a referral to a swimming pool or gym in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189514","189514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40055","2014-02-27","Home Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the introduction of a bidding system for allocation of permanent UK resident visas; and if she will publish a full equality impact assessment for such a policy.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189407","189407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40056","2014-02-27","Home Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on removing face coverings at border crossings.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189459","189459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40057","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many warrants to undertake surveillance on British nationals were issued by her Department between 1989 and 1992.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189333","189333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40058","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects the process of arbitration between her Department and Raytheon relating to the e-Borders programme to be completed.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189352","189352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40059","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to her Department is of legal expenses arising from arbitration between the Home Office and Raytheon relating to the e-Borders programmes to date.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189351","189351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40060","2014-02-28","House of Commons Commission","2014-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the cost was of replacing chairs in the Portcullis House atrium in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Thrse  Coffey","Dr Thrse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189365","189365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40061","2014-02-28","House of Commons Commission","2014-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, for what reasons the City of London Remembrancer is allowed access to the floor of the House; if the Commission will remove this right of access; and when the right of access for the Remembrancer was last reviewed.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189513","189513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40062","2014-02-28","Department for International Development","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with civil society groups in Uganda on new laws on homosexuality in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189364","189364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40063","2014-02-28","Department for International Development","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanisms her Department has in place to assess and demonstrate the impact of the ENABLE programme on poverty reduction.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189367","189367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40064","2014-02-28","Department for International Development","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Ugandan government on new laws on homosexuality in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189368","189368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40065","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the written Answer of 5 February 2014, Official Report, column 287W, on Domestic Violence, what the cost to his Department is of the Building Better Relationships programme.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189335","189335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40066","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether there is a difference in treatment of prisoners who maintain their innocence and those who admit their guilt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189336","189336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40067","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library the impact assessment for the policy of housing of young girls in secure colleges.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189338","189338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40068","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of compliance with the notice period required by the Duchy of Cornwall for the closure of Dartmoor prison.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189305","189305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40069","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has given the Duchy of Cornwall notice of the decision to close Dartmoor prison.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189297","189297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40070","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent to date on external legal advice on the design of contracts with community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189475","189475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40071","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who has been employed by his Department to provide legal advice on drawing up contracts for community rehabilitation companies; and how many such advisers are Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189477","189477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40072","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sex offenders were held in each prison in England and Wales between 2010 and 2013.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189463","189463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40073","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total cost incurred by his Department was in appeals against benefit sanctions imposed by the Department for Work and Pensions on claimants of employment and support allowance in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189431","189431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40074","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost incurred by his Department is over an appeal against a decision in the Department for Work and Pensions to sanction a claimant's jobseeker's allowance; and what the total cost of dealing with all such appeals has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189433","189433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40075","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many places are available annually on sex offender treatment courses in each prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189476","189476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40076","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what period of notice he is required to give the Duchy of Cornwall of the decision to close HMP Dartmoor.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189355","189355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40077","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions have been brought against train companies for infringements under section 17 of the Public Passenger Vehicles Act 1981 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189358","189358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40078","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals of each nationality were held in custody in each prison in England and Wales on 1 February (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189512","189512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40079","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in Preston are on the sex offenders register.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189494","189494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40080","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what review he intends to carry out on the use of (a) open prisons and (b) the system of release on temporary licence and escorted absences from prisons.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189510","189510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40081","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will sign up to the Mental Health Concordat.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189410","189410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40082","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what budget his Department allocated to (a) the Administrative Justice and Tribunals Council, (b) the Assessor for Compensation for Miscarriages of Justice, (c) the Civil Justice Council, (d) the Civil Procedure Rule Committee, (e) the Criminal Cases Review Commission, (f) the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority, (g) the Criminal Procedure Rule Committee, (h) the Crown Court Rules Committee, (i) the Family Justice Council, (j) HM Inspectorate of Prisons, (k) HM Inspectorate of Probation, (l) the Insolvency Rules Committee, (m) the Judicial Appointments Commission, (n) the Judicial Appointments and Conduct Ombudsman, (o) the Judicial Office, (p) the Law Commission, (q) the Legal Services Board, (r) the Legal Services Commission, (s) the National Offender Management Service, (t) the Probation Service, (u) the Court Funds Office, (v) the Office of the Information Commissioner, (w) the Office for Judicial Complaints, (x) the Legal Ombudsman, (y) the Office of the Public Guardian, (z) the Official Solicitor and Public Trustee, (aa) the Parole Board, (bb) the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman, (cc) the Sentencing Council, (dd) the Tribunal Procedure Committee, (ee) the Commissioner for Victims and Witnesses and (ee) the Youth Justice Board in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189454","189454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40083","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted in Preston for breaching their sex offenders order in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189486","189486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40084","2014-02-27","Home Office","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 600W, on homicide: children, how many children each (a) male and (b) female offender murdered; and what sentences were given in each case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189504","189504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40085","2014-02-27","Prime Minister","2014-02-25","To ask the Prime Minister, whether in the event that the Geneva Peace Talks failing, it will continue to be his policy to rule out a further vote on military intervention in Syria.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189488","189488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40086","2014-02-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Denbighshire County Council and (b) Vale of Clwyd.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189466","189466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40087","2014-02-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2013, Official Report, column 709W, on electoral register, what progress the Electoral Commission is making in its investigation as to whether to measure and set targets for the number of electoral registrations; and when such investigations will (a) be completed and (b) have their results reported to Parliament.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189415","189415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40088","2014-02-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2013, Official Report, column 709W, on electoral register, what targets exist for registration form downloads for all current (a) electoral registration drives and (b) awareness campaigns conducted by the Electoral Commission; and how such targets have been set.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189414","189414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40089","2014-02-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what evidence will be needed to de-register an elector after the implementation of individual voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189464","189464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40090","2014-02-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2013, Official Report, column 709W, on electoral register, what targets existed for electoral registration form downloads in each of the Electoral Commission's registration awareness campaign; and which such campaigns (a) exceeded and (b) did not meet their target.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189416","189416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40091","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he is taking steps to allocate intercity express programmes hybrid trains to be set aside to provide direct train links from London to Shrewsbury.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189406","189406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40092","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proposals there are in the Network Rail Control Period 5 for the upgrade of the East Coast Main Line between Huntingdon and Peterborough; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189478","189478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40093","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail on integrated transport and connectivity at the remodelled Peterborough railway station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189474","189474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40094","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of (a) the number of new buses which entered into service in 2013, (b) the number of such buses which are fitted with audio visual next stop and final destination announcements and (c) the number of such buses so fitted which operate outside London.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189404","189404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40095","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the accessibility of buses to blind and partially sighted passengers.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189402","189402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40096","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to assess the effectiveness of voluntary bus driver training; and how he will take into account the experiences of disabled bus passengers.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189401","189401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40097","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether there are proposals to increase night flights at Heathrow Airport from 2015.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189505","189505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40098","2014-02-28","Department for Transport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has under the new Thameslink Great Northern Franchise to ensure that refunds are processed automatically for any rail tickets purchased by credit or debit card.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189515","189515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40099","2014-02-27","Department for Transport","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what enforcement measures he plans to make available to passengers under the Thameslink Great Northern Franchise if the franchise falls below the passenger satisfaction obligation.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189484","189484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40100","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost is incurred by his Department over an appeal against a decision to sanction a claimant's jobseeker's allowance; and what the total cost to deal with all such appeals has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189442","189442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40101","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total cost incurred by his Department was in appeals against benefit sanctions imposed on claimants of employment and support allowance in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189430","189430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40102","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the mean average time taken to process an application for a personal independence payment from receipt of application to determination is; and what the longest time taken to determine any such application is.","Biography information for Charles Hendry","Charles Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189387","189387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40103","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that people on the Work Programme who miss appointments to attend job interviews are not penalised.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189392","189392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40104","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons people on the Work Programme are recorded as having missed appointment when the reason for missing the appointment is to attend a job interview.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189393","189393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40105","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to help older people in Chelmsford constituency claim the benefits to which they are entitled.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189434","189434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40106","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) referrals, (b) starts and (b) job outcomes have been made for Work Choice programme participants serviced by Remploy through grant-in-aid funded services in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189373","189373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40107","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of Jobcentre Plus offices had a dedicated Disability Employment Adviser in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189375","189375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40108","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of the cap on Work Choice referrals for each of the 28 contract package areas was in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189374","189374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40109","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to undertake an impact assessment on the effects on levels of child poverty of a rise in the national minimum wage to (a) 7.35, (b) 7.85, (c) 8.35 and (d) 8.85 an hour.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189332","189332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40110","2014-02-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance he has issued to local authorities on the length of time families with children should stay in annexe accommodation provided under Part 1 of the Housing Act 2004.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189371","189371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40789","2014-03-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department is providing to help freeze council tax.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902754","902754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40838","2014-03-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to increase the uptake of Right to Buy.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902768","902768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40839","2014-03-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to promote the new community rights established by the Localism Act 2011.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902767","902767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39410","2014-02-26","Attorney General","2014-02-24","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of civil servants in the Law Officers' Departments' who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189055","189055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39411","2014-02-26","Attorney General","2014-02-24","To ask the Attorney General, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in the Law Officers' Departments.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189075","189075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39412","2014-02-26","Attorney General","2014-02-24","To ask the Attorney General, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by the Law Officers' Departments' and (b) operated by a third party on the Law Officers' Departments' property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189095","189095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39413","2014-02-26","Attorney General","2014-02-24","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of civil servants in the Law Officers' Departments who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189155","189155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39414","2014-02-26","Attorney General","2014-02-24","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of civil servants in the Law Officers' Departments who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189175","189175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39415","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189154","189154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39416","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the case for an independent adjudicator for pubs and pub companies.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189194","189194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39417","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189174","189174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39418","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who had been on maternity leave were still employed in the Civil Service (a) six and (b) 12 months after their return to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189114","189114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39419","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189134","189134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39420","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will respond to the recommendations of the British Chambers of Commerce Skills and Employment Manifesto.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189053","189053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39421","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will adopt the proposal recommended in the British Chambers of Commerce Skills and Employment Manifesto for government to work with universities to incentivise a greater focus on the development of foreign language skills and overseas mobility.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189051","189051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39422","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189094","189094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39423","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote greater communication between the chambers of commerce, businesses, schools and universities.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189003","189003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39424","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which export promotion teams which include Ministry of Defence or military personnel (a) in UK Trade & Investment Defence & Security Organisation and (b) elsewhere promote the (i) Eurofighter Typhoon, (ii) combat ships, (iii) submarines and (iv) complex weapons.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189015","189015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39425","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189054","189054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39426","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189074","189074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39427","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will adopt the proposal recommended in the British Chambers of Commerce Skills and Employment Manifesto for government to work with the Chambers of Commerce and local bodies to provide greater employment opportunities and work experience for young people.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189050","189050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39428","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place in the Library all correspondence between his Department and other departments on the matter of union subscription check off.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189004","189004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39429","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189056","189056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39430","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189076","189076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39431","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189096","189096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39432","2014-02-26","Cabinet Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189156","189156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39433","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189171","189171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39434","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189111","189111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39435","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189071","189071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39436","2014-02-26","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189091","189091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39437","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Written Statement of 4 December 2013, Official Report, column 48WS, on the National Infrastructure Plan 2013, how many (a) car parks and (b) light bulbs the Government guarantee underwriting the National Car Parks Limited lighting installation programme has delivered to date.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188917","188917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39438","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many residences valued at over (a) 1 million, (b) 1.5 million, (c) 2 million, (d) 2.5 million, (e) 3 million, (f) 3.5 million, (g) 4 million, (h) 4.5 million and (i) 5 million was capital gains tax paid in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188961","188961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39439","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many transactions over the value of (a) 1 million, (b) 1.5 million, (c) 2 million, (d) 2.5 million, (e) 3 million, (f) 3.5 million, (g) 4 million, (h) 4.5 million and (i) 5 million was stamp duty land tax paid in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188962","188962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39440","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on (a) what date and (b) what basis the deemed workplace of a councillor was changed to that of the principal local authority for the purposes of HM Revenue and Customs' taxation of mileage.","Biography information for Dr Thrse  Coffey","Dr Thrse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188937","188937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39441","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189077","189077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39442","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189057","189057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39443","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189097","189097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39444","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189157","189157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39445","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many properties in each local authority area have been flooded during the recent severe weather; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189226","189226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39446","2014-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much each local authority has received from the local government emergency fund in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189195","189195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39447","2014-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to monitor the responses of insurance companies to the needs of people made homeless as a result of their homes being flooded in the recent severe weather; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189227","189227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39448","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189158","189158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39449","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by her Department and (b) operated by a third party on her Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189098","189098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39450","2014-02-27","HM Treasury","2014-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to tackle the concerns of the UK video gaming industry over delays in the decision by the European Commission on tax breaks for the industry.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189211","189211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39451","2014-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of the members of Team GB at the (a) London 2012 and (b) Sochi 2014 Olympic and Paralympic Games have been supported by the Talented Athlete Scholarship Scheme.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189220","189220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39452","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189058","189058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39453","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what provisions her Department makes available to those suffering from gambling addiction.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189026","189026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39454","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of people in (a) England and (b) the London Borough of Havering who suffer from gambling addiction.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189025","189025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39455","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the research being undertaken by the Responsible Gambling Trust into fixed odds betting terminals is a fair assessment of the situation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189041","189041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39456","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in her Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189078","189078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39457","2014-02-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Arts Council gave to (a) opera and (b) brass bands in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189014","189014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39458","2014-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many feature films produced by ethnic minority film makers have been supported by BFI in the past year; and what proportion of total spending on feature film support such support was.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188978","188978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39459","2014-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what support her Department provides for ethnic minority film makers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188980","188980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39460","2014-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she expects to publish an action plan for tackling nuisance calls.","Biography information for Mr Alan Reid","Mr Alan Reid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188959","188959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39461","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2014, Official Report, column 6, what recent discussions he has had with the Burmese army on that body's role in the Burmese parliament.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188938","188938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39462","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current manpower strength is of all naval personnel who are not Royal Marines.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188939","188939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39463","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what surface combat ships are currently (a) in build and (b) on order.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188940","188940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39464","2014-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the Watchkeeper Programme; when he expects the system to enter full service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188941","188941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39465","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189079","189079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39466","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what military personnel are stationed in each of the British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189022","189022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39467","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189059","189059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39468","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189099","189099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39469","2014-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189159","189159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39470","2014-02-26","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-24","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what estimate he has made of the additional costs to be reimbursed to local authorities for the transition of voter registration forms from A4 size to A3.","Biography information for Dr Thrse  Coffey","Dr Thrse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188934","188934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39471","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he expects to publish the results of the Teacher Workload Survey for 2014.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188991","188991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39472","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what grounds Tollbar Academy in Grimsby received more funding than other local academies in the north Lincolnshire area; and on what basis the funding for those academies was calculated.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188970","188970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39473","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will conduct an investigation into the reasons why pupils are being removed from school rolls before completing GCSE courses.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188982","188982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39474","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to publish the results of the teacher workload survey dated March 2013.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188914","188914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39475","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the findings of the report entitled Ruled Out, published in February 2014 by Ambitious About Autism, that substantial numbers of autistic children are being unlawfully excluded from schools.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188915","188915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39476","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received from the scientific and engineering communities on Ofqual's proposal to reform the A-level science curriculum by separating non-examined assessment from the final grade awarded to students.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188919","188919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39477","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189160","189160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39478","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189100","189100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39479","2014-02-27","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much correspondence Ministers in his Department have received on admission complaints for academy schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189222","189222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39480","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189060","189060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39481","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department issues on the standard of accommodation which should be provided to foster children.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189024","189024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39482","2014-02-26","Department for Education","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189080","189080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39483","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189081","189081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39484","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of civil servants in his Department on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189061","189061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39485","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189101","189101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39486","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with ministers in the Northern Ireland Executive on the effects of climate change on extreme weather events.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189219","189219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39487","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will seek to establish (a) how many households in Britain have a gas meter installed but receive no supply of gas to their property and (b) how many customers are subject to standing charges for such meters.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189218","189218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39488","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with the Minister of State at the Cabinet Office about the effects of climate change on civil contingency provisions.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189217","189217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39489","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189161","189161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39490","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the level of Government financial liability for radioactive incidents at UK nuclear plants.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188920","188920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39491","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the carbon impact of new nuclear power plants as a result of (a) obtaining uranium, (b) processing uranium and (c) storing radioactive waste.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188922","188922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39492","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households have registered in each collective switching scheme supported by the Cheaper Energy Together fund; and how many such households have switched energy suppliers.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188952","188952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39493","2014-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department takes to (a) monitor the level of and (b) support (i) individual and (ii) collective switching of energy companies by customers.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188955","188955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39494","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with his Irish counterpart on the Inter-Governmental Agreement on renewable energy trading.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188973","188973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39495","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when the Inter-Governmental Agreement between the UK and Ireland is likely to be signed.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188974","188974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39496","2014-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he has taken to ensure that an Inter-Governmental Agreement is signed in time for projects to export wind energy from Ireland to the UK to start by 2020.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188972","188972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39497","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the European Commission, (b) his European counterparts and (c) UK members of the European Parliament on European-wide counter-measures against invasive non-native species.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188928","188928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39498","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy that the new biodiversity offsetting scheme is mandatory.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188926","188926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39499","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on the inclusion of special habitats in the biodiversity offsetting scheme.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188927","188927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39500","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how his Department assesses the effectiveness of sustainable drainage solutions in ensuring that other properties are not adversely affected by water run-off from new developments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188918","188918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39501","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189162","189162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39502","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189102","189102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39503","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189062","189062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39504","2014-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189082","189082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39505","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189083","189083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39506","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Argentinian counterpart on UK oil drilling in the Falkland Islands since the beginning of 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189031","189031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39507","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Pakistan on preventing tensions in the region following reports that Iran may send troops into Pakistan.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189028","189028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39508","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189063","189063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39509","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to visit China in 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189046","189046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39510","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Spanish counterpart on Gibraltar in 2014 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189029","189029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39511","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Russian counterpart on the political instability in Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189047","189047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39512","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to improve US-UK trading relations since the beginning of 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189044","189044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39513","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking in respect of advice from the UN Human Rights Council to tackle human rights abuses in North Korea.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189027","189027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39514","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to offer diplomatic support to Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189042","189042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39515","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the process is by which UK citizens can relocate to Gibraltar.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189021","189021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39516","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189103","189103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39517","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189163","189163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39518","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department takes to offer financial support for the repatriation of a UK citizen's body if the citizen's relatives are in financial hardship.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188943","188943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39519","2014-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many bereaved families the EU Compensation Assistance team has helped since that body's formation.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188944","188944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39520","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many families have successfully claimed compensation from an overseas local authority following the death of a relative abroad in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188945","188945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39521","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of UK policy towards Egypt on Egyptian-Russian relations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189017","189017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39522","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Qatari government expressing the UK's opposition to their funding of the Muslim Brotherhood; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189018","189018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39523","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the European Commission on Gibraltar in 2014 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189019","189019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39524","2014-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on trade deals agreed between India and the UK since the visit by the Prime Minister in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189020","189020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39525","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress his Department has made on the release of files (a) related to violence against the Kenyan people at the hands of British colonial authorities and (b) relating to Britain's role in colonial Kenya; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189002","189002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39526","2014-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Peruvian counterpart on the case of Melissa Reid and Michaella McCollum Connolly.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188971","188971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39527","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his international counterparts in support of ratification of the UN Arms Trade Treaty; what discussions he has had with the European Commission on ratification of that Treaty; when he expects the UK to ratify the Treaty; and when he expects the Treaty to come into force.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188957","188957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39528","2014-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Pakistani counterpart on (a) that country's blasphemy laws and (b) the abolition of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188958","188958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39529","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to allow access to Abraxane form of protein-bound paclitaxel through the Cancer Drug Fund.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188960","188960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39530","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve mental health provision in England.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189006","189006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39531","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS service providers subcontract to a private provider for ambulance services.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189007","189007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39532","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of trends in call volume handled by each ambulance trust in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188956","188956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39533","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the cost of NHS England funding the RAS test and other companion diagnostic tests.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188932","188932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39534","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the steps (a) already taken and (b) planned to fully implement the Improving Outcomes guidance reports on cancer services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188963","188963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39535","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the availability of (a) Gamma Knife, (b) Novalis, (c) Cyberknife and (d) XKnife treatments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188964","188964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39536","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the Government's 450 million for earlier cancer detection has been spent on MRI machines for brain cancer.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188965","188965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39537","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS sites received new MRI machines in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188966","188966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39538","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria were used to determine which sites were provided with new MRI machines in the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188967","188967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39539","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how much was spent on the early diagnosis of brain cancer in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188968","188968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39540","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria his Department used to decide where new treatments for (a) cancer and (b) brain cancer will be placed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188969","188969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39541","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the efficacy of the steps taken by his Department to improve the quality of life of cancer patients since 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188983","188983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39542","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to implement the Improving Outcomes guidance reports on cancer services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188984","188984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39543","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many brain MRI scans were performed on suspected brain tumour patients in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188985","188985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39544","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to improve diagnosis and awareness of brain cancers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188986","188986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39545","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to increase the amount spent on funding brain tumour research; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188987","188987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39546","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many press officers were employed in his Department on 1 February 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189012","189012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39547","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings he has had with campaign groups dealing with the health risks of sugar since taking office.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189013","189013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39548","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to commission a vaccine for the H10N8 virus.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188948","188948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39549","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to detect the H10N8 virus in the UK population.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188949","188949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39550","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has in place to roll-out national commissioning of existing molecular pathology tests for cancer treatment.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188930","188930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39551","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has allocated to each ambulance trust in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188953","188953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39552","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) measures and (b) indicators his Department uses to assess the performance levels of ambulance trusts in England.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188954","188954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39553","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with NHS England on including molecular diagnostic testing of cancer within specialised commissioning; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 188931","188931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39554","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were promoted in each of the last five years were identified as (a) white British and (b) from any other ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189164","189164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39555","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of educational initiatives to support GPs and allied healthcare professionals with measures to improve the health of veterans.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189228","189228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39556","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on local NHS services of the floods; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189229","189229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39557","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of dangers to public health of (a) water-borne infections, (b) trauma and ill-effects to mental health and (c) hypothermia in areas suffering from flooding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189230","189230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39558","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many workplace nurseries (a) directly operated by his Department and (b) operated by a third party on his Department's property there were at (a) 5 May 2010 and (b) 5 February 2014; and how many such nurseries are expected to cease operating in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189104","189104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39559","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if NHS England will provide funding for selective dorsal rhizotomy surgery to go ahead for children who have already had the surgery arranged.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189236","189236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39560","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs per head of population were in practice in (a) Warrington, (b) the North West and (c) England in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189223","189223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39561","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will continue to fund selective dorsal rhizotomy surgery for children with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189210","189210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39562","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients waited longer than the specified 18 week period to begin NHS consultant-led treatment on referral from their GP in the latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189023","189023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39563","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of civil servants in his Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189064","189064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39564","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness with which NHS trusts arrange appointments; and what information it holds on the extent of variation in practice between trusts in arranging appointments.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189207","189207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39565","2014-02-26","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189084","189084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39566","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidelines his Department has given to NHS trusts on (a) the system used to arrange appointments and (b) the length of time between appointments.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189208","189208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39567","2014-02-27","Department of Health","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason NHS England has decided to stop funding selective dorsal rhizotomy surgery for children with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189209","189209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39568","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the standard level and duration is of contractual maternity pay paid to civil servants in her Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189085","189085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39569","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the continued deployment of immigration enforcement information vans across the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189032","189032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39570","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle human trafficking within the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189034","189034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39571","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that live animals seized by the UK Border Force are correctly and safely re-homed.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189033","189033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39572","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of civil servants in her Department who were on maternity leave in each of the last five years returned to work.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189065","189065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39573","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take to address unofficial websites offering passport application services.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189052","189052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/39574","2014-02-26","Home Office","2014-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to minimise the number of football match-related crimes.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189040","189040"
