"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043084","2019-01-22","Leader of the House","2019-01-17","To ask the Leader of the House, when she plans to table a substantive motion on proxy voting in the House of Commons.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209861","209861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043085","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prisoners given custodial sentences who were homeless before sentencing in Nottinghamshire in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209862","209862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043086","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what schemes that tackle homelessness in the Midlands receive government funding.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209863","209863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043087","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to employment and support allowance, how many ESA65B letters her Department has sent to GPs in each month since May 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209737","209737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043088","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to increase the uptake of flu vaccinations for primary-aged school children in Lancashire.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209760","209760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043089","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department has provided to Paul Whelan and his family following his detention in Russia.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209864","209864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043090","2019-01-22","Cabinet Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what dates he has held discussions with the National Cyber Security Centre to discuss the role of Huawei in the UK's Critical National Infrastructure.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209865","209865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043091","2019-01-22","Cabinet Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has been advised by the National Cyber Security Centre to restrict the access of Huawei to the UK's Critical National Infrastructure.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209866","209866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043092","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) initial and (b) additional allocated budgets for special needs provision in Nottinghamshire schools have been in each of the past three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209761","209761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043093","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January to Question 207241 on NHS: Fire Prevention, what the time frame is for the publication of the report on the construction types across the whole NHS Property Services portfolio of properties; and whether data on all combustible external wall materials found will be published.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209835","209835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043094","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of pupils in Nottinghamshire with individual education, health and care plans whose schools have yet to receive the additional funding needed for their implementation; and how long on average schools have waited to receive that funding in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209762","209762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043095","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how long on average it has taken for an education, health and care plan for a special needs child to be put in place from the date of initial request for assessment for such a plan in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209763","209763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043096","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many education, health and care plans are in place in Nottinghamshire schools; and how many were in place in each of the two previous academic years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209764","209764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043097","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) teaching assistants and (b) specialist support staff (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools have employed in Nottinghamshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209765","209765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043098","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were referred to children’s social care for an assessment of need in (a) Greenwich and (b) Bexley in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and what funding was provided for children’s services in (i) Greenwich and (ii) Bexley in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209766","209766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043099","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the causes of the recent increase in the number of looked after children in England.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209767","209767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043100","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of central Government funding for children’s services in the most recent 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209836","209836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043101","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the long-term economic benefits of early intervention services for children and young people.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209837","209837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043102","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to extend position of trust laws to sports coaches.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209768","209768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043103","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will assess the potential merits of introducing a discretionary compensation scheme for tenants of properties let on a non-commercial basis who are impacted by the HS2 line construction.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209867","209867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043104","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to meet UN Special Envoy Martin Griffiths before the next round of peace talks on Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209751","209751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043105","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many independent election observers (a) his Department and (b) other nations provided for the general election in Bangladesh; and what assessment he has made of the legitimacy of that election.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209769","209769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043106","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the trends in the level of (a) knife crime, (b) gun crime, (c) homicides and (d) gang-related crime in (i) Preston constituency and (ii) Lancashire.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209770","209770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043107","2019-01-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2019 to Question 206713 on Broadband: Rural Answers, what steps his Department takes to measure and report on (a) BT's capital contribution to the rural broadband roll-out and (b) BT gainshare or clawback.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209730","209730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043108","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had with LINK on the interchange rate for ATMs.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209838","209838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043109","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has estimated the potential cost of granting lifelong pensions for all police widows in England and Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209868","209868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043110","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police widows pensions ceased due to remarriage in each year since 1987.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209869","209869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043111","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the differences are in provision for police widows in the police pension schemes of (a) 1987, (b) 2006 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209870","209870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043112","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police widows have had their pensions revoked under the Police Pensions Regulations 1987 because they have remarried or moved in with a new partner for each police service in England and Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209902","209902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043113","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the cost per annum of reinstating widows pensions that have been revoked under the 1987 Police pension regulations for each Police Service in England and Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209871","209871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043114","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the current average police widows pension under the 1987 police pension regulations for each police service in England and Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209872","209872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043115","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many serving police officers in each police force in England and Wales are members of the Police pension scheme 1987.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209873","209873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043116","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department plans to publish its review of time limits on immigration detention.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209874","209874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043117","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has conducted an assessment of the potential effect of the proposed Immigration (Time Limit on Detention) Bill on (a) the number of people detained under immigration powers and (b) the number of Immigration Removal Centres required in the UK.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209875","209875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043118","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants in his Department work full-time on policy relating to the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209839","209839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043119","2019-01-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, by what date his Department plans to have brought forward legislative proposals to extend the scope of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 to cover relationships between sports coaches and 16-17 year olds in their care.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209876","209876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043120","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria are used to determine the sponsor of a school that is subject to an academy order.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209840","209840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043121","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what records his Department keeps of the ministerial decision process relating to selection of sponsors of schools which are converted to academies.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209841","209841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043122","2019-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 207294 on Social Security Benefits: EU Nationals, what discussions she has had with the Home Secretary on how EU Nationals' access to social security will be maintained for those awaiting the outcome of their application to the EU settlement scheme.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209877","209877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043123","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) necessity and (b) feasibility of Natural England granting licenses to shoot endangered native birds and wildlife.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209771","209771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043124","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to resolve the industrial dispute affecting the Northern Rail network.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209878","209878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043125","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how often the Retail Sector Council meets; and whether the dates of these meetings are in the public domain.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209772","209772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043126","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209879","209879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043127","2019-01-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209880","209880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043128","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209881","209881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043129","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209882","209882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043130","2019-01-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209883","209883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043131","2019-01-21","Department for International Development","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in her Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209884","209884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043132","2019-01-21","Department for International Trade","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209885","209885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043133","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209886","209886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043134","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in her Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209887","209887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043135","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209888","209888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043136","2019-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209889","209889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043137","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209890","209890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043138","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209891","209891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043139","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209892","209892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043140","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209893","209893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043141","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209894","209894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043142","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209895","209895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043143","2019-01-21","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information her Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in her Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209896","209896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043144","2019-01-21","Scotland Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209897","209897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043145","2019-01-21","Wales Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what information his Department holds on the rate of remuneration for (a) cleaners, (b) security guards and (c) catering staff in his Department in (i) Greater London and (ii) outside Greater London.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209898","209898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043146","2019-01-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has had discussions with Cabinet colleagues on expanding the role of the Civil Nuclear Constabulary to augment police resources in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209899","209899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043147","2019-01-22","Cabinet Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the Government document entitled The role of communication in rebuilding political trust in full.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209900","209900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043148","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking as part of the NHS Long Term Plan to ensure that there is an adequate number of staff to provide treatment for elderly people.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209752","209752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043149","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to increase attendance at diabetes education programmes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209753","209753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043150","2019-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 14 January 2019, HCWS1249, on pensions update, what estimate she has made of the number of people who will be affected by changes to pension credit in each local authority.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209773","209773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043151","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people attended diabetes education programmes in each clinical commissioning group area in 2018.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209754","209754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043152","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which 10 local authority areas had the highest rates of NHS opoid drug prescriptions in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209774","209774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043153","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to (a) reduce the incidence of Lyme disease and (b) increase awareness of that disease.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209775","209775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043154","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer on 11 January 2019 to Question 203813, how many claimants of personal independence payments who died within six months of their claim being registered received a payment.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209776","209776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043155","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer on 11 January 2019 to Question 203813, how many claimants who died after registering a personal independence payments claim but prior to her Department making a decision on their claim applied under (a) Normal Rules and (b) Special Rules.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209777","209777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043156","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer on 11 January 2019 to Question 203813, how many claimants of personal independence payments who died within six months of their claim being registered had their application rejected.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209778","209778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043157","2019-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average length of prison sentences in (a) England and (b) Wales in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209779","209779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043158","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of personal independence payments have died within three months of having their application rejected.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209780","209780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043159","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer on 11 January 2019 to Question 203813, how many claimants of personal independence payments (PIP) who have had their application rejected under Normal Rules subsequently reapplied for PIP under the Special Rules for Terminal Illness process.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209781","209781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043160","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer on 11 January 2019 to Question 203813, how many claimants of personal independence payments (a) had their application rejected under Normal Rules and (b) were subsequently awarded benefits after appeal; and what primary condition those claimants had.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209782","209782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043161","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress his Department has made on reducing the health inequalities for people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209842","209842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043162","2019-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of duck welfare rules for commercial duck farms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209783","209783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043163","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on increasing  the number of specialist learning disability nurses in the NHS.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209843","209843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043164","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of social care for people with a learning disability on the level of avoidable admissions to hospital of those people.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209844","209844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043165","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress his Department has made on ensuring that reasonable adjustments are made for people with a learning disability when using NHS services.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209845","209845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043166","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent comparative assessment he has made of the merits of community-based social care and assessment and treatment units.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209846","209846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043167","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase the social care packages for elderly people.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209784","209784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043168","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether EU students starting courses in England in the 2019-20 academic year will be eligible for home fee status in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209847","209847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043170","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the current time interval between initial screening and invitation for the next screening at Central and East London Breast Screening Service; and what that interval was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209738","209738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043171","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of patients that used the NHS personalised care model in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209785","209785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043172","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department will take to increase attendance at diabetes education programmes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209786","209786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043173","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the change in alcohol consumption as a result of alcohol duty freezes and reductions since 2013.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209901","209901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043174","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Frontline in improving retention rates among children’s social workers.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209849","209849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043175","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the National Productivity Investment Fund has been allocated to (a) housing, (b) research and development, (c) economic infrastructure and (d) skills since its inception.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209850","209850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043708","2019-01-23","Treasury","2019-01-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with insurance companies on the potential for discrimination through the use of criminal record information for the purpose of setting policy premiums.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210008","210008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041344","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of fires in (a) publicly and (b) privately owned high rise residential blocks in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208350","208350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041374","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to restrict the sale of faulty fire doors.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208363","208363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041688","2019-01-17","Department for International Development","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the long-term viability of the UN Relief and Works Agency.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208837","208837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042203","2019-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-16","When his Department plans to respond to its consultation entitled Food labelling: amending laws.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908633","908633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042204","2019-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-16","What recent discussions he has had with the Foreign Secretary on the protection of endangered species.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908630","908630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042205","2019-01-17","Scotland Office","2019-01-16","What recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits to the Scottish fishing industry of the UK leaving the Common Fisheries Policy.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908511","908511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042206","2019-01-16","Scotland Office","2019-01-16","What recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on the roll-out of broadband in Scotland.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908514","908514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042207","2019-01-16","Scotland Office","2019-01-16","What assessment he has made of the effect on low-income families of the roll-out of universal credit in Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908518","908518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042259","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of crowdfunding by lessees to raise money to challenge decisions made by pub companies in the courts.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209335","209335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042260","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with his Northern Ireland counterparts on the support offered to entrepreneurs seeking to start new businesses.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209336","209336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042261","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which EU member states have indicated that UK citizens living in those countries would continue to be able to access local health services in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209279","209279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042262","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a free railcard for people over the age of 65.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209337","209337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042263","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what conclusions the Road Collision Investigation Project has made on road accidents involving motorcyclists.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209338","209338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042264","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-16","If he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow roadside rescue and recovery operators to use red warning light on their vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209303","209303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042265","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment the Government has made of why uptake rates in groups eligible for free flu vaccination remain low.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209339","209339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042266","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to increase the level of immunisation performed by the NHS.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209340","209340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042267","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate his Department has made of funding in (a) 2019-20, (b) 2020-21, (c) 2021-22, (d) 2022-23 and (e) 2023-24 for (i) the acute sector, (ii) primary care, (iii) cancer services, (iv) mental health services, (e) community services, (f) NHS IT and digital services, (g) maternity services, (h) medicines and pharmaceuticals, (j) mental health, (k) diabetes and (l) dementia services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209341","209341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042268","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding has been allocated to training for professionals working with child mental health in North Herefordshire constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209304","209304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042269","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to respond to the letter of the hon. Member for Lincoln, of 5 October 2018, on issues at HMP Lincoln, reference MC062204.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209399","209399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042270","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Ministers were consulted by NHS England before they advised health bodies to request a signed authority from an honourable Member acting on behalf of a constituent; and for what reason that policy on this matter has been changed.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209287","209287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042271","2019-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his letter dated of 15 January 2019 in relation to Question 196768, what assessment he has made of the reasons why only a maximum of nine out of the full compliment of 11 full-time investigator posts have ever been filled in the office of the Service Complaints Ombudsman; and whether the problems identified in the United Kingdom Security Vetting agency by the National Audit Office in its report entitled Investigation into national security vetting, published in September 2018, have contributed to the posts being unfilled; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209305","209305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042272","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Indian Government on the demolition of the homes of British and EU citizens in Daman, India.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209288","209288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042273","2019-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what scenario planning his Department is undertaking on Military Aid to Civil Authorities.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209289","209289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042274","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date his Department awarded ETS a contract to undertake English language tests for overseas students.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209280","209280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042275","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what arrangements his Department has put in place to monitor performance on the contract awarded to ETS to undertake English language tests for overseas students.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209281","209281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042276","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many bidders were considered by his Department in the procurement exercise which led to a contract being awarded to ETS to undertake English language tests for overseas students.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209282","209282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042277","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the value was of the contract awarded to ETS to undertake English language tests for overseas students.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209283","209283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042278","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to reduce patient notification errors due to NHS bodies having different communication systems.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209342","209342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042279","2019-01-21","Department for International Development","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2018 to Question 200063 on Palestinians: Schools, whether her Department has commissioned the study into the new Palestinian textbooks referred to in that answer.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209284","209284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042280","2019-01-21","Department for International Development","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the health and well being of displaced Syrian refugees living in refugee camps during periods of adverse weather conditions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209290","209290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042281","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 207321, for what reasons that answer did not provide an estimate of what proportion of eligible businesses the 4000 companies now in scope for making tax digital represents.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209400","209400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042282","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to suspend the importation of trophies from ivory-bearing animals such as the hippopotamus until the conclusion of the consultation on adding other species to the Ivory Act 2018.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209401","209401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042283","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will conduct a review into the issuing of licences for the importation of hunting trophies.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209402","209402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042284","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the total cost to the public purse of the appeals process for personal independence payments assessments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209291","209291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042285","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with (a) learning disabilities and (b) autism are included in the development of mandatory disability and equality training for NHS staff.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209343","209343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042286","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what topics will be included in the mandatory training on learning disability and autism for NHS Staff.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209344","209344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042287","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure services funded by the NHS uphold national learning disability improvement standards; and if he will introduce a monitoring system to ensure compliance with those standards.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209345","209345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042288","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what oversight will be given to services funded by the NHS in relation to the implementation of national learning disability improvement standards.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209346","209346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042289","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of employment growth which can be attributed to (a) agency work, (b) self-employment and (c) zero-hours contracts in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209292","209292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042290","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons money is supplied to (a) the USA, (b) Japan and (c) other highly developed nations through the Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209403","209403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042291","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with United Nations representatives on the recent findings of a report from that organisation that one third of UN staff and contractors have experienced sexual harassment in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209293","209293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042292","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Health and Safety Executive on the (a) application and (b) enforcement of the UK Continental Shelf of Directive 2013/30/EU on the safety of offshore oil and gas operations in the event that the UK leaves the EU on 29 March 2019 without a deal.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209347","209347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042293","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the (a) Health and Safety Executive and (b) Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the status of the Offshore Safety Directive Regulator after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209348","209348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042294","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the Offshore Safety Directive Regulator last updated trade unions organising offshore oil and gas workers.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209349","209349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042295","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the provisions of the Offshore Installations (Offshore Safety Directive) (Safety Case etc.) Regulations 2015 (OSDR) require amendment in order to continue applying on installations on the UK Continental Shelf after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209350","209350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042296","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many meetings of the Offshore Major Accident Hazards Advisory Committee (OMAHAC) there have been since March 2016; and if she will list the attendees at each meeting of OMAHAC to date.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209351","209351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042297","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 207155 on Adult Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase participation rates in adult education courses.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209294","209294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042298","2019-01-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to support young people from deprived backgrounds to progress in the creative industries.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209404","209404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042299","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of prosecutions for psychoactive substances dealing.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209405","209405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042300","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will commission an independent review of the (a) adequacy, (b) cost effectiveness and (c) effect on the diversity of students of credibility interviews within the student immigration system.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209352","209352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042301","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to develop an international student growth strategy.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209353","209353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042302","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 207293 on Local Government Services: EU Nationals, whether carrying out their lives broadly as now includes accessing local authority-provided services.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209406","209406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042303","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young unemployed people have speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209273","209273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042304","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans does he have to increase the number of Registered Intermediaries.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209274","209274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042305","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has made a recent assessment of the value for money of a child being taken into care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209275","209275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042306","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many speech and language therapists work in virtual schools.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209276","209276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042307","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his timetable is for bringing forward legislative proposals on mental health care.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209277","209277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042308","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many adults in receipt of mental health services have (a) speech, language and communication needs and (b) dysphagia.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209278","209278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042309","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 69 of the NHS Long Term Plan, whether the four-week waiting time target for adults and older adults community mental health teams will be between referral and assessment or referral and treatment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209354","209354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042310","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2019 to Question 206815 on Independent Case Examiner, of the 2,514 cases closed following the High Court decision, how many of those cases related to complaints made on the grounds of maladministration.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209355","209355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042311","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 10 January 2019 and 9 October 2018 to Questions 205811 and 173497, if he will publish a breakdown of the number of (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff at the National County Lines Coordination Centre.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209285","209285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042312","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has undertaken to ensure that health services such as access to continuing healthcare plans are available to people with hearing impairments or profound deafness.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209356","209356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042313","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues in Cabinet meetings on the effect on local authorities of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209306","209306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042314","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, who was awarded the £70,000 contract to develop an online map to help carers and disabled people find Changing Places toilets.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209357","209357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042315","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether there was a tendering process for the £70,000 contract awarded to develop an online map to help carers and disabled people find Changing Places toilets.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209358","209358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042316","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of full-time practising GPs in (a) Hull clinical commissioning group, (b) the Yorkshire and the Humber NHS England North regional team area and (c) England in each of the last eight years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209307","209307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042317","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2018 to Question 199286 on Overseas Students: Immigration, what criteria are used to assess whether a student has a recognised connection with the UK.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209359","209359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042318","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to publish a long-term strategy for the apprenticeships sector.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209360","209360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042319","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the four-week waiting time target for adult and older adult community mental health teams on page 69 of the NHS Long Term Plan, what grade of healthcare professional will have responsibility for the (a) assessment and (b) treatment of those people seeking such care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209361","209361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042320","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what contribution to the pubic purse has been made by non-EU citizens in employment via (a) National Insurance contributions, (b) income tax, and (c) indirect taxation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209308","209308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042321","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has plans to abolish the NHS surcharge for non-EU citizens who pay National Insurance contributions.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209309","209309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042322","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Bridgend of 13 November 2018, reference MM/JH/12/11/2018.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209310","209310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042323","2019-01-21","Department for International Development","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which (a) for-profit private companies and (b) private contractors received official development assistance for the (i) delivery of education and (ii) facilitation of education programmes in (A) Kenya, (B) Nigeria and (C) Pakistan between 2015 and 2018.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209407","209407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042324","2019-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the cost per flight per hour of a Typhoon; what is included in calculating this cost; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209311","209311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042325","2019-01-21","Department for International Development","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on education (a) bilaterally and (b) multilaterally in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209408","209408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042326","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patients who are prescribed Naproxen continue to be able to receive that medication in the event of (a) the UK leaving the EU on 29 March 2019 and (b) the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209362","209362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042327","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress he has made on reducing teacher workload.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209363","209363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042328","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department undertook an impact assessment of its recently approved reductions in funding bands for management apprenticeships.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209364","209364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042329","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of English Hub schools having at least one member of staff who has received specialist speech, language and communication training.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209286","209286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042330","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of forthcoming changes to universal credit entitlement for mixed-aged couples on their level of income.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209365","209365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042331","2019-01-21","Prime Minister","2019-01-16","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will appoint a Minister with responsibility for poverty and hunger.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209366","209366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042332","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of Persistent Genital Arousal Syndrome (PGAS) have been recorded in each of the last five years; and how many PGAS specialists are currently practising in England.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209312","209312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042333","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been on refunding passengers as a result of the train delays and cancellations in 2018.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209367","209367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042334","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recommendations of the World Health Organization report, Artificial tanning devices: public health interventions to manage sunbeds, published in 2017.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209409","209409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042335","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 206393 on Drugs, how many and what proportion of those contract agreements (a) have and (b) have not been signed off.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209368","209368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042336","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date Amie Anelka was appointed to the role of Data Protection Officer in his Department; and for how long Ms Anelka held that role.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209295","209295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042337","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who was appointed to the role of Data Protection Officer in his Department on 4 November 2018.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209296","209296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042338","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 207224 on Universal Credit: Support for Mortgage Interest, what assessment he has made of the effect of the zero-earning rule on incentivising people to move into work.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209313","209313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042339","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 207224 on Universal Credit: Support for Mortgage Interest, what the policy objective is of Support for Mortgage Interest.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209369","209369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042340","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, where the contact details for his Department's Data Protection Officer are published; and (a) how and (b) when those contact details were communicated to the Information Commissioner's Office.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209297","209297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042341","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209314","209314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042342","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209315","209315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042343","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209316","209316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042344","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209317","209317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042345","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2013.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209318","209318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042346","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2012.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209319","209319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042347","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2011.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209320","209320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042348","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209321","209321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042349","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2009.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209322","209322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042350","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2008.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209323","209323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042351","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2007.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209324","209324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042352","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2006.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209325","209325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042353","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2005.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209326","209326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042354","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish his Department's devolution framework.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209370","209370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042355","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the acquittal of Laurent Gbagbo on the efforts of the International Criminal Court to enforce human rights standards.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209371","209371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042356","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of UK allies that have failed to comply with the International Criminal Court arrest warrant for Omar al-Bashir as a result of him being allowed through their territory since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209372","209372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042357","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Zimbabwean counterpart on that country's obligations under international human rights and international law in relation to the treatment of independent Trades Unions.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209373","209373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042358","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department holds statistics on the number of stores that closed in each quarter in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209374","209374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042359","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effect on mixed-age couples of the changes to eligibility for pensions credit.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209375","209375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042360","2019-01-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the recommendation made by the Film Diversity Action Group that film tax breaks should be conditional on the achievement of diversity targets  on the (a) finances of and (b) levels of diversity in companies in the film industry.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209376","209376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042361","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of local authorities enforcing 20mph zones in built-up areas on the level of pedestrians involved in traffic accidents.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209377","209377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042362","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage local authorities to issue public safety campaigns to reduce the number of pedestrians involved in traffic accidents.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209378","209378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042363","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many serious road traffic accidents there were in (a) the UK, (b) London, (c) Borough of Lewisham and (d) Borough of Bromley in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209379","209379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042364","2019-01-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his policy to require film companies to include in paperwork submitted for film classification, data on the level of diversity of those companies.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209380","209380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042365","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to increase road safety nationally.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209410","209410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042366","2019-01-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) financial effect and (b) effect on diversity in the film industry of the Film Diversity Action Group's November 2018 recommendation that a Diversity Monitor be set up to track diversity data across individual productions, sectors and segments of that industry and to publish its results quarterly.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209381","209381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042367","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will respond to the report published on 10 January 2019 by the Higher Education Policy Institute entitled The Impact of Selective Secondary Education on Progression to Higher Education.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209382","209382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042368","2019-01-21","Department for International Development","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2019 to Question 206450 on Developing Countries: Nutrition, what opportunities her Department plans to provide for civil society organisations to contribute to discussions the UK Government has prior to the Nutrition For Growth summit in 2020.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209411","209411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042369","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to improve the regulation of medical devices following recent public concern about patient safety.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209327","209327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042370","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of people with refugee status in the UK who are graduates.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209328","209328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042371","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of people in the UK with refugee status who are qualified doctors in their home country.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209329","209329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042372","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 206295 on Special Educational Needs, what proportion of the 0-25 year old population do those figures represent for each local authority.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209330","209330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042373","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prisoners per 100,000 people in (a) England and (b) Wales in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209331","209331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042374","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the use of short prison sentences for women.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209383","209383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042375","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the correlation between homelessness on release from prison and reoffending rates among prisoners serving sentences of under a year.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209384","209384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042376","2019-01-21","Women and Equalities","2019-01-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October to Question 179255, what progress her Department has made on introducing legislative proposals on the extension of civil partnerships to heterosexual couples.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209385","209385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042377","2019-01-21","Prime Minister","2019-01-16","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will publish the minutes of her meeting with Japanese Prime MInister Shinzō Abe on 10 January 2019 on the proposed Wylfa Newydd power plant.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209332","209332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042378","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his policy is on police forces passing to his Department information on victims of trafficking offences who are in the UK unlawfully in order to facilitate their deportation.","Biography information for Fiona Onasanya","Fiona Onasanya","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209412","209412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042379","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to prioritise mental health and wellbeing in the work place.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209413","209413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042380","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what are the minimum standards of (a) physical accommodation and (b) assistance G4S are required to provide to asylum seekers under the terms of their contract with the Home Office.","Biography information for Fiona Onasanya","Fiona Onasanya","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209414","209414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042381","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 8 November 2018 to Question 186211 and of 28 November 2018 to Question 196767 on Birds: Conservation, and with reference to the completion in November 2017 of phase 2 of the Special Protection Area review, what guidance he has received on improving the network for breeding and non-breeding curlew.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209298","209298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042382","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants in his Department have been seconded to the Department for Exiting the European Union.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209386","209386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042383","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) students and (b) students eligible for free school meals studied GCSE computer science in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209333","209333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042384","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) students and (b) students eligible for free school meals studied A Level computer science in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209334","209334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042385","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent research he has commissioned on the effect of the use of lead shot on the environment; and whether he has plans to abolish the use of lead shot.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209299","209299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042386","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 1.55 of the NHS Long Term Plan, what the timeframe is for the (a) development and (b) implementation of the new integration index; which organisations he plans to consult the development of that index; and what criteria his Department plans to use to determine the metrics to be included in that index.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209387","209387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042387","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, if he will publish the (a) terms of reference and (b) membership of the NHS Clinical Standards Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209388","209388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042388","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, what discussions his Department plans to hold with (a) healthcare professionals; (b) NHS providers; (c) charities; (d) patients and (e) the public in relation to the NHS Clinical Standards Review.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209389","209389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042389","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, whether there will be a consultation on the recommendations of the NHS Clinical Standards Review before its publication in Spring 2019.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209390","209390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042390","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, whether an impact assessment will be (a) conducted and (b) published as part of the clinical standards review.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209391","209391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042391","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, what evidence the Government plans to review when considering whether there is a stronger role for the NHS in commissioning sexual health services.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209392","209392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042392","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the commitment in the NHS Long-Term Plan’s to consider the potential for a stronger role for the NHS in commissioning sexual health services whether (a) reproductive health services and (b) contraception will fall within the scope of that process.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209393","209393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042393","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the commitment in the NHS Long Term Plan to consider the potential for a stronger role for the NHS in commissioning sexual health services, what the timeframe is for the (a) consultation on and (b) implementation of proposals for the commissioning of those services.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209394","209394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042394","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the commitment in the NHS Long Term Plan to consider the potential for a stronger role for the NHS in commissioning sexual health services, which (a) organisations and (b) expert bodies he plans to consult.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209395","209395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042395","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) finances and (b) usage of the football pools of the reduction in the pools duty from 15 per cent  to one per cent.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209396","209396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042396","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on reducing the Pools Duty to 10 per cent, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209397","209397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042397","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department have made an assessment of the potential effect on the betting industry of the effect of reducing the Pools Duty to 10 per cent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209398","209398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042398","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that loans provided (a) under English law and (b) by UK-based companies to (i) governments and (ii) with government guarantees are publicly disclosed when they are given.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209300","209300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042399","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect on business confidence in Northern Ireland of the backstop provisions in the Government's proposed EU Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209301","209301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042400","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect on (a) GDP and (b) wages in Northern Ireland of  the backstop provisions contained in the Government's proposed EU Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209302","209302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041493","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","What steps he is taking to secure the long-term future of the NHS.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908576","908576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041568","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in relation to (a) women and (b) political activists in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208797","208797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041569","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps is he taking to ensure that (a) Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe and (b) Narges Mohammadi receive adequate and timely medical care.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208798","208798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041570","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Israeli Government on that country's decision to approve the construction of 2,800 units in the occupied West Bank.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208799","208799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041571","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the proportion of self-employed delivery drivers in London whose income is (a) equal to and (b) more than the National Living Wage.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208738","208738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041572","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, from what date was BT’s Next Generation Access lines assessed separately for business rates from the rest of the BT network.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208739","208739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041573","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason the rating assessment for unbundled local copper loops included a concession that was not available to fibre telecommunications infrastructure constructed before April 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208740","208740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041574","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of an increase in non-tariff barriers on consumer prices in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208741","208741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041575","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which ports with regular ferry services to the UK he plans to designate as EU Border Inspection Posts by 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208742","208742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041576","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether in the past 24 months the Queen has declined any of the the Forfeiture Committee’s recommendations for the forfeiture of a person's honour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208749","208749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041577","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will provide a timetable for announcing the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208800","208800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041578","2019-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reservists at each rank are serving on Her Majesty's Ships on operational duty.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208736","208736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041579","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 December 2018 on Public Spending, HCWS 1205, if he will publish the budget headlines under which he plans to allocate the £190 million funding in relation to preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208861","208861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041580","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason he plans to establish new military bases in (a) the Caribbean and (b) South East Asia after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208862","208862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041581","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the costs of the (a) set up and (b) annual running of the proposed new military bases to be established in (i) the Caribbean and (ii) South East Asia after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208863","208863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041582","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) his European counterparts on the merits of the UK establishing new military bases in (i) the Caribbean and (ii) South East Asia after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208864","208864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041583","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role he plans for Parliament to play in the scrutiny of the establishment of the proposed new military bases in the (a) Caribbean and (b) South East Asia to be set up after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208865","208865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041584","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will write to the (a) Defence Select Committee and (b) Public Accounts Committee to outline his plans for establishing new military bases in (i) the Caribbean and (ii) South East Asia after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208866","208866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041585","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 20 December 2018, Personal Independence Payment, HCWS 1224, what resources are being redirected from other areas of PIP; and what those other areas are.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208867","208867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041586","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2018 to Question 182257 on Universal Credit: Lone Parents, what evidence her Department has that claimants who are under 25 have lower living costs.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208868","208868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041587","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Written Statement of 7 January 2019, Haulage Update, HCWS 1233, whether he has received any representations from cross channel freight service companies other than those named in that statement (a) expressing concern at the content of that statement and (b) offering additional capacity over and above the three contract awards outlined in that statement; and if he will make a further statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208869","208869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041588","2019-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to improve the levels of mobile connectivity available to passengers along the rail corridor.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208765","208765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041589","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with train operating companies on the delivery of mobile connectivity for rail passengers.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208766","208766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041590","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the level of mobile coverage provided to rail passengers.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208767","208767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041591","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the quality of Wi-Fi services available to rail passengers as required under the terms of rail franchise agreements.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208768","208768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041592","2019-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on establishing trials to provide mobile connectivity to passengers on the Trans-Pennine rail route as set out in Budget 2017.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208769","208769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041593","2019-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport,  with reference to Budget 2017, how much of the £35 million allocated to establishing trials to provide mobile connectivity to passengers on the Trans-Pennine rail route has been spent.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208770","208770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041594","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the levels of public spending required to provide a good standard of mobile connectivity to all rail passengers throughout the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208771","208771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041595","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the (a) Department for Transport and (b) Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport ahead of the 2019 Spending Review on the level of public funding required to provide (i) 4G mobile connectivity and (ii) Wi-Fi services to all rail passengers throughout the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208772","208772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041596","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of restrictions on media freedom in Tanzania; and what representations he has made to the Government of Tanzania on that subject.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208773","208773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041597","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the constitutional crisis in Catalonia; and what representations  he has made and to whom on that subject.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208774","208774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041598","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police working dogs have been successfully re-homed in the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208801","208801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041599","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Irish citizens have joined the British armed forces in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208802","208802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041600","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Commonwealth citizens have joined the British armed forces in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208803","208803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041601","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Havering Borough is planned to receive any funding from central government to implement the measures in the Local Cycling and Walking Infrastructure Plan.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208804","208804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041602","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have been migrated to universal credit since June 2018 in the Havering Borough Council area.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208805","208805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041603","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on the fight against Daesh in Syria of the decision of the US Administration to withdraw troops from that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208806","208806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041604","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Government next plans to provide an update to Parliament on the fight against Daesh.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208807","208807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041605","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received on the persecution of Christians in Tanzania; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208808","208808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041606","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received on the persecution of Christians in the Middle East; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208809","208809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041607","2019-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what funding his Department has allocated to arts and culture projects in Havering Borough in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208810","208810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041608","2019-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to introduce maximum five-year sentences for the worst cases of animal cruelty.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208811","208811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041609","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the strength of the UK space defence sector.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208812","208812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041610","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of people over the age of 70 that have not made a will.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208775","208775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041611","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to building owners of replacing faulty composite fire doors.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208750","208750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041612","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to issue additional guidance to building owners on the replacement of faulty composite fire doors.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208751","208751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041613","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department has allocated to support research into heart attacks in women; and for what reason that research was not included in the Government’s NHS Long-Term Plan.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208737","208737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041614","2019-01-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 111 of the Political Declaration Setting Out The Framework For The Future Relationship Between The European Union And The United Kingdom, published on 14 November 2018, which of the activities of the Cooperation Group the UK plans to maintain after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208870","208870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041615","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will include representatives from (a) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence, (b) the Department of Health and Social Care and (c) NHS England on his Honorary Medical Advisory Panel on driving and diabetes mellitus; and what steps he has taken to ensure that the Panel routinely seeks advice from those bodies","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208871","208871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041616","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of transferring responsibility for (a) the setting of standards for drivers with diabetes mellitus and (b) the operation of the Honorary Medical Advisory Panel on driving and diabetes mellitus to the Department of Health and Social Care.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208872","208872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041617","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much central government funding was allocated to local authority children and young people’s services in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018; and what proportion of that funding was allocated to early help services in each of those years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208743","208743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041618","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were referred to children’s services on multiple occasions before receiving support from those services in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208744","208744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041619","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many disabled children received social care in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208745","208745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041620","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much money from the public purse was spent by each of the Lords Lieutenants on (a) travel, (b) hospitality, (c) clothing and (d) other costs in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208776","208776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041621","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Lords Lieutenants have an ethnicity other than white British.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208777","208777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041622","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many royal warrants are extant for (a) HM The Queen, (b) the Duke of Edinburgh and (c) the Prince of Wales.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208778","208778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041623","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the process is to determine whether to grant a request for a royal warrant.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208779","208779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041624","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what procedure is in place to ensure that members of the Royal Warrant Holders Association do not use their membership of that body to disadvantage competitors in their personal business dealings or otherwise act to advantage themselves.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208780","208780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041625","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether goods obtained by the Royal Household from Royal Warrant holders are obtained at the normal commercial rate.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208781","208781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041626","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Royal Warrants have been withdrawn in each year since 2008; and if he will list those that have been withdrawn.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208782","208782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041627","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of enabling women under the age of 25 to undergo cervical screening.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208783","208783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041628","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has issued a response to HM Senior Coroner for Birmingham and Solihull in relation to the Regulation 28 report, dated 17 July 2018 on the deaths of two members of the Royal Tank Regiment on 14 June 2017.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208873","208873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041629","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) Scottish, (b) English and (c) Northern Irish Partnerships have been prosecuted each year since 2009 under Section 15.6 of The Partnerships (Accounts) Regulations 2008, for failure to make their accounts available (a) to Companies House, (b) at their Principal Place of Business and (c) through mechanisms provided in other EEA countries.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208874","208874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041630","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2018 to Question 195486 on guardianship for unaccompanied and separated children, what steps his Department is taking to (a) improve the (i) quality and (ii) timeliness of asylum decision making and (b) to ensure that decision makers understand the effects trauma can have on unaccompanied young people navigating the asylum system.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208875","208875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041631","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish any internal reviews undertaken by his Department on the effects of the asylum process on unaccompanied and separated children navigating the asylum system alone.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208876","208876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041632","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children are currently supported by Independent Child Trafficking Advocates (ICTA); and what was the (a) mean average, (b) longest and (c) shortest period of time between a child being identified as trafficked and being allocated an ICTA.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208877","208877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041633","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to introduce a post-study work visa which allows up to two years of work experience for international students in the UK.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208878","208878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041634","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there will be an independent review of credibility interviews within the student immigration system to ensure the system is (a) fit for purpose, (b) cost effective relative to current risk and (c) does not hinder universities’ ability to recruit a diverse range of students.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208879","208879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041636","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he had discussions with the Honours committees in advance of the OBE appointment of Vijay Patel in the New Year’s Honours list 2019.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208881","208881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041637","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department’s official representative on the Honours health committee had discussions with the Honours economy committee on the OBE appointment of Vijay Patel in advance of the New Year’s Honours list 2019.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208882","208882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041638","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential financial implications to the NHS of the reported practice of pharmaceutical companies dropping the brand name of out of patent products, relaunching those products under generic names and selling such products at a higher price.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208883","208883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041639","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2018 to Question 178508 on Drugs: Prices, for what reasons (a) the consultation on a new system of commissioning for special medicinal products has not begun and (b) unwarranted prices of unbranded generic medicines continues 18 months after the passing of the Health Service Medical Supplies (Costs) Act 2017.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208884","208884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041640","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of traffic using the Port of Dover is commercial through traffic from the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208813","208813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041641","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January 2019 to Question 205816 on walking, if he will provide a breakdown of the funding that is projected to be spent by his Department on (a) cycling and (b) walking in each year on each budget line from the start of this Parliament to 2021.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208885","208885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041642","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has received representations on noise and disturbance as a result of the decision by Chiltern Railway to use  Wrexham diesel express buggies trains on the Marylebone to South Ruislip line; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208746","208746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041643","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on hospice finances of the decision to raise NHS employer contributions to its pension scheme from April 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208747","208747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041644","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether compliance with national learning disability improvement standards will be mandatory for NHS funded services and whether those services will be (a) regulated and (b) rated for national learning disability improvement standards.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208814","208814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041645","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the prevalence of traffic incident’s on all-lane running motorways and motorways with hard-shoulders; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208815","208815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041646","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) research and (b) assessment his Department has undertaken into trends in the level of non-compliance on Smart Motorways.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208816","208816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041647","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has set a minimum acceptable level red-X non-compliance on smart motorways.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208817","208817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041648","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208818","208818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041649","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208819","208819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041650","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208820","208820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041651","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208821","208821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041652","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208822","208822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041653","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2013.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208823","208823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041654","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2012.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208824","208824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041655","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2011.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208825","208825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041656","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208826","208826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041657","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2009.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208827","208827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041658","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2008.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208828","208828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041659","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2007.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208829","208829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041660","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2006.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208830","208830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041661","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department entered into in 2005.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208831","208831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041662","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of any additional resources required to deliver an integrated care approach for 0-25 year olds with mental health problems across health, social care, education and the voluntary sector as outlined in the the NHS long-term plan.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208886","208886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041663","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the additional 345,00 children and young people with mental health problems expected to be accessing support from (a) NHS funded mental health services and (b) school or college-based mental health support teams as set out in the long-term plan for the NHS.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208887","208887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041664","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to proposals in the NHS Long Term Plan on expanding access to community-based mental health services, how many of the additional 345,000 children and young people expected to be accessing support via NHS funded mental health services and school or college-based Mental Health Support Teams are expected to be (a) 0-5, (b) 6-18 and, (c) 19-25 years old.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208888","208888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041665","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total contribution to the public purse has been from fines charged to (a) Scottish, (b) English and (c) Northern Irish Partnerships under Section 15.6 of The Partnerships (Accounts) Regulations 2008 for failure to make their accounts available either to Companies House, at their Principal Place of Business or through mechanisms provided in other EEA countries in each year from 2009.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208889","208889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041666","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 6 of his Department's publication entitled Facts on motorcyclists casualties, published in June 2015, what the proportion is of (a) car drivers and (b) light van drivers whose contributory factor of their accidents involving motorcyclists was their failure to look properly in each year from 2013 to 2017.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208890","208890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041667","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post offices there were by type of branch in each constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208891","208891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041668","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post offices were classified as under temporary closure by type of branch in each constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208892","208892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041669","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what criteria his Department uses to classify a post office under temporary closure.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208893","208893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041670","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what process his Department uses to re-open a post office that has been subject to temporary closure.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208894","208894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041671","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 190926 on Recycling: EU Law, if he will publish the (a) timetable (b) scope of the proposed consultation on the implementation of the 2018 EU Circular Economy Package.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208895","208895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041672","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to ensure that environmental regulations remain equal to those set by the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208896","208896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041673","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to promote the increased use of (a) recyclable and (b) repairable components in manufacturing.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208897","208897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041674","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to (a) increase recycling to 65 per cent of waste and (b) reduce landfill to 10 per cent of waste in conformity with the  2018 EU Circular Economy Package.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208898","208898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041675","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to maintain consumer protections in relation to the right to repair of electrical products after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208899","208899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041676","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the due diligence undertaken by the Government in advance of awarding public contracts to private sector providers as a result of the collapse of Carillion.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208900","208900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041677","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help the NHS minimise the risk of a winter crisis as a result of flu-related hospital admissions.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208832","208832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041678","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the NHS meets its flu immunisation targets for at-risk groups this winter.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208833","208833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041679","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to increase flu vaccination coverage rates throughout the UK.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208901","208901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041680","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase take-up rates for the flu vaccination by (a) healthcare professionals; (b) at-risk patient groups and (c) paid and unpaid carers.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208902","208902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041681","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the UK’s immunisation programme is adequately funded.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208903","208903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041682","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Clinical Commissioning Group place based allocations 2019/20 – 2023/24, what the real-term percentage increase in allocation from the 2018-19 adjusted baseline allocation to the 2023-24 final allocation for (a) England (b) each region of England is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208904","208904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041683","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2019 to Question 206466 on Universal Credit: Disability, what estimate she has made of the cost of providing information on how many people in receipt of the severe disability premium have been naturally migrated onto universal credit since 7 June 2018.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208905","208905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041684","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2017 to Question 206232 on Energy: Prices, what estimate he has made of the total cost incurred by (a) the public purse and (b) other energy suppliers as a result of the transfer of customers of domestic energy suppliers who cease trading through the Supplier of Last Resort process in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208752","208752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041685","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of effect of renewed rocket fire from Gaza into Israel on the political situation in that region.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208834","208834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041686","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of tunnel construction into Israel by Hamas in Gaza on the political situation in that region.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208835","208835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041687","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of adequacy of democratic processes in the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208836","208836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041689","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, how much funding has been allocated to specific new evidence-based NHS prevention programmes to (a) cut smoking, (b) reduce obesity,(c) the NHS Diabetes Prevention Programme, (d) limit alcohol related A&E admissions, (e) lower air pollution, and (f) in total; and whether that funding is (i) included and (ii) in addition to his Department’s public health grant to local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208906","208906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041690","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long-Term Plan, whether it remains his policy to meet the 92 per cent  referral to treatment waiting time target in 2019-20.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208907","208907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041691","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan how many (a) nurses and (b) doctors the NHS in England plan to recruit in each year up to 2022-24.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208908","208908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041692","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the commitment in the NHS Long Term Plan to reduce administrative costs by £700 million across commissioners and providers, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of jobs as a result of that reduction.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208909","208909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041693","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2018 to Question 201219 and with reference to the finding of Sands' Audit of Bereavement Care Provision in UK Neonatal Units 2018 that 12 per cent of neonatal units provide mandatory bereavement staff training, what steps his Department is taking to ensure neonatal units meet the Toolkit for High Quality Neonatal Services standard that all staff have bereavement training.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208910","208910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041694","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many employed mothers of babies who were admitted to neonatal care used their full 52 weeks of maternity leave entitlement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208911","208911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041695","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support working fathers whose babies have been admitted to neonatal units.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208912","208912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041696","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support improvement in police forces that are rated as inadequate or requiring improvement by Her Majesty’s Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire & Rescue Services.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208753","208753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041697","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Kenya; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208754","208754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041698","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support a peace process in Yemen.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208784","208784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041699","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the conclusions of his Department's consultation, Review of Post-18 Education and Funding.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208913","208913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041700","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of students leaving secondary education with a knowledge of basic cooking skills.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208755","208755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041701","2019-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the government of Japan to support the international ban on whaling.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208785","208785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041702","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether auditors from her Department  have the authority to instruct health professionals to make mandatory (a) specific and (b) general amendments to Independent Assessment Service reports.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208914","208914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041703","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Chinese Government on banning the Yulin dog meat festival.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208786","208786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041704","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to secure the release of UK-Iranian nationals imprisoned in Iran.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208787","208787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041705","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many health professionals from Independent Assessment Services have been (a) dismissed and (b) referred for further training as a result of her Department's audits of health professionals' reports.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208915","208915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041706","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to protect the rights and freedoms of journalists throughout the world.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208788","208788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041707","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have been engaged in work at Commercial Prison Industries' (a) DHL Workshop, (b) LMB Workshop, (c) Census Data Workshop and (d) Ink2Work Workshop in HMP Berwyn in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208916","208916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041708","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of hours worked per week is of prisoners working in Commercial Prison Industries' (a) DHL Workshop, (b) LMB Workshop, (c) Census Data Workshop and (d) Ink2Work Workshop in HMP Berwyn.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208917","208917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041709","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2018 to Question 171719 on Berwyn Prison, how many prisoners are engaged in work or learning and skills for more than 30 hours a week.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208918","208918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041710","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions the North Wales Fire and Rescue Service has been called to HMP Berwyn each year since that prison opened.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208919","208919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041711","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions ambulances have been called to HMP Berwyn each year since that prison opened.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208920","208920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041712","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers in positions as frontline operational staff at HMP Berwyn (a) by each prison block and (b) deployed in the care and separation unit have (i) less than two years experience and (ii) less than one year experience.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208921","208921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041713","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208789","208789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041714","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many use of force incidents have been recorded at HMP Berwyn in each month since the prison opened.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208922","208922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041715","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to issue further guidance to (a) businesses and (b) local authorities in line with Public Health England's advice on vaping in public places and workspaces.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208838","208838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041716","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question 202774 on Child Sexual Abuse Independent Panel Inquiry, what future support his Department plans to provide to the Family Restoration Fund for former child migrants","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208839","208839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041717","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests for transfers out of HMP Berwyn have been made by prisoners in each year since that prison opened.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208923","208923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041718","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff at HMP Berwyn are on (a) short term sick leave, (b) long-term sick leave, and (c) restricted duty.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208924","208924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041719","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff (a) resigned, (b) were regraded, (c) were transferred and (d) dismissed from HMP Berwyn in 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208925","208925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041720","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents at HMP Berwyn were referred to the police in 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208926","208926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041721","2019-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance this Department has made available to local community groups seeking to install a blue plaque commemorating key (a) local figures, (b) establishments and (c) the Blue Moon Club in Cheltenham.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208927","208927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041722","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2019 to Question 205987 on High Speed 2, when he plans to publish the barn owl mitigation plan.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208928","208928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041723","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to protect vulnerable road users from inappropriate parking penalties in private car parks.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208929","208929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041724","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of use of private parking operators by GP surgeries.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208930","208930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041725","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the closure of the Family Restoration Fund for former child migrants.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208840","208840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041726","2019-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department is giving to the Nigerian Government to repel attacks by armed insurgents in north-east Nigeria.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208931","208931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041727","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the strategic implications of the increased strength of armed insurgents in north-east Nigeria; and what support his Department is providing to Nigeria to tackle the insurgents.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208932","208932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041728","2019-01-21","Department for International Development","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what additional aid she will make available to support civilians forced to flee their homes to Monguno and Maiduguri following recent attacks by armed insurgents in north-east Nigeria.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208933","208933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041729","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the effective roll-out of universal credit in North Herefordshire constituency.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208790","208790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041730","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department plans to publish the results of its 2014 public consultation on the review of Section 24 of the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208841","208841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041731","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will ban live animal exports from UK ports in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208934","208934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041732","2019-01-21","Department for International Trade","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) value of Raytheon Paveway laser-guided bombs that have been approved for export to Saudi Arabia; what proportion of those bombs have been exported under (i) Standard Individual Export Licence and (ii) Ordinary Individual Export Licence in each quarter since June 2015; and at which locations those bombs were manufactured.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208935","208935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041733","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much his Department has spent on Overseas Development Aid in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208842","208842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041734","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department has spent on Official Development Assistance in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208843","208843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041735","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department has spent on Official Development Assistance in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208844","208844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041736","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs has spent on Official Development Assistance in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208845","208845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041737","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on Official Development Assistance in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208846","208846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041738","2019-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on Official Development Assistance in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208847","208847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041739","2019-01-21","Treasury","2019-01-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to protect consumers from high risk pay-day loans.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208936","208936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041740","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the increase in the work allowance of universal credit is worth per household.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208848","208848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041741","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the exceptional circumstances are which will allow full support under universal credit for third and subsequent children born after April 2017.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208849","208849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041742","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) reduce smoking and (b) encourage smokers to transition to vaping.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208850","208850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041743","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support local stop smoking services which encourage smokers to transition to vaping.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208851","208851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041744","2019-01-21","Wales Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with (a) ministerial colleagues, (b) his counterpart in the Japanese Government, and (c) representatives of Hitachi on the future of the proposed Wylfa Newydd power plant.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208791","208791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041745","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobcentre plus staff (a) joined and (b) left employment with jobcentre plus in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208792","208792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041746","2019-01-17","Department for International Development","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK will take to ensure food aid reaches people who need it in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208756","208756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041747","2019-01-17","Department for International Development","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what financial support the UK is providing to the Yemeni central bank.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208757","208757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041748","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of dedicated Clinical Nurse Specialists for patients with secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208937","208937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041749","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assurances he has sought from the US Administration on their commitment to resolving the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208758","208758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041750","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the UK is providing to the process of UN monitoring in the port of Hudaydah in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208759","208759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041751","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) funding allocated by his Department for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal and (b) proportion of that funding which has been allocated by ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208748","208748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041752","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help ensure that the Yemen peace agreements will endure.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208760","208760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041753","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 207170 on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund, if he will list the (a) engagement events that took place and (b) the region and nation in which they took place.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208793","208793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041754","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will issue instruction to NHS England that signed authority from a patient is not required for the NHS to progress an inquiry from an hon. Member pursuing a case on behalf of a constituent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208761","208761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041755","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many patients diagnosed with terminal brain tumours have been (a) placed in the work-related activity group and (b) required to attend interviews by DWP officers administering benefits.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208762","208762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041756","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department issues to staff dealing with applications for benefit by people diagnosed with brain tumour; and if she will place a copy of that guidance in the Library.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208763","208763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041757","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people (a) attempted and (b) succeeded in taking their own lives in each prison in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208794","208794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041758","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his letter of 15 January 2019 in relation to Question 196768, what steps he is taking to ensure the number of full-time investigation officer posts in the office of the Service Complaints Ombudsman's are fully staffed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208852","208852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041759","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reason the archive files relating to Britain’s nuclear weapons and atomic energy programmes were withdrawn from the National Archives by the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority in 2018.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208938","208938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041760","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his letter of 15 January 2019 in relation to Question 196768, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequacy of staffing levels in the office of the Service Complaints Ombudsman; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208853","208853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041761","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the upgrading of old SMETS1 meters so they have SMETS2 functionality, which types of SMETS1 meters will be enrolled into each phase of the upgrade programme; and which types of SMETS1 meters are not included in those plans.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208764","208764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041762","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his letter of 15 January 2019 in relation to Question, how many staff in the Service Complaints Ombudsman's office have taken sick leave as a result of stress related illnesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208854","208854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041763","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has met with vape product manufacturers in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208855","208855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041764","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to issue guidance to businesses and local authorities on vaping in public places and workplaces.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208856","208856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041765","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his letter of 15 January 2019 in relation to Question 196768, what the average length of investigations held by each full-time investigator was; and how many complaints were received relating to the length of time investigations were taking in the office of the Service Complaint Ombudsman in each quarter from March 2017 to 30 September 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208857","208857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041766","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the fall in smoking rates continues.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208858","208858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041767","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his letter of 15 January 2019 in relation to Question 196768 and with reference to the 122 cases currently unallocated within Service Complaints Ombudsman's office, what plans he has to increase the resources available to that office; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208859","208859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041768","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the minutes and notes of meetings between his officials and Healthcare Environmental Services.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208939","208939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041769","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his letter of 15 January 2019 in relation to Question 196768, what (a) the average number of applications made for vacant full-time investigator posts was and (b) the average length of time from a post being advertised and an appointment made was in the office of the Service Complaints Ombudsman from 31 March 2017 to 30 September 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208860","208860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041770","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what correspondence his Department has had with organisations on Healthcare Environmental Services in the last year.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208940","208940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041771","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, (a) what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the administration of round five of the coastal communities fund for England, (b) if he will publish the names of those winning bids for that fund, (c) how many complaints he has had about the administration of that fund and (d) how many requests he has had to halt the distribution of those funds.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208795","208795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041773","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to assess the number of eligible applicants who do not complete their application for universal credit.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208942","208942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041774","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to review the option of introducing a post-study work visa allowing up to two years of work experience for international students in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208943","208943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041775","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the current system of credibility interviews within the student immigration system is (a) cost-effective relative to current risk and (b) does not hinder universities’ ability to recruit a diverse range of students.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208944","208944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041776","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the number of international students choosing to study in the UK grows over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208945","208945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041777","2019-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many licences to shoot protected wild bird species were issued in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208946","208946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041778","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the siblings of children with life threatening and terminal conditions are identified as young carers.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208947","208947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041779","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding the Government provides to support the siblings of children with palliative care needs who meet the definition of being young carers.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208948","208948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041780","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department provides to primary schools seeking to achieve the goals set out for the PE and Sports Premium who wish to use that premium to buy equipment.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208949","208949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041781","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will extend the remit of the Rail Ombudsman to include oversight of train ticket selling platforms which are not operated by train operating companies.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208950","208950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041782","2019-01-17","Prime Minister","2019-01-15","To ask the Prime Minister, what estimate she has made of the total emissions created by her flights to Brussels since 1 October 2018.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208951","208951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041783","2019-01-21","Prime Minister","2019-01-15","To ask the Prime Minister, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of air travel by the Prime Minister to Brussels since (a)1 October 2018 and (b) 11 December 2018.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208952","208952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041784","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for how long lane closures will be in place on the M180 east of Scunthorpe; for what reason those lane closures have been introduced; and why work is not being carried out on a 24-hour basis to reduce the length of lane closures.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208796","208796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041785","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the risk of Newcastle disease in the UK; what advice he is giving to reduce such a risk; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208954","208954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041243","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the British Red Cross report entitled Still an ordeal: the move-on period for new refugees published in December 2018, if he will increase the period in which refugees continue to receive asylum support after receiving a positive decision on their asylum application to 56 days.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208296","208296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041244","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many judicial reviews there were of negative conclusive grounds decisions made by UK Visas and Immigration in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208232","208232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041245","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many judicial reviews of negative conclusive grounds decisions made by UK Visas and Immigration led to positive conclusive grounds decisions being made for the same claimant in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208233","208233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041246","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests for reconsideration there were of negative conclusive grounds decisions made by UK Visas and Immigration in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208234","208234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041247","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests for reconsideration of negative conclusive grounds decisions made by UK Visas and Immigration led to positive grounds decisions in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208235","208235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041248","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department's plans to ensure the supply of medicines in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal (a) have been or (b) will be subjected to an independent evaluation.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208297","208297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041249","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish (a) a list of medicines for which there is a supply risk in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal and (b) a plan to mitigate those supply risks.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208298","208298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041250","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding has been provided to the London Borough of Redbridge to tackle potholes in each year since 2010; and how that funding compares with the average funding allocated in each year to local authorities in (a) Greater London and (b) England.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208299","208299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041251","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Neighbourhood Plan (General) Regulations 2012, what the average time is between submitting an application for designation of a neighbourhood area and the decision on a plan proposal.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208236","208236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041252","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle the increase in demand for children's social care in (a) London and (b) England.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208300","208300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041253","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for British foreign policy of the decision of President Bashir of Sudan decision to meet with President Bashar al-Assad.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208185","208185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041254","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the midwife headcount in the NHS was in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and of those figures how many had (a) a recorded nationality and (b) a recorded nationality that was of an EU member state other than the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208301","208301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041255","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the age profile is of NHS midwives identified as nationals of an EU member state other than the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208302","208302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041256","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether it is his policy to encourage NHS employers to reimburse the £65 application fee for staff who need to apply to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208303","208303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041257","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to reach a final conclusion on the effect on veterans' health of the issuing of Larium to them while they were in the Armed Forces.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208186","208186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041258","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) service personnel and (b) veterans his Department has referred to the Mefloquine Single Point of Contact in each year since it’s inception.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208187","208187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041259","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the £20.5 billion of investment announced in the NHS Long Term Plan will be allocated to clinics dedicated to the treatment of problem gambling.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208214","208214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041260","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help employers to ensure that apprenticeships provide an effective route into permanent employment for adults diagnosed with autism.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208304","208304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041261","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the supported internships scheme in helping young people diagnosed with autism achieve sustainable paid employment.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208305","208305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041262","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the risks of smart home and internet-connected devices being used to enable domestic violence.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208306","208306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041263","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to prevent the misuse of smart home and internet-connected devices to enable domestic violence.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208307","208307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041264","2019-01-16","Wales Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 4 January 2018 to Question 205241, what discussions he has had Bangor University on the proposed closure of its chemistry department; and if he will he make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208237","208237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041265","2019-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department plans to provide to Kurdish groups in Syria after the withdrawal of US troops.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208198","208198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041266","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison staff have been deployed as part of the 10 Prisons Programme from other areas of the prison estate; and if he will list those numbers of staff by prison they have been deployed from.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208308","208308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041267","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the criteria were for selecting the 10 prisons to be included in the 10 Prison Programme.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208309","208309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041268","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has plans to provide transitional protection to people that will naturally migrate to universal credit as a result of a change in circumstances.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208310","208310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041269","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has to amend the Universal Credit (Managed Migration) Regulations 2018 after the conclusion of the 2019 test pilot.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208311","208311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041270","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will (a) list the prisons that were considered for but not included in the 10 Prisons Programme and (b) set out the reasons why those prisons were not included.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208312","208312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041271","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Autumn Budget 2018, whether the Department has plans to bring forward the two week run-on of legacy benefits for the universal credit managed migration pilot.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208313","208313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041272","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the announcement entitled, National operation to retest manipulated forensic samples continues, published by the National Police Chiefs' Council in December 2018, for which company does the independent expert employed to analyse the retest results work.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208314","208314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041273","2019-01-16","Department for International Trade","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which nations that have trade agreements with the EU have agreed to continue those agreements with the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208238","208238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041274","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria her Department will use to select the 10,000 people for managed migration test phase.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208315","208315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041275","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what dates he has held meetings with his European counterparts on the UK's continued partnership with the EU on cyber-related matters in the event the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208424","208424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041276","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she plans to take to ensure that the 10,000 people selected for the universal credit managed migration test phase will not be worse off as a result of participation in that test phase.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208316","208316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041277","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of air pollution on the (a) short-term and (b) long-term of (i) public health and (ii) the level of non-communicable disease mortality.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208317","208317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041278","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of air pollution in (a) the UK, (b) London and (c) Lewisham West & Penge constituency.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208318","208318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041279","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of air pollution in (a) the UK (b) London and (c) Lewisham West & Penge constituency.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208319","208319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041280","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department provides to local authorities to improve air quality.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208320","208320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041281","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of of the potential merits of introducing traffic exclusion zones near (a) schools, (b) nurseries and (c) playgrounds to help reduce children’s exposure to exhaust fumes.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208321","208321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041282","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing targets for the reduction of air pollution.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208322","208322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041283","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her oral answer of 7 January 2019 to Question 908384, Official Report, column 3, if she will published the updated guidance on real-time support for universal credit.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208425","208425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041284","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many armed forces veterans were in prison on 25 December 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208323","208323"
