"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423972","2015-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to provide financial support to help children under the age of three who are eligible for a disabled parking badge but are not eligible for the mobility component of the disability living allowance.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13360","13360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423973","2015-10-29","Cabinet Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the National Security Council has discussed the implications for national security of the recently announced closures of steel plants.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13441","13441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423974","2015-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2015 to Question 9704, whether current staffing levels for (a) torture prevention and (b) death penalty projects will be maintained in 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13269","13269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423975","2015-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2015 to Question 9704, whether his Department plans to renew its 2011 to 2015 Strategy for the Prevention of Torture.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13270","13270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423976","2015-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2015 to Question 9704, whether current funding levels for (a) torture prevention and (b) death penalty projects will be maintained in 2015-16 under his Department's Human Rights and Democracy Programme.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13278","13278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423977","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what payments were made to the devolved administrations under the terms of the 2014 Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme in each quarter of (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13351","13351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423978","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has received each quarter in rebate payments under the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme; and what estimate his Department has made of receipts for the remainder of that scheme.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13352","13352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423979","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2015 to Question 11101, on what dates his Department plans to begin and end its consultation on its mandate to NHS England.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13394","13394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423980","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2015 to Question 10736, on autism diagnosis waiting times, what plans his Department has in place to centrally collect clinical commissioning group waiting times data.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13468","13468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423981","2015-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department is doing to ensure that brownfield land which may have been used by heavy industry is cleaned and prepared for house building in (a) Bolton West constituency and (b) England and Wales.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13275","13275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423982","2015-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department provides to local authorities seeking a devolution deal.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13264","13264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423983","2015-10-28","HM Treasury","2015-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many full-time equivalent staff in the Tax Credit Office were allocated to deal with representations from hon. Members relating to constituents' concerns about tax credits on 1 October (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013, (d) 2014 and (e) 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13346","13346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423984","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices there were in the technology sector in (a) the UK, (b) the South East and (c) Windsor constituency in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13386","13386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423985","2015-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of homes in Windsor constituency have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13384","13384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423986","2015-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many households in the UK have been fitted with satellite broadband as part of the Government's broadband rollout.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13385","13385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423987","2015-10-29","Home Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of incidents in which tasers were used by the police in London in each of the last five years resulted in (a) an arrest, (b) a charge and (c) a conviction.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13288","13288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423988","2015-10-29","Home Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of people on whom the police used tasers were (a) BAME, (b) women and (c) under the age of 18 in each London borough in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13287","13287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423989","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers there were in London on 1 October (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13473","13473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423990","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers in London were contracted to work night shifts as at 1 October (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13474","13474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423991","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers were working night shifts in London on each day of September 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13475","13475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423992","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what definition his Department plans to use of large and small employers in relation to qualification for the apprenticeships levy.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13294","13294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423993","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how his Department plans to apply the apprenticeships levy in Wales.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13293","13293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423994","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether it is his policy that the apprenticeship levy will apply to labour-only subcontractors.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13335","13335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423995","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how he intends that small employers will access funding for apprenticeships.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13336","13336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423996","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he intends that the apprenticeships levy will replace the one-third contributions for post-19 apprenticeships as part of the Richard Review reforms.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13337","13337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423997","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether it is his policy that employers who pay the CITB levy will also have to pay the apprenticeships levy.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13338","13338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423998","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether it is his policy that employers will have to pay the apprenticeships levy if they do not take on apprentices.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13339","13339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423999","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much of the proposed apprenticeships levy employers will be able to claim back through the e-voucher.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13340","13340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424000","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the apprenticeships levy rate will be.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13341","13341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424001","2015-10-30","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will give consideration to introducing the testing of (a) night-time and (b) motorway driving as mandatory components of the driving test.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13459","13459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424002","2015-10-28","Department for International Development","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has contributed to the Global Fund to Fight AIDS, TB and Malaria (a) since the creation of that fund and (b) in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13371","13371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424003","2015-10-28","Department for International Development","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect that climate change is having on (a) clean water and (b) adequate sanitation facilities in developing countries.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13369","13369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424004","2015-10-28","Department for International Development","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department plans to contribute to the Global Fund in financial years (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13370","13370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424005","2015-10-28","Home Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pregnant women are detained at Yarl's Wood.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13393","13393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424006","2015-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will suspend the sale of arms to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13490","13490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424007","2015-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to encourage Saudi Arabia to destroy its stock of cluster munitions.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13390","13390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424008","2015-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his international counterpart the possibility of setting up a judicial mechanism to independently and impartially investigate reports of violations of international humanitarian law in Yemen.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13389","13389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424009","2015-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the provisions in Clauses 13 and 14 of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill on the welfare of cancer patients.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13392","13392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424010","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on the implementation of the Choice Review.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13391","13391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424011","2015-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many 19 to 24 year olds who already had a Level 3 qualification on the regulated qualifications framework started a Level 2 apprenticeship framework in 2013-14.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13494","13494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424012","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to appoint the consultant for the London and South Coast rail corridor study.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13495","13495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424013","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the London and South Coast rail corridor study to be published.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13496","13496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424014","2015-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department is providing to local authorities to meet localised demand for parking spaces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13430","13430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424015","2015-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has carried out of the adequacy of parking capacity across local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13427","13427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424016","2015-10-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment her Department has made of the ability of the UK solar industry to meet service demand; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13428","13428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424017","2015-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many sites are approved for fracking in England and Wales; what the location is of each such site; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13387","13387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424018","2015-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment her Department has made of the role of fracking in meeting the future energy needs of the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13368","13368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424019","2015-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2015 to Question 12252, what plans his Department has to increase the nutritional content of meals served to the prison population.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13376","13376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424020","2015-10-28","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2015 to Question 12620, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the level of public subsidy for train operators in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13388","13388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424021","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has carried out of the ability of road infrastructure to meet future demand; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13429","13429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424022","2015-10-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which events held by his Department were sponsored by Raytheon in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13456","13456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424023","2015-10-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what hospitality was provided to (a) Ministers and officials of his Department and (b) members of the armed forces by Raytheon in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13457","13457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424024","2015-10-29","HM Treasury","2015-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many former members of each branch of the armed forces are in receipt of (a) child and (b) working tax credits.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13458","13458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424025","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2015 to Question 12539, whether the meeting of the Board Investment and Commercial Committee on 23 March 2015 was attended by (a) Ministers in his Department, (b) special advisers in his Department and (c) officials in the Senior Civil Service grades.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13283","13283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424026","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2015 to Question 12538, and with reference to the statement in the Answer of 21 September 2015 to Question 10029 that Ely to Soham track doubling was among a small number of schemes that had been paused by Network Rail, which other schemes were paused by Network Rail.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13286","13286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424027","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2015 to Question 12213, whether his Department has imposed any penalties on bus operators who submitted ineligible claims for Bus Service Operators Grant support for closed school bus services.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13282","13282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424028","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when Network Rail first informed his Department of their estimate that electrification of the Great Western Main Line would cost more than £2 billion.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13431","13431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424029","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's expenditure on the Bus Service Operators Grant (BSOG) was in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15; and what his Department's projected expenditure on the BSOG is in 2015-16.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13432","13432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424030","2015-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to increase the use of CCTV in slaughterhouses; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13486","13486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424031","2015-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of UK slaughterhouses were inspected in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13317","13317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424032","2015-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the opinion of the Farm Animal Welfare Committee on CCTV in slaughterhouses, published in February 2015.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13316","13316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424033","2015-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Government made during recent discussions with the Chinese Prime Minister in agreeing a timetable for closing legal ivory markets at international and domestic levels.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13289","13289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424034","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, at what level tolls at the Severn Bridge will be set from January 2016.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13472","13472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424035","2015-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his oral contribution of 20 October 2015, Official Report, column 813, what discussions he has had with ministers in the Turkish government on ensuring that freedom of the press is upheld in that country as it relates to citizens of any country.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13331","13331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424036","2015-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average time taken to secure appeal hearings for people whose entry clearance applications have been refused.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13298","13298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424037","2015-10-29","Scotland Office","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent representations he has received on measures to rehabilitate land which has been defaced by opencast mining; and what steps he plans to take in response to those representations.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13439","13439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424216","2015-10-29","HM Treasury","2015-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers in the Scottish Government on the transfer of responsibility for Air Passenger Duty to the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901868","901868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424678","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the railway is able to accommodate the transport of full-sized lorry trailers on trains.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901885","901885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424757","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to minimise the extent and length of road works on the motorway network at times when work is not taking place.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901880","901880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424758","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on publishing a cycling and walking investment strategy.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901882","901882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424759","2015-10-29","Department for Transport","2015-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's policies on increasing access to public transport for disabled passengers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901881","901881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423502","2015-10-27","Attorney General","2015-10-23","To ask the Attorney General, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials in the Law Officers' Departments in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13168","13168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423503","2015-10-28","Attorney General","2015-10-23","To ask the Attorney General, what discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues in the Cabinet Office on the removal from the Ministerial Code of a reference to Ministers having a duty to comply with the law including international law and treaty obligations and to uphold the administration of justice.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13253","13253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423504","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) funding his Department is undertaking and (b) projects his Department has planned as part of the Government's Digital Inclusion Strategy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13243","13243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423505","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13158","13158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423506","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential economic value of the UK having an address file that was published as open data.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13140","13140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423507","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects the Land Registry to publish data on which foreign companies own which land property titles in England and Wales.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13201","13201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423508","2015-10-28","HM Treasury","2015-10-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the practice of insurers automatically signing up customers to annual renewals without the explicit consent of those policy holders.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13204","13204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423509","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what comparative assessment he has made of the level of patents granted in the UK with other (a) EU, (b) OECD and (c) developed economies in each of the last three years for which data is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13205","13205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423510","2015-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the level of staff turnover was in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's digital team in each of the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13207","13207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423511","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government has taken to promote research into sustainable aviation fuels and advanced fuels technologies.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13231","13231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423512","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much and what proportion of development land with planning consent is controlled by central government departments.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13197","13197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423513","2015-10-27","Cabinet Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which psychiatric disorder had the highest mortality rate in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13183","13183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423514","2015-10-27","Cabinet Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the One Public Estate programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13191","13191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423515","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much and what proportion of brownfield land is controlled by central government departments.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13195","13195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423516","2015-10-27","Cabinet Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of his Office in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13159","13159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423517","2015-10-28","Cabinet Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) funding his Department is undertaking and (b) projects his Department has planned as part of the Government's Digital Inclusion Strategy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13244","13244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423518","2015-10-27","HM Treasury","2015-10-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will issue an updated National Asset Register.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13193","13193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423519","2015-10-27","HM Treasury","2015-10-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to bring forward legislation for a city tax on tourists and other visitors.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13182","13182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423520","2015-10-27","HM Treasury","2015-10-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13239","13239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423521","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential cumulative financial effecr by 2021 on the twelve local authorities in the North East of the Government's proposal to localise business rates.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13234","13234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423522","2015-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the level of staff turnover was in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's digital team in each of the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13208","13208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423523","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of properties required to meet housing demand in Leeds City Region for the next (a) five years and (b) 15 years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13220","13220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423524","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to compel the housing associations who voted against an extension of the Right to Buy discount in the National Housing Federation ballot on 2 October 2015 to comply with that policy.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13153","13153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423525","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Community Right to Bid scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13194","13194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423526","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it is his policy that the Right to Buy extension for housing associations will apply to tenants whose properties were built exclusively with private finance.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13152","13152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423527","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of what proportion of the funding for the housing association Right to Buy policy will come from the new duty on local authorities to consider selling vacant high-value council homes, proposed in section 69 of the Housing and Planning Bill.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13151","13151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423528","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13160","13160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423529","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to make shared housing ownership schemes more accessible for buyers in (a) central London and (b) other areas with fast-rising house prices; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13154","13154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423530","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of new residential addresses have been created on brownfield sites since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13137","13137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423531","2015-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13161","13161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423532","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13162","13162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423533","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average response time was of Veterans UK to queries raised with them by veterans in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13169","13169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423534","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what preparations his Department has made for (a) upcoming changes in EU legislation regarding the chemical PFOA and (b) the technical effect of that legislation on the performance of camouflage print on the Army's multi-terrain pattern uniforms and ensemble.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13174","13174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423535","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy (a) officers and (b) rating recruits of each branch, specialisation and arm joined from foreign navies in each financial year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13188","13188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423536","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of Royal Navy (a) officers and (b) ratings in each branch, specialisation and arm were unavailable to be deployed in each year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13189","13189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423537","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel of each (a) rank and (b) branch, specialisation and arm left the Royal Navy in the first (a) three months, (b) three to six months, (c) six to nine months and (d) nine to 12 months of their service in each year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13186","13186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423538","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library copies of the Naval Service Operational Pinch Point Groups for (a) each quarter of each financial year from 2005-06 to 2014-15 and (b) the first two quarters of 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13187","13187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423539","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the Royal Navy's (a) branches, (b) specialisations and (c) sub-specialisations.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13190","13190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423540","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy recruits in each (a) rank and (b) branch specialisation and arm were (a) trained re-entrants, (b) partially trained re-entrants and (c) untrained re-entrants in each financial year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13192","13192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423541","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Royal Navy's (a) liability, (b) trained strength and (c) untrained strength for each (i) rank and (ii) branch specialisation and arm was in each financial year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13196","13196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423542","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of Royal Navy (a) officers and (b) ratings of each branch specialisation and arm were classified as non-deployable in each year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13198","13198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423543","2015-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on resolving the dispute between the Commonwealth War Graves Commission and its employees on that body's pension scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13202","13202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423544","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether celestial navigation forms part of the Royal Navy's phase one training.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13199","13199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423545","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the expected personnel (a) inflow and (b) outflow in each (i) rank and (ii) branch specialisation and arm in the Royal Navy over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13200","13200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423546","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total additional cost was of the net 52-month deferment of the final stage of the Core Production Capability Project.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13235","13235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423547","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of Army (a) officers and (b) regular soldiers are recruited from (i) Scotland, (ii) England and Wales and (iii) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13240","13240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423548","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will undertake a feasibility study on establishing a credit union open to British military personnel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13242","13242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423549","2015-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Ministers in his Department were made aware of the Mott Macdonald report 2012 submitted to his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13251","13251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423550","2015-10-27","Department for Education","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to promote STEM subjects and STEM career opportunities in schools.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13221","13221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423551","2015-10-27","Department for Education","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13163","13163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423552","2015-10-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13164","13164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423553","2015-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost to the public purse was of the solar industry feed-in tariff in (a) the UK and (b) London in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13211","13211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423554","2015-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to promote EU member states only sending animals to slaughterhouses which meet the standards set by the World Organisation for Animal Health.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13217","13217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423555","2015-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has established that there is a basis to permit fishing at levels higher than the limits set by the Common Fisheries Policy.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13175","13175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423556","2015-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of UK seas out to 200nm are designated as (a) Special Areas of Conservation and (b) Marine Conservation Zones.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13176","13176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423557","2015-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of progress on achieving an ecologically-coherent network of marine protected areas in UK seas.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13177","13177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423558","2015-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the number of assessed European fish stocks that are (a) fished at or below and (b) fished at higher than the maximum sustainable yield rate.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13178","13178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423559","2015-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is her Department's position in EU Council negotiations to develop Multi-Annual Fisheries Plans that ensure fishing limits do not exceed the maximum sustainable yield.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13179","13179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423560","2015-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13165","13165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423561","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will update the travel advice regarding the Punjab on his Department's website to advise travellers to give serious consideration to not travelling until the situation in that region stabilises.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13173","13173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423562","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13238","13238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423563","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Jammu and Kashmir.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13222","13222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423564","2015-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues in the Cabinet Office on the removal from the Ministerial Code of a reference to Ministers having a duty to comply with the law including international law and treaty obligations and to uphold the administration of justice.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13252","13252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423565","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what new performance target for Trusts and Foundation Trusts has been introduced since May 2010; and which new performance targets he plans to introduce for those bodies over the next five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13250","13250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423566","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to maintain ringfencing for total NHS funding in the Autumn Statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13249","13249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423567","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the decision to remove treatments for multiple myeloma from the Cancer Drugs Fund list on survival rates for patients with that condition.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13223","13223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423568","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to reform NICE to ensure that patient access to cancer treatments is guaranteed after the Cancer Drugs Fund is discontinued in April 2016.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13224","13224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423569","2015-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of the independent living fund in each of the last five years had a diagnosed mental health condition.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13213","13213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423570","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places in the Improving Access to Psychological Therapies service there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13214","13214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423571","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training GPs receive on eating disorders.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13215","13215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423572","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Improving Access to Psychological Therapies Training service places were commissioned in 2014-15.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13216","13216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423573","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13237","13237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423574","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings of the report, A Charge on Caring?, published by the Carers Trust in September 2015, on the level of compliance by councils with their duty under the Care Act 2014 to prevent carers developing a need for support.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13247","13247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423575","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the funding distributed by NHS England to improve eating disorder services has been spent; and what that funding has been spent on.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13212","13212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423576","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to address the availability of healthy and nutritious food for children during school holidays as part of its new obesity strategy.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13219","13219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423577","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that patients with multiple myeloma have access to extending medicines after treatments for that condition are removed from the Cancer Drugs Fund in November 2015.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13232","13232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423578","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that funding is available for treatments for multiple myeloma after the removal of treatments for that condition from the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13233","13233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423579","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library the minutes of each Public Health England board meeting in 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13156","13156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423580","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue a response to the report by the National Cancer Action Team, Lymphoedema Services in England: A Case for Change, published in March 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13149","13149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423581","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the introduction of the waiting time standards for eating disorder services by 2020.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13185","13185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423582","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Prescribed Specialist Services Advisory Group has made on discussions on proposals for a nationally-commissioned specialist lymphology service.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13148","13148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423583","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of support provided by the third sector in supporting people with eating disorders.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13184","13184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423584","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of Clinical Commissioning Groups (CCGs) commission services are for the treatment and care of lymphoedema patients; and what guidance has been issued to CCGs on the commissioning of those services.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13150","13150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423585","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of the delivery agreement and agreed deliverables between his Department and the Chartered Institute for Trading Standards.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13135","13135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423586","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a clause into the conditions relating to grants made by his Department to third parties to ensure that they are not used to fund activities intended to influence (a) parliament, government or political parties, (b) the awarding or renewal of Government contracts and grants and (c) legislative or regulatory action.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13136","13136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423587","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission a study of the prevalence of births of children damaged as a result of alcohol consumed by their mothers during pregnancy.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13138","13138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423588","2015-10-28","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of adults with brain damage caused by alcohol consumed by their mothers during pregnancy; and what assessment he has made of the level of awareness of health and other care professionals of the disability, and the consequences of that disability, which result from that activity.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13139","13139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423589","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing discount travel fares for all nurses registered with the Nursing and Midwifery Council.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13144","13144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423590","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings (a) he, (b) his officials and (c) the Minister for Public Health have had with representatives of (i) the Food and Drink Federation and (ii) companies producing food and drink in each month since January 2014; and what the agenda of each such meeting was.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13155","13155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423591","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions the Minister for Public Health has had with the Chief Executive of Public Health England in each month since January 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13157","13157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423592","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, over what period NHS England plans to run Winter Daily Situation Reports during the winter of 2015; over what period NHS England ran those reports in the past; by what process NHS England decides on the time period over which to run additional winter monitoring; and what guidance his Department issues to NHS England on the time period over which to run that monitoring.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13146","13146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423593","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many individual requests for cancer medicines have been made to the Cancer Drugs Fund in Bolton West constituency; how many patients received funding as a result of those requests; and how much the Cancer Drugs Fund allocated in respect of those patients.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13171","13171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423594","2015-10-27","Home Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have had their British citizenship removed under (a) section 40, Subsection 4A of the British Nationality Act 1981 since 27 July 2014 and (b) section 40, subsection (i) 2 and (ii) 3 of the British Nationality Act 1981 in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13147","13147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423595","2015-10-27","Home Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of times a removal direction was issued for people applying to remain in the UK while they were awaiting a court hearing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13172","13172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423596","2015-10-27","Home Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to arrange for a review of the operation of her powers under Section 40, Subsection 4A of the British Nationality Act 1981.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13145","13145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423597","2015-10-28","Home Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many former unaccompanied asylum-seeking children were removed to (a) Afghanistan, (b) Syria, (c) Libya, (d) Iraq, (e) Iran and (f) Albania in each year between 2007 and 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13206","13206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423598","2015-10-28","Home Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in (a) the UK and (b) London have gained dual citizenship (i) in total and (ii) with citizenship of each EU member state in each year from 2010 to 2015 to date.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13210","13210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423599","2015-10-28","Home Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times tasers have been used by the police in each London borough in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13248","13248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423600","2015-10-27","Home Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13236","13236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423601","2015-10-28","Home Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the level of staff turnover was in (a) her Department and (b) her Department's digital team in each of the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13209","13209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423602","2015-10-28","Home Office","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of each type of hate crime were recorded on public transport in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13254","13254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423603","2015-10-27","House of Commons Commission","2015-10-23","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, when the Commission plans to publish the list of Roll A Parliamentary Agents for the current Parliament.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13181","13181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423604","2015-10-27","House of Commons Commission","2015-10-23","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will review the right of access for the City of London Remembrancer to the Chamber of the House.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13180","13180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423605","2015-10-28","Department for International Development","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department takes to monitor how aid disbursed by the UK to the Palestinian Territories is used.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13203","13203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423606","2015-10-27","Department for International Development","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made on establishing a renewable power facility in Pitcairn Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13241","13241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423607","2015-10-27","Department for International Development","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13166","13166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423608","2015-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was paid in (a) year end and (b) in-year bonuses to officials of his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13167","13167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423609","2015-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) funding his Department is undertaking and (b) projects his Department has planned as part of the Government's Digital Inclusion Strategy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13245","13245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423610","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress the Highways Agency has made on noise mitigation measures on the M5 at Upton St. Leonards.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13170","13170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423611","2015-10-28","Department for Transport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the safety of civilian flights at RAF Northolt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13141","13141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423612","2015-10-28","Department for Transport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had on safety at RAF Northolt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13142","13142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423613","2015-10-28","Department for Transport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Civil Aviation Authority is exercising its duty to ensure the safety of civilian aircraft at RAF Northolt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13143","13143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423614","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of including producers of aviation fuel in the Renewable Transport Fuels Obligation.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13225","13225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423615","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to promote the development of sustainable aviation fuels in the UK.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13226","13226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423616","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support research into new aircraft and engine technologies to reduce noise emissions from aviation.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13227","13227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423617","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has conducted or commissioned on (a) how noise emissions from aviation affect local communities and (b) the effectiveness of different noise mitigation approaches in reducing the number of people affected by aircraft noise.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13228","13228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423618","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential for aviation emissions to be reduced through improved air traffic management.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13229","13229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423619","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to support the development and deployment of new aircraft and engine technologies in order to reduce emissions from aviation.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13230","13230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423620","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of the delays in state pension payments to British citizens living abroad.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13218","13218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423621","2015-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) funding his Department is undertaking and (b) projects his Department has planned as part of the Government's Digital Inclusion Strategy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13246","13246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423208","2015-10-26","Attorney General","2015-10-22","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 11678, how many prosecutions for trafficking offences linked to County Lines investigations there have been in cases where a child under the age of 18 was trafficked to another area to distribute drugs; and what the outcomes were of each such prosecution.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13035","13035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423209","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support small businesses in (a) West Yorkshire and (b) Yorkshire & Humber.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13037","13037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423210","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on granting Market Economy Status to China under World Trade Organisation rules.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13061","13061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423211","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many small businesses were registered in Dartford in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13065","13065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423212","2015-10-26","Cabinet Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people declared themselves as self-employed in each of the last three years in (a) Dartford and (b) Kent.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13066","13066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423213","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of efficiency savings arising from his Department's digital strategies in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13087","13087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423214","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the funds generated through the proposed apprenticeship levy which will be required for its administration costs.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13091","13091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423215","2015-10-27","Women and Equalities","2015-10-22","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what plans her Department has to close the gender pay gap.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13095","13095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423216","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research his Department has commissioned or undertaken to assess the potential effect on small businesses of proposed changes to Sunday trading laws.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13098","13098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423217","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials in his Department are working on the review of post-16 education and training institutions.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13131","13131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423218","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the timetable setting out when each area will have its post-16 education and training reviewed.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13133","13133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423219","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether hon. Members are always informed when a post-16 area-based review is announced for an area which includes their constituency.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12976","12976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423220","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of TTIP on different and separate regulatory systems for compliance with current ISDS provisions in different parts of the UK.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12972","12972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423221","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how long the process of undertaking a post-16 area-based review will take in each area for which they are planned or already underway.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12978","12978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423222","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the possible savings to his Department of the outcome of post-16 area-based reviews.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12979","12979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423223","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether an (a) free school, (b) academy, (c) school sixth form and (d) university technical college will be allowed to open while a post-16 area-based review is still taking place.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12977","12977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423224","2015-10-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects to begin the Government's consultation on a statutory pubs code.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12987","12987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423225","2015-10-27","Cabinet Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons the minutes of the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments have not been published since February 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13108","13108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423226","2015-10-27","Cabinet Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Special Advisors Remuneration Committee last met.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13086","13086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423227","2015-10-27","Cabinet Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government Digital Service plans to publish its business plan for 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13089","13089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423228","2015-10-27","Cabinet Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of efficiency savings arising from cross-departmental digital strategies in 2014-15.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13088","13088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423229","2015-10-26","Cabinet Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths in (a) Pendle, (b) the North West and (c) England have been caused as a result of people taking legal highs in each of the past three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13057","13057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423230","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK economy of Greece leaving the Eurozone.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13038","13038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423231","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on consumers of the practice of insurers in signing customers up to automatic policy renewals without the option to opt-out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13003","13003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423232","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on competition in the private motor insurance market of automatic policy renewals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13004","13004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423233","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Government's proposed changes to business rates on (a) Liverpool Walton constituency, (b) Liverpool City Council, (c) the North West and (d) the Liverpool City Region Combined Authority area.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13094","13094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423234","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has spent to date on legal fees in respect of the case against the Aggregates Levy brought by the British Aggregates Association.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13069","13069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423235","2015-10-27","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy in the forthcoming Comprehensive Spending Review to provide ring fenced funding for a feasibility study into the trunk road section of the A595.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13100","13100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423236","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many serving members of each branch of the armed forces are in receipt of (a) child and (b) working tax credits.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12998","12998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423237","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on consumers of the practice of insurers in not giving details of no claims bonuses to customers in their renewal notice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13001","13001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423238","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on consumers of the practice of insurers in automatically signing-up customers to annual policy renewals without their explicit consent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13002","13002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423239","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the average net benefit per household of the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12973","12973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423240","2015-10-27","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many official visits he has made to (a) Copeland constituency and (b) Cumbria as part of the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12937","12937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423241","2015-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of measures taken by local authorities in tackling loneliness; and what support the Government has provided for such measures.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12940","12940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423242","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what action the Government has taken to bring back into use long-term empty properties.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12960","12960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423243","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of properties required to meet housing demand in (a) England, (b) the North East and (c) Easington constituency in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12961","12961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423244","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding his Department has provided to renovate, repair and bring back into use long-term empty properties in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12962","12962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423245","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what investment in the road network the Government plans to make in (a) Copeland constituency and (b) Cumbria as part of the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13099","13099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423246","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new homes were built in Dartford constituency in 2014.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13067","13067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423247","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of empty properties in (a) England, (b) the North East and (c) Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13122","13122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423248","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the potential savings to local authorities of holding local council elections once every four years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13041","13041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423249","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made under what working assumptions of the potential cost of the holding of an election for a North East regional mayor.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13064","13064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423250","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made under what working assumptions of the cost and the salary and other elements of the remuneration package for the potential future position of regional mayor of the North East of England.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13062","13062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423251","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made under what working assumptions of the potential annual running costs for the office of a North East regional mayor.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13063","13063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423252","2015-10-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the planned date is for the roll-out of fibre broadband in (a) the Chryston area and (b) the constituency of Coatbridge, Chryston and Bellshill.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13006","13006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423253","2015-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the potential effects of changes in the Merseyside Police mounted division on that forces' capacity to police football matches at Anfield and Goodison Park.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13093","13093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423254","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy to procure 13 Type 26 frigates.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12944","12944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423255","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to make any further changes to the definition of defence expenditure in calculating the proportion of GDP spent on defence in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12949","12949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423256","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 45 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the increase in planned spending on submarines; and on what items that additional funding will be spent.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13112","13112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423257","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 53 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the increase in planned spending on the Weapons Programme; and on what items that additional funding will be spent.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13113","13113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423258","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 11 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the increase in centrally-held provision; and on what items that additional funding will be spent.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13111","13111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423259","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many serving members of each branch of the armed forces are in receipt of (a) child and (b) working tax credits.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12999","12999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423260","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 73 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the increase in planning spending on information systems and services; and on what items that additional funding will be spent.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12989","12989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423261","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 69 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the decrease in planned spending on ISTAR; and how that decrease will be achieved.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12990","12990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423262","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 65 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the decrease in planned spending on helicopter capabilities; and how that decrease will be achieved.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12991","12991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423263","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 61 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the decrease in planned spending in the air support sector; and how that decrease will be achieved.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12992","12992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423264","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 57 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the decrease in planned spending on the combat air sector; and how that decrease will be achieved.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12993","12993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423265","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 11 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the decrease in unallocated headroom; and how that decrease will be achieved.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12994","12994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423266","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 11 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the decrease in contingency provision; and how that decrease will be achieved.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12995","12995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423267","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 11 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the increase in spending on support for existing in-service equipment; and on what items that additional funding will be spent.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12996","12996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423268","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 11 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the increase in spending on support arrangements for new equipment; on what items that additional funding will be spent.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12997","12997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423269","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many locally-employed Afghan interpreters who worked alongside the British Army have (a) approached the Government for help and (b) been resettled in the UK under his Department's intimidation policy.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12975","12975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423270","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of unmanned drone missions flown over Syria in the last year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12980","12980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423271","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the report by the (a) Nuclear Propulsion Integrated Project Team and (b) Frazer Nash on plans to extend the time limit of restoration of Electrical Shore Supplies to nuclear powered submarines from 20 minutes up to a maximum of three hours.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13026","13026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423272","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has commissioned an Independent Nuclear Safety Assessment report on plans to extend the time limit of restoration of Electrical Shore Supplies to nuclear powered submarines from 20 minutes up to a maximum of three hours.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13025","13025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423273","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the required timescale is for the restoration of Electrical Shore Supplies with reference to the publication Safety Shutdown Procedure for Astute Class Vessels, published in 2012.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13024","13024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423274","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many locally employed Afghan interpreters who worked alongside the British Army have (a) approached the Government for help under the ex-gratia redundancy scheme and (b) been relocated to the UK under the ex-gratia redundancy scheme.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13116","13116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423275","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the first Type 26 frigate will be ready for service.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13123","13123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423276","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made by the UK and its Coalition Partners on disrupting the ability of ISIS to raise significant funds through oil revenues; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13125","13125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423277","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many full-time staff are based in the Kabul Intimidation Investigation Unit; and what the roles of those staff are.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13130","13130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423278","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons retired and out-of-date equipment, including FH70 howitzers and Jet Provost aircraft, were included in his Department's Defence in Numbers publication of August 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13128","13128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423279","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to maximise the role that UK suppliers can play in the development of the Type 26 programme.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13124","13124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423280","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with the Cypriot authorities about who has responsibility for the safety and wellbeing of refugees arriving at RAF Akrotiri.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13126","13126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423281","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to prepare a deal with further refugees arriving by sea at RAF Akrotiri.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13127","13127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423282","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with colleagues in other Departments about the national security implications of Chinese state involvement in the UK's domestic nuclear operations.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13129","13129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423283","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which pieces of equipment included in his Department's Defence in Numbers publication of August 2015 are used only for training or ceremonial use.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13007","13007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423284","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 41 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the increase in planned spending on surface ships; and on what items that additional funding will be spent.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13114","13114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423285","2015-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 49 of his Department's Defence Equipment Plan 2015, what the reasons are for the increase in planned spending on land equipment; and on what items that additional funding will be spent.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13115","13115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423286","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with Babcock on the proposal to extend the limit of restoration of Electrical Shore Supplies to nuclear powered submarines at HMNB Clyde from 20 minutes up to a maximum of three hours.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13019","13019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423287","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many former members of each branch of the armed forces are in receipt of (a) child and (b) working tax credits.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13031","13031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423288","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has instructed Babcock to extend the time a nuclear powered submarine can be without electrical power from 20 minutes up to a maximum of three hours.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13020","13020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423289","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the level of financial saving accruing to Babcock from the proposed extension of the time unit of the restoration of Electrical Shore Supplies from 20 minutes up to a maximum of three hours.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13023","13023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423290","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what analysis his Department has conducted of the effect on safety of the proposed extension of the restoration of Electrical Shore Supplies from 20 minutes up to a maximum of three hours.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13021","13021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423291","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the proposed extension of the time limit of restoration of Electrical Shore Supplies to nuclear powered submarines at HMNB Clyde from 20 minutes up to a maximum of three hours.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13022","13022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423292","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the Government plans to use the fines collected in Lancashire for parents taking their children out of school early in 2014-15.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13053","13053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423293","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the level of truancy was in Pendle in the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13054","13054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423294","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many parents were fined for taking children out of school early or for their children's truancy in Pendle in each of the past three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13055","13055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423295","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of the number of secondary school teachers accessing continuing professional development in design and technology in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13030","13030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423296","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2015 to Question 11372, how many local authorities have used her Department's eligibility checking system for free school meals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13032","13032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423297","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of the number of (a) academies, (b) free schools and (c) maintained schools which do not include design and technology on the school curriculum.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13029","13029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423298","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2015 to Question 11372, how many additional children are now in receipt of free school meals since the changes made to her Department's eligibility checking system.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13005","13005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423299","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many GCSEs were awarded for foreign language courses in Dartford constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13068","13068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423300","2015-10-27","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 12263, what estimate her Department has made of the number of Reception, Year 1 and Year 2 pupils who will qualify for free school meals in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12983","12983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423301","2015-10-27","Department for Education","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many officials in her Department are working on its review of post-16 education and training institutions.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12988","12988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423302","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when her Department last made an assessment of the carbon efficiency of heat pumps in obtaining their power from grid-supplied electricity.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12929","12929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423303","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential economic benefit of carbon capture and storage being used as a means to increase oil and gas production from the UK Continental Shelf.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12930","12930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423304","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of mandatory regulation to stimulate volumes of installations of heat pumps.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12931","12931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423305","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the impact of the reduction in the feed-in tariff rates proposed in the Government's consultation published on 27 August 2015 on the rooftop solar industry and solar installation companies in the South East region.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12974","12974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423306","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if her Department will take steps to investigate how the administrative governance of installation of renewable energy systems could be simplified.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12941","12941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423307","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many meetings her Department has had with Westinghouse officials to discuss the potential partnership between Westinghouse, interested nuclear industry partners and the Government on developing small modular nuclear reactors.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13011","13011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423308","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what response she has made to the proposal put forward on 21 October 2015 for a partnership between Westinghouse and the Government to develop small modular nuclear reactors.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13012","13012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423309","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the safety issues identified in the Generic Design Assessment for the European Pressurised Reactor that EDF Energy plans to build at Hinkley Point C have still not been resolved to the satisfaction of the Office for Nuclear Regulation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13014","13014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423310","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reasons the construction cost of the planned Hinkley Point C power station has reduced from £24.5 billion to £18 billion.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13015","13015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423311","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what date her Department commissioned a study of the technical and economic options for small modular nuclear reactors; which organisation her Department asked to carry this out; what departmental resources have been committed to support this study; and when the final report of that study is expected to be delivered.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13010","13010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423312","2015-10-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when her Department plans to publish its response to its consultation on feed-in tariffs.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13075","13075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423313","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on the administrative costs to consumers and businesses of regulations which govern household renewable energy systems and energy efficiency.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13060","13060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423314","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect of the Carbon Capture and Storage on achieving maximum economic recovery of oil and gas in the North Sea.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13059","13059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423315","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make an assessment of the (a) causes and (b) effect of the construction delays of reactors in China and France built by the proposed vendors of reactors planned for Hinkley Point C and Bradwell; and what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies on the construction of new nuclear power stations of these delays.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13044","13044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423316","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many visits her Departmental officials have made to China in support of the development of the Strategic Investment Agreement between EDF and China General Nuclear Corporation announced on 21 October 2015; how much each such visit cost; and if she will publish the minutes of each meeting held between UK and Chinese government officials on this agreement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13043","13043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423317","2015-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding her Department has made available for the maintenance of waterways in (a) Pendle, (b) the North West and (c) England in 2015-16.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13056","13056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423318","2015-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the contribution of the agricultural industry to total UK carbon dioxide emission levels in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13081","13081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423319","2015-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how frequently cattle in each region are tested for bovine TB.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12971","12971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423320","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of developments in the human rights situation in China since March 2015.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12932","12932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423321","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of freedom of religion or belief in Xinjiang Province.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12933","12933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423322","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has requested that the Chinese government discloses the number of executions taking place in China.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12934","12934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423323","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many prisoners of conscience in China have been visited by UK diplomatic staff during 2015.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12935","12935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423324","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Chinese government on that country's ratification of the International Covenant on civil and political rights.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12936","12936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423325","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has taken steps to ensure that contractors used by his Department do not instigate investigatory proceedings against staff for writing directly to him about their employment conditions or pay.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12951","12951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423326","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings he has had with cleaners working in his Department's premises to discuss payment of the living wage.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12948","12948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423327","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Minsk Agreement in reducing fighting in Ukraine.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12946","12946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423328","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library a copy of any letters or emails (a) sent to Interserve by his Department and (b) received by his Department from Interserve relating to a letter sent by cleaners working in his Department's premises to him regarding the living wage dated 21 July 2015.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12947","12947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423329","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his most recent assessment is of the political situation in Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12945","12945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423330","2015-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Saudi Arabian counterpart and other relevant stakeholders to ensure there is no further delay in the establishment of the UN Verification and Inspection Mechanism designed to increase the flow of commercial goods into Yemen.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12967","12967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423331","2015-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) whether the Saudi-led coalition warships off the Red Sea port of Hodeidah are continuing to prevent commercial vessels from docking and (b) the effect of continued restrictions to limit commercial and humanitarian supplies from entering Yemen on its people.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12968","12968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423332","2015-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that UK weapons are not used in strikes that constitute serious violations of human rights and of international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12965","12965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423333","2015-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance the Government plans to give to authorities in South Africa to help tackle high levels of crime in (a) rural and (b) other areas of that country.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13058","13058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423334","2015-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts about further expansion of the membership of the EU.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13039","13039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423335","2015-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the parties to the conflict in Yemen on their complying with obligations under international humanitarian law and on ending the use of explosive weapons with wide-area effects in populated areas.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12966","12966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423336","2015-10-27","Department for International Development","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which countries in the Middle East and North Africa her Department has assessed as able to provide safe refuge and access to essential services to refugees from Syria; and what estimate she has made of how many such refugees each of those countries could accommodate.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13071","13071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423337","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) the deaths of migrant construction workers engaged on building the infrastructure for the 2022 World Cup or (b) the kafala system of sponsoring migrant workers was raised by the Government during the Qatar-UK Sharaka bilateral dialogue in London on 15 October 2015.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13106","13106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423338","2015-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether contact was made between officials at the British Embassy in Brazil and the Brazilian government regarding the arrest of Ray Whelan in Rio de Janerio in July 2014; and whether the UK made any offers to assist the Brazilian authorities with their investigation into Mr Whelan.","Biography information for Damian Collins","Damian Collins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13107","13107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423339","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been referred to the About Health Group from practices in the North Tyneside Clinical Commissioning Group under the General Practitioners' Referral Management System.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13120","13120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423340","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients referred to the About Health Group from practices in the North Tyneside Clinical Commissioning Group under the General Practitioners' Referral Management System were subsequently refused treatment.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13121","13121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423341","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether addressing barriers to licensing off-patent, repurposed drugs in an aim of the current Accelerated Access Review.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13134","13134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423342","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the implementation of seven-day-a-week NHS services on the payment-by-results contracts in clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13028","13028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423343","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many in-patient NHS beds for mental health patients there were in Lancashire on 1st June (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015; and what the locations of beds were on each such date.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13101","13101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423344","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to encourage more people to join healthcare professions in rural areas experiencing difficulties with staff recruitment.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13027","13027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423345","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the North Tyneside Clinical Commissioning Group is a pilot under the General Practitioners' Referral Management System.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13117","13117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423346","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much is paid to the About Health Group for each patient referred by practices in the North Tyneside Clinical Commissioning Group under the General Practitioners' Referral Management System.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13118","13118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423347","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the provision by the NHS of free IVF to women whose partners have had immigration applications rejected.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13119","13119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423348","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the findings of the Carers Trust report published on 16 September 2015, Analysis of the UK and Impact of Charges by Councils Providing Support to Unpaid Carers; and if he will make an assessment of the effect of local authority charges on carers for the support they receive to help them in their caring role.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13008","13008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423349","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 12247, on breast cancer, what assessment his Department has made of the 26 recommendations produced by charities on access to off-patent, repurposed drugs following the roundtable event of February 2015.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13077","13077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423350","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Monitor plans to create a new maternity tariff for multiple pregnancies which more closely meets the costs associated with delivering the best practice care pathways outlined by NICE and the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13017","13017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423351","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2015 to Question 11322, on NHS training, for what reasons the materials were withdrawn from the Library.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13079","13079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423352","2015-10-26","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans for his Department's Innovation, Excellence and Strategic Development Fund to be used to support efforts to reduce still births and neonatal deaths in multiple pregnancies.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13018","13018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423353","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the diagnosis levels of inflammatory bowel diseases in England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12981","12981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423354","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of NHS treatment options for patients with inflammatory bowel diseases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12982","12982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423355","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many post-graduate training places were (a) commissioned and (b) filled for each of Health Education England's medical and dental foundation programme in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12985","12985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423356","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many members of staff his Department plans will be employed by each of his Department's three success regimes; and what the job titles and salary level will be of each member of such staff.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12984","12984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423357","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the healthcare chapter of the Armed Forces Covenant has been implemented.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12938","12938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423358","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital admissions occurred due to consumption of legal highs in (a) Copeland constituency, (b) Cumbria and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12939","12939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423359","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to monitor the cost to nursing homes of employing agency nurses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12950","12950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423360","2015-10-27","Department of Health","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to make bisphosphonates routinely available on the NHS to prevent the spread of breast cancer to bones.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12952","12952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423361","2015-10-27","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of fast-track passport applications made in the last six months have been processed within seven days.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12953","12953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423362","2015-10-27","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions did the National Crime Agency received notice of suspicion of terrorist financing from private sector institutions, under Part III of the Terrorism Act 2000, in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12956","12956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423363","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether estate agents who hold no client money fall under the scope of the Money Laundering Regulations 2007.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12970","12970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423364","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department holds on the number of police in different forces who are suspended or not on active duty as a result of investigations or complaint procedures.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12926","12926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423365","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the reasons for the recent reduction in the number of prosecutions for mobile telephone use while driving.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12927","12927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423366","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of calls received by Action Fraud have resulted in a police investigation to date; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12928","12928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423367","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to paragraph 49 of her Department's Counter-Extremism Strategy, published on 19 October 2015, if she will publish the terms of reference of the review on entryism and specify what resources have ben allocated to that review.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12969","12969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423368","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will set out the timetable for publishing the principles referred to in paragraph 97 of her Department's Counter-Extremism Strategy published on 19 October 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13033","13033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423369","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress is being made to facilitate the arrival of Syrian refugees to Northern Ireland under the vulnerable persons relocation scheme.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13036","13036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423370","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which non-governmental groups and individuals her Department consulted on its Counter-Extremism Strategy, published on 19 October 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13051","13051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423371","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she will Answer Question 11793 of 14 October 2015, on Home Office: staff.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13040","13040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423372","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects provisions in the Private Security Industry Act 2001 on private investigators to come into force; which individuals and organisations she has held discussions with on these powers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13034","13034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423373","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 46 of her Department's Counter-Extremism Strategy, published on 19 October 2015, how much funding her Department will make available for commissioning and funding research.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13049","13049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423374","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the criteria are for choosing the credible commentators referred to in paragraph 46 of her Department's Counter-Extremism Strategy, published on 19 October 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13050","13050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423375","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 88 of the Counter-Extremism Strategy, published on 19 October 2015, what support was given to the 700 individuals.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13045","13045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423376","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 117 of the Counter-Extremism Strategy, published on 19 October 2015, what the timescale is for introducing the Extremism Community Trigger.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13046","13046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423377","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what independent oversight arrangement has been established to monitor the Channel programme.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13047","13047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423378","2015-10-26","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide information on the (a) age, (b) race, (c) gender, (d) religion and (e) region of residence of the 700 individuals referred to in paragraph 88 of her Department's Counter-Extremism Strategy, published on 19 October 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13048","13048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423379","2015-10-27","Home Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2015 to Written Question 11808, who attended the first meeting of the Community Engagement Forum, on 13 October 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13090","13090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423380","2015-10-26","Department for International Development","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to assist Christian refugees in Syria who are being persecuted.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13013","13013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423381","2015-10-26","Department for International Development","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who represented the Government at the third International Conference on Financing for Development in Addis Ababa; and what steps the Government took to consult with NGOs, churches and other stakeholders on the UK's contribution in advance of that conference.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12943","12943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423382","2015-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what account was taken of the effect on access to justice in rural areas in his Department's consultation on the Provision of the Court and Tribunal Estate.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12963","12963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423383","2015-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many private family law cases there were in the (a) Gwent and (b) Wales civil and family tribunals cluster between April 2013 and April 2014; and in how many such cases both parties had legal representation.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12954","12954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423384","2015-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to support suicidal and vulnerable inmates in (a) HMP Liverpool and (b) HMP Altcourse.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12986","12986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423385","2015-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to re-open court room provision in (a) Todmorden and (b) other rural areas.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12964","12964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423386","2015-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department conducted an (a) impact assessment and (b) internal review of the effect of the transfer of responsibility for freedom of information to the Cabinet Office prior to that transfer.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13072","13072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423387","2015-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the overseas security and justice assistance guidance that was issued before the Government entered into the contract to provide training needs analysis to the Saudi penal system.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13078","13078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423388","2015-10-27","Cabinet Office","2015-10-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Ministerial Code updated in October 2015, what discussions he has had with the Cabinet Office on the removal from that code of reference to Ministers complying with international law, treaty obligations and upholding the administration of justice.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13073","13073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423389","2015-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the total cost to the public purse of his Department's proposed policies on (a) secure colleges, (b) the prisoners' book ban, (c) HMCTS privatisation and (d) Saudi prison contracts.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13074","13074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423390","2015-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, further to the Answer of 17 July 2013 to Question 163024, on Courts: Wales, what data his Department now centrally collates on litigants in person.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13082","13082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423391","2015-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to improve the (a) cleanliness, (b) degree of crowding and (c) safety of (i) prisoners and (ii) prison staff in HMP Liverpool.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13092","13092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423392","2015-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults on on-duty prison officers have occurred in (a) HM Prison Liverpool, (b) HM Prison Altcourse and (c) all other prisons in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13109","13109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423393","2015-10-27","House of Commons Commission","2015-10-22","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what progress has been made on confirming the final cost of the Options Appraisal Report into the refurbishment of the Palace of Westminster.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13110","13110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423394","2015-10-26","Prime Minister","2015-10-22","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 12154, for what reasons he did not refer to any legal basis in domestic law during (a) his oral statement of 4 September 2015, Official Report, column 23 and (b) the Answer of 14 September 2015 to Question 9571; and if he will describe the legal basis in domestic law used for the targeted killing of British citizens outside declared war zones; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13070","13070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423395","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential threat to national security of the choice of the Chinese government company General Nuclear International as an investment partner for the development of the Hinkley Point C nuclear plant.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13016","13016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423396","2015-10-26","Prime Minister","2015-10-22","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2015 to Question 8501, on the Wilson Doctrine, what responsibilities he has in relation to the operation of the Wilson Doctrine; what responsibilities the Home Secretary has in relation to that Doctrine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13009","13009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423397","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the transfer of Intercity 125 sets from the Great Western franchise to the Scotrail franchise in 2017-18 is conditional on Network Rail meeting its current regulated output targets on the Great Western Main Line electrification project.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13080","13080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423398","2015-10-26","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to respond to the letter from the Leader of Gateshead Council of 25 June 2015 on upgrading the A1 between the Birtley and Coal House interchanges.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13042","13042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423399","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October to Question 12230, if he will provide a breakdown by English region of the figures provided in the first table contained in that Answer under the headings (a) his Department's spend per head and (b) total spend per head.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13105","13105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423400","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 7 of his Department's publication, Bus Service Operators Grant (BSOG) Information pack and Conditions of Eligibility, how much his Department has spent on (a) the eight per cent ITSO smartcard BSOG supplement and (b) the two per cent Automatic Vehicle Location BSOG supplement in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15; and what his Department's projected expenditure is in 2015-16 on those items.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13102","13102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423401","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Chief Executive of Network Rail's letter to the Chair of the Public Accounts Committee of 19 October 2015, what the component cost headings of Network Rail's revised £2.5 billion to £2.8 billion cost estimate for Great Western Main Line electrification are.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13104","13104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423402","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 12187, which organisations were represented at the High Level Cycling Group's meeting on 13 July 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13103","13103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423403","2015-10-26","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the financial effect on consumers of the requirement for drivers to be insured at all times under the Road Safety Act 2006.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13000","13000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423404","2015-10-28","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans for the electrification of the Great Western Mainline to be completed.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12958","12958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423405","2015-10-28","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent by his Department on franchising negotiations since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12959","12959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423406","2015-10-28","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many complaints by passengers were received by Network Rail in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12957","12957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423407","2015-10-26","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans for the South East Flexible Ticketing scheme to be delivered.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12942","12942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423408","2015-10-27","Department for Transport","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the Severn bridges to return to public ownership.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12955","12955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423409","2015-10-27","Women and Equalities","2015-10-22","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether plans to amend the Civil Partnership Act to allow opposite sex partnerships.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13132","13132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423410","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to continue the Universal Jobmatch service after the contract expires in April 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13097","13097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423411","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of lessons from the experience of the Workforce Innovation and Opportunity Act in the US to inform his plans to replace the Work Programme when the current contracts come to an end.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13096","13096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423412","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of cases of complaints about gas safety are investigated by the HSE.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13085","13085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423413","2015-10-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what procedures his Department has in place to correct errors when benefits are paid into the wrong bank account.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13052","13052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423414","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what sanctions the HSE can place on companies breaching gas safety.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13083","13083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423415","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of complaints about gas safety to the HSE are (a) validated and (b) prosecuted.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13084","13084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/423416","2015-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of proposals for a lower benefit cap on carers.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13076","13076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424403","2015-10-28","Department for International Development","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the projects her Department funds which help disabled children access education in Kenya.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901844","901844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424404","2015-10-28","Department for International Development","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the progress of the economic recovery in Nepal since the recent earthquake in that country.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901847","901847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424405","2015-10-28","Department for International Development","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on her Department's work of re-allocating elements of her Department's budget to help local authorities deal with Syrian refugees.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901845","901845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424406","2015-10-28","Department for International Development","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress the Government is making on meeting the UK's international obligations to refugees fleeing Syria.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901850","901850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424407","2015-10-28","Department for International Development","2015-10-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any of her Department's spending will be counted towards the target of spending 2 per cent of gross national income on defence.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901843","901843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422837","2015-10-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the level of energy prices on the steel industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12722","12722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422838","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of whether insurers are increasing their premiums year on year due to the automatic renewal of policies without customers' explicit consent.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12727","12727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422839","2015-10-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships have been created under the Trailblazer scheme in the last nine months.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12763","12763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422840","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress he has made in implementing professor John Perkins' Review of Engineering Skills published by his Department in November 2013.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12911","12911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422841","2015-10-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage the European Commission to have measures approved to support UK steelmakers with their energy costs.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12870","12870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422842","2015-10-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations his Department has received about customers without internet access being charged to receive paper bills.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12871","12871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422843","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage employers in London to pay the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12895","12895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422844","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of students with a disability in higher education; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12896","12896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422845","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has reviewed the adequacy of financial support for students with disabilities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12897","12897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422846","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he took the decision not to provide funding to trainees to support the cost of gaining a large goods vehicle licence.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12925","12925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422847","2015-10-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the requirements are on places of public entertainment to have public liability insurance in place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12904","12904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422848","2015-10-23","Cabinet Office","2015-10-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-Party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014 on the activities of trades unions during the 2015 general election period.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin John Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12773","12773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422849","2015-10-23","Cabinet Office","2015-10-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-Party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014 on the activities of charitable bodies during the 2015 general election period.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin John Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12774","12774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422850","2015-10-23","Cabinet Office","2015-10-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress his Department has made on the Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12796","12796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422851","2015-10-23","Department of Health","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for NHS Productivity of 9 July 2015, Official Report, House of Lords, column 286, on proposals for an independent inquiry on the sustainability of the NHS, if he will take steps to ensure that any such inquiry (a) identifies possible consequential effects and (b) does not adversely affect the Scottish block grant.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12745","12745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422852","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of (a) the reduction in the level at which working tax credit begins to be withdrawn from £6,420 to £3,850 from April 2015 on work incentives for those on low incomes and (b) increasing of the taper rate to 48 per cent on work incentives for those on low incomes.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12725","12725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422853","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the reduction in household income arising from net tax and benefit reforms in the Summer Budget 2015 will be made up by an increase in household income arising from the new National Living Wage.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12726","12726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422854","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to support non-online applications for marriage allowance by couples on low incomes.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12791","12791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422855","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of recipients of working tax credits in Peterborough constituency are citizens of non-UK EU member states; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12792","12792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422856","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will allocate a proportion of road tax receipts to the repair of roads.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12805","12805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422857","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will allocate a proportion of fuel duty receipts to the repair of roads.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12806","12806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422858","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the Barnett consequentials for Wales resulting from public expenditure on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12781","12781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422859","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on small investors of planned restrictions on the relief on finance costs for landlords of residential property.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12733","12733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422860","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his most recent assessment is of the effect of the Help to Buy scheme on house prices.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12754","12754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422861","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the potential effects of the Japanese deflation on the UK economy.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12755","12755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422862","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward proposals to assist SMEs with higher labour costs by 2020 under the National Living Wage.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12756","12756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422863","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the funding raised from Libor fines has been distributed to charitable projects and good causes in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12742","12742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422864","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that every region and constituent part of the UK benefits from money raised from Libor fines.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12743","12743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422865","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2015 to Questions 3601 and 3602, if he will make an assessment of the potential economic effect on Cumbernauld of moving the HM Revenue and Customs office there elsewhere, as proposed in Building our Future - Continuing the Conversation, published in May 2015.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12759","12759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422866","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the likely change to levels of child poverty resulting from reductions in tax credits in 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12891","12891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422867","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect of reductions in tax credits on levels of housing benefit paid out in 2016-17.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12892","12892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422868","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on insurers not giving details of no claims bonuses to customers in their renewal notice.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12879","12879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422869","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on insurers signing customers up to future auto-renewals without the option to opt out.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12880","12880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422870","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support he plans to provide to home-buyers after the end of the mortgage guarantee scheme in 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12888","12888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422871","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) his ministerial colleagues and (b) external organisations on the future of the mortgage guarantee scheme of the Help to Buy policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12889","12889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422872","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of auto-renewals on competition in the private motor insurance market.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12882","12882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422873","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what budget reductions he plans to the fire and rescue service.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12883","12883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422874","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Part 2 of the Scotland Bill 2015, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the planned transfer of income tax powers on the operation of Gift Aid in Scotland.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12909","12909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422875","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what provision his Department has made for (a) payment of the national living wage by public sector employers and (b) the 3.4 per cent increase in Secondary National Insurance Contributions (NICs) from 2016-17 following the abolition of Contracted Out NICs.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12910","12910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422876","2015-10-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities he expects to lose 7.5 per cent of their business rate revenue after the introduction of his business rate reforms.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12864","12864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422877","2015-10-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was raised by business rates in the Newcastle upon Tyne local authority area in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12861","12861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422878","2015-10-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of his proposed changes to business rates on (a) the North East, (b) the North East Combined Authority area and (c) Newcastle upon Tyne local authority area.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12862","12862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422879","2015-10-26","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to tax credits on family incomes.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12916","12916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422880","2015-10-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of administering the proposed safety net mechanism for local authorities which lose more than 7.5 per cent of their business rate revenue in a year; and to what budget this will fall.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12863","12863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422881","2015-10-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities he estimates will have a net financial (a) gain and (b) loss in revenue from the proposed changes to business rate revenue allocation.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12865","12865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422882","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of proposed changes to tax credits on (a) nurses and (b) other NHS staff.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12809","12809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422883","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will have discussions with the Financial Conduct Authority on ensuring that when insurance companies issue annual renewal notices for policies they also issue a clear reference to the premium paid 12 months previously.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12821","12821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422884","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding to air ambulance services he has provided from Libor fines.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12826","12826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422885","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding for air ambulance services he plans to provide from Libor fines.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12827","12827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422886","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the average level of per car tax receipt in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12835","12835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422887","2015-10-23","Department for Transport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of likely spending by his Department on road repairs in each year between 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12837","12837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422888","2015-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2015 to Question 12052, for what reasons Part M building regulations do not apply to extensions to dwellings.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12918","12918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422889","2015-10-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the homelessness prevention grant.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12857","12857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422890","2015-10-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that reviews decisions by local authorities to rule that a person is intentionally homeless are conducted by people independent of that authority.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12764","12764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422891","2015-10-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what provisions are in place to safeguard vulnerable adults who are declared intentionally homeless and who do not want to be separated from family members also declared intentionally homeless in order to be rehoused.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12765","12765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422892","2015-10-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding has been returned to his Department by BT following take up beyond 20 per cent under the Broadband Delivery UK contract.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12762","12762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422893","2015-10-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that bookmakers have a code of conduct relating to fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12789","12789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422894","2015-10-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the level of mobile telephone coverage available to train passengers in tunnels; how that matches his Department's coverage targets; whether his Department classifies such coverage as in-building coverage; and what steps he is taking to improve that coverage.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12790","12790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422895","2015-10-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to maintain the level of regional news provision after the BBC Charter review.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12794","12794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422896","2015-10-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made on commemorations for the First World War.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12795","12795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422897","2015-10-23","HM Treasury","2015-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on employment in the hospitality sector of reducing the VAT rate in that sector to 10 per cent.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12825","12825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422898","2015-10-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to protect cultural heritage abroad.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12842","12842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422899","2015-10-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 7 of his Department's Triennial Review of gaming machine stake and prize limits, published in October 2013, whether it is his policy that there is a serious case to answer in relation to the potential harm caused by category B2 gaming machines.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12876","12876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422900","2015-10-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to his Answer of 13 October 2015 to Question 11722, which companies provide fixed broadband services in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12893","12893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422901","2015-10-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what comparative estimate he has made of the costs, other than initial offers, of a typical package of landline and broadband services in (a) the UK, (b) France, (c) Germany, (d) Spain and (e) Ireland.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12894","12894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422902","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish the Armed Forces Covenant Report 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12761","12761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422903","2015-10-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much UK-produced steel has been used in the manufacturing of the new icebreaking vessel being procured by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12747","12747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422904","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much UK-produced steel has been used in the manufacturing of the three offshore vessels being procured by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12748","12748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422905","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much UK-produced steel has been used in the manufacturing of the Scout Specialist Armoured Vehicles being procured by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12749","12749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422906","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much UK-produced steel has been used in the manufacturing of the MARS tankers being procured by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12750","12750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422907","2015-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on ensuring that UK-produced steel is used in items being procured by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12751","12751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422908","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many GCSE exam papers have been sent to other countries to be marked this year.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12721","12721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422909","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on children being absent from school to be on holiday.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12760","12760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422910","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on preparing to amend the Admissions Code to give parents of summer-born children a right to defer their start to school; and when a consultation on those amendments will take place.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12741","12741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422911","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the findings and recommendations of the National Deaf Children's Society report, One year on: impact of changes to the special educational needs system on deaf children, published on 1 September 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12732","12732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422912","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has assessed the implications of using a premature child's due date, rather than his or her birth date, for the purpose of determining when that child should start school.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12740","12740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422913","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will commission an update to the research study of Recruitment, Deployment and Management of Supply Teachers in England commissioned by her Department in 2006; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12887","12887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422914","2015-10-26","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the cost of privately-provided child care; what comparison she has made with the amounts which parents can claim for childcare from the Government; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12915","12915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422915","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that reviews into Ofsted's conduct are conducted by an independent body.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12878","12878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422916","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 2405, what the total cost to state-funded schools of hiring agency teachers was in (a) Brighton Pavilion constituency, (b) Brighton and Hove local authority area and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12884","12884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422917","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2015 to Question 36, if she will make it her policy to separately identify agency teachers in the annual School Workforce Census; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12885","12885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422918","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make a comparative assessment of the (a) cost to the public purse and (b) terms and conditions for supply teachers of the (i) local authority pool model, (ii) private agency model of supplying cover staff for state-funded schools and (iii) the supply register model operated in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12886","12886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422920","2015-10-23","Department for Education","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that there are adequate numbers of school places in Hendon constituency.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12844","12844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422921","2015-10-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the comparative merits of universities using (a) postcodes and (b) household incomes to determine whether a student lives in a low-participation neighbourhood for the purposes of eligibility for bursaries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12874","12874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422922","2015-10-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment she has made of the financial effect of the removal of pre-accreditation from the Feed-in-Tariff on businesses planning to pre-accredit renewable energy schemes before the end of 2016.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12875","12875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422923","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of changes to the Feed-in Tariff scheme on (a) jobs and investment opportunities, (b) renewable energy projects and (c) levels of carbon emissions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12919","12919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422924","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects to inform the Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon renewable energy project of its contract for difference strike price.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12913","12913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422925","2015-10-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will delay the implementation of the removal of the pre-accreditation scheme from the Feed-in Tariff.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12828","12828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422926","2015-10-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of reforms proposed in the review of the Feed-in Tariff scheme on the viability of future renewable energy projects.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12823","12823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422927","2015-10-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the change in the number of jobs in each region attributable to changes to feed-in tariffs.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12908","12908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422928","2015-10-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of cattle have been tested for bovine TB in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12739","12739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422929","2015-10-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects the Coastal Communities Fund to reopen for a further round of funding.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12744","12744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422930","2015-10-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to bring forward a draft Wild Animals in Circuses Bill; and whether the definition of a travelling circus will be included in the Bill.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12822","12822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422931","2015-10-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much revenue has been raised by the Agriculture and Horticulture Board through levies collected from the sale of pigs in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12839","12839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422932","2015-10-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to introduce legislation to ban the sale of primates as pets.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12838","12838"
