"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523370","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, HCWS30, what assessment he has made of the business need for the roles based at (a) the Sheffield office at St Paul's Place and (b) the London office at 1 Victoria Street.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39619","39619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523371","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, HCWS30, what proportion of the 1,500 roles will have ministerial exposure following the centralisation of policy functions in London.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39631","39631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523372","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, HCWS30, what estimate he has made of the transition costs associated with the decision to create a combined Business, Innovation and Skills headquarters and policy function in London.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39632","39632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523373","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he has met Mark Samworth, owner of the food manufacturing company Samworths, in the last six months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39669","39669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523374","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to reduce his Department's vacancy rate.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39715","39715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523375","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to involve small and medium-sized enterprises in the proposed digital apprenticeship system.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39704","39704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523376","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to promote action to remove space debris.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39726","39726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523377","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to support and spread awareness of cyber security insurance amongst businesses.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39727","39727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523378","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish his Department's consultation response on the proposal for a combined headquarters and policy centre in London.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39823","39823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523379","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the amount of funding that will be made available to each part of the UK for science, education and research purposes through EU schemes in the post-2020 Multiannual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39803","39803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523380","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39827","39827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523381","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether account is being taken in the proposed sale of the Land Registry of whether interested bidders are based in tax havens; what assessment his Department made in the awarding of such contracts of the competitive advantage given to companies based in tax havens; and what recent discussions he has had with his Ministerial colleagues on banning companies based in tax havens from purchasing assets sold during privatisations.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39816","39816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523382","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Freedom of Information requests have been refused by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39724","39724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523383","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials of his Department have specific policy responsibility for deregulation.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39723","39723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523384","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to promote a whistleblowing culture in his Department.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39720","39720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523385","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress he has made on bringing forward proposals for a modern public services ombudsman in the last three months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39718","39718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523386","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of people appointed to public bodies are women.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39721","39721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523387","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to promote a whistleblowing culture across the civil service.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39719","39719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523388","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the terms of reference are for the new Anti-corruption Innovation Hub.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39683","39683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523389","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of staff will be recruited to form the Anti-corruption Innovation Hub.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39682","39682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523390","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Government Minister will have responsibility for overseeing the implementation of the new anti-corruption strategy.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39684","39684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523391","2016-06-13","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 9 March 2016 to Question 29669, what progress he has made on establishing the cost to the public purse of the Independent Commission on Freedom of Information.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39672","39672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523392","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials in his Department have applied for special leave to carry out work for non-governmental departments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39680","39680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523393","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many job vacancies in his Department have been reserved as internal posts in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39681","39681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523394","2016-06-13","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to increase diversity in public appointments.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39603","39603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523395","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to launch the next Lloyds Bank share offer; and what incentives he plans to include in that offer to encourage small shareholders to retain shares that they purchase.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39642","39642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523396","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure people are not assigned incorrect tax codes.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39639","39639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523397","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce a payment of £1,000 to each person reaching the age of 100.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39641","39641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523398","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the cost to the EU economy of strikes by air traffic controllers across Europe in 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39708","39708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523399","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has seen the latest draft of the EU Commission's proposals for the (a) EU Budget and (b) any re-assessment and adjustments relating to previous years budgets; and if he will publish those proposals and their effect on the public purse before 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39777","39777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523400","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has met with Mr Mark Samworth in the last six months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39782","39782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523401","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39841","39841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523402","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce measures to prevent companies based in tax havens from purchasing assets during privatisations.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39770","39770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523403","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that the renegotiation of the UK-Malawi tax treaty supports development and helps tackle poverty in that country.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39860","39860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523404","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to improve the transparency of the negotiation process for UK tax treaties.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39861","39861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523405","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the UK's tax treaties with developing countries on tackling poverty in those countries.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39862","39862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523406","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of officials of his Department working on decentralisation and growth are based in London.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39850","39850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523407","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the increase in demand on housing caused by inward migration in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39851","39851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523408","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library the raw data from each English Housing Survey detailing the nationalities of the Household Representative Person.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39852","39852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523409","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many times he has visited Scotland since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings, with whom, were held on each of those visits.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39824","39824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523410","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there was in the amount the EU Commission proposed to make available in structural funds to Cornwall for the period 2014-2020 and the period 2007-2013; and what steps his Department took to limit such changes.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39793","39793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523411","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the level of structural funding that the EU Commission will allocate to each region in England in the post-2020 Multiannual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39805","39805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523412","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the level of structural funding that the EU Commission will allocate to Cornwall in the post-2020 Multiannual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39810","39810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523413","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36419, if he will set out the actions required of an hon. Member, including the number of parliamentary questions asked, contributions to debate and other relevant matters which are deemed to demonstrate sufficient interest in devolution, for such hon. Members to be invited to meetings on future plans for the area they represent.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39855","39855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523414","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the total number and proportion of dwellings in the UK occupied with the Households Representative Person being a foreign national from (a) another EU member state and (b) a non-EU country in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39854","39854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523415","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the additional new housing required to address demand caused by immigration from (a) other EU member states and (b) non-EU member states in each year to 2030.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39853","39853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523416","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the English Housing Survey Headline Report 2014 to 2015, published in February 2016, did not contain a breakdown of the nationality of the Households Representative Person by tenure; and if he will publish the data held on the nationality of the Households Representative Person by tenure for each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39706","39706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523417","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many unauthorised encampments were recorded in each county and metropolitan borough in 2015 in England.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39620","39620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523419","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations his Department has received from each (a) local authority, (b) Police and Crime Commissioner and (c) Police Chief Constable seeking further powers in relation to responsibilities to stop unauthorised encampments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39622","39622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523420","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the variation in spending by each local authority on physical activity services per capita.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39636","39636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523421","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many housing associations have demolished residential buildings that are less than 10 years old in each of the last five years; and what the reasons were for those demolitions.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39607","39607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523422","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Homes and Communities Agency and (b) Wandle Housing Association Limited on the demolition of residential buildings in Solomon's Passage, Peckham.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39608","39608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523423","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that staff in his Department receive religious literacy training.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39675","39675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523424","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to review the guidance provided in Approved Document B to the Building Regulations 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39625","39625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523425","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of all local authority spending was spent on physical activity services in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39635","39635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523426","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) eviction notices and (b) legal action related to the clearance of sites of unauthorised encampments in England in 2015.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39621","39621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523427","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many of his Department's civil servants were based in Coventry in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39666","39666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523429","2016-06-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what support the Government is providing to remote rural communities on obtaining reliable access to broadband.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39670","39670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523430","2016-06-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assistance the Government plans to provide to broadband suppliers to meet the terms of the Universal Services Obligation.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39671","39671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523431","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39828","39828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523433","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answers of 7 April 2014 to Questions 194734 to 194737, what checks were made on the provenance of the funds used to purchase Brompton Road underground station.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39792","39792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523434","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answers of 7 April 2014 to Questions 194734 to 194737, who made the highest bid for Brompton Road underground station.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39765","39765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523435","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39829","39829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523436","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Royal Navy has deployed any unmanned maritime systems for the purpose of (a) anti-submarine and (b) port and harbour security.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39740","39740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523437","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department (a) has allocated and (b) plans to allocate resources to study the potential threat posed by unmanned underwater vehicles to the SSBN fleet.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39741","39741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523438","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answers of 7 April 2014 to Questions 194734 to 194737, who the named official was who was responsible for the sale of Brompton Road underground station.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39791","39791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523439","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answers of 7 April 2014 to Questions 194734 to 194737, whether his Department was aware of the FBI investigation into Dmitri Firtash when it sold Brompton Road underground station.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39788","39788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523440","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answers of 7 April 2014 to Questions 194734 to 194737, who the independent marketing agent was for the sale of Brompton Road underground station.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39789","39789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523441","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answers of 7 April 2014 to Questions 194734 to 194737, who the 12 bidders were for Brompton Road underground station.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39790","39790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523442","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any RAF personnel have carried out airstrikes outside the coalition mission in the Iraq and Syria conflict zone since 2 December 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39785","39785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523443","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has demonstrated the capability of Certified Predator B for the duration of the Protector programme.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39786","39786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523444","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what timeline has been proposed for publication of the revised Joint Doctrinal Note on UK Unmanned Systems.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39787","39787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523445","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to safeguard Royal Navy submarines from risks posed by underwater drones.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39738","39738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523446","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33645, how many Puma Mk2 helicopters are fitted with the Wire Strike Protection System; and whether the Puma Mk2  that crashed in Afghanistan on 11 October 2015 was fitted with such a system.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39739","39739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523447","2016-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Welfare Reform and Work Act 2016 on access to housing for veterans.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39689","39689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523448","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 26 April 2016 to Question 35103, what the role is of the Liaison Officers deployed in Saudi coalition headquarters.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39711","39711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523449","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the cost of upgrading the mission software on F35B Lightning II aircraft operated by the Royal Air Force after the completion of Block 3F testing.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39657","39657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523450","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support the armed forces is providing to Iraqi forces related to the conflict with Daesh in Falujah.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39653","39653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523451","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports he has received on the extent of the withdrawal of Russian forces from the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39654","39654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523452","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent steps his Department has taken to adhere to the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39690","39690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523453","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel were medically discharged from the (a) Royal Navy excluding the Royal Marines, (b) Royal Marines, (c) Army and (d) Royal Air Force in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39645","39645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523454","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average length is of the transition period for personnel of each of the Armed Forces between a decision of the Medical Board recommending discharge and that discharge taking place; and what support is given to personnel during that period to support the transition to civilian life.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39646","39646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523455","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the role is of personal recovery officers related to different categories of injury of armed forces personnel who are due to receive medical discharge; how many such officers there are in each branch of the Armed Forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39647","39647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523456","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) army, (b) navy and (c) RAF personnel have registered with a doctor in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39581","39581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523457","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of students who have taken up computer science as an option in the EBacc in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39573","39573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523458","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37487, whether the Education Funding Agency has directed academies to admit pupils 10 or 12 times since 2012; and how many directions sought by local authorities and referred on to the Schools Adjudicator were upheld in each year from 2005 to 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39593","39593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523459","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy schools hold the freehold of their school sites.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39667","39667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523460","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that staff in her Department receive religious literacy training.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39676","39676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523461","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on travel and accommodation for civil servants accompanying the Minister of State for Schools on official business since July 2014.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39668","39668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523462","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 May 2016 to Question 37615, on academies: admissions, how many times local authorities asked her to intervene in each year from 2012 to 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39597","39597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523463","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what occasions (a) she, (b) Ministers of her Department and (c) the Chief Social Worker for Children have visited Birmingham Children's Services Department since 2012.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39857","39857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523464","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times she has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39830","39830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523465","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the number of unregistered schools in England.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39845","39845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523466","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Education Funding Agency guidance, Building Bulletin 100: Design for fire safety in schools, published on 11 March 2014, how many schools that scored high or medium on the risk assessment have not been fitted with sprinklers.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39767","39767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523467","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Education Funding Agency guidance, Building Bulletin 100: Design for fire safety in schools, published on 11 March 2014, how many schools with pupils with Special Educational Needs have scored (a) high, (b) medium and (c) low on the fire risk assessment.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39768","39768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523468","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many times she has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39831","39831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523469","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make it her policy for the UK to reduce its actual greenhouse gas emissions by 61 per cent below 1990 levels by 2030.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39703","39703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523470","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will estimate the average reduction in electricity bills in Great Britain for households in receipt of the Warm Home Discount Scheme.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39696","39696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523471","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent representations she has received on the extension of the Warm Home Discount Scheme to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39691","39691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523472","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much has been contributed by energy suppliers towards the rebate on electricity bills under the Warm Home Discount Scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39692","39692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523473","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussion she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the possible extension of the Warm Home Discount Scheme to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39693","39693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523474","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans the Government has to move the design and manufacture of specialised steel casks used to store nuclear fuels during transport to China.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39623","39623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523475","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she has received representations in the last 12 months on coal that has been or will be stockpiled in the UK.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39570","39570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523476","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the level of coal stockpiling in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39571","39571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523477","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of potential levels of UK coal exports in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39572","39572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523478","2016-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has issued guidance to local authorities on the conservation of nestling swifts in the demolition or renovation of old housing estates.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39574","39574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523479","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations her Department has made to the European Commission on the proposed reform of the EU Nature Directive.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39643","39643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523480","2016-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many consignments of dogs were exported from the UK to Hong Kong in 2015; and how many dogs were in each such consignment.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39701","39701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523481","2016-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times she has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39832","39832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523482","2016-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will estimate the amount of funding that will be made available to each part of the UK for the fishing industry through the Common Fisheries Policy in the post-2020 Multi Annual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39804","39804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523483","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38596, on beach huts: Christchurch, how Natural England plans to ensure that the proposal does not cause further harm to the geological interest.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39749","39749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523484","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38596, on beach huts: Christchurch, if she will publish a full record of the discussions between Natural England and Christchurch Borough Council.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39679","39679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523485","2016-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will estimate the amount of funding that will be made available to each part of the UK for rural development purposes through EU schemes in the post-2020 Multi Annual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39800","39800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523486","2016-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will estimate the amount of funding that will be made available to each part of the UK for farming and agriculture through the CAP in the post-2020 Multi Annual Framework.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39801","39801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523487","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38596, on beach huts: Christchurch, and with reference to the Guardian report of 15 April 2016, entitled Dorset residents angry over TV showing beach hut competition, whether Natural England  is comfortable with the idea of the development of residential beach chalets on Highcliffe clifftop.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39745","39745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523488","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the threats to the Tristan albatross and Gough bunting from invasive plants and mice; and if his Department will support the proposed initiative by the Tristan da Cunha council to protect those birds through mouse and invasive plant eradication projects.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39764","39764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523489","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will suspend arms export licences and reject new applications for arms exports to Saudi Arabia while there is a risk that they could be used in contravention of international humanitarian and human rights law.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39818","39818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523490","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will support the immediate establishment of an international, impartial investigation into repeated international humanitarian law violations by all parties to the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39819","39819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523491","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that Saudi Arabia and other Coalition states in Yemen cooperate with the UN to develop and implement an action plan to end and prevent violations against children.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39820","39820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523492","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policy of the recent UN Secretary-General's report on Children and Armed Conflict and its Annex which lists the Saudi-led Coalition as committing grave violations against children in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39821","39821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523493","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39833","39833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523494","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which sources independent of the Saudi government are assessed by the UK Government regarding the alleged use of cluster munitions by the Saudi led coalition in Yemen.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39712","39712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523495","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33935, whether the UK Government considers that the Saudi Arabian-led coalition forces have committed any violation of International Humanitarian Law during the Yemen conflict.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39713","39713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523496","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold discussions with his EU counterparts on the compatibility of recent sentencing decisions by the Israeli judiciary with the human rights standards set in the EU-Israeli Association Agreement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39714","39714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523497","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Iranian government on the treatment of (a) Maryam Nasim Naghash Zargaran and (b) other Christian prisoners in that country.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39717","39717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523498","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on the case of Andargachew Tsege and efforts to ensure proper legal and consular access for Mr Tsege and visitation rights for his family.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39705","39705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523499","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to Belize and Guatemala on (a) adhering to the provisions established under the 2005 Confidence Building Measures related to the disputed border between those countries and (b) steps to improve confidence and trust between those countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39652","39652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523500","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports the Government has received on the territorial dispute between Belize and Guatemala over the area around the Sarstoon River.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39651","39651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523501","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many representations he received from his (a) Yemeni and (b) Saudi Arabian counterparts in each of the last 12 months on the conflict in Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39665","39665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523502","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's recent estimate is of the number of civilian casualties in the conflict in Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39661","39661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523503","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many representations he has made to his (a) Yemeni and (b) Saudi Arabian counterpart in each of the last twelve months on the conflict in Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39662","39662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523504","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Kenyan counterparts on the proposed demolition of the Dadaab and Kakuma refugee camps in that country; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of those proposed demolitions on future migration flows across the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39655","39655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523505","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that staff in his Department receive religious literacy training.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39677","39677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523506","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons he has not yet called for the immediate release of Andargachew Tsege.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39568","39568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523507","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli government on that country's use of the courts to obtain information on the identities of soldiers who have served in Operation Protective Edge and testified about their experience with Breaking the Silence.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39582","39582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523508","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Iranian counterpart on the protection of Iranian human rights activists in that country.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39592","39592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523509","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of patients with severe asthma being referred to a specialist by their GP over the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39578","39578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523510","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of cancer patients in (a) England and (b) Copeland constituency waited six weeks or more for a diagnostic test in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39579","39579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523511","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of cancer patients in (a) England and (b) Copeland constituency received their first cancer treatment within 62 days of an urgent GP referral in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39580","39580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523512","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for Government policies of medical and scientific evidence on the effect of moderate alcohol consumption on the risk of death from cardiovascular disease.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39595","39595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523513","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37472, on fertility: medical treatments, whether he plans to review clinical commissioning groups' levels of compliance with NICE guidelines.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39596","39596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523514","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department is taking steps to set a national standard for a maximum number of patients that GPs, nurses and other primary care professionals can reasonably deal with during any working day.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39604","39604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523515","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to change surrogacy law to give single parents with children born through surrogacy the same rights as couples.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39605","39605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523516","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the declaration by Sir James Munby in the matter of Z (A Child) (No. 2), on 20 May 2016, that sections 54(1) and (2) of the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Act 2008 are incompatible with rights under Article 14 of the European Convention on Human Rights taken in conjunction with Article 8.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39606","39606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523517","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Government funding has been allocated to the research of Type 1 Diabetes in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39583","39583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523518","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what decisions his Department has made on the distribution of funding to relieve the immediate pressures in general practice, set out in NHS England's General Practice Forward View, published in April 2016.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39591","39591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523519","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of patients with long-term health conditions who cannot afford to pay the charges associated with their prescribed medication and subsequently require additional treatment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39569","39569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523520","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding is allocated to each region for support services for people with motor neurone disease.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39575","39575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523521","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission research into the costs to the NHS of delayed discharges.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39663","39663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523522","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with whom on future provision of services at Warrington Hospital; and when the decision on future provisions of services at that hospital will be announced.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39664","39664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523523","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will undertake a review of the reasons for the length of time taken by NHS Property Services to take decisions related to property in (a) West Sussex, (b) Mid Sussex and (c) East Grinstead.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39659","39659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523524","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who the senior leaders and board members are of the 44 Sustainability and Transformation Plan footprints.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39633","39633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523525","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made an assessment of the cost effectiveness of HIV PeEP if only given to a very small group of high-risk individuals.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39628","39628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523526","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the NHS England Specialised Commissioning Oversight Group plans to make an announcement on the recommendations of the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39616","39616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523527","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will give NHS England the power to commission HIV PeEP through the NHS public health functions agreement known as Section 7a; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39627","39627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523528","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether members of the public will have a right to attend Sustainability and Transformation Plan board meetings.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39612","39612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523529","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the legal status of a Sustainability and Transformation Plan will be.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39613","39613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523530","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of Sustainability and Transformation Plans have been submitted to his Department; and what the deadline is for such plans to be submitted.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39614","39614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523531","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of whether the Government is on target to eliminate avoidable blindness by 2020.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39772","39772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523532","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data his Department holds on adjusted mortality in care homes managed by each major provider.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39702","39702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523533","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had on (a) ending the role of GPs in (i) assessing eligibility for bus passes, parking badges, housing and gym membership and (ii) other non-NHS work and (b) ensuring that such work is commissioned from other sources by the requesting organisation.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39798","39798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523534","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to reduce indemnity costs on general practice.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39797","39797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523535","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what accountability mechanics are in place related to decisions in Sustainability and Transformation Plan footprints.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39795","39795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523536","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that GPs are able to routinely to offer 15 minute, or longer, consultations where necessary for patients with greater needs.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39742","39742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523537","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to reduce the financial burden of indemnity costs on general practice.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39743","39743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523538","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans that the new tobacco control plan will address the effects of (a) electronic vaping devices and (b) heat not burn devices.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39744","39744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523539","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the legal status is of the changes to health and social care proposed in Sustainability and Transformation Plans.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39771","39771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523540","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve GP access to natriuretic peptide testing.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39813","39813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523541","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the speed and accuracy of diagnosis for heart failure patients.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39814","39814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523542","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve co-ordination of care for heart failure patients across primary and secondary care.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39815","39815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523543","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that NHS staff receive religious literacy training.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39748","39748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523544","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the importance of the Corsellis Brain Collection for promoting research into brain diseases for the treatment of patients in the NHS.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39856","39856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523545","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has had discussions with the West London Mental Health Trust on future funding of the Corsellis Brain Collection.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39870","39870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523546","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has issued to NHS Property Services on charging clinical commissioning groups for void space in any NHS Property Services' properties.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39783","39783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523547","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had on (a) complete and (b) partial privatisation of the National Health Service's Property Services.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39784","39784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523548","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what decisions have been made on the distribution of funding announced in the General Practice Forward View to reduce the immediate pressures in general practice.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39799","39799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523549","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure the NHS is not charged a premium price by pharmaceutical companies for general prescription drugs.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39859","39859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523550","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NHS England Five Year Forward View on Mental Health, published in February 2016, what progress has been made on Recommendation 35 on staff awareness and confidence in dealing with mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39865","39865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523551","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NHS England Five Year Forward View on Mental Health, published in February 2016, what progress has been made on Recommendation 33 on health and wellbeing support to NHS organisations.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39866","39866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523552","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NHS England Five Year Forward View on Mental Health, published in February 2016, what progress has been made on Recommendation 32 on a multi-disciplinary workforce strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39867","39867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523553","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NHS England Five Year Forward View on Mental Health, published in February 2016, what progress has been made on Recommendation 34 on incentive payments.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39868","39868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523554","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NHS England Five Year Forward View on Mental Health, published in February 2016, what progress has been made on Recommendation 28 on digital infrastructure.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39869","39869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523555","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether changes have been made to the way evidence of illegal entry is recorded in response to the recommendations made in the report by the Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration, An Inspection of General Aviation and General Maritime, published in January 2016, and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39864","39864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523556","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many overstayers have (a) been removed and (b) voluntarily deported as a result of action taken by Capita in each month since October 2012; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39761","39761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523557","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of overstayers have subsequently been granted leave to remain due to their family or private life in the UK in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39762","39762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523558","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of failed asylum seekers who have been removed or voluntarily deported were (a) overstayers and (b) illegal entrants in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39763","39763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523559","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the general aviation risk assessment tool form has been amended in response to the recommendations made in the report by the Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration, An Inspection of General Aviation and General Maritime, published in January 2016; whether additional training has been provided to Border Force officers responsible for completing those forms; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39863","39863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523560","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total cost to her Department was of the van-based advertising campaign advising illegal immigrants to go home, launched in Autumn 2013; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39760","39760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523561","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for refugee family reunion have been (a) made, (b) resolved, (c) granted and (d) refused by nationals from (i) Syria, (ii) Eritrea, (iii) Afghanistan, (iv) Iran and (v) Sudan in each of the last 12 quarters.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39817","39817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523562","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer to Lord Ahmad of 7 April 2016 to Question HL7297, if her Department will make it its policy to use in all future documents and legislation a definition of extremism which includes the phrase mutual respect and tolerance of those with different faiths and beliefs, rather than the phrase mutual respect and tolerance of different faiths and beliefs.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39747","39747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523563","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the decision to introduce a 30-day deadline to travel once a family reunion visa has been issued; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39781","39781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523564","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to accelerate the family reunification process for unaccompanied children in Europe with family in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39794","39794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523565","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received on the College of Policing's relationship with Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39775","39775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523566","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times she has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39834","39834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523567","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the security arrangements under the Common Travel Agreement in preventing illegal immigration into the UK.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39697","39697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523568","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of people entering or leaving the UK by air had pre-boarding electronic checks in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39753","39753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523569","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which services have been sold for profit by (a) her Department and (b) the College of Policing to the Saudi criminal justice system in the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39773","39773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523570","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department had with the Royal Yacht Association on solutions to practical difficulties preventing pleasure craft from providing advance notification of arrival in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39754","39754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523571","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of flights identified as high-risk where Border Force officials have not attended in the last 12 months; when the automated system for airports to check the civil aviation tracking system will be introduced; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39755","39755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523572","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officials in (a) her Department and (b) the College of Policing have travelled to Saudi Arabia to discuss the British police force training given to the Saudi Arabian police force in the last three years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39774","39774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523573","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions there have been of applicants for asylum who have arrived without documents and concealed their identity to frustrate removal in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39757","39757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523574","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many airlines are required to copy passengers' documents, on how many flight routes, before the passenger is allowed to board.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39758","39758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523575","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employers received (a) one, (b) between two and four and (c) more than five fixed penalty fines for illegally employing immigrants in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39756","39756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523576","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her Saudi Arabian counterpart on the use of the advanced cyber-crime courses provided by the College of Policing to target pro-democracy activists in that country.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39776","39776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523577","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many clandestine entrants of each nationality were identified within the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39778","39778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523578","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how may airport liaison officers have been deployed to each location in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39759","39759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523579","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the programme managed by Capita to identify and remove overstayers; when the contract with Capita for that programme is due for renewal; whether she plans to make any amendments to the terms of that contract; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39779","39779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523580","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been refused permission to board flights to the UK as a result of checks carried out by airlines in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39780","39780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523581","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions of people involved in providing transport for illegal immigrants there have been in the each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39750","39750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523582","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of visa applicants to each visa application centre were fingerprinted before they travelled to the UK in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39751","39751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523583","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of migrants staying in the UK for more than three months did not have an ID card containing both their photograph and fingerprints in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39752","39752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523584","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the number of people whose asylum application has been transferred for consideration by the Government under the Dublin III Regulation as part of quarterly immigration statistics.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39609","39609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523585","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36277, how many requests have been made for asylum applications to be transferred for consideration by the UK from (a) Greece and (b) Italy since UK experts were deployed to support the respective Dublin units.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39630","39630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523586","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people not granted entry clearance or temporary admission were permitted to live in private accommodation before being deported in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39648","39648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523587","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who were not granted entry clearance or temporary admission and were permitted to live in private accommodation absconded in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39649","39649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523588","2016-06-09","Department for International Development","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that staff in her Department receive religious literacy training.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39678","39678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523589","2016-06-09","Department for International Development","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the likelihood of the yellow fever outbreak in Angola spreading beyond Africa; and what support the Government is providing to tackle that outbreak.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39656","39656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523590","2016-06-14","Department for International Development","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has provided to projects operating in the Dadaab refugee camp since 1 January 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39644","39644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523591","2016-06-09","Department for International Development","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many officials of her Department have applied for special leave to carry out work for non-governmental departments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39722","39722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523592","2016-06-09","Department for International Development","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the level of corruption in those states and territories in the Middle East which receive international development aid from the UK.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39694","39694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523593","2016-06-09","Department for International Development","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many times she has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39835","39835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523594","2016-06-09","Department for International Development","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will increase her Department's expenditure on water and sanitation.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39812","39812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523595","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what humanitarian support and assistance her Department plans to provide to aid agencies in Yemen in each of the next 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39846","39846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523596","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was levied in respect of financial remedies in each key performance indicator designated in respect of the contractual agreement between his Department and G4S Care and Justice Services (UK) Limited at HM Prison Birmingham in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39844","39844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523597","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been levied in respect of financial remedies in each key performance indicator designated in respect of the contractual agreement entitled the Provision of Total Facilities Management between his Department and (a) Amey Community Ltd, (b) Carillion (AMBS) Ltd, (c) EMCOR Facilities Services Ltd, (d) Enterprise Managed Services Ltd, (e) G4S Integrated Services (UK) Ltd, (f) Mitie Facilities Services Ltd and (g) Sodexo Ltd in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39843","39843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523598","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39836","39836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523599","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason the Government is proposing to raise the small claims limit to £5000 rather than to £3000.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39716","39716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523600","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of the offence of child destruction under the Infant Life Preservation Act 1929 for performing abortions on themselves or causing their own miscarriage in each year since 1986; and what each such case was.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39731","39731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523601","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of offences under section 59 of the Offences Against the Person Act 1861 related to abortions in each year since 1986; and what each such case was.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39730","39730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523602","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of offences under section 58 of the Offences Against the Person Act 1861 for performing abortions on themselves or causing their own miscarriage in each year since 1986; and what each such case was.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39728","39728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523603","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of offences under section 58 of the Offences Against the Person Act 1861 for performing abortions on other people in each year since 1986; and what each such case was.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39729","39729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523604","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of the offence of child destruction under the Infant Life Preservation Act 1929 for performing abortions on other people in each year since 1986; and what each such case was.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39732","39732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523605","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue a response to Early Day Motion 1150 of Session 2015-16, Legal protection for unborn children.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39733","39733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523606","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse of provision of abortion services in England was in each year from 1986 to 2013.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39734","39734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523607","2016-06-09","Cabinet Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to recommendation 2 on page 250 of the Report of the Macur Review, published in March 2016, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all government departments possess an accurate database of the documents and materials held by them.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39737","39737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523608","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to recommendation 5 on page 251 of the Report of the Macur Review, published in March 2016, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a police investigation to consider whether there is sufficient evidence and public interest relating to matters of malfeasance in public office in the Welsh Office in relation to the abuse of children in care in North Wales.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39736","39736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523609","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to recommendation 5 on page 251 of the Report of the Macur Review, published in March 2016, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a police investigation to consider whether there is sufficient evidence and public interest relating to matters of malfeasance in public office or perverting the course of justice in North West Wales Police in relation to the abuse of children in care in North Wales.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39735","39735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523610","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been levied in financial remedies relating to each key performance indicator in the contractual agreement between his Department and HM Prison Featherstone II in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39594","39594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523611","2016-06-09","Leader of the House","2016-06-07","To ask the Leader of the House, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39837","39837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523612","2016-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what change there was in the amount the EU Commission proposed to make available in structural funds to Northern Ireland for the period 2014 to 2020 from the period 2007 to 2013; what steps her Department took to limit such change; and if she will estimate the level of such funding that Northern Ireland will be allocated after 2020.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39807","39807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523613","2016-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will estimate the amount of structural funding that the EU Commission will allocate to Northern Ireland in the post-2020 Multiannual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39806","39806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523614","2016-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what preliminary work her Department has carried out in preparation for the possibility of a vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39695","39695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523615","2016-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with her Irish Republic counterpart on security co-operation since the latest published security assessment of the threat posed by Irish republican terrorists.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39698","39698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523616","2016-06-09","Prime Minister","2016-06-07","To ask the Prime Minister, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39838","39838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523617","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate the Government has made of the cost to the public purse to date of the adaptation of the Voyager aircraft for the transport of senior ministers.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39746","39746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523618","2016-06-09","Scotland Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the level of structural funding that the EU Commission's formula will allocate to Scotland in the post-2020 Multi Annual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39802","39802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523619","2016-06-09","Scotland Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39839","39839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523620","2016-06-09","Scotland Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what change there was in the amount the EU Commission proposed to make available in structural funds to Scotland for the period 2014 to 2020 from the period 2007 to 2013; and what steps his Department took to limit such change; and what estimate he has made of the level of such funding for Scotland after 2020.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39808","39808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523621","2016-06-09","Wales Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what change there was in the amount the EU Commission proposed to make available in structural funds to Wales for the period 2014 to 2020 from the period 2007 to 2013; what steps his Department took to limit such a change; and if he will estimate the amount of such funding made available to Wales after 2020.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39825","39825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523622","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39840","39840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523623","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the level of vehicular noise on the M1 passing Mill Hill town.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39796","39796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523624","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been paid in fines by Govia Thamelink Railway to his Department to compensate for poor performance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39858","39858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523625","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been paid in fines by Network Rail to Govia Thamelink Railway to  compensate for poor performance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39871","39871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523626","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of planting noise barriers with vegetation alongside motorways and trunk roads.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39710","39710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523627","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the Sheffield to Rotherham tram-train scheme has been delayed.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39699","39699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523628","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail on delays to the Sheffield to Rotherham tram-train scheme.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39700","39700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523629","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of installing a continuous noise barrier on the eastern side of the M1 passing through Mill Hill.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39709","39709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523630","2016-06-14","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage more cyclists to use cycle lanes rather than cycling on the main highway; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39600","39600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523631","2016-06-14","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to reduce congestion on the M25 motorway; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39601","39601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523632","2016-06-14","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the imposition of 50mph average speed limits on three stretches of M1 motorway, one in Northamptonshire and two in Leicestershire, were carried out consecutively rather than concurrently to avoid delays for motorists; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39602","39602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523633","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of registering bicycles with the DVLA.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39576","39576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523634","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the age requirements for the driving test were last reviewed.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39577","39577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523635","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with trades unions officials representing Highways England traffic officers on the potential danger of serious injury or death arising from trying to move a heavy goods vehicle from a live lane using a Highways England traffic officer 4 by 4 vehicle.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39584","39584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523636","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much compensation has been paid from the public purse to owners of heavy goods vehicles damaged as a result of being moved by Highways England traffic officers from live lanes to (a) hard shoulders and (b) emergency refuge areas in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39585","39585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523637","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Highways England traffic officers have moved heavy goods vehicles from live lanes to (a) hard shoulders and (b) emergency refuge areas in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39586","39586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523638","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Highways England traffic officers have been (a) trained to move heavy goods vehicles from live motorway lanes on Smart motorways to emergency refuge areas and (b) not so trained but issued with an instruction manual to move such vehicles.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39587","39587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523639","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission a study into the potential merits of the use of E10 petrol.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39640","39640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523640","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern contractual breach notice, dated 7 July 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39629","39629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523641","2016-06-14","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on his plans to limit motorway roadworks to no more than stretches of two miles.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39617","39617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523642","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what penalties he is able to levy on the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern franchisee if the terms of that franchise are breached or its performance is judged to be inadequate; and whether any such penalties have been imposed since that franchise commenced.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39626","39626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523643","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to assess the case for the proposed Crossrail 2 Eastern Phase.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39611","39611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523644","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential environmental and safety benefits of using single rather than double-decker buses during off-peak times on journeys with small numbers of passengers.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39673","39673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523645","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that cars and drivers for (a) Uber and (b) other private hire companies are adequately insured.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39658","39658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523646","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of flights in the UK North Sea oil and gas sector were undertaken by (a) Airbus EC225 and (b) AS332 helicopters airframes in each year since 2007-08.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39766","39766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523647","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37816, on level crossings, what his Department's expenditure on the level crossing reform programme was in the last Parliament; and how much such expenditure is budgeted in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39849","39849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523648","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated cost to the public purse was of preparing and publishing the (a) Bowe Report into the planning of Network Rail's enhancements programme published on 25 November 2015 and (b) Hendy Report on Replanning Network Rail's Investment programme, published January 2016.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39848","39848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523649","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 24 November 2014 to Question 214853, on travel, whether his Department has produced an updated National Transport Model estimate of future (a) annual trips by mode per person and (b) average length of trips by mode.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39847","39847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523650","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward planned improvements to the Northern Rail service between Scarborough and York that are due to take place in 2019.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39769","39769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523651","2016-06-09","Wales Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will place in the library an unredacted copy of Lady Macur's review of the Tribunal of Inquiry into the abuse of children in North Wales.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39624","39624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523652","2016-06-09","Wales Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what change there was in the amount of funding the EU Commission made available in structural funds to (a) Wales and (b) the Valleys for the period 2014 to 2020 from the period 2007 to 2014; what steps his Department took to limit such change; and if he will estimate the level of such funding that Wales will be allocated after 2020.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39811","39811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523653","2016-06-09","Wales Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will estimate the level of structural funding that the EU Commission will allocate to (a) Wales and (b) the Valleys in the post-2020 Multiannual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39809","39809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523654","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have claimed employment and support allowance after a paper-based review were refused a paper-based review upon re-assessment for that allowance in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39660","39660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523655","2016-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made on implementing the request by the governments of British Overseas Territories during the December 2015 Joint Ministerial Council on establishing parity of treatment between all British Overseas Territories on the uprating of pensions for UK state pension holders residing in those territories.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39650","39650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523656","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many requests for paper-based reviews for employment and support allowance were submitted in each year since 2009-10; and how many of those claims were (a) accepted and (b) rejected.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39674","39674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523657","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department plans to take to collect data on the number of people with arthritis who qualify for personal independence payments on the basis of their need to use aids and appliances.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39637","39637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523658","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Access to Work programme for young deaf people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39610","39610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523659","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of reductions in funding for the Health and Safety Executive in the period to 2019-20 on occupational health and safety; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39615","39615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523660","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people who qualify for personal independence payments on the basis of their need of use of aids and appliances have arthritis.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39634","39634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523661","2016-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times he has visited Scotland in an official capacity since the 2015 General Election; and what meetings were held on each such visit.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39842","39842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523662","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of workforce confidence in the safe operation of commercial helicopter transport in the North Sea oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39826","39826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523663","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of (a) Airbus EC225 and (b) AS332 helicopters have been withdrawn from commercial service in the UK North Sea oil and gas sector since the fatal incident off the coast of Bergen, Norway on 29 April 2016.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39822","39822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523664","2016-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to increase the range of statistics that his Department collects on income mobility.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39725","39725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523665","2016-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Welfare Reform and Work Act 2016 on access to housing for post-release young offenders.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39688","39688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523666","2016-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Welfare Reform and Work Act 2016 on access to housing for post-release offenders.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39687","39687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523667","2016-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Welfare Reform and Work Act 2016 on access to housing for victims of domestic violence.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39686","39686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523668","2016-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Welfare Reform and Work Act 2016 on access to housing for people with dementia.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39685","39685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524536","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the provisions of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 have been used to (a) protect victims of slavery and (b) target traffickers.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905365","905365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524537","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons people who have leave to remain in the UK while seeking permanent residence do not have the right to work.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905363","905363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524538","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has set a timetable for returning foreign national offenders remaining in UK prisons and communities to their countries of origin.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905366","905366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524539","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to ensure that Home Office rules do not deter women who are victims of domestic violence from accessing protection.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905370","905370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524540","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Immigration Rules on facilitating family reunification.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905362","905362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524541","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what meetings she plans to hold with the Mayor of London and the Deputy Mayor for Policing and Crime to discuss the policing structure in London.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905368","905368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524542","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Modern Slavery Act 2015.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905371","905371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524543","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of General Policy Recommendation No.16, by the European Commission against Racism and Intolerance, adopted on 16 March 2016, that doctors, teachers, landlords and other social service providers should not be obliged to report illegal immigrants.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905364","905364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524544","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to promote joint working between police forces and fire services to improve the service they provide to the public.","Biography information for Amanda Milling","Amanda Milling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905372","905372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522940","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) representations he has received from and (b) meetings his Department has had with companies based in the British Overseas Territories on the future of the Land Registry.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39278","39278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522941","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the letter he received from the hon. Member of Tottenham of 2 June 2016, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the privatisation of the Land Registry on the amount of money related to corruption entering the UK property market.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39280","39280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522942","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the letter he received from the hon. Member of Tottenham of 2 June 2016, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the privatisation of the Land Registry on transparency in the UK property market (a) in general and (b) with regards to public records of the corporate and beneficial ownership of properties owned by offshore companies.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39281","39281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522943","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to ensure that Land Registry service fees do not increase in the event of the privatisation of the Land Registry.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39282","39282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522944","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to ensure that information held by the Land Registry that is subject to Freedom of Information requests will continue to be covered by the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in the event of the privatisation of the Land Registry.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39283","39283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522945","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of Engineering and Physical Sciences Research Council and UK Space Agency cross-boundary research proposals submitted through the Joint Electronic Submission System received funding in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39309","39309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522946","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that UK businesses operating in Colombia respect the UN Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39314","39314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522947","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, on BIS consultation, HCWS30, what the evidential basis is for the decision to reduce the number of policy roles from 2,000 to 1,500 in his Department; and how many of those 1,500 staff will be allocated to which policy areas.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39323","39323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522948","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 12 May 2016 to Question 36974, on Department for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many policy staff are based at each of those 14 locations.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39324","39324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522949","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many live vacancies his Department currently has for policy roles.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39322","39322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522950","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in (a) Burnley and (b) Lancashire are qualified to National Qualifications Framework level 2 or above.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39334","39334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522951","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many of his Department's staff based at St Paul's Place, Sheffield, have a length of tenure of (a) under one year, (b) between one and five years, (c) between five and 10 years and (d) over 10 years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39340","39340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522952","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, on BIS consultation, HCWS30, how much vacant office space there currently is at the 1 Victoria Street offices.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39341","39341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522953","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, on BIS consultation, HCWS30, in which ways operating split-site and split-team working would put a strain on organisational effectiveness.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39342","39342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522954","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of research proposals submitted through the Joint Electronic Submission System which have been judged to cross the boundary between the Engineering and Physical Sciences Research Council and the UK Space Agency have gone through to peer review.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39343","39343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522955","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what mechanism exists to ensure that research proposals which have been judged to cross the boundary between the Engineering and Physical Sciences Research Council and the UK Space Agency proceed to peer review.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39344","39344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522956","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39375","39375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522957","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39394","39394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522958","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, on BIS consultation, HCWS30, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision to centralise policy functions in London on (a) the morale of staff working on higher education reform in the Department's Sheffield office and (b) his Department's ability to retain higher education policy officials.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39338","39338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522959","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, on BIS consultation, HCWS30, what proportion of his Department's £350 million projected savings by 2020 he expects to be achieved as a result of the decision to centralise policy functions in London.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39339","39339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522960","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37459, whether he plans to provide additional funding or other assistance to college governing bodies which need to assess the effect of changes on groups protected by the Equalities Act 2010; what estimate he has made of the average cost to colleges of making such an assessment; and if he will make an estimate of the potential cost to his Department of conducting a single equality impact assessment on its policy of merging further education colleges.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39355","39355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522961","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to attract more manufacturing jobs to the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39365","39365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522962","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016 on BIS consultation, HCWS30, whether his Department considered alternative solutions to closure of his Department's Sheffield office at St Paul's Place to address the strain on organisational effectiveness caused by split-site working.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39357","39357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522963","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016 on BIS consultation, HCWS30, how his Department plans to ensure organisational effectiveness in the operation of the proposed Business, Innovation and Skills regional presence.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39358","39358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522964","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016 on BIS consultation, HCWS30, whether he has made an assessment of the implications of the decision to create a combined Business, Innovation and Skills headquarters and policy function in London for the Government's objective to move graduate recruitment outside London.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39360","39360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522965","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016 on BIS consultation, HCWS30, what assessment he has made of the maximum potential savings that could be made by reducing headcount in the (a) London office at 1 Victoria Street and (b) Sheffield office at St Paul's Place through natural attrition, vacancy management and recruitment freezes.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39361","39361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522966","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016 on BIS consultation, HCWS30, what difficulties his Department experienced with split-site working in response to the steel crisis and Eurozone contingency planning.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39359","39359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522967","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39462","39462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522968","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39463","39463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522969","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39376","39376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522970","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department and its executive agencies spent on the publications (a) Who's Who, (b) Burke's Peerage and (c) Debrett's in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39447","39447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522971","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Prime Minister's Office spent on the publications (a) Who's Who, (b) Burke's Peerage and (c) Debrett's in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39448","39448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522972","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on his Department's plans to diversify the civil service.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39321","39321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522973","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the Government has made on implementing its policy to move graduate recruitment outside London and establish a regional assessment centre.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39302","39302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522974","2016-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the right hon. Member for Chingford and Woodford Green received a severance package following his resignation from the post of Secretary of State for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39306","39306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522975","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that people who are not eligible to vote in the EU referendum and who have received ballot papers in error are not able to use those ballot papers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39294","39294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522976","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information the Government has provided to British citizens living abroad who are eligible to vote in the EU referendum on that referendum.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39295","39295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522977","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was allocated to the married couples tax allowance in 2015-16; and how much was spent on that allowance in that year.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39336","39336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522978","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been allocated in the current financial year to the married couples tax allowance; and how much he expects the Government to spend on that allowance in this financial year.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39337","39337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522979","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's policy is on requests from taxation treaty partners for changes to the levels of source taxation in such treaties.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39346","39346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522980","2016-06-09","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's policy is on requests from developing countries with whom the UK has taxation treaties to renegotiate the terms of such treaties.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39345","39345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522981","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to regulate the level of bank account charges in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39461","39461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522982","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39478","39478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522983","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39391","39391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522984","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39407","39407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522985","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that every region in the UK benefits from future economic growth.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39428","39428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522986","2016-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39464","39464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522987","2016-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39395","39395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522988","2016-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39377","39377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522989","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on the National Litter Strategy which was announced on 5 December 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39439","39439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522990","2016-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2016 to Question 38323, whether an annual record is kept by his Department of locations visited by Ministers and officials of his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39438","39438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522991","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of how many full-time equivalent civil servants will support the West Midlands Combined Authority in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39484","39484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522992","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to relocate Civil Service staff from London to the West Midlands to support the West Midlands Combined Authority Deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39486","39486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522993","2016-06-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that legacy funding from the Government for the Great Exhibition of the North is spent effectively.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39354","39354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522994","2016-06-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment the Government has made of the contribution of the work of the Olympic Legacy Park in Sheffield to breaking down distinctions between sport and wider physical activity.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39320","39320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522995","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the one per cent rise from 2016-17 on the (a) wage levels in real terms, (b) living standards and (c) disposable income of workers in the Information Commissioner's Office to the end of this Parliament.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39308","39308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522996","2016-06-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39378","39378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522997","2016-06-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39396","39396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522998","2016-06-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39465","39465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522999","2016-06-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons the food and drink industry does not meet his Department's criteria for inclusion on its list of creative industries.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39414","39414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523000","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39466","39466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523001","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39397","39397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523002","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39379","39379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523003","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has conducted of whether military personnel and contractors are able safely to load and unload equipment from Ministry of Defence vessels onto the pier head at Ascension Island.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39460","39460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523004","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the defence procurement budget was spent on foreign military sales in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39498","39498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523005","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the defence budget was spent on foreign military sales in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39499","39499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523006","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many foreign military sales contracts there have been since 2010; and what the value was of those contracts.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39500","39500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523007","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts on the target to spend two per cent of GDP on defence.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39329","39329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523008","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to build smaller warships.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39328","39328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523009","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Challenger 2 Main Battle Tanks are held in reserve in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39350","39350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523010","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what will comprise a Carrier Escort Group in respect of (a) air-defence, (b) counter-mine and (c) anti-submarine escorts.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39351","39351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523011","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which regiments of the Royal Armoured Corps are equipped with the Challenger 2 Main Battle Tank; and what the allocation is to each such regiment of such tanks.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39352","39352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523012","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Challenger 2 Battle Tanks are maintained in Germany; and what the state of readiness is of such tanks.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39353","39353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523013","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what detailed plans he has for the defence of the UK.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39284","39284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523014","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department first knew of the possible psychotic side effects of Lariam form of mefloquine.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39289","39289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523015","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children living in the Copeland constituency have been eligible to receive free school meals in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39296","39296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523016","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with special needs or disabilities are in mainstream schools in (a) Lancashire and (b) Burnley.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39362","39362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523017","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school breakfast clubs there are in (a) Burnley and (b) Lancashire.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39363","39363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523018","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of qualified early years teachers in nurseries.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39347","39347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523019","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the level of affordability of childcare.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39348","39348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523020","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to implement the provision of 15 additional hours of free childcare for working parents provided for under the Childcare Act 2016.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39349","39349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523021","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the National pupil projections statistics release, published on 22 July 2015, if she will publish updated pupil projection data prior to 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39373","39373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523022","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the National pupil projections statistics release, published on 22 July 2015, if she will publish the (a) assumptions and (b) estimated total migration figures that were used in the calculation of the (i) migrant component of the principal population projection and (ii) high migrant variant in Table 3a of that data release.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39372","39372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523023","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to close attainment gaps within schools in the north of England that are rated good or outstanding.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39369","39369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523024","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the National pupil projections statistics release, published on 22 July 2015, how many people were defined as (a) migrants and (b) children of migrants from (i) other EU member states and (ii) non-EU member states in the principal population projection in each year between 2015 and 2024.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39371","39371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523025","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children from disadvantaged backgrounds in (a) Burnley and (b) Lancashire gained five or more GCSEs including English and mathematics in (i) 2014 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39364","39364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523026","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how  many children in (a) Burnley and (b) Lancashire eligible for free school meals attain level four or above at Key Stage 2 in reading, mathematics and writing.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39333","39333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523027","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the teacher to pupil ratio is in (a) secondary and (b) primary schools in Lancashire.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39332","39332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523028","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what were the 10 foreign languages most spoken by pupils for whom English is listed as an additional language in the annual school census in (a) 2000 and (b) 2015; and how many pupils were recorded as speaking each of those languages in each of those years.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39310","39310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523029","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38393, what estimate she has made of the total amount awarded to schools in pre-opening support grants in each month in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39437","39437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523030","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of staff in her Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39380","39380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523031","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the National pupil projections statistics release, published on 22 July 2015, how many people defined as migrants are included in the principal population projections in each (a) local education authority and (b) region in each year between 2015 and 2024.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39374","39374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523032","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants in her Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39398","39398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523033","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in her Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39467","39467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523034","2016-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in her Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39468","39468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523035","2016-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many civil servants in her Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39399","39399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523036","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will (a) list the titles of and (b) publish on her Department's website all reports prepared by (i) officials of her Department and (ii) contractors for her Department since May 2015 on options for financing new nuclear power plants.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39423","39423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523037","2016-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of staff in her Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39381","39381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523038","2016-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information she has been provided by the Office for Nuclear Regulation to demonstrate the safety of Sizewell B nuclear plant restarting after in-service inspection of the reactor pressure vessel undertaken by EDF; and what assessment she has made of the implications for that process of hydrogen flaking present in the RPV Doel 3 and Tihange 2 reactors in Belgium.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39427","39427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523039","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the oral evidence given by the Minister of State for Energy to the Energy and Climate Change Committee on 24 May 2016, at Question 200, what the basis is for the Minister's statement that the case brought by the government of Austria in the European Court on the European Commission decision on state aid for the Hinkley Point reactor has no merit; and whether that statement refers to lack of legal or of political merit.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39482","39482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523040","2016-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the Civil Nuclear Constabulary conducts an annual survey of its staff.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39287","39287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523041","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Government has made on rebalancing the UK's inland water quotas to smaller, specific locally-based fishing communities.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39285","39285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523042","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department provides to local authorities on the (a) issuing and (b) geographical extent of abatement notices to homes affected by noise nuisance.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39293","39293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523043","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many consignments of dogs were exported from the UK to Hong Kong in the last 12 months; and how many dogs were exported within those consignments.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39331","39331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523044","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to prevent the trade of (a) greyhounds and (b) other animals to countries with little or no protection for animals rights.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39319","39319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523045","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of staff in her Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39382","39382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523046","2016-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential (a) negative and (b) positive effects on (i) society and (ii) human health of an increase in air temperatures arising from climate change.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39425","39425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523047","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many civil servants in her Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39400","39400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523048","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in her Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39469","39469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523049","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 17 November 2015 to Question 15358, what recent progress has been made on the review into the Code of Practice for the Welfare of Privately Kept Non-Human Primates.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39436","39436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523050","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39470","39470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523051","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39401","39401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523052","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the application from Mr Hamde Abu Rahma to visit Scotland was rejected; and if she will instigate a review of that decision.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39424","39424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523053","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39383","39383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523054","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department and its executive agencies spent on the publications (a) Who's Who, (b) Burke's Peerage and (c) Debrett's in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39451","39451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523055","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to develop a long-term strategy for Ascension Island.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39456","39456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523056","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the US administration to secure its co-operation in surveillance and enforcement of closed marine areas in (a) British Indian Ocean Territory and (b) Ascension Island.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39458","39458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523057","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimates his Department has received for the cost of refurbishing the pier head at Ascension Island.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39457","39457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523058","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on the future of the Chagos Islanders.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39440","39440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523059","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterparts in the Iranian government on violations of human rights through executions, torture and arbitrary arrests in that country.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39446","39446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523060","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Colombia.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39313","39313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523061","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which overseas trips by Ministers of the Scottish Government were supported by (a) his Department and (b) British embassies and consulates in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39335","39335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523062","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to implement the recommendation in the report by Human Rights Watch and the Bahrain Institute for Rights and Democracy, The Blood of People Who Don't Co-operate, published in November 2015, that the Government should suspend support for security service reform until the other recommendations of that report are complied with.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39304","39304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523063","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what issues the Government plans to discuss with the President of Colombia during his state visit to the UK in November 2016.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39316","39316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523064","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has (a) received and (b) made to the Egyptian government on investigations in Egypt into non-governmental organisations and their funding which form part of Case No. 173 (2011).","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39317","39317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523065","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the report, The Blood of People Who Don't Cooperate, published by Human Rights Watch in November 2015, if he will review his Department's policy of providing funding for the training of prison and security officers in Bahrain.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39356","39356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523066","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department provided to the delegation to Iran led by the Rt. hon. Member for Gordon and the hon. Member for Ochil and South Perthshire in December 2015.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39370","39370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523067","2016-06-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what reports he has received on the costs, time taken and other difficulties related to the visa process for UK musicians performing in the US; and whether his Department has made representations on those costs and difficulties to the US government.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39286","39286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523068","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average proportion of GP's working time spent outside of the surgery is.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39291","39291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523069","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of a quadrivalent vaccine programme for school-aged boys equivalent to that in place for school-aged girls; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39297","39297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523070","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the average waiting time between cancer referral and diagnosis in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39298","39298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523071","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of how many men who have sex with men will receive the HPV vaccination as part of the proposed pilot.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39299","39299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523072","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pilot areas his Department plans for the HPV vaccination for men who have sex with men; where his Department plans for those pilots to take place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39300","39300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523073","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings of the Royal College of Physicians' report, End of Life Care Audit: Dying in Hospital, published in March 2015, what steps his Department has taken to improve end-of-life care in the NHS.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39279","39279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523074","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost to the NHS of each new HIV infection.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39368","39368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523075","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GPs who have left the NHS since 1 January 2016.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39318","39318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523076","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the average waiting time between cancer diagnosis and treatment in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39311","39311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523077","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will arrange for the Chief Executive of West Midlands Ambulance Service to send a reply to the hon. Member for Walsall North to his letter of 9 May 2016; and if he will ascertain for what reason there was no acknowledgment or substantive reply to that letter.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39312","39312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523078","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the proportion of people in the UK (a) who smoke and (b) from other EU member states who smoke.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39303","39303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523079","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of pharmacies which will potentially be affected financially by planned changes to funding in the Bradford District Care Trust area.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39330","39330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523080","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) capacity of and (b) skills and knowledge of local mainstream advice and advocacy services in Lambeth, Southwark and Lewisham health authority area to be able to meet the support needs of local people living with HIV following implementation of the proposed reduction in specialist HIV support services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39453","39453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523081","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to meet the (a) advice and advocacy and (b) psychosocial needs of people living with HIV in Lambeth, Southwark and Lewisham health authority area following implementation of the proposed reduction in specialist HIV support services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39454","39454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523082","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 38058, if he will make it his policy to collect centrally information on the costs incurred by the NHS for legal advice and representation at inquests by cause of death.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39501","39501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523083","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how long a person with HIV will have to wait to access psychosocial support in Lambeth, Southwark and Lewisham health authority area following implementation of the proposed reduction in specialist HIV support services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39452","39452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523084","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the possible benefits of pre-exposure prophylaxis for preventing HIV exposure.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39481","39481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523085","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39384","39384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523086","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the NHS's policy is on prescribing gluten-free food items to coeliacs; and whether any changes have recently been made to the allowance for such items.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39426","39426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523087","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges on the introduction of microscopic magnetic bead injections for the treatment of strokes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39418","39418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523088","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to reduce bed-blocking in hospitals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39419","39419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523089","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39402","39402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523090","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39471","39471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523091","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to make the Cefaly headband for the treatment of migraines available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39420","39420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523092","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38480, whether his Department is taking steps in response to use of the NHS logo by the Vote Leave Campaign.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39429","39429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523093","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37840, what discussions he had with (a) the Chief Nursing Officer for England and (b) the Chief Executive of NHS England about replacing bursaries; and what views those officials put forward in those discussions.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39430","39430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523094","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to reduce the time taken for a shotgun and firearm application to be processed.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39415","39415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523095","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of incidents of drunkenness on aeroplanes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39416","39416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523096","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many reported drink-related violent incidents involved the use of alcohol bottles in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39417","39417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523097","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in her Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39472","39472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523098","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil servants in her Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39403","39403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523099","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of staff in her Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39385","39385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523100","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department and its executive agencies spent on the publications (a) Who's Who, (b) Burke's Peerage and (c) Debrett's in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39449","39449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523101","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of (a) immigration rules in general and (b) income requirements on the eligibility of British citizens with non-EU partners to return to the UK and the incidence of family separation.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39422","39422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523102","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to improve the ability of Border Force to gather and exploit information to improve its performance in enforcing general maritime security; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39496","39496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523103","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to improve levels of knowledge within Border Force about the threats and risks associated with maritime and aviation border security; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39497","39497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523104","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has taken steps to make advance passenger information available to Border Force general maritime officers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39493","39493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523105","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many carrier liability charges were issued to commercial transport firms, airlines, ferry companies and other operators for transporting illegal immigrants into the UK in total by (a) port and (b) firm in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39494","39494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523106","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children arrived in the UK and claimed asylum (a) for each country of origin, (b) by each commercial company who provided transport if known, (c) at each port and (d) in total in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39495","39495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523107","2016-06-09","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to local authorities on the Psychoactive Substances Act 2016.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39305","39305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523108","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government's policy is on the use of child advocates to support social workers working with unaccompanied migrant children.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39292","39292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523109","2016-06-08","Department for International Development","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government will be allocating official development assistance to Sri Lanka in response to the appeal by the Sri Lankan government for international finance for reconstruction following the floods in that country.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39288","39288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523110","2016-06-08","Department for International Development","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether other government departments are required to provide evidence to her Department that official development assistance disbursed by that department tackling global challenges is in the national interest.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39301","39301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523111","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the peace process in Colombia.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39315","39315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523112","2016-06-08","Department for International Development","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to include best practice bio security and waste management requirement clauses in the next contract for the Pitcairn Islands supply ship.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39459","39459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523113","2016-06-08","Department for International Development","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of staff in her Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39386","39386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523114","2016-06-08","Department for International Development","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many civil servants in her Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39404","39404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523115","2016-06-08","Department for International Development","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in her Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39473","39473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523116","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39474","39474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523117","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38441, what role he has asked the Chairman of the Parole Board, Professor Nick Hardwick, to undertake in relation to people serving sentences of imprisonment for public protection.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39431","39431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523118","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to answer Question 37057, tabled on 18 May 2016.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39432","39432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523119","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38441, what estimate he has made of the date by which all prisoners serving sentences of imprisonment for public protection whose tariffs have expired will be released.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39433","39433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523120","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38441, what average rate people serving sentences of imprisonment for public protection have served over their tariff.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39434","39434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523121","2016-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38441, what additional resources have been allocated to the management of prisoners serving sentences of imprisonment for public protection in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39435","39435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523122","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39405","39405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523123","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of re-offending.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39409","39409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523124","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to reduce re-offending.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39410","39410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523125","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39387","39387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523126","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people with imprisonment for public protection sentences have been recalled to custody since the introduction of that sentence; and how many such people have been subsequently re-released.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39443","39443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523127","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people with imprisonment for public protection sentences have applied to have their licences terminated; and how many such applications have been successful.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39444","39444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523128","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will review the automatic imposition of a life licence for all people with imprisonment for public protection sentences released from prison.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39445","39445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523129","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department and its executive agencies spent on the publications (a) Who's Who, (b) Burke's Peerage and (c) Debrett's in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39450","39450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523130","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has issued guidance to the Parole Board on the need speedily to review imprisonment for public protection cases following recall.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39441","39441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523131","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons people serving imprisonment for public protection sentences were recalled to custody in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39442","39442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523132","2016-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will make it her policy to hold discussions with the Northern Ireland Executive on the Offences Against the Person Act 1861.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39307","39307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523133","2016-06-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of staff in her Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39388","39388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523134","2016-06-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in her Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39475","39475"
