"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176198","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral Answer of 26 January 2015, Official Report, column 547, on mental health (employment opportunities), what each innovative approach to employment support for those with mental health problems is; where each pilot is taking place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222217","222217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176199","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people who qualify for attendance allowance are made aware of the scheme and of their eligibility for it.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222151","222151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176200","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral Answer of 26 January 2015, Official Report, column 550, on job creation (Yorkshire), what the evidential basis is for the statement that of the jobs created in Shipley and Yorkshire, 80 per cent are full-time and 75 per cent are managerial and professional.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222218","222218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176368","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support economic growth in coastal communities.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907348","907348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176935","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent comparative assessment his Department has made of the supply of and demand for affordable housing in (a) Bristol and (b) the South West region.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907351","907351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176936","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the use of neighbourhood plans to ensure development is in accordance with the wishes of local residents.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907343","907343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176937","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to support local shops and high streets.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907349","907349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176938","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of real terms cumulative changes in local authority spending power on services in communities with the greatest needs since 2010-11.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907340","907340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176939","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to support local shops and high streets.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907350","907350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175645","2015-01-28","Attorney General","2015-01-26","To ask the Attorney General, what guidance has been issued by the Crown Prosecution Service on prosecuting digital and online crime.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221998","221998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175646","2015-01-28","Attorney General","2015-01-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many recruitment and employment agencies the Law Officers' Departments have used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222076","222076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175647","2015-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222075","222075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175648","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average time was for businesses applying for and receiving financial support under the Apprenticeship Grant for Employers Scheme; and what (a) benchmarks and (b) targets he has set for that time period.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222106","222106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175649","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices aged (a) 16 to 18, (b) 19 to 24 and (c) 25 or over are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222107","222107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175650","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what employment protections exist for staff in the offshore oil and gas sector in the event of an employer seeking to replace them with non-UK based workers on lower rates of pay.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221933","221933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175651","2015-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much and what proportion of land was registered in Wales in each year since 1985.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221987","221987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175652","2015-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the ownership of unregistered land in Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221988","221988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175653","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which winning bidders have withdrawn from each bidding round of the Regional Growth Fund in each region; on what date each such withdrawal took place; and what the monetary value was of each such bid.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222042","222042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175654","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many firms have received financial support under the Export Refinancing Scheme to date; and on what date each such instance of support was received.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222043","222043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175655","2015-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship starts there were in Stafford constituency in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222041","222041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175656","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the retail and wholesale industry.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221980","221980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175657","2015-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value is of student grant over-payments by the Student Loans Company since 2010.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221965","221965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175658","2015-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to tackle student grant overpayments by the Student Loans Company.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221966","221966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175659","2015-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many explosions of manhole covers there have been since 2000; in how many such cases people were injured; how many explosions have occurred twice in the same location; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221975","221975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175660","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2014 to Question 208599, on the minimum wage, how many notices of underpayment have been issued since 1 October 2013 in cases where the investigation commenced on or after that date.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221930","221930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175661","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect that the present low price of oil is having on the preservation and development of the oil and gas industry skills base.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221931","221931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175662","2015-01-28","Cabinet Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost has been to the public purse of independent policy advisers across all government departments since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221941","221941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175663","2015-01-28","Cabinet Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222077","222077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175664","2015-01-29","Cabinet Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women were diagnosed with cervical cancer in (a) the borough of Barnsley and (b) the UK in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222073","222073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175665","2015-01-28","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222096","222096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175666","2015-01-28","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints his Department has received concerning the inability of people who have applied for pensioner bonds to have their applications dealt with owing to breakdowns in the website of the agency handling the sale.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221926","221926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175667","2015-01-28","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what value of pensioner bonds have been sold to applicants from (a) Northern Ireland, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) England.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221927","221927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175668","2015-01-28","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total value was of the pensioner bonds that were issued in the recent sale of those assets.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221928","221928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175669","2015-01-29","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on using the tax system to incentivise (a) job sharing, (b) maintenance backlog work, (c) drilling work and (d) skills training in the offshore oil and gas industry during the current period of low oil prices.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221932","221932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175670","2015-01-29","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of claims for interest rate swap mis-selling have reached the redress offer and acceptance stage; and what proportion these represent of redress offers made for (a) Barclays, (b) RBS, (c) HSBC, (d) Lloyds and (e) Standard Chartered.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221979","221979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175671","2015-01-28","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Exchequer of reducing (a) Band A and (b) Band B air passenger duty by 50 per cent, excluding Scotland, from 1 April 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222011","222011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175672","2015-01-28","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2015 to Question 218249, if he will provide a breakdown of the figures in the Answer by (a) employment sector and (b) gender; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222025","222025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175673","2015-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on collecting payments for repairs to leasehold properties covered by the Decent Homes programme.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222030","222030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175674","2015-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to answer Question 219077, tabled on 17 December 2014.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222070","222070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175675","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to protect bereaved families if their funeral plan provider goes out of business; and if he will review the effectiveness of procedures in place for those circumstances.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222074","222074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175676","2015-01-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222078","222078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175677","2015-01-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222079","222079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175678","2015-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222080","222080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175679","2015-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2015 to Question 220804, on military aircraft, if he will place a copy of the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory document in the Library.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222053","222053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175680","2015-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has for further reductions to the headcount of the Army.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221939","221939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175681","2015-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the year-on-year future spending on the development phase of the replacement for Trident.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222052","222052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175682","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department recently further delayed publication of the investigation into the case of Corporal Stewart McLaughlin; and what date his Department plans to publish the findings of that investigation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222048","222048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175683","2015-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Minister made the decision to conduct the Army Command Review; and when that decision was made.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222006","222006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175684","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to conduct command reviews for the Royal Air Force or the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222014","222014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175685","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to publish the Army Command Review upon its completion.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222015","222015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175686","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to conduct command reviews for the reserve branches of the Army, Royal Air Force and Royal Navy, similiar to that being carried out for the Regular Army under the Army 2020 process.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222016","222016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175687","2015-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date the review of the numbers of senior ranks in the Army as part of Army 2020 will consult with (a) NATO allies and (b) other groups.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221996","221996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175688","2015-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when exactly the review of the numbers of senior ranks in the Army will conclude.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222003","222003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175689","2015-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff work on the Army Command Review.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222004","222004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175690","2015-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the Army Command Review will cost to produce.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222005","222005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175691","2015-01-28","Cabinet Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Office has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222081","222081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175692","2015-01-28","Department for Education","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many recruitment and employment agencies her Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222082","222082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175693","2015-01-29","Department for Education","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many weapons were confiscated from pupils in each age group in schools in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222069","222069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175694","2015-01-29","Department for Education","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils attended (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five and (f) more than five (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in the most recent school year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222020","222020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175695","2015-01-29","Department for Education","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils in each year group received (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five and (f) more than five fixed-term exclusions in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222019","222019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175696","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information his Department holds on the number of families with children in (a) North West Durham constituency and (b) the UK who are currently in debt to their energy suppliers.","Biography information for Pat Glass","Pat Glass","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222023","222023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175697","2015-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will take steps to ensure that the recent oil price reduction will lead to a reduction in the price of liquefied petroleum gas in rural areas.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221991","221991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175698","2015-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222083","222083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175699","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will amend the Social and Environment Statutory Guidance to the Gas and Electric Market Authority to include families with children as a vulnerable group.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222108","222108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175700","2015-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of animals which died from consumption of ethylene-glycol based anti-freeze in the last year; and what steps the Government has taken to reduce the number of animal deaths from ingestion of that substance.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222056","222056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175701","2015-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many recruitment and employment agencies her Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222084","222084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175702","2015-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what further investment in Norfolk's flood and sea defences she plans to make; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221989","221989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175703","2015-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will ban the use of battery cages to confine breeding pheasants and partridges used for sporting purposes.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222009","222009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175704","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the article by Christophe McGlade and Paul Ekins entitled The geographical distribution of fossil fuels unused when limiting global warming to 2°C, published in Nature on 8 January 2015, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies of the research contained in that paper.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221959","221959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175705","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the protection of cephalopods under the provisions of Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 as amended.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221976","221976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175706","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the trade (a) in the UK and (b) internationally in illegal medicines made from endangered species.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221977","221977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175707","2015-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to ensure that supermarkets (a) do not sell British milk below the cost of production and (b) include British milk under their Fairtrade agendas.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221946","221946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175708","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Minister for Agriculture and Rural Development in the Northern Ireland Executive on the effect of the recent reduction in milk prices on dairy farmers.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221949","221949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175709","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations she has received on the implementation of the basic farm payment scheme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221950","221950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175710","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the ability of (a) decapod crustaceans and (b) cephalopods to experience pain.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221955","221955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175711","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance the Government is supplying to the Nigerian government in the form of intelligence and counter-terrorism expertise to help in the fight against Boko Haram.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221952","221952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175712","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the situation in Libya on UK-Libyan relations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221953","221953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175713","2015-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the Kurdistan regional government did not participate in the London conference of the International Coalition against ISIS in January 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221961","221961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175714","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will commission research into possible links between ISIL and the smuggling of contraband tobacco.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221957","221957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175715","2015-01-28","HM Treasury","2015-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his European counterparts on measures to reduce error in the accounts of the EU to a point at which they will not be qualified by the European Court of Auditors.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221938","221938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175716","2015-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on UK trade of plans to establish a Free Trade Area of the Asia Pacific.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221944","221944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175717","2015-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent contracts his Department has had with the pro-democracy movement in Hong Kong; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221945","221945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175718","2015-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his overseas counterparts on the multilateral disarmament of nuclear weapons.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222027","222027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175719","2015-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken towards its aim of achieving nuclear disarmament.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222035","222035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175720","2015-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Egyptian counterparts on the closure of the Rafah crossing.","Biography information for James Morris","James Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222007","222007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175721","2015-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the terror threat to Jewish targets in Europe.","Biography information for James Morris","James Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222008","222008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175722","2015-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222085","222085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175723","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representatives of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region government met the Minister of State at the Foreign and Commonwealth Office during his visit to that region in January 2015.","Biography information for Sir Richard Ottaway","Sir Richard Ottaway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222047","222047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175724","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which organisations (a) were invited to and (b) attended roundtable discussions with him regarding conversion therapy in early March or late April 2014.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222055","222055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175725","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Questions HL4063 and HL4228, how the Expert Panel convened by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority (HFEA) were assured that the children concerned were genetically normal; whether each of the mitochondrial diseases listed in Annex D of the Department of Health's consultation document Mitochondrial Donation is associated with an abnormal karyotype; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the correspondence between the member of the HFEA's Expert Panel and the Zhang research group.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222066","222066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175726","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what amount of contribution private healthcare providers which are unable to arrange their own insurance make to the Clinical Negligence Scheme for Trusts; and whether that amount is the same as the contributions required of NHS trusts.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222058","222058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175727","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will clarify the steps taken to ensure that private healthcare providers performing NHS contracts hold sufficient indemnity cover to meet all future medical negligence claims and associated legal costs against the NHS arising from negligent treatment by the private provider.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222057","222057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175728","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will require contracts between NHS hospitals and private surgery providers to include a clause preventing the NHS from being sued for libel if it publishes any report investigating damage caused by surgery carried out by the provider.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222100","222100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175729","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure NHS hospitals are not sued for damages if they sub-contract or outsource surgery to a provider which then injures patients as a result of negligence.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222101","222101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175730","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which voluntary registers have applied for accreditation as accredited voluntary registers with the Professional Standards Authority (PSA); and which such registers are (a) awaiting a decision and (b) have been rejected by the PSA.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222102","222102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175731","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222087","222087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175732","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of levels of hand hygiene compliance in hospital Trusts.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221964","221964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175733","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) actuarial analysis and (b) financial modelling was carried out before a decision was taken on self-insuring by NHS trusts.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221983","221983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175734","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on awareness campaigns for children's cancer since May 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222049","222049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175735","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many amenity beds there were in the NHS in each year from 2009-10 to the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222051","222051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175736","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government plans to commission Translarna during NHS England's public consultations on its principles and approach to decision making on drug licensing.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222036","222036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175737","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures apply to independent sector places when there has been a failure to comply with the requirements of the revised Procedures for the Approval of Independent Sector Places for the Termination of Pregnancy and his Department's Guidance in Relation to the Requirements of the Abortion Act, both published in May 2014.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222044","222044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175738","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the results of his Department's audit of specialised neuromuscular services in the North East.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222045","222045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175739","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to make Translarna available whilst NHS England's public consultations are completed on the principles and approach to decision making on drug licensing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222037","222037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175740","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for how long NHS England's public consultations about the principles and approach to decision making on drug licensing will last.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222038","222038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175741","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority Expert Panel became aware of the 2003 study by John Zhang et al reported in Fertility and Sterility September 2003 Volume 80, Supplement 3, Page 56.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222039","222039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175742","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what financial and ethical stringency tests his Department applies to (a) private healthcare providers bidding for NHS contracts and (b) the parent companies of those providers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222040","222040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175743","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce conditions for outsourced NHS work by the private healthcare providers to waive any right to commercial confidentiality and abide by the obligations of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 for the production of relevant documents and safety and performance data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222028","222028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175744","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many discharge episodes there have been with a (a) primary and (b) secondary diagnosis of coronary heart disease in (i) each clinical commissioning group or its predecessor organisation and (ii) England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222024","222024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175745","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Royal London Hospital in Whitechapel is meeting the four-hour A&E waiting times target.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222029","222029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175746","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Ambulatory Care Centre at the Whittington Hosital since it opened in 2012.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222026","222026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175747","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons NHS trusts are not allowed to enter into insurance arrangements with commercial insurers.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221995","221995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175748","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2015 to Question 221099, and with reference to his speech to the King's Fund on 13 November 2014 in which he cited the claim by the London Health Commission that the total value of surplus NHS estate in the capital is worth £1.5 billion, what information he holds on the evidential basis of that claim; what assessment he has made of whether that claim is compatible with the data given in the Answer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222022","222022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175749","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to incentivise NHS trusts to reduce levels of healthcare-associated infections.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221942","221942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175750","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an estimate of the (a) average and (b) total cost to the NHS of healthcare-associated infections.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221940","221940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175751","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Public Health England on targeted campaigns in regions where HPV vaccination rates have fallen below the national average; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221935","221935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175752","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) NICE and (b) the Care Quality Commission about healthcare-associated infections in the last 12 months; and what steps he is taking as a result of those discussions.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221936","221936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175753","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to report on progress on the National Service Framework for long-term conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221937","221937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175754","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2014 to Question 216805, whether he plans to make representations to the German government over compensation for British survivors of Thalidomide.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221974","221974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175755","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance the Government provides to hospitals on how to mitigate the risk of (a) incidents where costs might exceed the £1 million NHS Litigation Authority Property Expenses Scheme limit and (b) other major incidents.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221962","221962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175756","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Cancer Drugs Fund list will next be updated.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221954","221954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175757","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has plans to introduce plain packaging for spirits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221956","221956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175758","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved administrations about possible additional measures to respond to an outbreak of Ebola in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221951","221951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175759","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with the British Shooting Sports Council and the British Association for Shooting and Conservation on flagging up the medical records of people who hold shotgun and firearms certificates.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221947","221947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175760","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on (a) academic and (b) other research conducted in (i) the UK and (ii) other European countries that establishes a link between the funding of ISIL and the trade in contraband (A) cigarettes and (B) other goods.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221948","221948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175761","2015-01-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to regulate social media providers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221971","221971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175762","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she has issued to police forces on the steps they should take to investigate allegations of digital or cyber-crime.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221973","221973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175763","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she has issued to police forces on how they record digital, cyber and online crime.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221969","221969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175764","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she has issued to police forces on training for police officers on tackling digital, cyber- and online crime.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221972","221972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175765","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on sharing intelligence information to counter terrorism in Europe.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222021","222021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175766","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Home Office enforcement visits were undertaken without notice to (a) employers, (b) colleges and (c) universities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222012","222012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175767","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that medical records flag up people who hold shotgun and firearms certificates and that appropriate medical conditions are rapidly communicated to the police.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222010","222010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175768","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many allegations of misconduct were made against the Police Service in each of the last five years; and how many police officers have been dismissed for misconduct in that period.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222033","222033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175769","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fixed penalty notices were issued for each type of offence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222050","222050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175770","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many instances of online (a) stalking, (b) harassment, (c) fraud and (d) identity theft were reported to the police in the most recent year for which figures are available; and how many of each category of reported instance resulted in a criminal charge.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221994","221994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175771","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in what proportion of complaints of crime reported to the police there was a digital or cyber element in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221992","221992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175772","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training police and crime commissioners and their staff receive on the circumstances of, and responses to, digital and online crime.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221993","221993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175773","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance is issued by (a) her Department, (b) the College of Policing and (c) the Association of Chief Police Officers on the recording and investigation of online and digital crime.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221997","221997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175774","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support services are available for victims of digital and online crime.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221999","221999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175775","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recruitment and employment agencies her Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222088","222088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175776","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department plans to pay (a) Ben Emmerson QC, (b) other legal representatives and (c) panel members for their work on the Child Abuse inquiry.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222105","222105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175777","2015-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of places in refuges for women fleeing domestic violence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222072","222072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175778","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many companies were fined for employing illegal immigrants in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222054","222054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175779","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of child abuse the police recorded in each of the last five years; and how many people have been arrested on charges of child abuse in each force area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222071","222071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175780","2015-01-28","House of Commons Commission","2015-01-26","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many recruitment and employment agencies the House of Commons Commission has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222089","222089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175781","2015-01-28","Department for International Development","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many recruitment and employment agencies her Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222090","222090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175782","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's centrally awarded contracts were won by UK firms in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222001","222001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175783","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which offices of her Department are authorised to invest in returnable capital.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222002","222002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175784","2015-01-28","Department for International Development","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that the World Bank's environmental and social safeguard policies take account of the rights and needs of (a) LGBT people and (b) other vulnerable groups.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221929","221929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175785","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2015 to Question 220282, and with reference to page 234 of the Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, what the reason is for the planned increase in funding to the Department's Caribbean programme in 2014-15 compared with 2013-14.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221958","221958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175786","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what additional funding her Department is providing to mitigate the refugee situation in northern Nigeria and surrounding areas.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221978","221978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175787","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether G4S has replaced the credit union operating at Parc Prison with an in-house saving scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221960","221960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175788","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will direct the National Offender Management Service to ban cigarette smoking on the prison estate.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221967","221967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175789","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason the National Offender Management Service suspended the pilot scheme to ban cigarette smoking on the prison estate.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221968","221968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175790","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions his Department has had with the Prison Officers Association on the proposal to ban cigarette smoking on the prison estate.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221970","221970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175791","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers took sick leave in each prison in England and Wales in each month in 2014.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221984","221984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175792","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many days sick leave were taken by prison officers in each prison in England and Wales in each month in 2014.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221985","221985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175793","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on access to legal aid in family courts of the evidence given on 1 December 2011 to the Justice Committee by the President of the Family Division.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221990","221990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175794","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his estimate he has made of the number of people convicted of an offence involving domestic abuse who were also involved in digital or cyber-crime against the same victim in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222000","222000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175795","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to resume the pilot arrangements for banning cigarette smoking on the prison estate.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222013","222013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175796","2015-01-28","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222091","222091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175797","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the effect of the Criminal Justice and Courts Act 2015 on the number of prison places which are required.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222059","222059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175798","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the effect of section 28 of the Criminal Justice and Courts Act 2015 on the number of prison places which are required.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222060","222060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175799","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Minister plans to answer Question 216465 tabled on 28 November 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222061","222061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175800","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times police cells were used to hold prisoners overnight in each month in 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222062","222062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175801","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the effect of the proposed merger of the South and West Cambridgeshire and North and East Cambridgeshire and Peterborough coroner areas on the time taken for completion of investigations and inquests.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222067","222067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175802","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) coroners, (b) deputy coroners and (c) coroner's staff are employed in (i) South and West Cambridgeshire and (ii) North and East Cambridgeshire and Peterborough coroner areas; and what estimate he has made of how many such employees will be working in the new area after the proposed merger of those areas.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222068","222068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175803","2015-01-28","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many recruitment and employment agencies her Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222092","222092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175804","2015-01-28","Cabinet Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many recruitment and employment agencies 10 Downing Street has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222093","222093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175805","2015-01-29","Prime Minister","2015-01-26","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he will allow a free vote on amendments and new clauses to the Serious Crime Bill dealing with sex-selective abortion.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222017","222017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175806","2015-01-29","Prime Minister","2015-01-26","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he will allow a free vote on the draft Human Fertilisation and Embryology (Mitochondrial Donation) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222018","222018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175807","2015-01-28","Scotland Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222094","222094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175808","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222095","222095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175809","2015-01-29","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221267, what the reasons were for each of the agent's fees of more than £100,000 in financial year 2013-14; and what the amount was that was paid to each agent.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222103","222103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175810","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221267, what the reasons were for each instance of reprographic expenditure totalling more than £10,000 in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222099","222099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175811","2015-01-29","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, to which organisations his Department paid subscriptions of more than £1,000 in 2013-14; and how much his Department paid to each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222064","222064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175812","2015-01-29","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221267, what the reasons were for the 10 largest items of media and publicity expenditure in financial year 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222065","222065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175813","2015-01-29","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221267, which banks charged his Department more than £1,000 in 2013-14; and what the reason was for each such bank charge.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222063","222063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175814","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the at-seat catering service provided under the directly awarded franchise on the Great Western Main Line will be in addition to a buffet car or café-bar on the train.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221986","221986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175815","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the terms of the rail franchise directly awarded to First Great Western in October 2014 retain the role of guard on all trains for the duration of the contract.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221981","221981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175816","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the food for the at-seat catering service provided under the rail franchise directly awarded to First Great Western in October 2014 will be prepared by staff on-board the trains.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221982","221982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175817","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funds will be made available for protection against terrorist attacks on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221943","221943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175818","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the (a) negotiations and (b) consultation on the Cross Country franchise direct award to begin.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221963","221963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175819","2015-01-28","Wales Office","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222097","222097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175820","2015-01-28","Women and Equalities","2015-01-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many recruitment and employment agencies the Government Equalities Office has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222086","222086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175821","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral Answer to the hon. Member for Easington of 26 January 2015 to Question 907220, what the evidential basis was for the statement that according to figures from the International Labour Organisation, youth unemployment is down on the quarter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222104","222104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175822","2015-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222098","222098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175823","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many improvement notices were issued to oil and gas companies operating in the North Sea by the Health and Safety Executive in the period from 1 January 2014 to date; and in how many such cases the company has yet to comply with the improvement notice.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221934","221934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175824","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many job centres there were on 1 January (a) 2010 and (b) 2015; and how many job centres have closed since 1 January 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222031","222031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175825","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost was of maintaining the Jobcentre Plus estate in 2013-14.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222032","222032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175826","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training has been given to staff working in universal credit service centres on dealing with the housing benefit component of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222046","222046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175827","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on rent for the Jobcentre Plus estate in 2013-14.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222034","222034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175936","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support bees and pollinators.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907284","907284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175937","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure the provision of adequate flood protections.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907283","907283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175938","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many UK food and drink products have protected status under European law.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907294","907294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176425","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish without redaction the Shale Gas: Rural Economy Impacts report, published by her Department with redactions in March 2014.","Biography information for Duncan Hames","Duncan Hames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907292","907292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175420","2015-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what retraining his Department provides to reservists who are discharged as a result of injury sustained during training or mobilisation and are unable to resume their civilian occupation as a result.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221824","221824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175421","2015-01-28","Department for Education","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase teacher recruitment in (a) Hertfordshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221823","221823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175422","2015-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the consequences of Iran's refusal to allow International Atomic Energy Agency inspectors access to its Arak and Parchin nuclear-related facilities.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221808","221808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175423","2015-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of Iran's financial and material support for Hezbollah.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221809","221809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175424","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of patients with each type of cancer began first treatment within 62 days of a GP referral at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals in each quarter since 2005.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221810","221810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175425","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of people in the Mansfield and Ashfield Clinical Commissioning Group area waited more than a week to see a GP in each year since that Group was set up.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221811","221811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175426","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of people in the Mansfield and Ashfield Clinical Commissioning Group area who have a preferred GP saw another GP when they last went to their surgery in each year since that Group was set up.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221812","221812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175427","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of people at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals waited more than 18 weeks to start consultant-led treatment for non-urgent conditions in each quarter since 2005.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221813","221813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175428","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) district nurses, (b) health visitors, (c) community psychiatric nurses, (d) community matrons and (e) community learning disability nurses have been employed in each clinical commissioning group area in Nottinghamshire in each year since those groups were set up.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221814","221814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175429","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of patients at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals were seen by a consultant within two weeks of a GP referral with each type of cancer in each quarter since 2005.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221815","221815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175430","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered (a) nurses, (b) midwives, (c) doctors and (d) surgeons have been made redundant at (i) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (ii) Nottingham University Hospitals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221816","221816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175431","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) nurses, (b) doctors, (c) surgeons and (d) midwives have been employed at (i) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (ii) Nottingham University Hospitals in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221817","221817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175432","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training posts for (a) nurses, (b) doctors, (c) surgeons and (d) midwives have been commissioned at (i) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (ii) Nottingham University Hospitals in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221818","221818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175433","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of ambulances have had to queue for more than 30 minutes outside A&E at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals in each quarter since 2005.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221819","221819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175434","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of elective operations were cancelled on or after the day of admission for non-clinical reasons at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals in each quarter since 2005.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221820","221820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175435","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of patients had to wait for four hours or more at A&E at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals in each quarter since 2004.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221821","221821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175436","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients aged over 90 arrived at A&E at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals in a blue light ambulance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221822","221822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175437","2015-01-27","HM Treasury","2015-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he has made on his fiscal consolidation plans.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221838","221838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175438","2015-01-28","HM Treasury","2015-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of cheques sent to HM Revenue and Customs that were fraudulently intercepted and (b) value of these cheques in each month since December 2013.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221869","221869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175439","2015-01-27","HM Treasury","2015-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Action Plan on Modern Slavery, to be prepared by HM Revenue and Customs' new Modern Slavery Strategic Lead, will be published.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221881","221881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175440","2015-01-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the comparative change has been in local authority funding at the 10 (a) most and (b) least deprived local authority areas since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221842","221842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175441","2015-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to reach a decision on the future use of the shipbuilding sheds in Portsmouth which have been handed back to his Department by BAE Systems.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221835","221835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175442","2015-01-27","Department for Education","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the Philips HeartStart FRx devices on which her Department negotiated a discounted price have been sold to which schools.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221839","221839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175443","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the feasibility of teaching water safety education in schools as a distinct topic from the national curriculum requirement for schools to teach children to swim.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221844","221844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175444","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools currently teach water safety education.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221845","221845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175445","2015-01-28","Department for Education","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in each local authority area applied for additional capital funding for the universal infant free school meals initiative through the local authority capital bidding round; and how much additional capital funding for that initiative was applied for by each local authority.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221920","221920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175446","2015-01-28","Department for Education","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many complaints her Department has received about careers advice in schools in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221921","221921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175447","2015-01-28","Department for Education","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2015 to Question 221152, how many staff in schools had the role of careers adviser in the academic year (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221922","221922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175448","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that families with children are treated as a vulnerable group by energy companies.","Biography information for Pat Glass","Pat Glass","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221924","221924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175449","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to support families with children who fall behind on payments to energy companies.","Biography information for Pat Glass","Pat Glass","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221923","221923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175450","2015-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with the Oil and Gas Authority regarding the (a) regulatory and (b) industry response to the slump in global oil prices.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221871","221871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175451","2015-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Health and Safety Executive about backlogs of safety-critical maintenance work on offshore installations in the North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221872","221872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175452","2015-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent steps he has taken to protect (a) employment levels, (b) infrastructure integrity and (c) production capacity in the offshore oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221873","221873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175453","2015-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to amend or repeal the Hunting Act 2004 before the end of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221841","221841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175454","2015-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Palestinian Authority about the steps it can take to ensure the unhindered operation of the Gaza Reconstruction Mechanism.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221867","221867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175455","2015-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the stability of the Fatah-Hamas Unity government in the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221868","221868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175456","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research has been undertaken by his Department into the effect that an individual's knowledge of cardiopulmonary resuscitation has on their (a) confidence and (b) efficacy in using an automated emergency defibrillator.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221846","221846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175457","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the instructions provided with automated external defibrillators; and what assessment he has made of the ability of an untrained individual to use such defibrillators effectively on the basis of those instructions alone.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221843","221843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175458","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the confidence of the general public in using an automated external defibrillator in an emergency.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221847","221847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175459","2015-01-28","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220819, what weight was given to previous evidence of successful management of NHS data programmes in appointing the Senior Responsible Officer of the care.data programme.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221840","221840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175460","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Ashfield constituency have received social care in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221834","221834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175461","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he took to ensure that the process of reviewing the treatments listed on the Cancer Drugs Fund fully took into account the needs of patients who have cancers with limited treatment options.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221866","221866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175462","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on cancer patients of the delisting of treatments from the Cancer Drugs Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221865","221865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175463","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what analysis his Department has made of the effect the Government's Strategy for UK Life Sciences on the referral of women with ovarian cancer to suitable trial centres in the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221903","221903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175464","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve the participation of women in trials for ovarian cancer treatments.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221904","221904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175465","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve early diagnosis of ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221905","221905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175466","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the full evaluation report of the Be Clear on Cancer regional pilot for ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221893","221893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175467","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department provides incentives to individual hospital trusts and clinicians to participate in (a) clinical trials in general and (b) clinical trials for ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221894","221894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175468","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times and on which dates she has met representatives of the Police Superintendents Association of England and Wales since May 2010.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221899","221899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175469","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training regional organised crime units have received on enforcement of labour standards as a means of preventing human trafficking for labour exploitation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221876","221876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175470","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 4.31 of the Modern Slavery Strategy, published in December 2014, what the role the Gangmasters Licensing Authority will be in the work of the proposed Joint Border Intelligence units.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221900","221900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175471","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the terms of reference are of the work the University of Derby is conducting for her Department to assess the need for extension of the remit of the Gangmasters Licensing Authority to sectors beyond its current remit.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221882","221882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175472","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the need to extend the remit of the Gangmasters Licensing Authority to the (a) cleaning, (b) care, (c) hospitality, (d) construction and (e) manufacturing sectors.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221884","221884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175473","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims of human trafficking had been previously identified as having been trafficked into the UK in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221901","221901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175474","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times and on which dates she has met representatives of the Police Federation of England and Wales since May 2010.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221896","221896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175475","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the UK Human Trafficking Centre report, A strategic assessment on the nature and scale of human trafficking in 2012, published in August 2013, and the National Crime Agency strategic assessment, The nature and scale of human trafficking in 2013, published in September 2014, how many of the (a) 402 victims of trafficking in 2012 and (b) 594 victims of trafficking in 2013 who received a positive conclusive grounds decision from the National Referral Mechanism have subsequently claimed asylum in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221902","221902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175476","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times and on which dates she has met representatives of the Association of Chief Police Officers since May 2010.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221897","221897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175477","2015-01-28","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times and on which dates she has met representatives of HM Inspectorate of Constabulary since May 2010.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221898","221898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175478","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the National Referral Mechanism Review, published in November 2014, if she will publish the terms of reference of the proposed National Referral Mechanism Pilots.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221907","221907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175479","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to establish the EU forum on vulnerable workers proposed in her Department's Modern Slavery Strategy launched in November 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221877","221877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175480","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for asylum were made within (a) one week, (b) one month, (c) three months, (d) six months, (e) between six months and one year and (f) more than one year of the applicant's arrival in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221863","221863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175481","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the terms of reference of her Department's evaluation of the effectiveness of its campaign to raise awareness of modern slavery; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221875","221875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175482","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2014 to Question 216344, when the findings of her Department's evaluation of the effectiveness of its campaign to raise awareness of modern slavery will be published; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221885","221885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175483","2015-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on proactive inspection of houses of multiple occupation for cases of labour exploitation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221886","221886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175484","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219531, what recommendations have been made by the policy review undertaken by the Asset Recovery Task Force.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221837","221837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175485","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that UK aid programmes protect the resilience of small-scale farmers.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221833","221833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175486","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on health projects in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221849","221849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175487","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on projects in conflict states in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221850","221850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175488","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on family planning projects in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221848","221848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175489","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on health projects in Sierra Leone in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221856","221856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175490","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on economic development projects in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221860","221860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175491","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on water and sanitation projects in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221857","221857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175492","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent in Brazil in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221851","221851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175493","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent in Russia in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221852","221852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175494","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on education projects in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221858","221858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175495","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent in India in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221853","221853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175496","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on projects for women and girls in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221862","221862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175497","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on projects in fragile states in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221861","221861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175498","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent in China in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221854","221854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175499","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent in Africa in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221855","221855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175500","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on nutrition projects in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221859","221859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175501","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff in her Department worked on issues relating to taxation in the developing world in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221906","221906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175502","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to implement the European Directive 2012/29/EU on victims of crime; and what assessment he has made of the implications of that Directive for the work of the police and Crown Prosecution Service.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221918","221918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175503","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of existing civil torts in enabling victims of human trafficking to claim damages from their traffickers.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221878","221878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175504","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what damages were awarded to victims of trafficking in actions under existing civil torts since 2010.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221879","221879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175505","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases of (a) trafficking for sexual exploitation, (b) trafficking for other exploitation and (c) forced labour, slavery and servitude (i) were prosecuted and (ii) resulted in convictions in 2013.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221880","221880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175506","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 6.3.11 of the National Referral Mechanism Review published in November 2014, if he will review the provision of legal aid to potential victims of human trafficking.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221908","221908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175507","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will implement a victim's bill of rights.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221909","221909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175508","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will review the cross examination of witnesses in child abuse prosecutions.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221914","221914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175509","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it mandatory for a victim's impact statement to be presented in criminal proceedings at Crown court.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221910","221910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175510","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will give victims the right to be represented at mental health tribunals.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221911","221911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175511","2015-01-27","Attorney General","2015-01-23","To ask the Attorney General, how many victims have exercised the right to review a Crown Prosecution Service decision not to prosecute; and in how many of those cases the decision was changed.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221912","221912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175512","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it mandatory for prosecutors to meet victims before the start of trials at Crown court.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221915","221915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175513","2015-01-27","Attorney General","2015-01-23","To ask the Attorney General, what training Crown prosecutors receive on victims issues.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221916","221916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175514","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will give transcripts of trials to the families of murder victims.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221917","221917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175515","2015-01-27","Attorney General","2015-01-23","To ask the Attorney General, what the functions of Crown Prosecution Service victim liaison units are; and how their performance is monitored.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221913","221913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175516","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims of trafficking have brought claims against their traffickers under existing civil torts in the last five years; and how many such claims have resulted in awards for damages.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221883","221883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175517","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer from the Secretary of State for Health of 2 January 2015 to Question 219648, if he will make arrangements for any decision to start collecting care.data information from GP practices to be approved by the House.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221827","221827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175518","2015-01-27","Leader of the House","2015-01-23","To ask the Leader of the House, what the cost to the public purse was of the Leader of the Opposition's Short Money travel allowance, paid to the Labour Party, in each individual financial year in the 2010 Parliament to date.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221925","221925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175519","2015-01-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-01-23","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what advice is offered to people on how to find their national insurance number or to be provided with one when they apply to vote.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221832","221832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175520","2015-01-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-23","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many people have been informed that their application for inclusion on the voting register was not valid because their national insurance number was not provided since the introduction of individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221831","221831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175521","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funds the Government has provided to tackle potholes in Esther and Walton constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221870","221870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175522","2015-01-27","Department for Transport","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the consequence for his policies of the decision in the Appeal Court in the case of Doug Paulley v First Bus Group.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221895","221895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175523","2015-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many calls were made to the disability living allowance helpline, 08457 123456 in each of the last five financial years; how much revenue was generated from these calls; and by when he expects to end the use of this number.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221919","221919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175524","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2014 to Question 207976, whether his Department's review of its provision of alternative formats for information provision for blind and partially sighted people has been completed; and if he will make the report of the review available to the disabled people who contributed to it, stakeholder organisations and Members of Parliament.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221836","221836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175525","2015-01-28","Cabinet Office","2015-01-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of young people aged 16 to 18 living in (a) Bethnal Green and Bow constituency and (b) England had a working or educational status classified as unknown in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221825","221825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175526","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219706, what criteria he has used to (a) specify the costs which are necessary for a simple, respectful, low-cost funeral and (b) determine the level of those costs.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221826","221826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175527","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who are unable to afford a simple, respectful low-cost funeral due to the declining value in real terms year-on-year of Social Fund funeral payments.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221828","221828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175528","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the letter sent to people when they receive their national insurance number.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221829","221829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175529","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take in the next three months to advertise how people can (a) get a national insurance number if they do not have one and (b) find out their national insurance number if they do not know it.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221830","221830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175530","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether people are informed when they are sent their national insurance number that they will need it in order to register to vote.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221864","221864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175531","2015-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which operational installations in the North Sea have a backlog of safety-critical maintenance work; and what the deadlines are for completion of such work in each case.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221874","221874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175210","2015-01-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will direct the Insolvency Service to reduce its fees in cases of insolvency.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221676","221676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175211","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the sale of more low-alcohol drinks in pubs.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221683","221683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175212","2015-01-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 6 May 2014 to Questions 196539 and 196540, how much of the funding for (a) adult further education and skills and (b) apprenticeships was spent in 2013-14.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221718","221718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175213","2015-01-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what provisions exist to prevent agencies providing staff to companies deliberately wrongly designating them as apprentices in order to pay them less than the minimum wage; and what instances of such practices have been brought to his attention.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221724","221724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175214","2015-01-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made in implementing the recommendations of the Richard review of apprenticeships.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221767","221767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175215","2015-01-27","Cabinet Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of women earned less than two-thirds of the median hourly pay, excluding overtime, of all full- and part-time employees in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221739","221739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175216","2015-01-27","Cabinet Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions Ministers and officials in his Department have had with their counterparts in the Ministry of Defence on Ministry of Defence Police pensions.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221774","221774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175217","2015-01-26","HM Treasury","2015-01-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the benefits to the public purse of the cancellation of the replacement for the Trident successor programme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221744","221744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175218","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his Department's policy that Government funds paid to external organisations to provide abortions and ancillary services are not used to campaign for changes in UK law.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221694","221694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175219","2015-01-26","HM Treasury","2015-01-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2015 to Question 220189, whether his Department has developed specific guidelines to ensure that HM Revenue and Customs acts reasonably when dealing with taxpayers who seek additional time to pay as a consequence of accelerated payment notices.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221768","221768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175220","2015-01-26","Church Commissioners","2015-01-22","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, how much the Commissioners have spent on the Employment Tribunal action by the Reverend Mark Sharpe against the Bishop of Worcester and the Worcester Diocesan Board of Finance.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221769","221769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175221","2015-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will investigate the destination of the £9 million spent by Lancaster City Council on the Chatsworth Gardens area of the west end of Morecambe over the last 10 years.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221786","221786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175222","2015-01-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to ensure that approved building inspectors are (a) independent and (b) not subject to conflicts of interest.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221684","221684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175223","2015-01-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations other than from the National Housebuilding Council he has received on section 6 of Approved Document M of the Building Regulations.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221685","221685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175224","2015-01-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations other than from the National Housebuilding Council he has received on the Building (Approved Inspectors etc) Regulations 2000.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221686","221686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175225","2015-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of houses in England and Wales whose owners do not have household insurance; and if he will make an assessment of the number of households in the social and private rented sectors which do not have household insurance.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221749","221749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175226","2015-01-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what support his Department is providing for UK cities considering a bid for the title of 2023 European Capital of Culture.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221734","221734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175227","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it remains her policy that Part 2 of the Leveson Inquiry into the relationship of the police and the press will take place; and when she expects that part of the inquiry to begin.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221692","221692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175228","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times aircraft were intercepted by Quick Reaction Alert flights in 2014; and what the (a) intercepted aircraft type and (b) location were.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221677","221677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175229","2015-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the suitability of the new Civil Service Pensions Scheme for Ministry of Defence Police officers.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221775","221775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175230","2015-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the proposals of the Defence Police Federation on Ministry of Defence Police pensions.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221773","221773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175231","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons members of the armed forces  stationed in the Falkland Islands do not receive free wifi; and if he will make it his policy to ensure that all UK bases overseas offer access to a free wifi connection.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221766","221766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175232","2015-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to confirm future arrangements for Ministry of Defence Police pensions.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221803","221803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175233","2015-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the services currently available to military personnel suffering from mental illness.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221805","221805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175234","2015-01-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people applied for part-time university courses in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221806","221806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175235","2015-01-27","Department for Education","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much capital the Government has provided for investment in York schools in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221784","221784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175236","2015-01-27","Department for Education","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of bullying incidents reported at schools in England but not recorded centrally in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221748","221748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175237","2015-01-26","Department for Education","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2015 to Question 219582, how her Department monitors the progress of local authorities in meeting the requirement to develop easily accessible policies to describe how they will support children in the care of family and friends.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221698","221698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175238","2015-01-26","Department for Education","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220175, on what occasions her Department has intervened when a local authority had not complied with its statutory responsibility of meeting the six-week regulation for visits of children since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221699","221699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175239","2015-01-26","Department for Education","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were born to a parent who resides in residential care in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221700","221700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175240","2015-01-26","Department for Education","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department offers to teenage mothers in residential care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221701","221701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175241","2015-01-26","Department for Education","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what records her Department collects on pregnancy rates for women (a) under and (b) over 16 who live in residential care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221702","221702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175242","2015-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of (a) future changes in fossil fuel energy prices and (b) the implications of such changes for the calculation of the value for money of his Department's energy policies and alternative energy pathways.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221753","221753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175243","2015-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 219697, if he will revise calculations of value for money delivered by the non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive to take account of falling fossil fuel energy prices.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221795","221795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175244","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that Circle not be selected as preferred partner for the running of NHS trusts or facilities.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221723","221723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175245","2015-01-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 January 2015, HC WS183, on Nuclear Decommissioning Authority, if he will publish on his departmental website the documents on the basis of which the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority concluded that a change in the parent body contractor for Sellafield management was now the best way forward.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221725","221725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175246","2015-01-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, columns 141-2W, on Sellafield, what the evidential basis was for the Government's decision to endorse the decision of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority to continue the contract of Nuclear Management Partners into a second five-year period as the best way forward at that time.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221726","221726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175247","2015-01-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will conduct an impact assessment on freezing energy bills on the energy sector and its potential effect on the workforce that sector employs.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221785","221785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175248","2015-01-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made on the level of funding available for the Northamptonshire Action with Communities in Rural England.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221789","221789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175249","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help dairy farmers to export more milk products.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221741","221741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175250","2015-01-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 15 December 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr A. Webster.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221743","221743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175251","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions he has had with the UK's international partners on providing additional funding for the UN World Food Programme.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221688","221688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175252","2015-01-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken in response to the increase in the number of political prisoners in Burma in the last year.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221704","221704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175253","2015-01-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Indian government on the use of torture on terror suspects; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221770","221770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175254","2015-01-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219031, whether there were any discussions between UK Ministers or officials and members of the US administration, US officials or legislators on the Senate Committee on Intelligence's study into the Central Intelligence Agency's Detention and Interrogation Program from its commencement in 2009, other than those referred to in his Answer.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221756","221756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175255","2015-01-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219031, whether he was consulted by the intelligence agencies or other UK officials on which redactions to request from the report of the Senate Committee on Intelligence on the Central Intelligence Agency's Detention and Interrogation Program; and whether any of his Ministerial colleagues were consulted on the same matter.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221759","221759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175256","2015-01-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219031, on how many occasions the intelligence agencies discussed the report of the Senate Committee on Intelligence on the Central Intelligence Agency's Detention and Interrogation Program with US administration officials.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221758","221758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175257","2015-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to support the establishment of an independent, international inquiry to investigate allegations of crimes against humanity, ethnic cleansing and genocide in Rakhine State, Burma.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221792","221792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175258","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date negotiations on the price of the new meningitis B vaccine began; and whether an end date has been set for those negotiations.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221807","221807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175259","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his estimate is of the number of children under the age of 16 who have been diagnosed with mental health problems in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221804","221804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175260","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people presented at the A&E Department at York Hospital in each month of (a) 2014 and (b) the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221798","221798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175261","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people living in (a) York, (b) Yorkshire and Humber and (c) England sought advice from NHS Direct in each of its last five years of operation.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221797","221797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175262","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what scope the joint committees of NHS England and clinical commissioning groups will have to deviate from national service specifications for specialised services in (a) 2015-16 and (b) future years.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221765","221765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175263","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England will remain the sole budget-holder and accountable commissioner for all specialised services in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) future years.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221772","221772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175264","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made by NHS property services, the Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group and the Leeds and York Partnership NHS Foundation Trust in preparing plans for the replacement of (a) Bootham Park Hospital and (b) Lime Trees in York; when he plans to make a public announcement about those plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221799","221799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175265","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of GP appointments for people in Dudley.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221730","221730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175266","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs there were in Dudley in (a) 2010 and (b) each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221731","221731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175267","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs per head of population were in practice in (a) Dudley, (b) the Black Country and (c) England in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221732","221732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175268","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Written Statements of 18 December 2013, Official Report, column 110WS and of 20 November 2014, WS14, and pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2014 to Question 214789, what his policy is on the role of clinical trials in ensuring the safety and efficacy of innovative treatments; and what Departments are responsible for the regulation of such trials.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221733","221733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175269","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department last updated the guidance it issues to the NHS on dealing with women who have undergone FGM.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221745","221745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175270","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 24 February 2014 by Earl Howe on 24 February 2014, Official Report, columns WA174-5, how many human embryos have been destroyed in the UK; and how many of those embryos were generated by (a) somatic cell nuclear, (b) pronuclear and (c) spindle-chromosomal complex transfer.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221752","221752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175271","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when and for what reason the NHS walk-in centre in Monkgate, York has closed; and how many people used that centre in its last year of operation.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221796","221796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175272","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the scoring tool used by NHS England in the review process for treatments on the Cancer Drugs Fund was developed; what scientific evidence was used in the development of the tool; and how clinicians and patients were involved in the development of the tool.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221764","221764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175273","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has issued to hospitals on their use of management consultants.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221680","221680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175274","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 220130, which member of the expert panel convened by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority had an email exchange with one of the authors of the research published in Fertility and Sterility; how that member of the expert panel shared this information with other members of the expert panel; and for what reason it would not be appropriate for this correspondence to be placed in the Library.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221693","221693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175275","2015-01-27","Department of Health","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has issued guidance on the appropriate ratio in  hospitals of permanent staff to locum staff.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221678","221678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175276","2015-01-26","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department intends to reply to the letter to the Immigration and Security Minister dated 16 December 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr M Ilyas.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221742","221742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175277","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 219638, whether the potential timelines for legislative change to allow the mothers of brides and grooms to be named on marriage certificates include an option for the change to be made before the 2015 general election.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221750","221750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175278","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what courses her Department offers for training on FGM for regulated professions; and how many people attended those courses in each English region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221751","221751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175279","2015-01-26","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on the review of information contained on marriage certificates; and when she plans to bring forward proposals to allow mothers' names to be recorded on marriage certificates.","Biography information for Jonathan Evans","Jonathan Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221713","221713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175280","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many local authorities have (a) applied for and (b) received funding from her Department for the purposes of resettling Syrian refugees; and what the total value was of that funding.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221697","221697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175281","2015-01-26","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of providing security for Tony Blair and his office in respect of (a) accommodation within the UK, (b) hospitality on foreign visits, (c) air and train travel to and from government-related appointments, (d) local transportation overseas, (e) accommodation at UK embassies and hotels overseas, (f) attendance at official receptions and (g) catering since Mr Blair left office.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221719","221719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175282","2015-01-26","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of Syrian refugees resettled by local authorities in the UK to date.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221687","221687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175283","2015-01-27","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been allocated to her Department's inquiry into child sexual abuse for (a) 2014-15 and (b) all future years for which funding has been estimated.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221790","221790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175284","2015-01-26","Home Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) requests, (b) arrests and (c) surrenders have been made relating to people wanted from the UK or wanted by the UK for human trafficking offences through the European Arrest Warrant since that mechanism was introduced.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221757","221757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175285","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to encourage the Nigerian government to allow international aid agencies to carry out their work in the north-east of that country.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221800","221800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175286","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with the UN High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR) on the ability of Syria's neighbouring countries to manage the safety and security of Syrian refugees; and what discussions she has had with the UNHCR on the particular requirements relating to refugees with urgent medical needs, children and victims of torture and sexual violence.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221760","221760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175287","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on programmes designed to strengthen the tax systems in each country in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221761","221761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175288","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's budget has been spent on programmes designed to strengthen tax systems in the developing world in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221762","221762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175289","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if the Government will provide funding to meet the humanitarian needs of people affected by the insurgency in Nigeria.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221763","221763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175290","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support refugee camps in (a) Jordan, (b) Lebanon, (c) Turkey, (d) Egypt and (e) Iraq.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221695","221695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175291","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans the Government has to provide increased support to people displaced as a result of the violence by Boko Haram in Northern Nigeria.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221727","221727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175292","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to provide support for the education of girls and young women in conflict-affected areas of Northern Nigeria.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221728","221728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175293","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the restrictions recently placed on Syrian refugees seeking to enter Lebanon.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221747","221747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175294","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will appoint dedicated humanitarian advisers on a permanent basis in Nigeria to oversee the distribution of humanitarian funds and the work of aid agencies.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221754","221754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175295","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on programmes designed to strengthen tax systems in the developing world in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221755","221755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175296","2015-01-27","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with Saudi Arabia on supporting Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221696","221696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175297","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she next plans to visit Syrian refugee camps in (a) Jordan, (b) Lebanon, (c) Turkey, (d) Egypt and (e) Iraq.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221689","221689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175298","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with which countries she has had discussions on additional funding for UN High Commissioner for Refugees.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221690","221690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175299","2015-01-26","Department for International Development","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Arab League on co-ordinating support for Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221691","221691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175300","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Transforming Rehabilitation contracts with Tier 1 providers state (a) that people on short prison sentences must be supervised and (b) the date from which such supervision must be provided.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221776","221776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175301","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what dates the Transforming Rehabilitation contracts with (a) Tier 1, (b) Tier 2 and (c) Tier 3 providers were signed.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221777","221777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175302","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date the successful bidders will assume control of the Community Rehabilitation Companies.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221778","221778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175303","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date the supervision of people on short prison sentences by Community Rehabilitation Companies will begin.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221779","221779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175304","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what date all the Transforming Rehabilitation contracts with (a) Tier 1, (b) Tier 2 and (c) Tier 3 providers will be signed.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221780","221780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175305","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Prison Service post-assault protocol for supporting staff in the young people's estate.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221710","221710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175306","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to roll-out the Prison Service post-assault protocol for supporting staff across the wider prison estate.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221711","221711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175307","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many calls were received by the NOMS 24-hour staff helpline in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221707","221707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175308","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times a governor has granted sick absence excusal to staff in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221705","221705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175309","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many NOMS staff well-being events have been held in 2014-15 to date; and what target his Department has set for the number of such events in that year.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221706","221706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175310","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many stress-awareness workshops NOMS has held since the roll-out of that initiative across the prison estate.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221708","221708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175311","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library copies of the Prison Service regional stress action plans.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221709","221709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175312","2015-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he plans to take to reduce the number of suicides within prisons in England and Wales.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221788","221788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175313","2015-01-27","Prime Minister","2015-01-22","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to empower Ministers to compel public inquiries to publish reports by a given date.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221679","221679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175314","2015-01-27","Prime Minister","2015-01-22","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with the Chair of the Iraq inquiry on the publication of the findings of that inquiry.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221681","221681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175315","2015-01-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-01-22","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many 17-year-old attainers were registered in December (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 in (i) the UK, (ii) each region and constituent part of the UK and (iii) each local authority area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221714","221714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175316","2015-01-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-01-22","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Electoral Commission provides to local authority electoral registration offices and local authority canvassers when they are distributing and collecting completed individual elector registration forms on the doorstep.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221715","221715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175317","2015-01-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-01-22","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what estimate the Electoral Commission has made of the number of local authorities whose canvassers are declining to collect completed individual electoral registration forms on the doorstep.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221716","221716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175318","2015-01-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-01-22","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many young people were included on the electoral register in December (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 in (i) the UK, (ii) each region and constituent part of the UK and (iii) each local authority area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221717","221717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175319","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the impact that HS2 will have on rail freight operations on the West Coast Mainline.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221793","221793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175320","2015-01-28","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what incentives are in place for freight operators to reduce road freight and use other modes of transport.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221794","221794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175321","2015-01-27","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what organisations responded to the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchise consultation; and whether those responses are publicly available.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221737","221737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175322","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to update the Government's Aviation Policy Framework following the publication of the Airports Commission Final Report; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221712","221712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175323","2015-01-27","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the invitations to tender will be issued for the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221738","221738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175324","2015-01-27","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many responses have been received to the consultation on the future of the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221735","221735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175325","2015-01-27","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many responses to the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchise consultation (a) supported and (b) opposed driver-only operation.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221736","221736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175326","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many miles of cycle lanes were created on (a) the strategic road network and (b) other roads in (i) England and (ii) Birmingham in 2014.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221703","221703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175327","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to relocate officials from his Department to Birmingham to work alongside officials from HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221771","221771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175328","2015-01-27","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, from whom are the new premises into which HS2 Ltd are relocating being let.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221802","221802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175329","2015-01-27","Department for Transport","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the budget is for relocating HS2 Ltd to Birmingham; how many HS2 Ltd staff will be relocated; what the annual cost is of the premises to be occupied by HS2 Ltd; and what the address and square footage of those premises is.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221801","221801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175330","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus staff were subject to disciplinary action in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221791","221791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175331","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the change in the inactivity rate recorded in the Office of National Statistics Labour Market statistics issued on 21 January 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221787","221787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175332","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on the use of Braille to communicate with benefit claimants.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221682","221682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175333","2015-01-26","Cabinet Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many children there were in workless households in (a) 2010, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221722","221722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175334","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the eligibility criteria are for a UK pensioner living in France to receive winter fuel payments.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221740","221740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175335","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former incapacity benefit claimants found fit for work after being reassessed for employment and support allowance between October 2010 and March 2014 have found work as a result of the Work Programme in (a) Edinburgh, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221729","221729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175336","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households were in relative poverty in (a) 2010, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221721","221721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175337","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have moved into work after being subject to the welfare cap in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221720","221720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175338","2015-01-26","Cabinet Office","2015-01-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many long-term unemployed people claim jobseeker's allowance in Thirsk and Malton constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221746","221746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175339","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of disability living allowance (a) have had their rate of entitlement changed, (b) have lost any entitlement and (c) no longer receive the mobility component since the transition to personal independent payments.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221781","221781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175340","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to provide an appropriate level of support to people with mental health problems on employment and support allowance participating in the Work Programme.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221782","221782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175341","2015-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time is for the completion of the mandatory reconsideration of disability living allowance claims in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221783","221783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174983","2015-01-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the EU can apply parts of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership within EU competence after the Partnership has been signed when ratification of elements of the Partnership that fall within member states' competence has been refused by a member state.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221494","221494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174984","2015-01-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which provisions under negotiation for the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership are not a matter of EU competence and will require ratification by each EU member state.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221495","221495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174985","2015-01-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase job creation and economic growth in the north of England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221486","221486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174986","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on small and micro businesses of centralising local land charges registers.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221555","221555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174987","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what secondary legislation would be required, in addition to the Infrastructure Bill, in order to extend centralisation of local land charges register data to CON29 searches.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221556","221556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174988","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for how many months since 2010 the role of Chief Scientific Adviser for his Department has been vacant.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221580","221580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174989","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to create jobs in Huddersfield.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221612","221612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174990","2015-01-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if the Government will consider extending the student loans system to cover training and apprenticeships for the freight industry.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221616","221616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174991","2015-01-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-01-21","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance his Department provides to Returning Officers on the eligibility of 18 year olds to stand for election to a local council in a ward in which they go to school but do not live.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221492","221492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174992","2015-01-26","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what (a) assessment he has made of the efficiency of and (b) representations he has received about the telephone service for pensioner bond applications.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221484","221484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174993","2015-01-23","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will provide additional resources to the devolved administrations to tackle coastal erosion.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221515","221515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174994","2015-01-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he will take to ensure that, in relation to home heating and travel, consumers will benefit directly from the recent fall in oil prices.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221516","221516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174995","2015-01-26","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average waiting time was for calls to the pensioner bond application telephone service in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221483","221483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174996","2015-01-23","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with business organisations about changes to VAT invoicing requirements when discounting for early payment.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221481","221481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174997","2015-01-23","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the effect on businesses of changes to VAT invoicing on discounting for early payment schemes.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221482","221482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174998","2015-01-23","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2014 to Question 215879, what plans he has to publish the futures analysis on the potential impact of the introduction of standardised packaging on the illicit trade in tobacco.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221535","221535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174999","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to revise the impact assessment for the proposed introduction of standardised packaging of tobacco in response to the analysis of that impact assessment by the Regulatory Policy Committee; and what plans he has to commission research to support such a revision.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221536","221536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175000","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to commission or conduct research on the potential cost of compensation to the intellectual property sector for the proposed introduction of standardised packaging of tobacco.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221537","221537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175001","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take in response to the request of the Regulatory Policy Committee that compensation be included as a transition cost in a revised impact assessment of the proposed introduction of standardised packaging.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221538","221538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175002","2015-01-23","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the issue of pensioner bonds in January 2015, what lessons his Department has learnt on the ability of online application systems and telephone enquiry services to deal with large numbers of applicants, in planning for new public bond issues.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221543","221543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175003","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding from LIBOR fines was distributed to veterans' charities in each (a) region and (b) constituent part of the UK in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221590","221590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175004","2015-01-26","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the combined financial effect on (a) small and (b) all businesses of government policy on business rates (i) in cash terms and (ii) in real terms since May 2010.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221663","221663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175005","2015-01-23","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of VAT collected from the sale of sanitary products in the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221584","221584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175006","2015-01-26","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reduce fuel duty and VAT on road fuel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221667","221667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175007","2015-01-26","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will increase tax incentives for the adoption of greener fuels and technologies.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221668","221668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175008","2015-01-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes were adapted for disabled tenants using the Disabled Facilities Grant in each year from 2009-10 to 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221591","221591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175009","2015-01-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average cost has been of adapting homes for disabled tenants under the disabled facilities grant since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221592","221592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175010","2015-01-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the Government spent on legal fees in the case of Moore and Coates v the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in which ruling was made on 21 January 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221613","221613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175011","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the super-affirmative procedure will be followed when the Government brings foward proposals to amend the Greater Manchester Combined Authorities Order 2011 to create an interim eleventh chair of Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221610","221610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175012","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what Government support (a) is available and (b) has been provided to secure private sector investment in the Thames Gateway since 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221627","221627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175013","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of progress in securing private sector investment in the Thames Gateway since 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221628","221628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175014","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has for Ministers to visit locations in the Thames Gateway in the period up to the dissolution of Parliament; and what the planned locations of those visits are.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221629","221629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175015","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to ensure that development of new Thames Gateway communities is sustainable, cohesive and integrated.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221630","221630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175016","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of progress in securing private sector investment in Thames Gateway projects at (a) London Gateway Port, (b) Purfleet, (c) Paramount Park and (d) Southend Airport since 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221631","221631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175017","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government of 15 December 2014, Official Report, columns 1148-56, if the Minister will meet the Fire Brigades Union and fire authority employers, and their respective legal representatives, to discuss how commitments that she gave in that debate on fire service pensions will be implemented in practice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221637","221637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175018","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that local authorities trading under the general power of competence granted by the Localism Act 2011 do not unfairly compete with existing local small businesses.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221562","221562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175019","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from small business owners about unfair competitive practices from local authorities trading under the general power of competence granted by the Localism Act 2011.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221563","221563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175020","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many local authorities were involved in trials of the new local land charges register scheme.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221557","221557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175021","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what safeguards are in place to ensure that prospective home-ownership deals do not collapse as a result of centralising local land charges registers.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221558","221558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175022","2015-01-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to improve access to the arts for children from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221485","221485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175023","2015-01-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2015 to Question 221061, what the annual cost to the public purse is of his Department's office space at 179A Tottenham Court Road.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221509","221509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175024","2015-01-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for how many months since 2010 the role of Chief Scientific Adviser for his Department has been vacant.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221581","221581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175025","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many organisations in Scotland have signed the Corporate Covenant relating to reservists, veterans and families of service personnel.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221594","221594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175026","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, over what time period the contract between his Department and CGI to provide security vetting services will run; and what the cost of that contract will be per year.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221649","221649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175027","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on recruitment to each of the armed forces in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221646","221646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175028","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 220095, how many personnel were recruited to the regular Army between April and December 2014; and what his Department's recruitment target for that period was.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221647","221647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175029","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2015 to Question 216757, on vetting, what the average time to process applications has been in each month since January 2014; and what the cost of bringing in additional personnel to help deal with the high volume of applications has been.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221648","221648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175030","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what response he has made to the recommendation in the Veterans Transition Review, published on 11 February 2014, that security-vetted armed forces champions should be appointed in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221490","221490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175031","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive about the appointment of a representative from Northern Ireland to the Armed Forces Covenant Reference Group.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221491","221491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175032","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to ensure that the Common Security and Defence Policy continues to increase Britain's capability in ensuring international security.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221524","221524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175033","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech in Nottingham on 12 January 2015, what assessment he has made of the implications for the defence industrial sector of changing the rules governing access to encrypted messages; and whether he has discussed those proposed changes with representatives of that sector.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221533","221533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175034","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to make surplus Ministry of Defence housing in Lisburn available for sale to housing associations.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221532","221532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175035","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many vehicles within each group, included in his Department's contract made as a result of the sale of the Defence Support Group, need to be kept at readiness under that contract; whether the level of that readiness is decided by (a) the Joint Terrorism Analysis Centre or (b) him; and whether that contract contains provisions to allow that number to be changed in response to changing security threat situations.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221534","221534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175036","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on preparations for the next Strategic Defence and Security Review; and what recent discussions he has had with stakeholders in that review.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221587","221587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175037","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings he has had with stakeholders on the next (a) National Security Strategy and (b) Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221588","221588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175038","2015-01-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on preparations for the next National Security Strategy; and what discussions he has had with stakeholders in that strategy.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221589","221589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175039","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to increase the average length of Royal Navy deployments in the South Atlantic and the Gulf; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221526","221526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175040","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many airborne sorties have been carried out by the Royal Air Force to intercept Russian military aircraft approaching or entering British airspace in each month since April 2005.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221517","221517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175041","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) length and (b) area was of each deployment by each Royal Navy (i) destroyer and (ii) frigate since 2005.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221527","221527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175042","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many naval service personnel were deployed in breach of the Royal Navy's harmony guidelines in each financial year from 2005-06 to 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221528","221528"
