"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023213","2018-12-17","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers are currently living in the UK.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201230","201230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023214","2018-12-17","Treasury","2018-12-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what projections his Department has produced of the tax receipts arising from the changes to IR35 rules as announced in Budget 2018.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201166","201166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023215","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the level of resources required by the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority as a result of the introduction of the new seasonal workers pilot in the agricultural sector.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201231","201231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023216","2018-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to respond to his Department's paper entitled, Seasonal workers pilot: request for information, published in September 2018.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201232","201232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023217","2018-12-17","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to section 5 of the Gangmasters (Licensing) Act 2004, how the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority plans to license non-EU labour providers engaged in the seasonal workers pilot in the agricultural sector.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201233","201233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023218","2018-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives from the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority on the seasonal workers pilot.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201234","201234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023219","2018-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Seasonal Workers Pilot in the agricultural sector, how much time will be provided to the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority to develop a system for worker oversight and protection in the UK and overseas from the point at which Pilot Operators are chosen to the point at which the pilot starts to provide workers to growers and employers in the UK.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201235","201235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023220","2018-12-17","Department for Transport","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December to Question 198250 on the South Eastern Rail Franchise, on what date in the New Year he plans to make the announcement on the successful bidder of the new South Eastern rail franchise by; and what steps he is taking to ensure that there will not be a delay in  the new operator taking over in April 2019.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201123","201123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023221","2018-12-17","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make and assessment of adequacy of the guidance issued to schools, local education authorities and other responsible bodies to ensure that classroom notice boards are installed correctly and in accordance with fire standards that are legally compliant.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201108","201108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023222","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans (a) Ofsted and (b) the Care Quality Commission have to automatically require a written statement of action where joint commissioning arrangements for speech, language and communication needs and related needs, including (i) social, (ii) emotional and (iii) mental health, classified as inadequate.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201090","201090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023223","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of excluding a child from school.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201091","201091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023224","2018-12-17","Cabinet Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to answer Question 189621 on the membership of the Financial, Professional and Education Services Business Council tabled on 9 November 2018 by the hon. Member for Bristol East.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201124","201124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023225","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the planned execution of Abbas al-Hassan and 11 other individuals for exercising their rights to freedom of religion and association.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201125","201125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023226","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the Government of Saudi Arabia's compliance with international agreements on the use of torture, forced confessions and capital punishment in the sentencing of Abbas al-Hassan and eleven other individuals for exercising their rights to freedom of religion and association.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201167","201167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023227","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the planned execution of Israa al-Ghomgham for demanding greater rights for women in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201168","201168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023228","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in Saudi Arabia on the use of that country’s Specialised Criminal Court to prosecute and convict individuals seeking to protest or exercise their human rights in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201169","201169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023229","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the prosecution of Professor Chan Kin-Man; and what assessment he has made on whether the potential imprisonment of Professor Chan Kin-Ma complies with the 1984 Sino-British Joint Declaration.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201170","201170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023230","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the banning of the Hong Kong National Party; and what assessment he has made on whether the decision to ban that party complies with the 1984 Sino-British Joint Declaration.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201171","201171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023231","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Brazilian counterpart on the protection of the Amazon rainforest and its indigenous tribes.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201172","201172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023232","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Brazilian counterpart on that country’s commitment to the Paris Climate Change Agreement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201173","201173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023233","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's position is on providing a State Visit to President Bolsonaro of Brazil.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201174","201174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023234","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help the Afghan authorities respond effectively to attacks on the Hazara community in Afghanistan and to prevent the occurrence of future attacks.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201175","201175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023235","2018-12-13","Department for International Development","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what additional humanitarian aid the Government is giving in advance of the upcoming winter months to help Hazara families displaced by recent violence against their communities in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201176","201176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023236","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his US counterpart on the planned reduction in the number of refugees to be admitted to that country next year to 30,000 from the 90,000 admitted each year under the previous administration; and what plans he has to lead international efforts to fill the gap created by that reduction.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201177","201177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023237","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Pakistani counterpart on the citizenship status of the 1.5 million children of Afghan refugees currently living in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201178","201178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023238","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department instructed the Home Office not to offer asylum to Asia Bibi due to concerns for the safety of British consular staff in Pakistan.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201179","201179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023239","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on the detention of Golrokh Ebrahimi Iraee for insulting Islamic sanctities by advocating against the use of stoning as a punishment.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201180","201180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023240","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on the jailing of (a) Farajollah Bangaleh and (b) Mitra Badrnejad for practicing their Ba’hai faith; and whether he raised the Iranian authority's treatment of the Ba’hai people on his recent trip to Tehran.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201181","201181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023241","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of calls from Reporters Without Borders for the creation of a UN Special Rapporteur with responsibility for monitoring the protection of journalists and press freedom.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201182","201182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023242","2018-12-17","Cabinet Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in each nation and region of the UK (a) were targeted by and (b) interacted with social media advertising promoting the Withdrawal Agreement that was paid for by the public purse.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201126","201126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023243","2018-12-17","Cabinet Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the electorate in each parliamentary constituency have been targeted by social media advertising which has been paid for by the public purse and which promotes the Prime Minister's EU Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201127","201127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023244","2018-12-17","Cabinet Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place in the Library all social media adverts that the Government has used to promote the Prime Minister's EU Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201128","201128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023245","2018-12-13","Cabinet Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many offences involving a knife have been committed in (a) London and (b) Lewisham in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201236","201236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023246","2018-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on local traffic levels of the proposed Category C prison at Full Sutton; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201129","201129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023247","2018-12-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Scotland on businesses in Scotland deploying no-deal contingency plans as a result of the Government deferring the meaningful vote on the Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201183","201183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023248","2018-12-17","Treasury","2018-12-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to provide financial support to businesses in Scotland deploying no-deal contingency plans as a result of the Government deferring the meaningful vote on the Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201184","201184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023249","2018-12-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will make an estimate of the number of businesses deploying no-deal contingency plans as a result of the Government deferring the meaningful vote on the Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201185","201185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023250","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the £50 million committed to long-term mental and physical health checks and treatment for people affected by the Grenfell Tower will include the emergency service personnel who responded to that disaster.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201237","201237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023251","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Independent Review of Building Regulations and Fire Safety: final report, published in May 2018, what the timescale is for the implementation of the recommendations in that report.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201238","201238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023252","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government,  with reference to the Independent Review of Building Regulations and Fire Safety: final report, published in May 2018,, which recommendations from that report his Department plans to implement.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201239","201239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023253","2018-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many meetings his Department has held with compliance organisations  to discuss the forthcoming resources and waste strategy in 2018.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201240","201240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023254","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Written Statement of 11 December 2018 on Clinical Waste, Official Report, HCWS1168, if he will publish the NHS trusts that continue to receive services from Healthcare Environmental Services.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201130","201130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023255","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Written Statement of 11 December 2018 on Clinical Waste, Official Report HCWS1168, what assessment he has made of the reasons why clinical waste from NHS trusts was not collected and properly disposed of by Healthcare Environmental Services.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201131","201131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023256","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of buildings that have been constructed or refurbished which has lead to combustible materials being installed since (a) 14 June 2017, (b) 1 January 2018 and (c) 3 October 2018.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201241","201241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023257","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Government Procurement Agreement, published in 29 November 2018, which types of combustible cladding are included in the ban on the use of combustible materials announced in that press release.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201242","201242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023258","2018-12-17","Scotland Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he has plans to hold discussions with Cabinet colleagues on businesses in Scotland deploying no-deal contingency plans for after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201243","201243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023259","2018-12-17","Scotland Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make an assessment of the financial effect on Scottish businesses of those businesses' contingency plans in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201244","201244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023260","2018-12-17","Scotland Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what representations he has received from businesses in Scotland on the financial effect of contingency plans made by those businesses in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201245","201245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023261","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children who have (a) permanent residence, (b) indefinite leave to remain and (c) British citizenship have a parent detained for immigration purposes.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201246","201246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023262","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of residency in the UK is for people who are detained for immigration purposes.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201247","201247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023263","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals to the National Referral Mechanism for those who are detained for immigration purposes there have been; and how many of those referred were (a) released and (b) kept in detention.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201248","201248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023264","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people detained for immigration purposes and removed from the UK have been subsequently re-detained for immigration purposes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201249","201249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023265","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been released from detention for immigration purposes to no fixed abode in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201250","201250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023266","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of (a) suicide and (b) self-harm requiring medical treatment occurred at each immigration removal centre in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201251","201251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023267","2018-12-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the equality impact assessment prepared by his Department on the pension proposals for the Civil Nuclear Police on behalf of the Department for Business, Energy, Energy and Industrial Strategy will be published.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201252","201252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023268","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many rule 35 reports were issued by medical practitioners at each immigration removal centre in each of the past three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201253","201253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023269","2018-12-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of enabling parents to pursue Child Support Agency arrears written off under the Child Support (Miscellaneous Amendments) Regulations 2018 through the legal system.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201254","201254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023270","2018-12-13","Attorney General","2018-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, what recruitment process his Department followed when appointing its Data Protection Officer (DPO); how that position was advertised; how many candidates applied for that post; what criteria were used to assess the candidates' (i) professional qualities and expert knowledge of data protection law and practices and (ii) their ability to fulfil the tasks referred to in Article 39 of the General Data Protection Regulation; who was appointed as DPO for his Department; when and where his Department has published its DPO's contact details; and what lines of reporting exist within his Department in respect of its DPO.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201132","201132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023271","2018-12-13","Attorney General","2018-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, what complaints procedure is open to members of the public if they wish to complain that (a) his Department’s Data Protection Officer and (b) any staff of his Department is in breach of the Civil Service Code; how many complaints have been made against staff of his Department for breaches of the Civil Service Code in each of the last two years; when, how and by whom those staff have been investigated; and what outcomes of those investigations have been recorded.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201133","201133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023272","2018-12-13","Attorney General","2018-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, who in his Department holds the position of Senior Information Risk Owner; when and how that official was appointed; what criteria were used to assess the professional qualities and expert knowledge of data protection law and practices of the candidates for that post; and who has held that position in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201134","201134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023273","2018-12-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many new Energy Performance Certificates band (a) A, (b) B and (c) C were issued in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201186","201186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023274","2018-12-17","Department for Transport","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what methodology his Department uses to assess the performance of franchises in relation to delivering a good service for disabled users.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201187","201187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023275","2018-12-17","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total cost to the public purse has been of converting local authority schools to academy schools since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201188","201188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023276","2018-12-17","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK citizens have been wrongly deported by his Department since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201189","201189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023277","2018-12-17","Department for Transport","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what performance indicators his Department uses to measure the number of times that trains run by franchise operators have not stopped at a station as a result of a service already being late running.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201190","201190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023278","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help ensure a free and fair election in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201191","201191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023279","2018-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 190538 on Army: Young People, how many of those people who started basic training (a) completed basic training, (b) qualified, (c) dropped out before completing training and (d) qualified but have since left the armed forces.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201255","201255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023280","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new personal independence payment claimants with multiple sclerosis in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland and (c) Wales did not receive an award during their initial personal independence payment assessment and subsequently received an award at (i) mandatory reconsideration and (ii) tribunal in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201192","201192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023281","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland and (c) Wales who were in receipt of disability living allowance and have undergone a reassessment for personal independence payments appealed the decision at tribunal and (i) had their decision overturned and (ii) had their mobility award increased from none or standard rate to the higher rate.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201193","201193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023282","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland and (c) Wales who were previously in receipt of disability living allowance and have undergone a reassessment for personal independence payment applied for mandatory reconsideration of the decision in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201194","201194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023283","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people with multiple sclerosis in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland and (c) Wales are no longer eligible for the higher rate of mobility support as a result of the transition from disability living allowance in each year since the introduction of personal independence payment.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201195","201195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023284","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number and proportion of babies that had not received the mandatory 12-month health check when they were (a) 12 months, (b) 15 months, (c) 18 months and (d) 24 months old in (i) England and (ii) in each local authority or Clinical Commissioning Group area in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201196","201196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023285","2018-12-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Charity Commission on the time taken to conduct investigations into charities.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201135","201135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023286","2018-12-17","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools paying the apprenticeship levy have taken on apprentices since that levy was introduced.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201136","201136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023287","2018-12-13","Department for International Trade","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans his Department has to pursue (a) reform of the World Trade Organisation and (b) free trade.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201197","201197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023288","2018-12-17","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect on school budgets of the requirement to pay the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201137","201137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023289","2018-12-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the total amount of money spent by the Government was to seek permission from the Supreme Court to appeal the decision of the Inner House to make a reference to the Court of Justice of the European Union on Wightman and Others v Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201256","201256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023290","2018-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to publish its Peat Strategy.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201257","201257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023291","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the appropriateness of the Single Technology Appraisal process for rare diseases that do not meet the Highly Specialised Technology criteria.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201198","201198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023292","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many rare disease treatments appraised through the Single Technology Appraisal process have been approved by NICE.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201199","201199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023293","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to reduce variations in access to rare disease medicines in England, Wales, Scotland and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201200","201200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023294","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to ensure that UK patients with rare diseases will continue to be able to receive access to the highest quality medicines after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201201","201201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023295","2018-12-17","Department for Transport","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many controlled airspace infringements there have been in 2018.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201138","201138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023296","2018-12-13","Department for Transport","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the factors that contribute to airspace infringements in the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201139","201139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023297","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on implementing a state-backed GP indemnity scheme in England; and whether the scheme will be implemented in April 2019.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201258","201258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023298","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants subject to recovery of recoverable hardship payments have them recovered at a rate of 40 per cent.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201202","201202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023299","2018-12-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letter of 15 November 2018 from the hon. Member for Croydon North on the use of combustible building materials after the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201203","201203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023300","2018-12-17","Treasury","2018-12-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of UK expenditure on research and development as a proportion of GDP in 2017-18; and how that level of expenditure compares to (a) other G7 countries and (b) the EU.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201140","201140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023301","2018-12-17","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the UK spent on policing as a proportion of GDP in the 2017-18 financial year; and how that figure compares to the (a) G7 and (b) EU average.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201141","201141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023302","2018-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the UK spends on prisons as a proportion of GDP in the 2017-18 financial year; and how that figure compares to the (a) G7 and (b) EU average.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201142","201142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023303","2018-12-13","Treasury","2018-12-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of Foreign Direct Investment in the UK in 2017-18 was represented by (a) acquisitions, mergers and joint ventures and (b) new investments or expansions.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201143","201143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023304","2018-12-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2018 to Question 199419 on Sleeping Rough, how much funding his Department will provide to Streetlink in winter 2018.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201204","201204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023305","2018-12-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many complaints he has received under the Green Deal Framework (Disclosure Acknowledgement Redress etc.) Regulations 2012; and on how many of those complaints he has issued a decision.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201259","201259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023306","2018-12-13","Department for Transport","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of merits of lowering the age of eligibility for the older person’s bus pass to 60 years old nationwide.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201260","201260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023307","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to tackle the challenges people with dementia face in obtaining (a) good residential care and (b) access to community support services.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201261","201261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023308","2018-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average number of prison officers in each of the under-18 young offender institutions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201205","201205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023309","2018-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what mandatory training is provided to prison officers working in under-18 young offender institutions; and what is distinctive about this training in comparison to that provided to officers working with adult prisoners.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201206","201206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023310","2018-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the proportion of prison officers working in each of the under-18 young offender institutions that have undergone a DBS enhanced check.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201207","201207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023311","2018-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prison officers in each of the under-18 young offender institutions that were dismissed or disciplined in each of the last five years; and for what reasons was each of those dismissed or disciplined.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201208","201208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023312","2018-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of allowing a submission from (a) victims and (b) their families to be considered as part of the decision making process by the Parole Board in relation to a recommendation to transfer an offender to open prison.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201262","201262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023313","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on allegations that Israeli security forces impersonated humanitarian workers while conducting a military operation inside the Gaza Strip in November 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201109","201109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023314","2018-12-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much has been disbursed on the land assembly fund since its announcement in Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201110","201110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023315","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, the total sum spent by his Department on the housing infrastructure fund.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201111","201111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023316","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much has been spent to date through the National Productivity Investment Fund to accelerate the building of homes on small, stalled sites as announced in Budget 2017.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201112","201112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023317","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, the total sum spent by his Department on the home building fund.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201113","201113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023318","2018-12-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much of the £8 billion of new guarantees to support housebuilding announced in Budget 2017 has been spent.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201144","201144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023319","2018-12-19","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pots of funding there are in his Department for external bodies to access for training, upskilling and incentivising recruitment; and what the value is of those funds.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201263","201263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023320","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department shares national pupil data with the Home Office for purposes related to immigration; and how many records have been shared by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201095","201095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023321","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, by what process may schools retract nationality data submitted to his Department between October 2016 and June 2018.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201096","201096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023322","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assurance his Department provides to parents that data on children collected for educational purposes will not subsequently be used for immigration enforcement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201097","201097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023323","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for (a) citizenship, (b) visas and (c) asylum have been refused on the basis of notoriety in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201098","201098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023324","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 195079 on Pneumococcal Diseases: Vaccination, whether the modelling paper used by Public Health England to support the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation in its advice on the pneumococcal vaccination programme will be (a) made publicly available and (b) reviewed by external experts in advance of any ministerial decision being made on a change to the pneumococcal vaccination schedule.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201209","201209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023325","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his Answer of 24 October 2018 to Question 180205 on Pneumococcal Diseases: Vaccination, whether the expected number of cases of pneumococcal disease following the advice to change the vaccination schedule will be (a) made publicly available, (b) communicated to patient groups and (c) open to peer review in advance of any ministerial decision being made on a change to the pneumococcal vaccination schedule.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201210","201210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023326","2018-12-13","Department for International Development","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects her Department supports to better facilitate health-related exit permits and medical delegations in Gaza.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201114","201114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023327","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment the Government has made of the effect of military action on port operations at Hodeidah, Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201145","201145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023328","2018-12-13","Department for International Development","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to protect Yemen from famine.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201146","201146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023329","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many CCTV cameras there are in each category (a) A and (b) B prison.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201264","201264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023330","2018-12-13","Treasury","2018-12-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many investigations have been conducted by HMRC into UK businesses by region since the 2016-17 financial year up to the most recent data available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201211","201211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023331","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average proportion of space accessible to prisoners which is covered by CCTV camera in each category (a) A and (b) B prison.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201265","201265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023332","2018-12-17","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans by the Hon Member for Bristol South to answer Question 197648 on Airguns: Reviews tabled on 30 November 2018.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201266","201266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023333","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to protect the rights of Gypsies, Travellers and Roma in his Department's response to the consultation on powers for dealing with unauthorised development.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201212","201212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023334","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of installing and upgrading CCTV cameras across the prison estate in each of the last five years in each category (a) A and (b) B prison.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201267","201267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023335","2018-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many enforcement actions the Environment Agency has taken against each water company in England in each of the last 10 years; and of those enforcement actions how many resulted in financial sanctions against the water company.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201099","201099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023336","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has taken steps to (a) ensure that all practitioners who work in the youth justice system are trained in recognising and responding appropriately to communication needs and (b) develop a referral pathway for youth offenders to access speech and language therapy.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201268","201268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023337","2018-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many investigations Ofwat has undertaken into each water company in England and Wales in each of the last 10 years; and how many of those investigations resulted in a water company receiving a financial penalty.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201100","201100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023338","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS Clinical Commissioners on ensuring that speech and language therapy service specifications (a) require those services to have a pathway for when a child or young person is not brought to an appointment, (b) appropriately resource those services to provide support in settings that meet the needs of the child or young people and their parent and carer and (c) monitor and report on the number of children and young people who are discharged from those services because they did not attend an appointment.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201269","201269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023339","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, based on the read codes in the Comprehensive Health Assessment Tool’s SystmOne, how many young people currently in young offender institutions have (a) evidence of lack of understanding, (b) difficulty understanding verbal language, or (c) difficulty with speech.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201270","201270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023340","2018-12-17","Prime Minister","2018-12-11","To ask the Prime Minister, what estimate she has made of (a) the cost to the public purse and (b) the carbon footprint of her visits to her counterparts in other EU member states and the representatives of the EU Council and the Commission between 10 December 2018 and 13 December 2018.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201271","201271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023341","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with the Education Endowment Foundation on ensuring that funding for improving outcomes for pupils with SEND has a focus on children and young people with speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201272","201272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023342","2018-12-17","Department for International Development","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has plans to allocate additional aid for Eritrea as a result of the lifting of international sanctions.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201115","201115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023343","2018-12-17","Cabinet Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of ministerial visits by his Department to discuss the withdrawal agreement from 3 to 10 December; and if he will place the itineraries of those visits in the Library before the Christmas recess.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201273","201273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023344","2018-12-17","Treasury","2018-12-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the findings of the his Department's investigation into the scheme for VAT avoidance on private jets in the Isle of Man.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201088","201088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023345","2018-12-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of ministerial visits of his Department to discuss the withdrawal agreement from 3 to 10 December; and if he will place the itineraries of those visits in the Library before the Christmas recess.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201274","201274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023346","2018-12-17","Treasury","2018-12-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of ministerial visits of his Department to discuss the withdrawal agreement from 3 to 10 December 2018; and if he will place the itineraries of those visits in the Library before the Christmas recess.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201275","201275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023347","2018-12-17","Treasury","2018-12-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to report on the HM Treasury investigation into the Isle of Man's administration of VAT for private jets that was due to be completed in Spring 2018.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201092","201092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023348","2018-12-17","Department for Transport","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is projected to meet its target proportion of new car sales to be ultra low emission vehicles by 2030.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201147","201147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023349","2018-12-17","Department for Transport","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2018 to Question 194792 on Electric Vehicles, if he will publish the internal assessment referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201276","201276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023350","2018-12-17","Department for Education","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of (a) the cost to the public purse of increasing free childcare provision to all two year old and younger children, and (b) the economic effect of increasing free childcare provision.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201277","201277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023351","2018-12-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the category 1 mean response time has been in each quarter since the classification of ambulance response times changed.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201278","201278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023352","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children were granted leave to enter the UK under the Calais Child Refugee scheme in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201116","201116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023353","2018-12-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has for the future of nuclear power in the UK as a result of the collapse of the NuGen consortium; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201148","201148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1024041","2018-12-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has for parliamentary scrutiny of the responsibilities of the European Commission that will be transferred to the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy in relation to the Accounts and Reports (Amendment) (EU Exit) Regulations 2018, which were laid before the House on 31 October 2018.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201672","201672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022407","2018-12-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","What steps his Department is taking to reduce homelessness.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908105","908105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022408","2018-12-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","What recent steps his Department has taken to support local government.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908107","908107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022409","2018-12-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","What steps his Department is taking to reduce homelessness.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908108","908108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022423","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to increase the marriage allowance.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908132","908132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022818","2018-12-13","Department for Transport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 178358 on London-Brighton Railway Line: Fares, what progress his Department has made on simplifying the fare structure for rail services on the Brighton main line.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200662","200662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022819","2018-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the European Commission on UK’s future involvement in Creative Europe and Horizon2020.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200739","200739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022820","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved Administrations on the potential establishment of a mesh database on a UK-wide basis.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200663","200663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022821","2018-12-13","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to change paragraph 1.20 of the civil service nationality rules in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200599","200599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022822","2018-12-13","Department for International Development","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2018 to Question 194657, whether the Memorandum of Understanding between her Department and the Palestinian National Authority was extended beyond 31 March 2016; and if she will place copies of all ministerial correspondence with the Palestinian Authority extending and amending that agreement in the Library.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200567","200567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022823","2018-12-12","Treasury","2018-12-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Department of the Treasury on creation of accidental Americans through the US Foreign Account Tax Compliance Act.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200664","200664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022824","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Italian counterpart on the Italian Government's policy towards search and rescue ships in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200665","200665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022825","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2018 to Question 188904, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the voluntary erasure code in cases where a GP is under investigation.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200666","200666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022826","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with stakeholders on the development of the early careers framework for teachers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200539","200539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022827","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of applications to (a) open and (b) take over an (i) academy, (ii) free school and (iii) faith school that were rejected because the applicant was unable to provide satisfactory assurances on the education and protection of (A) girls and (B) LGBT+ pupils.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200667","200667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022828","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) schools, (b) teachers and (c) school governors and administrators in (i) London and (ii) Englandthat were subject to a sanction for failure related to the welfare of LGBT children in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200668","200668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022829","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will introduce an incentive scheme to attract GPs to Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200600","200600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022830","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a GP university tuition fee remission scheme for newly trained GPs working in areas with a shortage of GPs.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200601","200601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022831","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of GPs that plan to retire in Easington constituency in the next five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200602","200602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022832","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to encourage GPs to relocate to areas with a GP shortage; and what steps he is taking to improve working conditions in those areas.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200603","200603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022833","2018-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department plans to conduct a review of eligibility criteria for carer’s allowance as a result of the number of carers that have been overpaid.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200669","200669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022834","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2018 to Question 197449 on Palliative Care: Children and Young People, whether Health Education England is taking steps to develop staff to fulfil the end of life choice commitment for children as set out in its mandate from the Government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200568","200568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022835","2018-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the merits of introducing a taper for claimants of carers allowance once the claimant has reached the earnings threshold.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200670","200670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022836","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of contracts his Department has with Babylon Healthcare.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200671","200671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022837","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of cases related to EHIC fraud that were (a) investigated, (b) determined to be a probable case of fraud and (c) determined to be a definite case of fraud by the NHS Counter Fraud Authority in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200672","200672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022839","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of suicides in (a) young offenders institutes and (b) juvenile wings of prisons in 2017.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200673","200673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022842","2018-12-13","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of suicides among students of further and higher education in the 2017-18 academic year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200674","200674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022845","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to comply with the requirements of the Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women and Domestic Violence (Ratification of Convention) Act 2017.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200675","200675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022848","2018-12-13","Department for International Development","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development,  if he will make representations to his counterpart in the Democratic Republic of Congo on the recent Ebola outbreak in eastern DRC.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200569","200569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022851","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Government officials attended the future investment initiative conference in Saudi Arabia in October 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200676","200676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022854","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December to Question 196177 on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Integrity Initiative, whether that funding is allocated from the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund; and what estimate he has made of the contribution of official development assistance to the (a) integrity initiative and (b) Institute for Statecraft.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200677","200677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022857","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to order the HMI Constabulary and Fire and Rescue Services to undertake an investigation into the performance of Gloucestershire Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200540","200540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022859","2018-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the target for the reduction of nitrogen dioxide pollutants in the air for 2019 is.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200570","200570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022861","2018-12-13","Church Commissioners","2018-12-10","To ask the Right Honourable Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of contributions to churches helping run Christians Against Poverty Centres in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200571","200571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022864","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Ecuadorian counterpart on Mr Julian Assange.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200572","200572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022867","2018-12-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2018 to Question 196873 on Dover Port: Domestic Visits, if he will publish the dates of visits to the port of Dover by his predecessors.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200678","200678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022870","2018-12-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2018 to Question 196873 on Dover Port: Domestic Visits, if he will publish (a) dates and (b) details of the 19 port visits by Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200679","200679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022873","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) tier 3 and (b) tier 4 weight management services have been decommissioned in each (i) region and (ii) Clinical Commissioning Group area in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200573","200573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022876","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Clinical Commissioning Groups commission (a) a multidisciplinary tier 3 and (b) a tier 4 weight management service.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200574","200574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022879","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have received (a) a tier 3 and (b) a tier 4 weight management service in each (i) region and (ii) Clinical Commissioning Group area in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200575","200575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022882","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was for bariatric surgery in each NHS trust in each of the last five calendar years; and how much has each trust paid in penalties incurred as a result of those waiting lists in each of those years.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200680","200680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022885","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the number of people with obesity in (a) England and (b) each Clinical Commissioning Group area by (i) age and (ii) gender for each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200681","200681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022888","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Clinical Commissioning Groups include weight management services on their list of procedures of limited clinical value.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200682","200682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022891","2018-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the development of hybrid-electric aircraft.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200683","200683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022894","2018-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the development of battery-electric aircraft.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200684","200684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022897","2018-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the development of new air transport concepts.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200685","200685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022900","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support the least active young people to participate more in PE and school sport.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200686","200686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022903","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support schools and children’s groups to develop appropriate physical activity facilities and equipment for children with disabilities.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200687","200687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022906","2018-12-13","Treasury","2018-12-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will be affected by the new 2019 loan charge (a) in total and (b) who are public sector workers.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200576","200576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022909","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 May 2018 to Question 145568, whether proposals have been brought forward for a GCSE in British Sign Language.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200688","200688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022912","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the value of his Department's contracts with Interserve.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200577","200577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022915","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the financial health of Interserve plc.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200578","200578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022918","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the value of contracts held by his Department with Interserve.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200579","200579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022921","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the financial health of Interserve.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200580","200580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022924","2018-12-13","Women and Equalities","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the launch of the EnAble Fund for Elected Office, what support her Department is providing to help disabled candidates standing for parliamentary elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200689","200689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022927","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the number is of gay and bisexual men who participated in the pilot HPV vaccination programme available in sexual health clinics who were aged (a) under 25, (b) 25 to 35, (c) 35 to 45, (d) 45 to 55 and (e) 55 and over.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200604","200604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022928","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the results of the pilot HPV vaccination programme for men who have sex with men.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200605","200605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022929","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the HPV vaccination is planned to be available in sexual health clinics across England for men who have sex with men; and in how many sexual health clinics that vaccination is planned to be available in.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200606","200606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022930","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to ensure take-up of the HPV vaccination by men who have sex with men.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200607","200607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022931","2018-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of mandatory reconsiderations for personal independence payments have (a) overturned and (b) upheld the original assessment decision in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200690","200690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022932","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the total number of local authorities that have seen an overall loss in their reserves between 2010 and 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200543","200543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022933","2018-12-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Government response to the Housing, Communities and Local Government Select Committee report on land value capture, published in November 2018, Cm 9734, when he will plans to publish updated guidancec on compulsory purchase compensation.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200551","200551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022934","2018-12-13","Department for Transport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of High Speed Two.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200544","200544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022935","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of human rights protections in Nicaragua.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200545","200545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022936","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recruitment process his Department followed when appointing its Data Protection Officer (DPO); how that position was advertised; how many candidates applied for that post; what criteria were used to assess the candidates' (i) professional qualities and expert knowledge of data protection law and practices and (ii) ability to fulfil the tasks referred to in Article 39 of the General Data Protection Regulation; who was appointed as DPO for his Department; when and where his Department has published its DPO's contact details; and what lines of reporting exist within his Department in respect of its DPO.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200552","200552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022937","2018-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Chinese Government on their treatment of ethnic minority Uighur Muslims.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200546","200546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022938","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what complaints procedure is open to members of the public if they wish to complain that (a) his Department’s Data Protection Officer and (b) any staff of his Department is in breach of the Civil Service Code; how many complaints have been made in each of the last two years against staff of his Department for breaches of the Civil Service Code; when, how and by whom those staff have been investigated; and what outcomes of those investigations have been recorded.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200553","200553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022939","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department (a) leases (b) provides in kind any (i) office space and (ii) other resources to the Institute for Statecraft.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200608","200608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022940","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who in his Department holds the position of Senior Information Risk Owner; when and how that official was appointed; what criteria were used to assess the professional qualities and expert knowledge of data protection law and practices of the candidates for that post; and who has held that position in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200554","200554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022941","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the welfare system in helping to alleviate levels of pensioner poverty.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200547","200547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022942","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Ministry of Defence apprentices there have been in the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Royal Air Force and (c) Army in each constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200691","200691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022943","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which cadet units are in each constituency; and what the sponsoring Service is of each of those units.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200692","200692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022944","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the outcomes were of his visit to Nigeria in November 2018 to (a) promote women, peace and security and (b) invest in counter-IED equipment.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200693","200693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022945","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2018 to Question 194146 on Prisons: Contracts, what the estimated cost is of the production of the public-sector benchmark against which potential operators’ bids will be assessed.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200609","200609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022946","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2018 to Question 194146 on Prisons: Contracts, what the estimated timetable is for the production of the public sector benchmark against which potential operators’ bids will be assessed.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200610","200610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022947","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2018 to Question 194146 on Prisons: Contracts, how many staff of each grade have been tasked with the production of the public sector benchmark against which potential operators’ bids will be assessed.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200611","200611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022948","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2018 to Question 194146 on Prisons: Contracts, whether he plans to publish the public sector benchmark which against potential operators’ bids are to be assessed once the competition process has been completed.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200612","200612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022949","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the set number of profiled hours for the keyworker system is in each open prison; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200613","200613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022950","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the target number of keyworkers is for each prison establishment to enable it to deliver the keyworker system.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200614","200614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022951","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the target date is for each prison to have a full complement of keyworkers in place to deliver the keyworker system.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200615","200615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022952","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what joint military exercises the UK armed forces plan to undertake with Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200616","200616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022953","2018-12-13","Treasury","2018-12-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2018 to Question 198212 on Global Navigation Satellite Systems: Costs, which Departmental budget will provide the cost of the proposed Global Navigation Satellite System.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200617","200617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022954","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2018 to Question 198212 on Global Navigation Satellite Systems: Costs, what funds his Department has allocated to the proposed Global Navigation Satellite System.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200618","200618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022955","2018-12-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2018 to Question 198212 on Global Navigation Satellite Systems: Costs, what funds his Department has allocated to the proposed Global Navigation Satellite System.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200619","200619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022956","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the correlation between deprivation and demand for children’s services.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200581","200581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022957","2018-12-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits of taking steps to tackle gazumping in the housing market.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200694","200694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022958","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers local authorities have to prevent cars parking on verges and footpaths.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200695","200695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022959","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 196129 on Overseas Visitors: Visas, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of providing a substantive answer to that question.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200582","200582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022960","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 196130 on Overseas Visitors: Visas, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of providing a substantive answer to that question.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200583","200583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022961","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2018 to Question 185683 on Coroners: Legal Representation, how many cases his Department provided funding for legal representation for prisons and probation staff at inquests on deaths in prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200696","200696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022962","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral evidence of 26 June 2018 by the Minister of State of his Department to the Justice Committee on Prison Population 2022: planning for the future, Question 81, what the target number of key workers is for each prison establishment to enable each of those establishments to deliver the key worker system.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200697","200697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022963","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral evidence of 26 June 2018 by the Minister of State of his Department to the Justice Committee on Prison Population 2022: planning for the future, Question 81, when HM Prison and Probation Service plans to complete the roll-out of the key worker scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200698","200698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022964","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral evidence of 26 June 2018 by the Minister of State of his Department to the Justice Committee on Prison Population 2022: planning for the future, Question 81, whether key worker contact for at least 45 minutes a week is the target throughout the (a) female, (b) young offender and (c) open prison estate.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200699","200699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022965","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the contractual expiry date is for each private sector contracted prison.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200700","200700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022966","2018-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2012 to Question 124033 on Prison Service: Staff, if he will provide updated figures for each year since 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200701","200701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022967","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners categorised as suitable for Category C accommodation are housed in Category B training prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200702","200702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022968","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times HMP Birmingham has been placed in special measures in each year since 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200703","200703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022969","2018-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, many convictions have been secured under the 2004 Hunting Act in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200620","200620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022970","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the security of the technology used for military systems.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200621","200621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022971","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made in trends in the number of aggressive tactics by Russian by (a) sea and (b) air in relation to (i) Royal Navy and (ii) Royal Air Force operations in the last two years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200622","200622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022972","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to encourage people to join the reserve forces.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200623","200623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022973","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has a strategy to tackle the issue of applicants to the armed forces not being fit enough to pass initial army selection.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200624","200624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022974","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of his Department's budget has been spent on administration costs in each year for which information is available; and how much is projected to be so spent in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200625","200625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022975","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school closures there were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200626","200626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022976","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will provide funding for extracurricular activities for schools to help tackle childhood obesity.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200627","200627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022977","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to help newly qualified teachers who have been unemployed for two or more years to find work.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200628","200628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022978","2018-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the risks to human and animals of trail hunts encroaching on roads and railway lines.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200629","200629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022979","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many RAF personnel took part in the Green Flag Exercise with the Royal Saudi Air Force; for what reason that exercise took place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200704","200704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022980","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessments were made using beta, gamma and X-ray detection of likely alpha radiation contamination as a result of Operation Grapple Y at Christmas Island in 1958.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200584","200584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022981","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of war pension applications claiming injury as a result of radiation exposure were (a) approved, (b) denied and (c) approved on appeal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200585","200585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022982","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on data that was gathered from blood samples taken from servicemen (a) before, (b) during and (c) after their service at the UK nuclear tests in the 1950s and 1960s.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200586","200586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022983","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the information on the possibility of genetic damage that was given to participants in the UK nuclear tests in the 1950s and 1960s (a) before, (b) during and (c) after their service.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200587","200587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022984","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) documents and (b) photographs his Department holds on the flight of a Canberra B6 aircraft with the number 980 at Christmas Island on 30 April 1958.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200588","200588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022985","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) documents and (b) photographs the Atomic Weapons Establishment holds on the flight of a Canberra B6 aircraft with the number 980 at Christmas Island on 30 April 1958.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200589","200589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022986","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to give the Parole Board powers to commission independent (a) psychological and (b) other expert reports if the recommendations of the prison and defence submitted reports differ.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200705","200705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022987","2018-12-12","Attorney General","2018-12-10","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions he has received requests to refer an individual sentence to the Court of Appeal on the grounds of undue leniency in each of the last five years; and on how many of those occasions was the request granted.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200706","200706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022988","2018-12-13","Department for Transport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans for a new direct high speed rail link between Liverpool and High Speed Two; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200590","200590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022989","2018-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the more than 750 agreements with more than 168 countries in which the UK participates as an EU member, how many agreements the EU has informed third countries the UK is to continue participating in during the transition period; how many countries have agreed to each of those more than 750 agreements; what oversight the UK has of that process; and whether the Government is taking steps to secure agreement on rolling over those deals with those countries.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200630","200630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022990","2018-12-12","Department for International Trade","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many of the trade agreements that the UK has as an EU member with third countries will continue in the event that the UK leaves the EU on 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200631","200631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022991","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how funding is allocated to local authorities to tackle sexual health concerns.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200632","200632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022992","2018-12-13","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the total value of contracts outsourced by central Government to the private sector.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200555","200555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022993","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people in Lambeth had HIV in (a) 1997, (b) 2001, (c) 2005, (d) 2010, (e) 2015 and (f) 2017.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200633","200633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022994","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the change was in the number of people with HIV in Lambeth between 2010 and 2018.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200634","200634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022995","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people there were with HIV in Lambeth in each age category in (a) 2010, (b) 2015 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200635","200635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022996","2018-12-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the future funding needs of the Charity Commission; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200707","200707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022997","2018-12-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent support he has given to music conservatoires.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200591","200591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022998","2018-12-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many youth service centres have closed down in Lambeth in each month since 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200636","200636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1022999","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many offences involving (a) a firearm and (b) a knife have been committed in (i) London and (ii) Lambeth since 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200708","200708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023000","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times employers have used his Department's employer checking service to check an employee’s or potential employee’s immigration status in each year since that service was introduced.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200709","200709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023001","2018-12-13","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government has spent on promoting awareness of the employer checking service among employers in each year since that service was created.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200710","200710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023002","2018-12-12","Department for International Trade","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many (a) small, (b) medium and (c) large businesses in Lambeth have licences to export outside the EU.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200711","200711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023003","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many EU nationals live in (a) Streatham and (b) Lambeth.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200712","200712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023004","2018-12-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the ability of UK writers to travel to the EU for (a) writing trips, (b) residencies and (c) poetry performances after the UK has left the EU; and what assessment he has made of the ability of UK writers to undertake such activities in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200592","200592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023005","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will undertake a review of the categories of conditions eligible for medical exemption certificates for NHS prescriptions to ensure that there is provision for mental health conditions.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200637","200637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023006","2018-12-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the reciprocal relationships the UK has with the EU that enable UK authors to claim public lending right payments when their books are borrowed in other EU countries.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200593","200593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023007","2018-12-12","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle the issue of citizenship applications taking longer to process than the service standard of six months.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200713","200713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023008","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding was allocated from the public purse to mental health services for young people in each year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200714","200714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023009","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff of his Department have (a) left his Department and (b) been seconded from his Department to work for the Building Research Establishment in each of the last five years .","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200715","200715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023010","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS Improvement's Quarter three 2017-18 performance report, published in February 2018, how many of the (a) 35,000 nurse vacancies and (b) nearly 10,000 doctor post vacancies identified in that report have now been filled.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200716","200716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023011","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff of his Department have previously been employed by the Building Research Establishment.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200717","200717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023012","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of unreported crimes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200718","200718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023013","2018-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people that were in receipt legacy payments are financially better off as a result of the move to universal credit.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200719","200719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023014","2018-12-13","Treasury","2018-12-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution of 6 December 2018, Official Report, column 1091, if he will publish the enhanced equivalence arrangements for regulating financial services between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200541","200541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023015","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what resources have been allocated to the NHS Business Services Authority to support victims of the contaminated blood scandal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200720","200720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023016","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase public awareness of the link between alcohol consumption and cancer.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200638","200638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023017","2018-12-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK economy of the O2 data failure of 6 December 2018.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200594","200594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023018","2018-12-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to reduce incidences of data outages by mobile phone companies.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200595","200595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023019","2018-12-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the economic effect of mobile data outages on the UK economy in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200596","200596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023020","2018-12-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the public services affected by the data outage experienced by O2 customers on 6 December 2018 are planned to receive compensation for the disruption to service.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200597","200597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023021","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether High Speed Two will begin operations in December 2026.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200721","200721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023022","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much new capacity will be delivered by the 7200 new trains to come on to the rail network between 2014 and 2021; and how many of those new trains are like-for-like replacements of the existing stock.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200722","200722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023023","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress his Department has made on testing delivery models for the healthy schools rating scheme; and when he plans to conclude the testing phase of the scheme.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200723","200723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023024","2018-12-12","Treasury","2018-12-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings Ministers of his department have had with representatives of (a) the alcohol industry and (b) organisations working to reduce alcohol-related harm in 2018; and if he will publish the (i) dates, (ii) attendees and (iii) topics of each of those meetings.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200639","200639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023025","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives from the dental industry on reforming the Units of Dental Activity system of funding.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200640","200640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023026","2018-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 10 December 2018 on the Type 31e Frigate, HCWS1161, whether he has made an estimate of the value of government furnished equipment for the Type 31e frigate programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200598","200598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023027","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of updating the units of dental activity rates used in dentistry.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200641","200641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023029","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the units of dental activity funding system in dentistry on the provision of dental care for families in deprived communities.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200642","200642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023030","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Government has spent from the public purse on Facebook advertising in (a) November and (b) December 2018.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200643","200643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023031","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on the provision of adult social care services of projected increases in the elderly population.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200725","200725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023032","2018-12-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will include alcohol products in the proposed consultation on a 9pm watershed on the advertising of unhealthy foods.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200726","200726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023033","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether (a) he, (b) Ministers and (c) officials of his Department have had meetings with the UN Special Rapporteur on extreme poverty and human rights to discuss poverty in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200727","200727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023034","2018-12-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that developers remove onerous ground rent clauses in leasehold contracts.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200728","200728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023035","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2018 to Question 195084 on Universal Credit: Slough, if he will publish that information for claimants of benefits by nationality at the point of National Insurance number registration.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200729","200729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023036","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to 2018 Budget, how much of the increase in funding allocated to the NHS over the next five years will be allocated to South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200730","200730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023037","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with  reference to the announcement by the Children's Commissioner's Children's Mental, published November 2018, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of referrals of children with mental health problems being closed before those children entered treatment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200731","200731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023038","2018-12-13","Treasury","2018-12-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the financial package agreed by the Government, Transport for London and the Mayor of London for additional funding to support Crossrail will result in Barnett consequentials for Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200644","200644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023039","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the early years attainment gap over the last ten years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200645","200645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023040","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money from the public purse his Department has allocated to marketing for the (a) early years initial (b) primary and (c) secondary teacher training courses.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200646","200646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023041","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what is the average salary is for an early years teacher working in the private, voluntary and independent sector.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200647","200647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023042","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what is the average salary was of an early years teacher in the (a) private, voluntary and independent and (b) public sector.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200648","200648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023043","2018-12-13","Department for International Development","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK Government is taking to tackle the humanitarian situation in Cameroon.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200649","200649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023044","2018-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his French Government counterparts on the humanitarian crisis in Cameroon.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200650","200650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023045","2018-12-13","Department for International Development","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK Government is taking to help support communities in Cameroon affected by the political situation in that country.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200651","200651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023046","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had with Interserve on the viability of existing apprenticeship training following their refinancing talks.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200556","200556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023047","2018-12-12","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many online frauds have (a) been reported to the police and (b) resulted in a police investigation in each of the last five years; and how many of those cases so reported have resulted (i) in a suspect being charged and (ii) in a conviction being made in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200732","200732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023048","2018-12-12","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has plans to introduce guidance to online dating site providers on how to detect false profiles; and in what circumstances such providers must report such matters to the police.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200733","200733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023049","2018-12-12","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports to the police have been made of (a) sexual assaults and (b) fraud arising from contact made by individuals from online dating sites; and in how many cases those reports resulted in a prosecution in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200734","200734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023050","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions (a) he and (b) the Minister of State for Apprenticeships and Skills has had with the Institute for Apprenticeships on the viability of existing apprenticeship training at Interserve following their refinancing talks.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200557","200557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023051","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate the Government has made of the number of people at risk of experiencing rising debt as a result of the six week transitory wait from legacy to universal credit.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200652","200652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023052","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2018 to Question 191917 on Carer's Allowance, whether her Department has made an estimate of the number of (a) pensioners and (b) students in full-time education who have taken on significant caring responsibilities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200653","200653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023053","2018-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2018 to Question 191918 on  Social Security Benefits: Medical Examinations, which external organisations her Department plans to work collaboratively with.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200654","200654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023054","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what contingency plans his Department has to protect apprentices in the event of the collapse of Interserve.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200558","200558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023055","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many UCAS points a T Level is planned to be worth.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200559","200559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023056","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the policy paper entitled Keep on caring: supporting young people from care to independence, published in July 2016, when will the Government plans to review the implementation of the Staying Put programme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200655","200655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023057","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with university groups on whether they will accept T Levels as part of their admissions policies.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200560","200560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023058","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report entitled, Staying Put: An Unfulfilled Promise, published in November 2018 by the Fostering Nework, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the introduction of a national minimum allowance for Staying Put programme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200656","200656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023059","2018-12-13","Department for Education","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprentices are currently receiving training from Interserve Learning and Employment.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200735","200735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023060","2018-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to attend the Yemen peace talks in Stockholm.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200548","200548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023061","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the commitments that the Government made at the London Anti-Corruption Summit 2016, when he plans to launch a consultation on introducing a criminal offence of failing to prevent economic crime.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200736","200736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023062","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans publish a response to his Department's publication entitled, Corporate liability for economic crime: call for evidence, published on 13 January 2018.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200737","200737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023063","2018-12-12","Attorney General","2018-12-10","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussion he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on proposals to reform the law on corporate liability for economic crime.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200738","200738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023064","2018-12-12","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria are used in the allocation of police funding to tackle violent crime.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200549","200549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023065","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of suicides in England and Wales in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200550","200550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023066","2018-12-12","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been granted permission to work in the UK while their cases are being considered in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200561","200561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023067","2018-12-12","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support his Department provides to asylum seekers that seek to volunteer in their local communities.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200562","200562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023068","2018-12-12","Home Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have participated in the pilots for the EU Settlement scheme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200563","200563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023069","2018-12-12","Attorney General","2018-12-10","To ask the Attorney General, whether a suicide note is classified as a legal document.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200564","200564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023070","2018-12-12","Prime Minister","2018-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she had with her counterparts at the G20 Summit in Argentina on a ceasefire in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200565","200565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023071","2018-12-12","Department for International Trade","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effect of the WTO reforms proposed at the G20 summit in Argentina on UK trade with the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200566","200566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023072","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his oral contribution of 27 November 2018 to the Health and Social Care Committee, Question 127, what the positive impacts are for the NHS of the Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200657","200657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023073","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the £936 million funding for health facilities announced on 27 November is in addition to the £20.5 billion of funding for the NHS announced on 18 June 2018.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200658","200658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023074","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the £936 million in additional funding announced on 7 December 2018 will be allocated to mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200659","200659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023075","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the £936 million in additional funding for health facilities announced on 7 December 2018 will be allocated to mental health services in Liverpool.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200660","200660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023076","2018-12-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the £936 million in additional funding for health facilities announced on 7 December 2018 will be allocated to children and young people's mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200661","200661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023077","2018-12-13","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much money the Government spent on advertising an explanation of its EU withdrawal agreement on social media in 2018.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200537","200537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023078","2018-12-13","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which social media platforms the Government has paid to advertise its EU withdrawal agreement; and how much the Government has paid to each of those platforms for that purpose in 2018.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200538","200538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1023079","2018-12-13","Cabinet Office","2018-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Government has spent on advertising on social media platforms in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200542","200542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1017273","2018-12-03","Home Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to give due consideration to the Public Sector Equality Duty in his response to the consultation on powers for dealing with unauthorised development and encampments, which closed on 15 June 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197400","197400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020698","2018-12-10","Treasury","2018-12-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many farmers have been excluded from the agricultural flat-rate VAT scheme since its introduction in each region of the UK in each year since the scheme's introduction.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199853","199853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020775","2018-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Royal Navy of the Joint Guidance for the RAN-RN Relationship signed by the First Sea Lord and Chief of the Royal Australian Navy on 28 November 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200132","200132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020776","2018-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK defence forces will participate in EU Battlegroups in 2019-20.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200090","200090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020777","2018-12-12","Department for International Development","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of UK Official development Assistance on low income countries in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200091","200091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020778","2018-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in the South Sudanese Government on ensuring adherence to the peace deal signed in September 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200092","200092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020779","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2018 to Question 194629, what medals UK citizens who serve in OSCE missions are eligible to receive.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200098","200098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020780","2018-12-11","Department for Education","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has for (a) the Union Learning Fund and (b) other trade union workplace training programmes after the UK leave the EU.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200152","200152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020781","2018-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Cost of Energy Review published in October 2017, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the cost of electricity.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200119","200119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020782","2018-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 160 of the Industrial Strategy, published in November 2017, what progress his Department has made on reducing electricity prices for businesses.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200120","200120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020783","2018-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to close the gap between industrial electricity prices in the UK and those in France and Germany.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200121","200121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020784","2018-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the recommendations to close the gap between UK and EU industrial electricity prices for steel producers in the report, The energy price scandal, a fair power deal for UK steel, published by UK Steel in December 2018.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200122","200122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020785","2018-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that the UK has the lowest energy prices in the EU.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200123","200123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020786","2018-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to introduce a Steel Sector Deal.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200124","200124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020787","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to reduce the rate of the UK carbon tax.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200125","200125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020788","2018-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last spoke with President Poroshenko of Ukraine;  and what issues were discussed at that time.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200138","200138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020789","2018-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last received a request from the Government of Ukraine for a telephone conversation with the President of that country.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200139","200139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020790","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS prescription penalty notices were issued between August 2017 and August 2018; and how many recipients of those notices have subsequently been confirmed as having made a valid claim for free prescriptions.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200141","200141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020791","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what process is in place for the NHS Business Services Authority to check a claimant's eligibility for free prescriptions with the Department of Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200142","200142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020792","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to introduce the digitised system enabling pharmacies instantly to verify a person's entitlement to free prescriptions.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200143","200143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020793","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement of 29 November 2018 on Prisons Update, Official Report HCWS1123, what criteria his Department plans to use to decide which unsuitable accommodation is to be closed and replaced by 10,000 modern prison places.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200144","200144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020794","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement of 29 November 2018 on Prisons Update, Official Report HCWS1123, when it is planned to open the new prisons in (a) Wellingborough and (b) Glen Parva.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200145","200145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020795","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement of 29 November 2018 on Prisons Update, Official Report HCWS1123, when he plans to close the current unsuitable accommodation.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200146","200146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020796","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison custody officers were certified at each contracted prison on the last date for which Ministry of Justice Controller records are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200147","200147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020797","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many certified prison custody officers were on duty at 9am at each contracted prison on the last date for which Ministry of Justice Controller records are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200148","200148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020798","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of stroke care at University Hospitals Coventry and Warwickshire NHS Trust.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200078","200078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020799","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November to Question 192117, if he will publish the Civil Service Benchmark Scores; Whitehall 18 Trends; and All Organisation Scores for the engagement index, engagement drivers, and 62 attitudinal questions from the Civil Service People Survey 2018 results before 20 December 2018.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200153","200153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020800","2018-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the total amount of money transferred from mobility allowance paid to disabled people to the Mobility Scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200079","200079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020801","2018-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Indonesian counterpart on the arrest of West Papuan protesters across the region who were marking independence day on 1 December.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200156","200156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020802","2018-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Government of South Sudan over that Government's use of the death penalty.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200080","200080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020803","2018-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress of denuclearisation in North Korea.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200081","200081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020804","2018-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the House of Commons Library Briefing Paper, Brexit questions in national and EU courts, Number 8415, published on 6 December 2018, what estimate he has made of the total cost to the public purse of the Government's legal action in Brexit-related cases.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200082","200082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020805","2018-12-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding local government receives to deliver children’s services.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200075","200075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020806","2018-12-11","Department for Education","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the overspend on children’s services in the 2017-18 financial year; and how much additional investment for children’s services was announced in Budget 2018.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200076","200076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020807","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of total public expenditure is spent on children’s services delivered by local government.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200077","200077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020808","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 4 December 2018, Official Report, column 879, what information his Department has received from the Electoral Commission on whether the EU referendum 2016 was a fair poll.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200130","200130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020809","2018-12-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on making available additional funding for the NHS to prepare for a potential increase in demand for health services between December 2018 and March 2019.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200129","200129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020810","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of (a) the average delay on trains between Sheffield and London St Pancras since the new timetable was introduced in May 2018 and (b) the average delay in the same period in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200086","200086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020811","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned timeframe is for the commencement of High Speed Two services to Sheffield.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200087","200087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020812","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned timeframe is for completion of the northern link for services from Sheffield to the main High Speed Two line.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200088","200088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020813","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his timeframe is for completion of improvements to the Hope Valley line.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200089","200089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020814","2018-12-12","Department for International Development","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of the continued military offensive on Hodeidah port on the delivery of humanitarian aid in Yemen; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure humanitarian and commercial imports are delivered into and throughout Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200068","200068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020815","2018-12-12","Department for International Development","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the reports by the UN World Food Programme that there has been a decrease in accuracy of operations at Hodeidah port in recent weeks.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200069","200069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020816","2018-12-11","Department for International Development","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to respond to the risk of famine in Yemen; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200070","200070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020817","2018-12-11","Department for International Development","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the conflict in Yemen on that country's economy; and what steps her Department is taking to support the Yemen economy.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200071","200071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020818","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to respond to Question 192923, on 19 November 2018, asked by the hon. Member for Brighton Pavilion.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200103","200103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020819","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2018 to Question 193427 on Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty, on how many occasions under the trilateral Agreement of 6 September 1976 between the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, the European Atomic Energy Community and the Agency in Connection with the Treaty on the Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons, notifications were made by the UK of withdrawal of nuclear materials from safeguards for national security reasons in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200104","200104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020820","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) security and (b) humanitarian situation in Dimit, Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200072","200072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020821","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the average length of time between notification of unsuccessful claims for personal independence payments and tribunal hearing for appeals of those refused claims in the most recent period for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200083","200083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020822","2018-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the length of time taken for the transfer of documents between her Department and the Courts and Tribunal Service relating to personal independence payments claimants who are appealing the refusal of their claim in the most recent period for which figures are available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200084","200084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020823","2018-12-12","Treasury","2018-12-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that taxpayers were made aware of the introduction of the High Income Child Benefit Charge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200085","200085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020824","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned completion date is for road improvements to the A140 in Suffolk close to the Norfolk border; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200105","200105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020825","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Thai Government on the treatment of (a) Karen and (b) Shan refugees in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200073","200073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020826","2018-12-11","Department for International Development","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the level of access by providers of humanitarian aid to (a) Kachin and (b) Shan State in Burma.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200074","200074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020827","2018-12-12","Department for International Development","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development,  pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2018 to Question 171641 on Palestinians: Schools, whether her Department has commissioned the study into the new Palestinian textbooks.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200063","200063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020828","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Mayor of London on transferring franchising authority to Transport for London for contracting Great Northern metro train services that run to and from Moorgate station.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200064","200064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020829","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to transfer commuter rail services to Transport for London as proposed in Chris Gibb's independent report to the Department for Transport on the Govia Thameslink Railway franchise.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200065","200065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020830","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings he has had with the Mayor of London on plans for devolving commuter rail services to Transport for London.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200066","200066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020831","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has completed its hard review of the Govia Thameslink Railway franchise; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200067","200067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020832","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2018 to Question 176223 on Housing Associations: Finance, whether that new spending will result in Barnett consequentials for the devolved administrations.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200107","200107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020833","2018-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children were granted legal aid under exceptional case funding each (a) year and (b) quarter since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200099","200099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020834","2018-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young adults were granted legal aid under exceptional case funding each (a) year and (b) quarter since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200100","200100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020835","2018-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were granted legal aid under exceptional case funding each (a) year and (b) quarter since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200101","200101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020836","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department sign the TUC’s Dying to Work Charter.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200108","200108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020837","2018-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of applications for exceptional case funding were granted legal aid in every year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200102","200102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020838","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to commence the equal pay review within his Department.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200109","200109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020839","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for (a) his Department and (b) each agency of his Department, what proportion of staff in the 2018 People Survey reported that during the past 12 months they had personally experienced (a) discrimination and (b) bullying or harassment at work.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200110","200110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020840","2018-12-11","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for each People Survey undertaken in the (a) Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency and (b) Driving Standards Agency which proceeded it, what proportion of staff reported that during the past 12 months they had personally experienced bullying or harassment at work.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200111","200111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020841","2018-12-12","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the dates of all the consultation meeting officials of his Department (a) held and (b) planned with trades union health and safety representatives on the Modernisation of Office Environment project.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200112","200112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020842","2018-12-11","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list all the risk assessments conducted by officials of his Department relating to the Modernisation of Office Environment project; and whether trade union health and safety representatives were consulted for each of those risk assessments.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200113","200113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020843","2018-12-11","Department for Transport","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when officials of his Department plan to consult trade union health and safety representatives on (a) any further moves of staff of out of his Department’s Great Minster House headquarters building and (b) on future building works to be carried out in that building in 2019.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200114","200114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020844","2018-12-11","House of Commons Commission","2018-12-07","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, whether Plymouth Gin will be served in Parliamentary catering establishments ahead of Mayflower 400 commemorations.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200158","200158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020845","2018-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department has used paint containing (a) hexavalent chromium and (b) chromium VI in servicing vehicles.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200133","200133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020846","2018-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 28 November 2018 to Question 194225, whether Queen's Regulation J975 is compatible with the lack of a mandatory requirement to hold a fatal accident inquiry for a military death in Scotland prior to the Inquiries into Fatal Accidents and Sudden Deaths etc. (Scotland) Act 2016.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200134","200134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020847","2018-12-12","Treasury","2018-12-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he plans to respond to the House of Lords Economic Affairs Sub-Committee report entitled The Powers of HMRC: Treating Taxpayers Fairly, HC 242.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200140","200140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020848","2018-12-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on the establishment of a comprehensive database of mesh implants.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200155","200155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020850","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Government plans to designate a marine reserve around South Sandwich Islands.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200159","200159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020851","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the timeframe is for the designation of a marine reserve around South Sandwich Islands.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200160","200160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020852","2018-12-11","Home Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is his policy to allow third-party payment of the fees for applications for settled status for EU citizens.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200136","200136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020853","2018-12-11","Cabinet Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of non-UK EU citizens working in health and social care in the UK.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200137","200137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020854","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number non-UK EU citizens employed by in each Government Department as a (a) civil servant and (b) contractor.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200126","200126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020855","2018-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her letter of 5 December 2018 on the Work Capability Assessment, when her Department will provide statistics on how many people flowed off Employment and Support Allowance whose date of death was at the same time, and who had a Work Capability Assessment decision of fit for work between March 2014 and February 2017.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200157","200157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020856","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse would be of not charging for applications for Settled Status from non-UK EU nationals employed directly by the Government.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200127","200127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020857","2018-12-12","Cabinet Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what restrictions there would be on the employment by civil service of EEA in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200128","200128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020858","2018-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse has been of the development of the ecoSUB-µ5-SVP vehicles to be deployed from HMS Enterprise.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200135","200135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020859","2018-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of Crown Post Offices that will be closed following his announcement of 11 October 2018.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200154","200154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020860","2018-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many meetings (a) she and (b) her predecessor had with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 September and 30 November 2018.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200093","200093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020861","2018-12-12","Scotland Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 September and 30 November 2018.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200094","200094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020862","2018-12-12","Department for Education","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 September and 30 November 2018.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200095","200095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020863","2018-12-12","Department for International Development","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many meetings she had with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 September and 30 November 2018.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200096","200096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020864","2018-12-11","Wales Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 September and 30 November 2018.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200097","200097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020865","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2018 to Question 183515 on Eating Disorders, what measures Health Education England is requesting in the General Medical Council training review to improve eating disorders training among doctors.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200115","200115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020866","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2018 to Question 183515 on Eating Disorders, whether his Department is taking steps to seek to ensure that thereis an increase in the number of training ours undertaken on eating disorders under the medical school curricula.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200116","200116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020867","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2018 to Question 186311 on Mental Health Services, which child and adolescent mental health services he has visited since taking on his position; and on what dates those visits took place.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200117","200117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020868","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of people admitted to hospital after a suicide attempt were discharged with no follow-up appointment or care plan.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200106","200106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020869","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what date the NHS 10-year plan will be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200118","200118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020870","2018-12-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to reduce the risk of fraud from the availability of personal information on the Companies House database.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200149","200149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020871","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to ensure that those affected by the 2019 loan charge are not forced into bankruptcy by the repayments.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200150","200150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020872","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to respond to the House of Lords Economic Affairs Sub-Committee report entitled The powers of HMRC: treating taxpayers fairly, HL 242.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200151","200151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020873","2018-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that direct payments from universal credit to landlords of rent and arrears continue (a) when a claimant moves from live to full universal credit service and (b) during the managed migration process.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200161","200161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020874","2018-12-12","Northern Ireland Office","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what role his Department played in (a) organising and (b) financing the visit to Parliament by Northern Ireland business representatives during the week commencing Monday 3 December 2018 to meet with hon. Members and Peers.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200162","200162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020875","2018-12-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2018 to Question 183510 on Suicide: Bereavement Counselling, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS staff members affected by patient suicide are proactively offered support.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200163","200163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020573","2018-12-11","Home Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Department has taken to honour its commitment to implement the Dubs amendment; what assessment he has made of whether his Department has met that commitment.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199927","199927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020574","2018-12-11","Department for Transport","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will accompany a person with disabilities on public transport in order to gain first-hand experience of the difficulties disabled people can face when accessing public transport.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199889","199889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020575","2018-12-11","Department for Transport","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve assisted travel for disabled people across public transport.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199890","199890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020576","2018-12-11","Attorney General","2018-12-06","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of cases of alleged hate crimes ending before going to court as a result of such complaints being withdrawn.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199928","199928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020577","2018-12-11","Cabinet Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the proportion of global phishing attacks that target the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199929","199929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020578","2018-12-11","Cabinet Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the GovTech innovation fund has made on tackling loneliness and isolation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199930","199930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020579","2018-12-11","Home Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers (a) with children and (b) without children resided in the Cardiff South and Penarth constituency and were subsequently held in detention centres each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199875","199875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020580","2018-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Cardiff and (b) Vale of Glamorgan have made successful claims for underpayments of universal credit since the beginning of the roll-out; and what the average value is of each such claim.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199876","199876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020581","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential cost to local authorities of mandatory separate food waste collections in England.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199931","199931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020582","2018-12-11","Home Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to plan for processing new residence documents as outlined in Article 18 of the EU Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199877","199877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020583","2018-12-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with officials from other Departments on the availability and price of fresh fruit and vegetables in UK shops to support its healthy eating policies.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199926","199926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020584","2018-12-11","Home Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Early Intervention Youth Fund; and what accomplishments that fund has achieved.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199932","199932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020585","2018-12-11","Home Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to make meaningful progress on the Disclosure and Barring Service modernisation programme.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199933","199933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020586","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Customs Declaration Service will be fully operational by January 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199789","199789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020587","2018-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with online media providers on preventing fake news from being placed on their platforms.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199790","199790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020588","2018-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the change in the number of dogs with electronic collars has been in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199791","199791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020589","2018-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled The status of UK SPAs in the 2000s: the Third Network Review, published by the Joint Nature Conservation Committee in 2016, what representations have been received by (a) his Department, (b) his Department's agencies and (c) his Department's non-departmental public bodies on completing the network of Special Protection Areas for Curlew in the breeding and non-breeding seasons.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199770","199770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020590","2018-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence,  whether the UK will continue to participate in the Coordinated Annual Review on Defence after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199792","199792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020591","2018-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to include in proposals for a Domestic Abuse Bill, provisions to ban the cross-examination of victims by perpetrators of domestic abuse in the family courts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199893","199893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020592","2018-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to restart Project Pegasus.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199830","199830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020593","2018-12-11","Home Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer dated 4 December 2018 to Question 197314, in what circumstances was it (a) relevant and (b) not relevant to require people with TOEIC certificates whose results were found by ETS to be questionable to undertake a fresh test or an interview.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199763","199763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020594","2018-12-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 188822 on Department for Exiting the European Union: Facebook, which geographies including the details of any postcodes used have been targeted by his Department to ensure that their adverts are optimised to reach the right audience.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199866","199866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020595","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November to Question 188205, what range of models involving investment in infrastructure his Department plans to use to meet the proposals set out in the 2017 National Infrastructure and Construction Pipeline.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199867","199867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020596","2018-12-11","Department for International Development","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether his Department allocates funding to the church-led people-to-people initiatives in South Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199771","199771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020597","2018-12-11","Department for International Development","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department allocates funding to women-led peace initiatives in South Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199772","199772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020598","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he Department allocates funding to projects to reduce the number of small arms imported into South Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199773","199773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020599","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the wider take-up of restorative justice as a form of reconciliation in South Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199774","199774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020600","2018-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received a benefit sanction in December 2017.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199891","199891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020601","2018-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her policy is on the provision of Departmental (a) guidance and (b) information to people that are subject to universal credit migration.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199829","199829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020602","2018-12-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of the recommendations for spectrum licensing made in the report, High Performance Wireless Broadband: An Opportunity for Rural and Enterprise 5G, published by the Independent Networks Cooperative Association in June 2018.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199916","199916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020603","2018-12-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received on the quality of fruit and vegetables available in the school fruit and vegetable scheme.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199806","199806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020604","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the conclusions of the report entitled, Two Authorities, One Way, Zero Dissent on arbitrary arrest and torture under the Palestinian Authority and Hamas, published in October 2018 by Human Rights Watch.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199894","199894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020605","2018-12-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data he holds on the treatments available for people with Parkinson’s disease in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199802","199802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020606","2018-12-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with Parkinson’s disease in each region of the UK are offered the full range of available treatments.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199803","199803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020607","2018-12-10","Women and Equalities","2018-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Education on using the national curriculum to tackle misogyny.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199794","199794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020608","2018-12-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for appeals for social security and child support cases.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199804","199804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020609","2018-12-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to support SMEs that are run by women.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199795","199795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020610","2018-12-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was for a Social Security and Child Support case to be resolved in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199805","199805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020611","2018-12-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what further support the Government plans to provide to women who have received Government start-up loans to help them maintain their start-ups past the first year.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199796","199796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020612","2018-12-10","Women and Equalities","2018-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what representations she has had from civil society organisations on bringing Section 106 of the Equality Act 2010 into force.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199797","199797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020613","2018-12-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of universal credit being paid into a single bank account on the (a) independence of women and (b) balance of power in their relationships.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199798","199798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020614","2018-12-10","Women and Equalities","2018-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to encourage employers to offer flexible working arrangements to women going through the menopause.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199799","199799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020615","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of political stability in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199778","199778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020616","2018-12-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many eligible gay and bisexual men have completed the human papillomavirus vaccine programme.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199807","199807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020617","2018-12-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has plans for a catch-up programme for all boys up to the age of 18 to access the human papillomavirus vaccine.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199808","199808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020618","2018-12-11","Treasury","2018-12-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to advise small and medium-sized businesses on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on tax regulations.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199779","199779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020619","2018-12-10","Department for Education","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent changes to pay levels in further education colleges on the ability of such institutions to recruit and retain staff.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199887","199887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020620","2018-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of human rights protection in Egypt.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199780","199780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020621","2018-12-11","Home Office","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Department for Exiting the European Union policy paper entitled Citizens’ Rights - EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU published on 6 December 2018, how the Government will distinguish between EU citizens who are resident in the UK before 29 March 2019 and those who arrive after that date.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199919","199919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1020622","2018-12-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has been made of the effect of single family payments of universal credit on people who are in violent or coercive relationships.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199782","199782"
