"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45909","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of the illegal use of controlled substances in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) Brigg and Goole constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194486","194486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45910","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in probable psychological disturbance reported in Understanding Society from 18.0 per cent in 2009-10 to 18.6 per cent in 2011-12.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194398","194398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45911","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are affected by motor neurone disease in (a) St Albans, (b) Hertfordshire, (c) the East of England and (d) the UK; and what funds his Department has spent on tackling that disease in (i) St Albans, (ii) Hertfordshire, (iii) the East of England and (iv) the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194384","194384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45912","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of missed NHS appointments in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) East Lancashire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194347","194347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45913","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has issued on reporting to the police registered medical practitioners who do not return complete HSA4 forms.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194427","194427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45914","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK recognises as EU citizens all Latvian and Estonian citizens of Russian ethnic grouping born in Latvia and Estonia at the time of or since the EU accession of those countries.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194342","194342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45915","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the UK Border Agency designates citizens who live and may have been born in Latvia and Estonia, whom the governments of Latvia and Estonia continue to designate as Russian by cultural and language testing.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194343","194343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45916","2014-04-03","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what deadline she has provided to chief constables by which they must hand over any evidence to the Independent Police Complaints Commission in relation to Hillsborough.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194494","194494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45917","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the terms of reference are for the inquiry led by Mark Ellison QC announced on 6 March 2014 into whether undercover police officers caused miscarriages of justice; whether Mr Ellison will be given access to all documentation from Operation Herne for his review; whether members of the public will be able to give evidence to Mr Ellison during his review; and whether the review will cover cases involving the National Public Order Intelligence Unit.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194475","194475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45918","2014-04-02","House of Commons Commission","2014-03-31","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many police officers have been employed in office-based roles in SO17 Palace of Westminster in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194360","194360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45919","2014-04-02","House of Commons Commission","2014-03-31","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many police officer managers have been deployed at SO17 Palace of Westminster in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194361","194361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45920","2014-04-02","House of Commons Commission","2014-03-31","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the police staff turnover rates have been at SO17 Palace of Westminster over the last 10 years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194359","194359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45921","2014-04-02","Department for International Development","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department allocated to microfinance schemes in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194399","194399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45922","2014-04-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged 18 years and over convicted of the offence of threatening with article with blade or point or offensive weapon have received a sentence of (a) under six months, (b) six months and (c) over six months in each year since that offence's inception; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194374","194374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45923","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women were refused bail and remanded in custody where the allegation related to (i) an offence against the person, (ii) a public order offence and (iii) a harassment offence in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194404","194404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45924","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in each prison establishment are not being held in relation to criminal proceedings; and what the reason is for their being so held in each case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194405","194405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45925","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for burglary for an individual convicted of an offence of burglary without being sent to prison was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194406","194406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45926","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what programmes which receive funding from his Department are available solely to (a) men and (b) women.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194407","194407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45927","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) male and (b) female prisoners were released on temporary licence by way of (i) resettlement day release, (ii) resettlement overnight release and (iii) childcare resettlement in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194409","194409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45928","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people with 15 or more previous convictions were not sent to prison on conviction for (a) burglary and (b) violence against the person in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194408","194408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45929","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish his Department's equality impact assessment of its policy on uniforms for male and female prisoners.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194430","194430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45930","2014-04-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many individuals aged under 18 years convicted of the offence of threatening with an article with blade or point or offensive weapon received a sentence of (a) under four months, (b) four months and (c) over four months in each year since the offence's inception; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194378","194378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45931","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) advice and (b) written guidance (i) he, (ii) Ministers and (iii) officials in his Department have given to Aspire to Change (A2C) since December 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194432","194432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45932","2014-04-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged (a) under 18 years old and (b) 18 years and over (i) were prosecuted and (ii) received a custodial sentence for the offence of threatening with article with blade or point or offensive weapon in each year since the offence's inception.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194379","194379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45933","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been paid by his Department to Aspire to Change (A2C) since its formation; for what purpose each payment was made; what assessment he has made of the value for money of such expenditure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194433","194433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45934","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been given more than one life sentence on separate sentencing occasions in the last 10 years; and what the offences were for which they received those life sentences.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194380","194380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45935","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the proportion of offences where the victim surcharge is ordered and there is no victim.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194381","194381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45936","2014-04-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2014, Official Report, column 293W, on prisons: mother and baby units, what the reasons were for the time taken to provide a substantive answer day to the named day question tabled for answer on 10 February 2014.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194372","194372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45937","2014-04-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged (a) under 18 years old and (b) 18 years and over were (i) prosecuted and (ii) received a custodial sentence for carrying a bladed or pointed article in a public place in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194369","194369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45938","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the ratio of prison officers to inmates by gender was in each (a) prison establishment and (b) category of prison in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194419","194419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45939","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he or his officials have had with the management of HM Prison Oakwood about staffing levels at that prison.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194420","194420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45940","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of a magistrates' court proceeding was in (a) all cases and (b) cases relating to the non-payment of the television licence fee.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194436","194436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45941","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what increase in staffing levels at HM Prison Oakwood his Department has agreed with G4S.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194421","194421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45942","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many chief executives of probation services have formed a mutual; how many of those mutuals have passed the pre-qualification questionnaire in the competitiveness process of community rehabilitation companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194439","194439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45943","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) discussions with and (b) representations from Aspire to Change (A2C) (i) he, (ii) Ministers and (iii) officials in his Department have had since December 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194440","194440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45944","2014-04-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new cases were allocated by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority to be dealt with by each of their regional teams in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194426","194426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45945","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects to announce the finalists for each community rehabilitation company; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194437","194437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45946","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many bids have been received for each community rehabilitation company; how many of those were (a) successful and (b) discounted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194438","194438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45947","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of presumption for contact in relation to the role of fathers in the family courts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194357","194357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45948","2014-04-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of prisoners' access to books on (a) prisoners' educational achievements, (b) prisoners' behaviour and (c) reoffending rates; and what steps he is taking to improve prisoners' access to books.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194424","194424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45949","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which books are available to be bought from the shop in prisons in England.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194356","194356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45950","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what consultation his Department undertook before excluding damage sustained in utero as a result of illegal drug taking from the definition of a crime of violence under Annex B paragraph 4(e) of the Criminal Compensation Scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194338","194338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45951","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the expected additional cost is in 2014-15 of the increased staffing levels agreeed for HM Prison Oakwood.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194364","194364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45952","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison custody officers are employed at HMP Oakwood.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194348","194348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45953","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans are in place to increase the operational capacity at HMP Oakwood.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194349","194349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45954","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much in legal aid claims has been paid to Leigh Day and Public Interest Lawyers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194326","194326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45955","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow mandatory sentencing in cases of carrying an article with blade or point of offensive weapon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194327","194327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45956","2014-04-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of those aged under 25 years in Northern Ireland are registered to vote.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194490","194490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45957","2014-04-03","Prime Minister","2014-03-31","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with his Commonwealth counterparts on the resolution passed by the 25th Human Rights Council session on Promoting Reconciliation, Accountability and Human Rights in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194375","194375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45958","2014-04-02","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-31","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2013, Official Report, columns 611-2W, on electoral registration officers, when the Electoral Commission will make available its final assessment of performance for 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194423","194423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45959","2014-04-02","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-31","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2013, Official Report, columns 611-2W, on electoral registration officers, which local authorities failed to meet performance standard 1 on using local government databases, in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194403","194403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45960","2014-04-02","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-31","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 620W, on the electoral register, what progress the Electoral Commission has made in improving registration rates of attainers; and what measures the Electoral Commission uses to judge its performance of increasing registration rates of attainers.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194422","194422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45961","2014-04-02","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-31","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, with which (a) mobile telephone companies, (b) voluntary groups and (c) travel card providers the Electoral Commission is working to improve registration rates of young people.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194344","194344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45962","2014-04-02","Department for Transport","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the maximum amount available to councils who apply for extra funding for potholes is; and what funding his Department provides to tackle pot holes in St Albans.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194434","194434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45963","2014-04-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what service level agreements his Department has with companies contracted to carry out the assessment process for the personal independence payment.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194367","194367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45964","2014-04-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time is for applicants for personal independence payment in each region of the UK to be assessed by (a) Capita Health and Wellbeing and (b) Atos Healthcare in each region.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194368","194368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45965","2014-04-02","Cabinet Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the percentage change in long-term youth unemployment was in each constituency between 2010 and the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194345","194345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45966","2014-04-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 162W, on employment and support allowance, when his Department expects to publish data on mandatory reconsiderations of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194425","194425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46012","2014-04-03","Attorney General","2014-03-31","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions have been (a) commenced, (b) resulted in a non-custodial sentence and (c) resulted in a custodial sentence for (i) witness intimidation, (ii) perverting the cause of justice and (iii) conspiracy to pervert the course of justice as a result of incidents arising from cases involving domestic violence in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194444","194444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46013","2014-04-03","Attorney General","2014-03-31","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been prosecuted under the Domestic Violence, Crime and Victims Act 2004 for breach of a non-molestation order in each police force area in each year since that Act came into force.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194445","194445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46014","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to A UK Strategy for Agricultural Technologies, what progress he has made in establishing a Centre for Agricultural Informatics.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194481","194481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46015","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to A UK Strategy for Agricultural Technologies, whether UK Trade & Investment has established a new dedicated team to increase the volume and value of overseas investment into the UK agri-tech sector.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194482","194482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46016","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to A UK Strategy for Agricultural Technologies, if he will list the activities undertaken by the UK Trade and Investment Business Ambassador to champion UK agri-tech; and which early stage markets have been identified for future growth.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194467","194467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46017","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to A UK Strategy for Agricultural Technologies, for what reason Qatar was chosen as the first country for UK Trade and Investment to work with.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194468","194468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46018","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to A UK Strategy for Agricultural Technologies, what progress UK Trade and Investment has made on identifying possibilities for UK-based  food and drink producers through the High Value Opportunity Programme for Food Security.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194469","194469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46019","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to A UK Strategy for Agricultural Technologies, how many times the Leadership Council has met; and what the items for discussion were at each meeting.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194470","194470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46020","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to support part-time entrepreneurs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194519","194519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46021","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to A UK strategy for agricultural technologies, what progress has been made in mapping and evaluating private and government funding available for research, translation and innovation.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194535","194535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46022","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many posts in his Department will be relocated to the South West in the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194572","194572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46023","2014-04-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps UK Trade and Investment has taken to help export business in Morecambe and the surrounding area.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194559","194559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46024","2014-04-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will introduce joint and several liability across the UK labour market to ensure subcontractors throughout a supply chain comply with employment law obligations.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194556","194556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46025","2014-04-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of whether companies that post workers to the UK from other countries can create unfair competition for UK businesses.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194557","194557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46026","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to A UK Strategy for Agricultural Technologies, how much of the £90 million to establish centres for agricultural innovation has been allocated; and how many such centres have been established.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194478","194478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46027","2014-04-02","Cabinet Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the standardised mortality rate from diabetes was in each parliamentary constituency in the latest year for which figures are available; and what the average standardised mortality rate from diabetes in England was in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194564","194564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46028","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households have used the (a) the Help to Buy (Equity Loan) and (b) Help to Buy (Mortgage Guarantee) scheme; and how many households he originally expected to use each scheme.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194511","194511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46029","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the rules set out in the HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) manual BIM24000, whether HMRC has collected the appropriate rates of corporation tax from member-owned golf clubs; and what steps HMRC plans to take to recoup tax losses due to unlawful tax declarations by member-owned golf clubs where they have been found to have underpaid corporation tax.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194534","194534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46030","2014-04-03","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applicants to the Help to Buy (Mortgage Guarantee) scheme to date were not born in England (a) in absolute terms and (b) as a percentage of overall applicants.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194545","194545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46031","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many posts HM Revenue and Customs will relocate to the South West in the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194570","194570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46032","2014-04-03","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value was of penalties issued to overseas landlords who failed to submit the tax returns issued to them in each of the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194576","194576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46033","2014-04-03","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to consult on changes to the eligibility for the Enterprise Investment Scheme announced in Budget 2014; and whether owners and promoters of community energy schemes will be included in the stakeholders consulted.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194552","194552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46034","2014-04-03","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion by value was paid of the penalties that were issued to overseas landlords who failed to submit the tax returns issued to them in each of the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194577","194577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46035","2014-04-03","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much rental income was declared by overseas landlords in each of the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194578","194578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46036","2014-04-03","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce a registration scheme to monitor the flow and location of posted workers to assist tax collecting agencies in inspection and enforcement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194554","194554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46037","2014-04-03","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total value of tax self-assessed by overseas landlords was; and what proportion was paid in each of the tax years (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12 and (iv) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194579","194579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46038","2014-04-03","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to compel companies that post workers to the UK to retain copies of employment contracts and pay slips in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194555","194555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46039","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many overseas landlords had their application to have rent paid to them without tax being deducted at source (a) approved and (b) declined in each of the tax years (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12 and (iv) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194581","194581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46040","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the five most common reasons were for declining an application from an overseas landlord to have rent paid to them without tax being deducted at source in each of the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194582","194582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46041","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many overseas landlords had tax returns issued to them in each of the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194583","194583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46042","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many overseas landlords submitted the tax returns issued to them in each of the tax years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194584","194584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46043","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the European Court of Justice ruling on the Bridport and West Dorset case of 19 December 2013, what measures will be taken to ensure that the refund of VAT to member-owned golf clubs will be distributed to club members.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194532","194532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46044","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will extend the equity loan for new homes in the Help to Buy scheme to older properties.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194544","194544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46045","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much corporation tax has been paid to the Exchequer in respect of visitors fees for member-owned golf clubs since 1990.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194533","194533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46046","2014-04-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many men received statutory paternity pay for (a) ordinary paternity leave and (b) additional paternity leave in (i) 2011-12 and (ii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194505","194505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46047","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to implement the recommendations made by the Natural Capital Committee in its Second state of natural capital report which are relevant to his Department.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194466","194466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46048","2014-04-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homeless households were accepted as being owed a duty of accommodation by their local authority in each year since 2010; and how many such acceptances were the result of domestic violence.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194443","194443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46049","2014-04-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many first time buyers have been helped by the Government's Help to Buy scheme (a) nationally and (b) in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194542","194542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46050","2014-04-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's (a) catering and (b) hospitality budget was in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194474","194474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46051","2014-04-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what reports he has received of levels of council tax set by Lancaster District Council for 2014-15.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194560","194560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46052","2014-04-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what reports he has received of levels of council tax set by Lancashire County Council for 2014-15.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194561","194561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46053","2014-04-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of local authorities who will hold a referendum as a result of raising council tax by two per cent or more for 2014-15.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194562","194562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46054","2014-04-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many council houses or social housing new builds have been built by Lancaster District Council, and in which areas, since 1997.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194539","194539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46055","2014-04-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department has provided to Lancaster City Council to ensure affordable homes are built in rural areas in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194541","194541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46056","2014-04-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to lift people over 75 years of age out of council tax.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194543","194543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46057","2014-04-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the status is of the ICT Relet Project; what costs his Department has incurred; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194510","194510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46058","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) personnel and (b) assets are participating in NATO's Baltic Regional Training Events in 2014; and what (i) personnel and (ii) assets participated in the events in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194525","194525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46059","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether both Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carriers can be docked at Portsmouth Harbour simultaneously.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194522","194522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46060","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which bidders and consortia have passed the pre-qualification stage to purchase the land-focused business of the Defence Support Group.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194517","194517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46061","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to designate the Aircraft Carrier Alliance as a public body for the purposes of the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194566","194566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46062","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Defence Infrastructure Organisation will allow the contract to dredge Portsmouth Harbour so the Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carrier can navigate it; what estimate he has made of the contract's cost to the public; and when work will (a) commence and (b) finish.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194526","194526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46063","2014-04-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what collision warning capability the Rangeless Autonomous Information Debriefing System had.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194549","194549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46064","2014-04-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the installation of an EASAMS Collision Warning System in Tornado aircraft was not completed following the successful trials of the system in 1995 and 1996.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194547","194547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46065","2014-04-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the fitting of the Rangeless Autonomous Information Debriefing System equipment to Tornado aircraft was regarded as mitigation for the collision warning risk over the last decade.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194548","194548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46066","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times a day the Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carrier will be able to enter Portsmouth Harbour during spring tides.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194528","194528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46067","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which companies tendered for the Portsmouth Harbour dredging contract.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194529","194529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46068","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times HMS Hermes docked in Portsmouth Harbour.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194530","194530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46069","2014-04-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any other aircraft were operating in the area at the time of the collision between the two Tornado aircraft above the Moray Firth on 3 July 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194551","194551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46070","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what interruption to commercial and recreational shipping traffic is expected during the dredging of Portsmouth Harbour.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194531","194531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46071","2014-04-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraphs 7.22, 7.21 and 7.7 of Joint Service Publication 832, if he will place in the Library and on his Department's website a copy of the Service inquiry regarding the collision of two Tornado aircraft over the Moray Firth on 3 July 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194550","194550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46072","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) beam and (b) draft is of the  Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carrier when it is loaded to its maximum configuration.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194527","194527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46073","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which sites used by the land-focused business of the Defence Support Group will be (a) sold, (b) leased to the buyer and (c) closed with a view to being put on the open market for development.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194518","194518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46074","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what collision warning system is currently being tested on Typhoon aircraft; when he expects testing to be completed; when a decision will be taken to install such a system; and what the estimated total cost is.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194523","194523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46075","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many air proximity incidents by classification took place with a Typhoon aircraft in each of the last three years; and what the other aircraft involved was in each incident, broken down by by location.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194524","194524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46076","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much electricity is consumed by a Queen Elizabeth class carrier when it is alongside with no internal power generation taking place.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194520","194520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46077","2014-04-02","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what work is required to the docks at Portsmouth to accommodate the Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194521","194521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46078","2014-04-03","Cabinet Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Debate of 3 March 2014, Official Report, columns 726-32W, on Census (Kashmiri ethnic representation), if he will add a category of Kashmiri to the tick boxes on the Census.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194387","194387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46079","2014-04-03","Department for Education","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what reports he has received about teaching standards and education at Ad-Deen Primary School, Ilford; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194388","194388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46080","2014-04-03","Department for Education","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on implementing the early help recommendation of the Munro Review.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194392","194392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46081","2014-04-03","Department for Education","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which establishments are being investigated in relation to historical abuse by Jimmy Savile.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194393","194393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46082","2014-04-02","Department for Education","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase freedoms for special schools to design their own curriculum.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194569","194569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46083","2014-04-02","Department for Education","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the involvement of practising teachers in the design of the national curriculum.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194571","194571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46084","2014-04-02","Department for Education","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will include cancer awareness education as part of the national curriculum in personal, social and health education.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194537","194537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46085","2014-04-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 31W, on the Environment Agency, when the review of existing workloads against enforcement priorities and available budgets will be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194449","194449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46086","2014-04-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish (a) the results of the review of each area of the Environment Agency's existing workloads against enforcement priorities and available budgets and (b) any decisions made about the future workload and priorities of the enforcement and legal caseload.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194450","194450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46087","2014-04-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff worked in investigation, legal and enforcement action in each geographical area of the Environment Agency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194447","194447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46088","2014-04-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cases were (a) investigated for enforcement action, (b) issued and proceeded in the courts, (c) discontinued completely, (d) enforced using a lower level of action than originally envisaged and (e) ceased to be investigated in each Environment Agency area since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194446","194446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46089","2014-04-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Turkish Prime Minister on show-trials and the jailing of journalists in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194463","194463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46090","2014-04-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what asset freezes and visa bans he plans to impose following Russia's illegal annexation of the Crimea.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194558","194558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46091","2014-04-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received about (a) attempts by the Iranian state to incite hatred towards the Bahá'í community and (b) the number of religiously motivated attacks on the Bahá'í  in Iran.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194575","194575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46092","2014-04-03","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent changes have been made in the issuing of visa applications at the Visa Centre in Moscow.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194580","194580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46093","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which of the mitochondrial replacement techniques under consideration that have been developed in the UK have been shown to work safely and efficiently in monkeys.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194585","194585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46094","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the risks of (a) chromosomal abnormalities and (b) abnormal embryo development in embryos created through Maternal Spindle Transfer and Pronuclear Transfer.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194586","194586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46095","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of lives saved annually by the new in-vitro-fertilisation techniques of Maternal Spindle Transfer and Pronuclear Transfer.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194587","194587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46096","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's press release, Innovative genetic treatment to prevent mitochondrial disease, of 28 June 2013, which of the two fertilised embryos used in pronuclear transfer his Department considers saved as a result of the process.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194589","194589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46097","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the debate of 12 March 2014, Official Report, column 171WH, on Mitochondrial Transfer (Three Parent Children), if he will reassess his Department's statement that there is no genomic DNA in mitochondria.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194588","194588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46098","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the relationship between eating disorders and type 1 diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194573","194573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46099","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many posts in his Department will be relocated to the South West in the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194574","194574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46100","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons his Department has planned the start of the care.data extraction of patient data to begin before the results of the Health and Social Care Information Centre cyber security review become available in October 2014.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194516","194516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46101","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the level of black, Asian and minority ethnic patients accessing mental health services through a referral from the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194513","194513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46102","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides to local health trusts and clinical commissioning groups to enable them to promote cancer awareness education.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194538","194538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46103","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration he has given to making compulsory the recording of the ethnicity of a patient when constraint and control measures are used within the NHS.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194514","194514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46104","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration he has given to improving the monitoring of black, Asian and minority ethnic patients accessing mental health services through a referral from the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194512","194512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46105","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2014, Official Report, column 582W, on medical records: databases, if he will provide more information on the range of uses beyond direct care to which data collected under care.data will be put; who will be responsible for deciding what use of the data is acceptable and by whom; and what auditing procedures will be in place to monitor such use.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194509","194509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46106","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the use of community treatment orders in relation to black, Asian and minority ethnic patients.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194515","194515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46107","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment was made of the compliance of the Health and Social Care Act 2012 with human rights legislation.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194536","194536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46108","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether evidence held by his Department about the disposal of foetal remains without the consent of the parents will be referred to the police under the Human Tissue Act 2004.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194504","194504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46109","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people had TB in the UK  in each of the last three years; and what reports he has received of a connection between TB and cats.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194464","194464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46110","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 125W, on medical records: databases, whether private companies will be permitted to tender for involvement in extracting patient information as part of care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194508","194508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46111","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice he gave to (a) primary care trusts and (b) clinical commissioning groups about adherence to NICE guidelines in commissioning services.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194451","194451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46112","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many independent funding requests and better care better value decisions were submitted to English primary care trusts in 2012-13 and to clinical commissioning groups in 2013-14; and what proportion of each of these were (a) approved and (b) appealed by the patient in each year.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194452","194452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46113","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of reports that carrots can reduce cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194456","194456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46114","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many keyhole surgery operations for heart surgery there were in each of the last three years in each (a) region and (b) constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194460","194460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46115","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) physicists, (b) radiotherapists and (c) chemotherapy nurses working in cancer care; and what his estimate is of the optimum level of each of those specialists in cancer care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194497","194497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46116","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to develop a population-wide measure of levels of loneliness for inclusion in the Adult Social Care Outcomes Framework.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194498","194498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46117","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include a population-wide measure of levels of loneliness in the Public Health Outcomes Framework.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194499","194499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46118","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent by the QUIT campaign in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194500","194500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46119","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 18 March 2014, Official Report, column 563W, on abortion and of 20 March 2014, Official Report, column 725W, on congenital abnormalities, for what reason the information requested cannot be provided.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194473","194473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46120","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been referred to the NHS for cosmetic surgery  where an operation has not been completed by a private provider due to that provider going out of business in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194462","194462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46121","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current average waiting time is for talking therapies for children with mental health problems, by local health area.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194391","194391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46122","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research he has (a) commissioned and (b) evaluated on the potential connection between diabetes and dementia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194454","194454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46123","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he issues on ensuring that cancer drugs are not withheld from elderly terminally ill patients aged over 65 years old.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194457","194457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46124","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that radiotherapy should be routinely made available as a treatment to reduce female breast cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194455","194455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46125","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which health establishments are now covered by his Department's investigation into historical abuse by Jimmy Savile; when he plans that the review findings will be published; and what the timetable is for the investigation.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194389","194389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46126","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when Bruton's tyrosine kinase inhibitor will be available on the NHS for the treatment of lymphoma blood cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194453","194453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46127","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children have been treated in adult mental health wards in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194390","194390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46128","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what monitoring his Department undertakes of the implementation of guidance from the National Institute for Health and Clinical Excellence and his Department on patients in treatment for opioid dependence receiving comprehensive assessment when entering treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194480","194480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46129","2014-04-03","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pregnant women are held in immigration detention.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194441","194441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46130","2014-04-03","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women detained at Yarl's Wood Detention Centre have been held for (a) four years or more, (b) three years or more and (c) two years or more.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194442","194442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46131","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the efficiency and consistency with which the Permitted Paid Engagements scheme has been applied to musicians, composers and artists visting the UK.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194465","194465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46132","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2014, Official Report, column 821W, on immigration controls, what procedures are in place to ensure that immigration officers ensure the removal of any face coverings before authorising entry to the UK; how many incidents have been recorded where the correct procedures relating to the removal of face coverings have not been followed by immigration officers in each of the last three years; and what disciplinary action has been taken in such incidents in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194471","194471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46133","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many gun dogs have been stolen in each of the last three years in each region in England.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194458","194458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46134","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many men were victims of sexual violence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194459","194459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46135","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to allow the IPCC to consider complaints regarding police conduct from third parties.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194565","194565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46136","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of (a) the cost to set up and (b) annual running costs of full border control with Scotland.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194540","194540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46137","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides to the police on managing public protests; and what discussions she has had with chief constables and the IPCC on the management of such protests.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194567","194567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46138","2014-04-03","Home Office","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to regulate workers posted to the UK by companies.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194553","194553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46139","2014-04-02","Department for International Development","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to A UK Strategy for Agricultural Technologies, how much of the £10 million provided by her Department to support the transfer of technology and new products to developing countries has been spent; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194479","194479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46140","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women were refused bail and remanded in custody where the alleged offence related to an incident involving domestic violence in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194414","194414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46141","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons have recycling units run by (a) prisoners and (b) outside contractors.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194413","194413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46142","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners who are in open prisons are serving (a) a life sentence and (b) an indeterminate sentence for public protection.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194415","194415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46143","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what offences were committed by prisoners serving their sentences in open prisons.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194416","194416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46144","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases were dealt with in magistrates' courts in 2013 (a) in total and (b) for non-payment of a television licence.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194495","194495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46145","2014-04-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what funds his Department has spent on preparing HM Prison the Verne for re-role as an immigration detention centre to date.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194448","194448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46146","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been subject to (a) restorative justice and (b) non-committal to prison in each of the last three years; and for what range of offence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194461","194461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46147","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 95W, on non-molestation orders, what the figure for previous convictions or cautions is for (a) male and (b) female offenders.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194472","194472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46148","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of a smoking ban in prisons on the number of incidents of violence relating to cigarettes.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194411","194411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46149","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners being held in prisons in England and Wales are serving sentences passed in jurisdictions outside England and Wales.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194412","194412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46150","2014-04-03","Department for Transport","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what Directly Operated Railways' total staffing budget was in each of the years since 2010-11; and what its planned staffing budget is for 2014-15 and 2015-16.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194502","194502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46151","2014-04-03","Department for Transport","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff were employed by Directly Operated Railways in March (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194501","194501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46152","2014-04-03","Department for Transport","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who is responsible for enforcing standards in the hygiene of toilets on trains; and who is accountable for any failings in this area.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194496","194496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46153","2014-04-03","Department for Transport","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what subsidiary companies of Directly Operated Railways have been created in connection with the direct awards programme.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194503","194503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46154","2014-04-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which companies have entered into contracts to deliver community work placements in each region and country of the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194506","194506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46155","2014-04-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funding the European Social Fund will contribute to community work placement contracts in England for 2014-15.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194507","194507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46156","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many posts in his Department will be relocated to the South West in the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194568","194568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46157","2014-04-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2013, Official Report, column 419W, on employment and support allowance, whether his Department expects to complete the incapacity benefit reassessment process in April 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194546","194546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46158","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his letter of 20 March 2014, what the evidential basis is for his statement that allowing people receiving employment and support allowance to do some work within a specified 52 week period is the best way of encouraging a move towards work of 16 hours or more a week.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194563","194563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46171","2014-04-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he next expects to meet the Green Investment Bank to discuss whether its investment strategy is in line with the Waste Hierarchy.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903459","903459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46246","2014-04-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to help households improve their energy efficiency.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903482","903482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45785","2014-04-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the economic benefits to the UK of international students.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194285","194285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45786","2014-04-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the effect on higher education providers of charging fees to international students for use of the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194286","194286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45787","2014-04-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the findings of the Oxford Economics report commissioned by the University of Sheffield entitled the Economic Costs and Benefits of International Students, January 2013.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194284","194284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45788","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what provision exists under his Department's Traineeships Programme for individuals with special needs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194303","194303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45789","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what incentives his Department provides to companies who pioneer initiatives designed to tackle unemployment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194316","194316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45790","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many full-time equivalent staff work in his Department's Major Infrastructure Tracking Unit.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194287","194287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45791","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the revenue likely to accrue to the Exchequer from the sale of EU Emissions Trading Scheme allowances in each year to 2021.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194278","194278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45792","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to set a time limit within which property management companies will have to produce their service charge accounts.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194294","194294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45793","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many social housing tenants who were liable to pay the under-occupancy penalty have moved house since 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194296","194296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45794","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Rhondda of 27 March 2014, Official Report, column 347W, on housing benefit: social rented sector, if he will commission a one year evaluation of the effects of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194295","194295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45795","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons his Department has not published data on the effects of the under-occupancy penalty on the number of social housing tenants who have moved home or fallen into rent arrears.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194297","194297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45796","2014-04-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the projected spending is by her Department in 2015-16 by functional flows to (a) museums and galleries, (b) communications, (c) libraries, (d) tourism, (e) the Royal Parks, (f) equalities, (g) BBC Public Sector broadcasting, (h) S4C, (i) arts, (j) sports, (k) gambling and National Lottery, (l) architecture and the historic environment and (m) the creative industries, disaggregating (i) grant-in-aid and Lottery and (ii) capital and current expenditure.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194280","194280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45797","2014-04-02","HM Treasury","2014-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funds were disbursed through the Enterprise Investment Scheme to film projects in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194281","194281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45798","2014-04-02","Department for Education","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of secondary school children in England learning to play a musical instrument in school (a) paid a charge and (b) received their tuition free of charge in school years (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12, (iv) 2012-13 and (v) 2013-14.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194313","194313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45799","2014-04-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much Arts Council Enlgand spent on consultants in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194314","194314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45800","2014-04-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many applications his Department has received for (a) one-year, (b) three-year and (c) 15-year contracts relating to (i) gas and (ii) coal under the capacity market.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194282","194282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45801","2014-04-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he will reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Sunderland Central dated 27 February 2014 relating to the Eggborough power station.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194302","194302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45802","2014-04-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the socio-economic development performance of NMP in West Cumbria.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194320","194320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45803","2014-04-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the socio-economic development performance of Magnox in North Ayrshire.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194319","194319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45804","2014-04-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department has plans to extend the life of generating capacity currently scheduled to be closed in the event that delays in new investment arise as a result of uncertainty about the outcome of the competition investigation by the Competition and Markets Authority.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194312","194312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45805","2014-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the amount of British-grown wheat used in bio-fuel production.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194276","194276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45806","2014-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) the welfare of horses is considered a priority in live exports and (b) laws relating to the welfare of horses are being enforced.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194277","194277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45807","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request NHS England to inform  him when the hon. Member for Hartlepool can expect to receive a reply to his letter dated 17 December 2013, on the subject of availability and funding of cosmetic surgery for people born with cleft lip and palate.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194279","194279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45808","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on medical research by the (a) National Institute for Health Research and (b) Medical Research Council, broken down by category in each case in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for George Freeman","George Freeman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194301","194301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45809","2014-04-09","Department of Health","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding, information and training available for people with epilepsy and their families.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194300","194300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45810","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2014, Official Report, column 949W, on abortion, how many Ground E terminations were permitted due to a sex-linked inherited condition in the foetus in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194306","194306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45811","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 March 2014, Official Report, column 372W, on driving: licensing, how many drivers who received driving convictions undertook speed awareness courses in each year since 2010, in each force area.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194304","194304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45812","2014-04-02","Home Office","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 March 2014, Official Report, column 372W, on driving: licensing, how many drivers within the two-year probationary period who received driving convictions undertook speed awareness courses in each year since 2010 (a) in total and (b) by police force area.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194305","194305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45813","2014-04-02","Department for International Development","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will itemise all sectoral budget support given to the Ethiopian government in the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194298","194298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45814","2014-04-01","Department for International Development","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she intends to respond to the email of 17 October 2013 sent by the hon. Member for Denton and Reddish concerning her Department's plan for spending and distributing the core funds of £375 million that were pledged in June 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194311","194311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45815","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on which occasions prisons (a) reached and (b) exceeded their (i) occupational capacity and (ii) in-use certified normal accommodation in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194307","194307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45816","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much capital investment there was in each secure estate establishment closed since May 2010 in the 12 months prior to the public announcement of the closure of that establishment; and what items were purchased at a cost in excess of £100,000 at each such establishment.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194308","194308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45817","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) operational capacities and (b) certified normal accommodations were of each privately run prison with which a contract for additional places has been signed since January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194309","194309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45818","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many spaces were agreed under each contract with a private provider for additional spaces in existing prisons signed since May 2010; how long each contract was for; and what the value was of the contract (a) in total and (b) per space agreed.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194310","194310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45819","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the required prison officers in post figures are as part of the benchmarking process for each prison; and what the corresponding current full-time equivalent prison officer figures are.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194299","194299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45820","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information (a) his Department and (b) HM Tribunals Service hold on the socio-economic status of people (i) prosecuted and convicted for television licence evasion and (ii) imprisoned for non-payment of a fine for television licence evasion.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194290","194290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45821","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information (a) his Department and (b) HM Tribunals Service hold on the age of people (i) prosecuted and convicted for television licence evasion and (ii) imprisoned for non-payment of a fine for television licence evasion.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194291","194291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45822","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information (a) his Department and (b) HM Tribunals Service hold on the gender of people (i) prosecuted and convicted for television licence evasion and (ii) imprisoned for non-payment of a fine for television licence evasion.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194289","194289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45823","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2014, Official Report, column 255W, on Personal Independence Payment, what his Department's original guideline assumptions were of the percentage of personal independence payment new claim referrals that would involve a consultation assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194283","194283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45824","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2014, Official Report, column 318W, on Personal Independence Payment, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of personal independence payment claim processing times.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194293","194293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45825","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2014, Official Report, column 318W, on Personal Independence Payment, what discussions he has had with providers about personal independence payment claim processing times.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194292","194292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45826","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 March 2014, Official Report, columns 232-3W, on social security benefits: young people, if he will publish information relevant to the original question in whatever format that is available.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194288","194288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45827","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people returning to Jobcentre Plus after two years on the Work Programme are aged under 25 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194315","194315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45828","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate has been made of how much his Department is likely to save annually as a result of the removal of warm phones from Jobcentre Plus offices.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194317","194317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45829","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department records the number of referrals made to local third-sector advice providers (a) to use the telephone, (b) for help filling in forms and (c) providing other support.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194318","194318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45509","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students started at Russell Group universities to study STEM subjects from (a) City of Chester constituency and (b) Cheshire West and Chester council area in (i) 2009 and (ii) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194071","194071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45510","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many of the Office of Fair Trading's incomplete (a) market studies, (b) competition enforcement cases and (c) consumer enforcement cases will be continued by which new enforcers after 1 April 2014.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194145","194145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45511","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many of the Competition Commission's incomplete (a) market investigations, (b) merger inquiries, (c) regulatory references and (d) undertakings or order reviews will be continued by which new enforcers after 1 April 2014.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194146","194146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45512","2014-04-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will place in the Library a copy of the current marketing and advertising strategy document of the National Careers Service.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194169","194169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45513","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which trades unions are involved with health and safety committees in his Department.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194158","194158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45514","2014-04-01","Cabinet Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the Government has made of the likely change in the number of people in the UK who will be aged 90 years and over between 2012 and 2023.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194120","194120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45515","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effects of the removal of air passenger duty (APD) on the number of passengers travelling between Belfast and Newark International; and if he will take that assessment into account when considering changes to levels of APD for other flights from and within the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194123","194123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45516","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the HM Revenue and Customs computable general equilibrium model used to assess the effect on GDP of illustrative policies to meet targets in the fourth carbon budget includes (a) avoided costs of flooding and damage caused by flooding as a result of climate change, (b) a carbon price, (c) avoided costs of air pollution and (d) macroeconomic effects of an increased take up of domestic and commercial energy efficiency.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194139","194139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45517","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made made of the accuracy of the ONS index of rental prices; and what recent assessment he has of the changes in the cost of private renting in Slough since 2010.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194133","194133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45518","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has discussed with Ofcom the future of licences held by Sunrise; and if she will take steps to urge Ofcom to retender the Slough licence.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194159","194159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45519","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with the United States Department of Defense (USDoD) in respect of the installation by BT of a special communications system to link RAF Croughton in Northamptonshire with the USDoD headquarters in Washington DC and the US Africa headquarters for unmanned aircraft operations in Djibouti.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194144","194144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45520","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what non-lethal military support his Department has provided to Tunisia in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194080","194080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45521","2014-04-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support British service personnel are providing to the Afghan National Security Forces to ensure that the elections in Afghanistan are free and fair.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194094","194094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45522","2014-04-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support the UK is offering to the (a) EU and (b) OSCE election monitoring missions to Afghanistan.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194095","194095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45523","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 March 2014, Official Report, column 181W, on D-Day landings: anniversaries, on what date his Department received confirmation that each of the 70th anniversary D-Day commemoration events in the UK would take place.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194130","194130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45524","2014-04-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the armed forces will tender for the successor to the SA80 L86A2.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194154","194154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45525","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 March 2014, Official Report, column 181W, on D-Day landings: anniversaries, how many (a) veterans, (b) armed forces' widows, (c) armed forces' spouses and (d) carers his Department expects will be in attendance for each of the 70th anniversary D-Day commemoration events in the UK.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194131","194131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45526","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in how many joint NATO training exercises in which countries the UK plans to participate in the next six months.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194061","194061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45527","2014-04-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the 60 questions relating to the future Strategic Defence and Security Review to which the Permanent Under-Secretary of his Department referred during his oral evidence to the Defence Select Committee on 25 March 2014.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194118","194118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45528","2014-04-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to hold Armed Forces Day events in Northern Ireland in June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194119","194119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45529","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate the attendance of (a) veterans, (b) armed forces' widows, (c) armed forces' spouses and (d) carers to the 70th anniversary D-Day commemoration events at (i) Portsmouth on 5 June 2014, (ii) London on 22 June 2014, (iii) York on 20 July 2014 and (iv) London on 16 October 2014.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194124","194124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45530","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 March 2014, Official Report, column 181W, on D-Day Landings: anniversaries, with which service and veterans' charities his Department has been liaising for each of the 70th anniversary D-Day commemoration events in the UK.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194125","194125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45531","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what non-lethal military support his Department has provided to Libya in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194081","194081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45532","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what non-lethal military support his Department has provided to Algeria in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194082","194082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45533","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what non-lethal military support his Department has provided to Egypt in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194083","194083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45534","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students sat A-levels in (a) mathematics, (b) further mathematics, (c) physics, (d) chemistry and (e) biology in (i) City of Chester constituency and (ii) Cheshire West and Chester council area in (A) 2009 and (B) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194068","194068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45535","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students obtained eight GCSE B grades or above in (a) City of Chester constituency and (b) Cheshire West and Chester council area in (i) 2009 and (ii) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194070","194070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45536","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many serious case reviews have been (a) commissioned and (b) published since June 2010.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194098","194098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45537","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what interaction the National Panel on Serious Case Reviews has had with the Local Safeguarding Children's Board Network.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194099","194099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45538","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of all primary school age children in England were learning a musical instrument in (a) academies, (b) community schools, (c) free schools, (d) primary schools and (e) other schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194088","194088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45539","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of all secondary school age children in England were learning a musical instrument in (a) academies, (b) community schools, (c) free schools, (d) primary schools and (e) other schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194089","194089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45540","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the three most popular instruments are for primary school children in England who are learning an instrument in school.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194090","194090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45541","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the three most popular instruments are for secondary school children in England who are learning an instrument in school.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194091","194091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45542","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of primary school children in England learning an instrument in school (a) paid a charge and (b) received their tuition free of charge in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194092","194092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45543","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) 14, (b) 15, (c) 16, (d) 17 and (e) 18 year olds enrolled at each university technical college in 2013-14.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194108","194108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45544","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what dates the National Panel on Serious Case Reviews has met; and if he will publish the minutes of that Panel's meetings.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194096","194096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45545","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions (a) he and (b) other Ministers in his Department have had with members of the National Panel on Serious Case Reviews.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194097","194097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45546","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, to whom the National Panel on Serious Case Reviews is accountable; and what the terms of reference of that Panel are.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194100","194100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45547","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of long-term trends in the number of hours of literacy teaching which primary school children receive and how this affects reading and writing attainment.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194155","194155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45548","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what requirements there are for academies and free schools to publish their curriculum for prospective parents; and what form that must take.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194157","194157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45549","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of homes classified as solid wall construction and built before 1920 that possess fillable cavities.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194138","194138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45550","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate he has made of the number of treatable cavity wall homes in areas prone to flooding treated with inappropriate filling agents.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194136","194136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45551","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the average treatment cost to insulate (a) narrow cavity hard-to-treat walls, (b) uneven cavities in walls constructed of natural stone, (c) homes with defective or missing damp proof courses, (d) solid wall properties treatable with internal cladding and (e) solid wall properties treatable with external cladding.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194137","194137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45552","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimates he has made of the effect of his plans to establish a capacity market on (a) domestic and (b) industrial energy bills between (i) 2015 to 2020 and (ii) 2021 to 2025.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194140","194140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45553","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what bilateral funding arrangements his Department has with (a) governmental and (b) non-governmental projects and bodies in Argentina.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194079","194079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45554","2014-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether the estimated cost of the direct damage caused by recent flooding in Somerset meets the eligibility criteria for the European Union Solidarity Fund; and what discussions his Department has had with EU officials on an application to that fund.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194106","194106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45555","2014-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Hunting Act 2004.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194121","194121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45556","2014-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many civil servants in his Department spent some or all of their time working on the Hunting Act 2004 in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014 to date; and what the grade is of each such staff member.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194164","194164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45557","2014-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has allocated staff resources or established a dedicated unit in his Department to deal with proposed amendments to the Hunting Act 2004.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194165","194165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45558","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will establish shale gas extraction exclusion zones in sensitive areas for wildlife and water resources.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194143","194143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45559","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to meet representatives of Cuadrilla and other members of the shale gas industry.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194142","194142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45560","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he next plans to meet representatives of organisations that have made representations on the environmental effects of the shale gas industry.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194141","194141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45561","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with EU counterparts about an EU response to the Greek government's proposed amendment to Article 19 of that country's draft immigration code.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194074","194074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45562","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Greek government about its amendment to Article 19 of that country's draft immigration code which would allow for the arrest, prosecution and deportation of migrants who report law enforcement abuse.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194075","194075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45563","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to respond to the Greek government's decision to remove the humanitarian clause from that country's immigration code.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194076","194076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45565","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what outcomes he expects to be achieved over the next 12 months as a result of steps taken to reduce the level of still birth and infant mortality rates.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194122","194122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45566","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedure NHS England uses to benchmark the reduction of inappropriate face-to-face contact in line with Commissioning for Quality and Innovation guidance.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194058","194058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45567","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if NHS England will publish updates on (a) the three million lives programme and (b) NHS adoption of telehealth and telecare models of service provision.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194059","194059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45568","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts have strategies to exploit the commercial advantage of intellectual property developed at the trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194060","194060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45569","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the cancellation of the commissioning for quality and innovation pre-qualification criteria on the uptake of the high impact innovations identified through innovation, health and wealth.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194062","194062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45570","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital procedures have been carried out using intra-operative fluid management technologies in each NHS trust in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194063","194063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45571","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts have developed an action plan for the delivery of mobility services for children based on the best performing providers identified by innovation, health and wealth.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194064","194064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45572","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time was for children requiring wheelchairs in each NHS trust in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194065","194065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45573","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts have a strategy to ensure that the carer of every person who is admitted to hospital with a diagnosis of dementia is provided with advice and support.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194066","194066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45574","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff are employed at Public Health England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194107","194107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45575","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure consistency of training and skills for practitioners of tattooing and piercing.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194078","194078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45576","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) fixed costs and (b) annual running costs of Public Health England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194105","194105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45577","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were eligible for and participated in the bowel cancer screening programme in (a) England, (b) each of the five regional programme hubs and (c) each of the 59 regional screening centres in (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12, and (iv) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194093","194093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45578","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what requirements there are on hospital trusts to stock medication for Parkinson's disease in their emergency medications cupboards.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194084","194084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45579","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of deaths attributable to long-term exposure to particularate air pollution in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194102","194102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45580","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, under what circumstances a carer may administer a person's medication in hospital.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194085","194085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45581","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that local authorities in England pursue a continuous improvement in the proportion of the eligible population offered and taking up NHS health checks.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194103","194103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45582","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that all NHS trusts are providing the full range of mental health interventions recommended by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194104","194104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45583","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to regulate temporary tattooing and piercing establishments such as tattoo fairs and pop-up shops; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194086","194086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45584","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that approved training and qualifications for practice of tattoos and piercings are carried out by qualified practitioners.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194077","194077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45585","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of ambulance service category A 8-minute responses were initially met by (a) a team and vehicle capable of providing patient transport, (b) first or co-responders and (c) paramedics using a motorbike or car in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194073","194073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45586","2014-04-01","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has spent on legal fees in immigration cases when she has been (a) the defendant and (b) the appellant, in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194153","194153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45587","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fines have been levied under The Immigration (Employment of Adults Subject to Immigration Conrol) (Maximum Penalty) Order 2008 of a value of (a) up to £1000, (b) between £1000 and £2000, (c) between £2000 and £5000 and (d) between £5000 and £10000 to date.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194134","194134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45588","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fines levied under the Immigration (Employment of Adults Subject to Immigration Conrol) (Maximum Penalty) Order 2008 of a value of (a) up to £1000, (b) between £1000 and £2000, (c) between £2000 and £5000 and (d) between £5000 and £10000 remained unpaid.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194135","194135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45589","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many deportations of foreign national offenders there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194087","194087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45590","2014-04-01","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2014, Official Report, column 238W, on driving: licensing, what proportion of new drivers obtaining driving convictions were offered speed awareness courses in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194127","194127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45591","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the current requirements for seizing property or cash under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 to bring those requirements into line with the new powers of HM Revenue and Customs to seize money from an individual's bank account without a warrant.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194067","194067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45592","2014-04-01","Department for International Development","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking in her role as co-chair of the Mexico High Level Meeting of the Global Partnership for Effective Development to ensure that future development co-operation respects the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Developments Busan Principles (a) generally and (b) as they apply to aid allocated to private sector organisations.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194129","194129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45593","2014-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent purchasing additional prison places from existing privately run prisons in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194110","194110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45594","2014-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, from which companies additional spaces have been purchased in which prisons in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194109","194109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45595","2014-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total amount of fines levied on but uncollected from people found guilty of non-payment of (a) a television licence, (b) vehicle excise duty and (c) council tax was on 1 March 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194111","194111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45596","2014-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average fine was for people found guilty of non-payment of (a) a television licence, (b) vehicle excise duty and (c) council tax in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194112","194112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45597","2014-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women were serving custodial sentences for non-payment of (i) a television licence, (ii) vehicle excise duty and (iii) council tax on 1 March 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194101","194101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45598","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2013, Official Report, columns 652-3W, on special educational needs, whether his Department has any plans in future to commence publishing figures on the proportion of hearings where (a) local authorities and (b) parents were legally represented.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194156","194156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45599","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of recent changes to the funding of Greater Manchester Police on crime rates in that region.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194132","194132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45600","2014-04-01","Scotland Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on maximising tourism opportunities in Scotland.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194116","194116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45601","2014-04-01","Scotland Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on NHS Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194117","194117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45602","2014-04-01","Scotland Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the number of homeless (a) single people and (b) families in Scotland.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194115","194115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45603","2014-04-01","Scotland Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs in Scotland that depend on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194114","194114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45604","2014-04-01","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) net franchise payment, (b) revenue support sum and (c) net subsidy are for the 22 month direct award of the northern franchise to Northern Rail Ltd.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194113","194113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45605","2014-04-01","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Transport for London on the South East Flexible Ticketing scheme.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194128","194128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45606","2014-03-31","Wales Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many students obtained eight GCSE B grades or above in (a) Flintshire council area and (b) Wrexham council area in (i) 2009 and (ii) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194072","194072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45607","2014-03-31","Wales Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many students sat A-levels in (a) mathematics, (b) further mathematics, (c) physics, (d) chemistry and (e) biology in (i) Flintshire Council area and (ii) Wrexham council area in (A) 2009 and (B) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194069","194069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45608","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many outstanding cases of social fund loan repayments his Department is curretnly pursuing; in what year each such loan was issued; what estimate he has made of the total value of such outstanding repayments; and how much his Department is paying a debt management service to pursue such repayments.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194152","194152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45609","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many repeat employment and support allowance claimants have been placed in the work-related activity group with the prognosis that engagement in work is unlikely in the longer term since October 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194166","194166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45610","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new employment and support allowance claimants have been placed in the work-related activity group with the prognosis that engagement in work is unlikely in the longer term since October 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194167","194167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45611","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance was given to Jobcentre Plus offices on supporting people internally rather than externally following the recent removal of warm phones.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194151","194151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45612","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department collects information from Jobcentre Plus offices on the number of people referred to local advice providers to use telephones.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194147","194147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45613","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Ministerial Statement of 27 March 2014, Official Report, columns 56-8WS, on Atos, how much Atos has paid to his Department in order to exit its contract early; and whether he plans for the new contract provide for payments calculated on the number of assessments completed.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194148","194148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45614","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department makes available to people who are unable to work whilst receiving treatment for cancer and what assets which cannot quickly be converted to enough money to cover consequential costs.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194168","194168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45615","2014-03-31","Attorney General","2014-03-27","To ask the Attorney General, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by the Law Officers' Departments' were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194213","194213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45616","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what health and safety committees operate in his Department.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194172","194172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45617","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of undergraduate university courses charged at the maximum tuition fee allowed.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194234","194234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45618","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the timetable is for the proposed selling of the pre-2012 student loan book.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194235","194235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45619","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194212","194212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45620","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the average total tuition fees incurred by a UK citizen studying full-time for an undergraduate degree at a university in England or Wales.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194236","194236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45621","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of student loans issued under (a) the pre-2012 funding system and (b) the new system that will be fully or partially written off.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194237","194237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45622","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will place in the Library an updated version of the ready reckoner on student loans and debt repayment reflecting his most recent estimate on future earnings, fees and RAB charges.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194238","194238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45623","2014-04-01","Cabinet Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many disabled people were in paid work in Brigg and Goole constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194258","194258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45624","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will request that the Office for National Statistics publishes the evidential basis for the comment by the Minister for Housing of 3 March 2014, Official Report, column 606, on changes in rents in London.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194170","194170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45625","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194214","194214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45626","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the analysis underlying the costings of the policy of reducing the withdrawal tax rate for income from pensions from 55 per cent to the marginal rate of income tax.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194247","194247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45627","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish his Department's analysis of the potential risk to (a) the economy and (b) the prospects for long-term investment arising from the changes to the taxation regime for pensions.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194248","194248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45628","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the analysis underlying the decision to allocate £20 million to the provision of consumer advice for pensions.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194249","194249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45629","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the guidance given to those approaching retirement will be a specific recommendation of a product to secure the best income in retirement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194272","194272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45630","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the analysis underlying the feasibility of delivering face-to-face financial guidance to an additional 500,000 people from April 2015.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194250","194250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45631","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on (a) prices and (b) availability of annuities.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194273","194273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45632","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect of the changes on the distribution of pensions tax relief by income decile.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194251","194251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45633","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect of the changes on the overall level of tax paid by an individual in each income decile.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194252","194252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45634","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on the price of an annuity for those with pension pots worth (a) £10,000, (b) £20,000, (c) £30,000, (d) £40,000, (e) £50,000 and (f) £100,000.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194274","194274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45635","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assumption he has made about the number of (a) basic, (b) higher and (c) additional rate tax payers who will cease to purchase an annuity as a result of the changes announced in Budget 2014.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194253","194253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45636","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on the availability of an annuity for those with pension pots worth (a) £10,000, (b) £20,000, (c) £30,000, (d) £40,000, (e) £50,000 and (f) £100,000.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194275","194275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45637","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect on revenue of the planned changes to the pensions system in each year from 2016 to 2025.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194254","194254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45638","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assumptions he has made about the number of people who will continue to take out an annuity.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194255","194255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45639","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194230","194230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45640","2014-03-31","Church Commissioners","2014-03-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church Commissioners are considering changing the compulsory retirement age for clergy.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194239","194239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45641","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194215","194215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45642","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by her Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194216","194216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45643","2014-04-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his policy to follow the model used for the restriction of the resale of football match tickets for other live events.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194233","194233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45644","2014-04-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what action his Department is taking to prevent the resale of event tickets on the internet at a significant increase to their original face value.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194271","194271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45645","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average career length is of a soldier in each regiment or unit who enlisted (a) aged under 18 and (b) aged 18 or above.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194161","194161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45646","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) junior entry and (b) standard entry soldiers enlisted in the Army in 2012-13; and how many such people left before completing Phase 2 training.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194162","194162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45647","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the tritium gas emissions have been from RNAD Coulport in each of the last four years; and what estimate he has made of emissions in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194177","194177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45648","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of each type of radioactive emission will change at (a) RNAD Coulport and (b) HMNB Clyde in each of the next six years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194178","194178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45649","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's agreement in principle for three offshore patrol vessels with BAE Systems.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194242","194242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45650","2014-04-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) men and (b) women there were in the reserve forces in Brigg and Goole constituency in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194259","194259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45651","2014-04-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he or officials of his Department will discuss the issues raised by Lieutenant General Christopher Bogdan of the US Air Force in his testimony on the F-35 programme to the US House Armed Services Tactical Air and Land Forces sub-committee with their US counterparts.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194198","194198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45652","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets and how many service personnel were involved in NATO exercise Joint Warrior from (a) the UK, (b) NATO members and (c) non-NATO members in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194176","194176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45653","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194217","194217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45654","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel are taking part in the Seedcorn initiative; what the location is of each such person; and with what equipment such personnel are training.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194241","194241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45655","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194218","194218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45656","2014-04-01","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber were adopted in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194260","194260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45657","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what systems his Department has in place to monitor the implementation of the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194240","194240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45658","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2014, Official Report, columns 787-8W, on pupil exclusions: autism, how his Department deals with allegations that schools are disregarding the statutory guidance on exclusion in respect of students with autistic disorders.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194185","194185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45659","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he plans to allow Ofsted to inspect bodies which run chains of academy schools.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194163","194163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45660","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what consultation he plans on regulations relating to houses in multiple occupation as part of the forthcoming consultation on regulations relating to minimum standards of energy efficiency for the private rented sector.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194160","194160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45661","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what modelling he has undertaken of the viability of the offtaker of last resort system for independent renewable energy generators under the revised arrangements for auctions for contracts for difference for established technologies.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194245","194245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45662","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what account he took of the estimates of numbers of homes with (a) partial fill cavity walls, (b) uneven cavities in natural stone walls, (c) defective or missing damp proof courses and (d) party wall cavities in the 2012 inbuilt report on hard to treat homes in the revised plans for treatment targets under the ECO scheme.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194246","194246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45663","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194219","194219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45664","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194220","194220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45665","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances of (a) faecal contamination, (b) cellulitis, (c) dermatitis, (d) ascites, (e) salpingitiss, (f) egg impaction, (g) peritonis, (h) pericarditis, (i) pericarditis, (j) foot infections or problems, (k) arthritis and joint problems, (l) septicaemia and fever, (m) tumours, (n) air sacculitis, (o) Marek's disease, (p) white muscular disease and (q) Aspergillosis have been identified at post mortem inspection of poultry and prevented from entering the food chain 1 April 2012.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194203","194203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45666","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances of (a) pneumonia, (b) septic pneumonia, (c) Pericarditis, (d) Septic Pericarditis, (e) Peritonitis, (f) septic peritonitis, (g) Oedema, (h) Emaciation, (i) Bruising or trauma, (j) Abscesses in offal, (k) Abscesses in carcases, (l) Pyaemia, (m) animals with septicaemia, (n) Animals with tumours, (o) Hydronephrosis, (p) Nephritis and septic nephritis, (q) Lymphadenitis, (r) Tuberculosis, (s) Erysipelas in pigs, (t) Steatosis, (u) Actinobacillous and (v) Actinomycosus in red meat animals have been identified at official post mortem inspection and prevented from entering the food chain by officials working for an on behalf of the FSA since 1 April 2012.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194202","194202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45667","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the liver fluke fasciola hepatica identified at official post mortem inspection has been prevented from entering the food chain by officials working for and on behalf of the Food Standards Agency performing thorough meat inspection since 1 April 2012.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194266","194266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45668","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times lesions on livers caused by the intermediate stage of the parasitic roundworm ascaris suum identified in pigs at official post mortem inspection have been prevented from entering the food chain by officials working for or on behalf of the Food Standards Agency since 1 April 2012.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194265","194265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45669","2014-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to his Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 33W, on flood control, what the reasons are for the disparity between the figures given in that Answer and those contained in the Red Book Table 2.1 Line 34 for 2014-15 and 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194187","194187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45670","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances of parasitic lung worms have been identified at official post mortem inspection and prevented from entering the food chain by officials working for and on behalf of the Food Standards Agency since 1 April 2012.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194194","194194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45671","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances of the cystic stage (C Bovis) of the human tapeworm Taenia Saginata have been identified at official post mortem inspection and prevented from entering the food chain by officials working for and on behalf of the Food Standards Agency since 1 April 2012.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194195","194195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45672","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances of (a) Cysticercus Tenuicollis (adult tapeworm - Taenia Hydatigena), (b) Cysticercus Ovis (adult tapeworm - Taenia Ovis), (c) Hydatid Cysts (adult tapeworm - Echinococcus Granulosus), (d) Generalised (cysts identified in multiple parts of the animal including the musculature the consumer would define as meat) and (e) Cysticercus Ovis have been identified at official post-mortem inspections and prevented from entering the food chain by officials working for and on behalf of the Food Standards Agency since 1 April 2012.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194196","194196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45673","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to reply to the letter to him dated 20 February 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms T Morris.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194175","194175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45674","2014-04-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the UK is taking to promote peaceful dialogue in Venezuela between the government and of that country and political opponents.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194197","194197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45675","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194221","194221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45676","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that sex-selective abortion does not place in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Julian Brazier","Mr Julian Brazier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194256","194256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45677","2014-04-02","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to amend HAS4 abortion referral forms to include a declaration on the part of registered medical practitioners that they are satisfied that the women is not seeking an abortion the grounds of foetal sex.","Biography information for Sir Julian Brazier","Mr Julian Brazier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194257","194257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45678","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194223","194223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45679","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure there is a quick and easy way for a patient with Parkinson's disease to lodge a complaint against a hospital trust should they not receive their medicine on time during their stay.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194193","194193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45680","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department spent on (a) genito-urinary medicine and (b) sexual health in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194209","194209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45681","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what pay rise NHS employees on incremental schemes will receive if they are already at the top of their banding levels.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194188","194188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45682","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) sexual health and (b) gum clinics there were in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194210","194210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45683","2014-04-03","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many members of staff were employed in (a) sexual health and (b) gum clinics in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194211","194211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45684","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in providing funding for counselling and psychotherapy for pupils in schools.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194173","194173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45685","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Food Standards Agency has carried out any research on the European Commission's published proposals to change EU Regulation 882/2004 governing official controls in the food and agriculture industries.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194261","194261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45686","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what initiatives are in place to train health professionals on the importance of providing people with Parkinson's disease medication on time while they are in hospital.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194192","194192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45687","2014-04-01","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to work with police forces across the country to protect children from online sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194269","194269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45688","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which local authorities are currently in discussions with her Department on the vulnerable persons relocation scheme for Syrian nationals.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194171","194171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45689","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2014, Official Report, column 685W, on human trafficking, whether she plans for the review of the National Referral Mechanism to be completed before committee stage of the Modern Slavery Bill.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194183","194183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45690","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by her Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194224","194224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45691","2014-03-31","Department for International Development","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by her Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194225","194225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45692","2014-04-01","Department for International Development","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking as co-chair of the Mexico High Level Meeting of the Global Partnership for Effective Development co-operation to ensure that future aid to the private sector respects the Busan principles.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194268","194268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45693","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of the people imprisoned in 2012 for non-payment of fines relating to television licence evasion had other unpaid fines for other offences; and how many outstanding fines on average such people had.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194244","194244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45694","2014-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable is for the contracting-out of the Probation Service during 2014.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194199","194199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45695","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194226","194226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45696","2014-03-31","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by her Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194227","194227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45697","2014-03-31","Scotland Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194228","194228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45698","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194229","194229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45699","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assets he has designated for search and rescue under section 2.5 of Annex 12 of the Convention on International Civil Aviation; and where each such asset is located.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194243","194243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45700","2014-04-01","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce which stations will receive (a) access for all funding and (b) national station improvement programme funding between 2014 and 2019.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194262","194262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45701","2014-04-01","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date he expects all peak services provided by Southeastern to be formed of 12 car trains.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194263","194263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45702","2014-04-01","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent by his Department on platform lengthening on the Integrated Kent Franchise routes in each year since 2000, by station.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194264","194264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45703","2014-04-01","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate his Department has made of the cost per mile of building cycle lanes; and what steps he is taking to reduce this cost in rural areas.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194267","194267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45704","2014-04-01","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will update the business case for High Speed 2 to reflect the fact that there will be no link with High Speed 1.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194270","194270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45705","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to improve rail infrastructure between Sittingbourne and London stations.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194174","194174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45706","2014-03-31","Wales Office","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194231","194231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45707","2014-03-31","Women and Equalities","2014-03-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by the Government Equalities Office were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194222","194222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45708","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) 20 highest and (b) 20 lowest value contracts awarded by his Department were in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194232","194232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45709","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have moved off jobseeker's allowance to jobs on zero-hours contracts in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194205","194205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45710","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance is issued to Jobcentre Plus on recommending jobs on zero-hours contracts.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194206","194206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45711","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy that applicants for means-tested benefits aged 55 years and above will not be deemed for purposes of benefit eligibility assessment to have vested in the capital and potential income held within their defined contribution pension pots.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194190","194190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45712","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer 6 March 2014, Official Report, columns 971-2W, on Remploy, which businesses were sold; and whether profit from such sales has been passed back to HM Treasury.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194184","194184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45713","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion and number of job outcomes from the work programme were in zero-hours contracts roles in each month since the programme began.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194207","194207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45714","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion and number of jobs currently advertised through Jobcentre Plus are on zero-hour contracts.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194208","194208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45715","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research has been undertaken on the prospects of former Remploy factory workers who were made redundant in (a) 2007-08 and (b) phases 1 and 2 of the 2012-13 factory closures.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194186","194186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45716","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to provide that persons aged 55 years old and over enrolled in hybrid pension schemes will acquire the same rights to access pension pots accrued from additional voluntary contribution payments as holders of defined contribution pensions.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194181","194181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45717","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each parliamentary constituency are currently incurring the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194189","194189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45718","2014-04-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been referred to jobs on zero-hours contracts through Jobcentre Plus in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194204","194204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45719","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the total value of funds held by pension providers on behalf of individuals who contracted out of the state earnings-related pension; and what arrangements will need to be made to allow people aged 55 years old and over to access such funds.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194182","194182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45720","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether people aged 55 years old and over enrolled in hybrid pension schemes will acquire the same right to access pension pots conferred upon those in defined contribution schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194180","194180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45721","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people enrolled in hybrid workplace pension schemes.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194179","194179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45722","2014-04-01","HM Treasury","2014-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of extending the rights to exercise choice in the future investment of the proceeds of defined contribution pensions to all pension holders who have bought an annuity since 6 April 2013.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194191","194191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45723","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provisions are in place to enable a lone parent on out-of-work benefits and on a course taking up more than 16 hours per week, whose youngest child turns five years old, to complete the course notwithstanding the 16 hour rule.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194200","194200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45724","2014-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent guidance his Department has issued to Jobcentre Plus staff on how to advise clients on alternatives to warm phones for contacting Jobcentre Plus or applying for jobs by telephone.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194201","194201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45151","2014-03-31","Attorney General","2014-03-26","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of employees in the Law Officers' Departments of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193956","193956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45152","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of employees in his Department of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193955","193955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45153","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance he has given to local enterprise partnerships about the inclusion of higher education in their strategic economic plans.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193952","193952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45154","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will increase the maximum amount that students at alternative providers can borrow from the Student Loans Company to £9,000.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193953","193953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45155","2014-04-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage alternative providers of higher education to offer courses in STEM subjects.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193954","193954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45156","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that European Commission free trade agreement negotiations with (a) Thailand and (b) India safeguard access to affordable medicines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193854","193854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45157","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he intends to publish a response to the consultation on pub companies and tenants.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193855","193855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45158","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to assist the manufacturing sector and promote an export-led recovery in the economy.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193741","193741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45159","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many workplaces in (a) Harlow constituency and (b) Essex employed an apprentice in each of the last five year.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193751","193751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45160","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings officials in his Department have had with representatives of (a) students and (b) higher education providers and universities on the implications of the Consumer Rights Bill for fee-paying students; and what the Civil Service grades of officials present were.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193792","193792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45161","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to encourage businesses to implement and abide by the code of the Electronics Industry Citizenship Coalition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193991","193991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45162","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what scrutiny the Major Projects Authority has given to the Emergency Services Mobile Communications Programme.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194002","194002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45163","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what Red, Amber, Green ratings the Major Projects Authority has given to the Emergency Services Communications Programme.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194003","194003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45164","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Government contracts have been given to Airwave; and what the (a) value and (b) duration is of each such contract.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194011","194011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45165","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to encourage the Government Procurement Service to adopt (a) UN Global Compact and (b) ILO standards; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193994","193994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45166","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2013, Official Report, columns 291-2W, on the Electoral Register, whether the information on how many (a) UK- and (b) foreign-born citizens over the age of 18 and qualified to vote in UK parliamentary elections in each English and Welsh parliamentary constituency is now available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193803","193803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45167","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of employees in his Department of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193957","193957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45168","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of women in Brigg and Goole constituency were diagnosed with ovarian cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193908","193908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45169","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what rate of return will be offered through the new pensioner bond.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193913","193913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45170","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what criteria people will be eligible for the new pensioner bond.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193914","193914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45171","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what basis the projection in the Budget 2014 that the pension proposals will generate £1.2 billion in marginal taxation by 2018-19 was calculated.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193892","193892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45172","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the upper limit will be of the amount of state pension top-up people can buy.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193915","193915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45173","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the top-up of state pensions for each of the next 20 financial years.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193916","193916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45174","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to protect those who wish to take out an annuity against a significant deterioration in the annuity market reducing the pool of resources and both raising the cost of annuities and reducing their rate of return.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193898","193898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45175","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of employees in his Department of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193974","193974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45176","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of the introduction of electronic Vehicle Excise Duty on (a) the transfer of personalised number plates and (b) car sale purchases.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193831","193831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45177","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the publication by the Office for National Statistics entitled Scotland-Household Taxes and Benefits: update, if he will publish the data contained in that document on non-cash benefits from public spending, cash benefits and taxes paid by decile groups as it relates to Scotland.","Biography information for Mr Gordon Brown","Mr Gordon Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193841","193841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45178","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the value of unsecured debt owed by individuals in each income decile in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193861","193861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45179","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many endowment mortgage complaints have been rejected by insurance companies and upheld by the Financial Ombudsman Service since 2010.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193862","193862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45180","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual change in the rate of VAT registrations was in each of the previous five years; and what estimate he has made of the effect of such charges on revenue.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193863","193863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45181","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the UK's current account deficit.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193883","193883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45182","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the Financial Conduct Authority to publish the results of its study of the costs and benefits of account number portability.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193875","193875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45183","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the impact of the pension proposals on social care for the elderly. [R]","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193903","193903"
