"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348341","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received from the farming community about applications to the Basic Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1036","1036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348342","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the statement made by the Minister of State for Farming, Food and the Marine Environment to the Western Morning News on 25 May 2015, what the scientific evidential basis is for the statement that there is not a great deal of difference in practical terms between shooting badgers and shooting other wildlife.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1037","1037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348343","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to start the third phase of badger cull pilots in Somerset and Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1038","1038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348344","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to extend badger culling to areas outside the pilots in Somerset and Gloucestershire in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1039","1039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348345","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received supporting repeal of the Hunting Act 2004 since 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1040","1040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348346","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to repeal the Hunting Act 2004 in this parliamentary Session.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1041","1041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348347","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what impact assessment his Department has made of the proposed expansion of right to buy to housing association properties; and if he will place that assessment in the Library.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1059","1059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348348","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what legal advice his Department has received about the compulsory sale of housing association properties; and if he will place that advice in the Library.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1060","1060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348349","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average value is of local authority properties which are among the most expensive third of all properties of that type in their area.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1048","1048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348350","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with banks and other financial institutions about extension of the right to buy to encompass housing association properties.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1049","1049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348351","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the extension of right to buy on the availability of affordable housing.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1050","1050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348352","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with housing associations on the expansion of right to buy.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1051","1051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348353","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average value is of high-value council houses.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1052","1052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348354","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1053","1053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348355","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to prevent the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1054","1054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348356","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effectiveness of a licensing regime for the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1055","1055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348357","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what definition her Department uses of coasting schools.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1081","1081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348358","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many unqualified teachers are teaching in England and Wales.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1082","1082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348359","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on recruiting teachers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1083","1083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348360","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received on the amount of notice given by academies of their closure.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1084","1084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348361","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how she plans to increase the supply of childcare.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1085","1085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348362","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to increase the rate paid to nurseries for childcare.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1086","1086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348363","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what impact assessment his Department has made of extending the right to buy scheme; and if he will place that assessment in the Library.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1078","1078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348364","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability of talking therapies in (a) Sheffield and (b) England.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1087","1087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348365","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authority properties in each English region are among the most expensive third of all properties of that type in their area; and how many such homes become vacant each year by English region.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1079","1079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348366","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes for social rent were built in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1091","1091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348367","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is in (a) Sheffield, Heeley constituency and (b) Sheffield for access to talking therapies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1088","1088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348368","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will increase the discretionary housing payments budget when the reduced benefit cap is introduced.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1092","1092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348369","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how his Department defines a high-value council house; and how many such homes became vacant in each English region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1080","1080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348370","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the sale of high-value local authority housing on the cost to the public purse of housing benefit.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1089","1089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348371","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the extension of the right to buy to housing association tenants on housing benefit.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1090","1090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348372","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent (a) discussions he has held and (b) representations he has received concerning Southend University Hospital NHS Foundation Trust's performance on A&E waiting times; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1096","1096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348373","2015-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers of his Department and (c) officials of his Department have had with the Chief Executive of the Essex Community Rehabilitation Company; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1097","1097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348374","2015-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance on recruitment of officials (a) he, (b) Ministers of his Department and (c) officials of his Department (i) have issued since January 2015 and (ii) plan to issue within the next six months to Essex Community Rehabilitation Company; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1098","1098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348375","2015-06-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons the UK has not ratified the 1954 Hague Convention for the Protection of Cultural Property in the Event of Armed Conflict; and whether he plans to ratify that treaty.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1024","1024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348376","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what variation there is in (a) prices paid by NHS trusts for implantable defibrillators and cardiac resynchronisation defibrillators and (b) the costs for such devices that trusts pass back to NHS England.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1047","1047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348377","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what preparations his Department is making for the commencement of the Standardised Packaging of Tobacco Products Regulations 2015 on 20 May 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1058","1058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348378","2015-06-08","Cabinet Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much financial assistance the Government has given to the children's charity Kids Company since its creation.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1061","1061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348379","2015-06-08","Cabinet Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what government funding to the children's charity Kids Company will be for the financial year 2016-17.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1062","1062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348380","2015-06-08","Cabinet Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what government funding was provided to the children's charity Kids Company in financial years (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1063","1063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348381","2015-06-08","Cabinet Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the children's charity Kids Company about the provision of long-term government funding to that charity.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1064","1064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348382","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the children's charity Kids Company about the provision of long-term Government funding to that charity.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1065","1065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348383","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people and what proportion of those eligible to take advantage of the pensions flexibilities have received (a) face-to-face and (b) telephone advice through Pension Wise.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1071","1071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348384","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what preparations her Department is making to ensure that mandatory microchipping of dogs comes into effect in April 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1066","1066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348385","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have been victims of fraud and mis-selling related to the new pensions flexibilities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1072","1072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348386","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to monitor the prevalence of fraud related to the new pensions freedoms.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1073","1073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348387","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to conduct research into the use of savers make of money withdrawn under the new pensions freedoms.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1074","1074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348388","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to continue the Targeted Affordability Fund beyond financial year 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1075","1075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348389","2015-06-08","Cabinet Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2015 to Question 321, what qualifications and at what level are required by non-National Citizens Service personnel in charge of children taking part in residential training weeks under the National Citizen Service scheme.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1056","1056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348390","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what preparations his Department is making for the commencement of the Smoke-free (Private Vehicles) Regulations 2015 on 1 October 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1077","1077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348391","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 1 May 2014, Official Report, column 1052, on cervical cancer screening, whether Ministers in his Department hosted a special day in Parliament on the take-up of cervical cancer screening and HPV vaccinations.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1100","1100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348392","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 1 May 2014, Official Report, column 1052, on cervical cancer screening, what steps his Department has taken to modernise the NHS cervical cancer screening programme; what progress has been made by Public Health England on addressing low coverage of cervical cancer screening in certain areas and working on local action plans to improve such coverage; and what work his Department has carried out with employers to encourage them to make it clear to young women that they will facilitate them taking time off for cervical cancer screening.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1101","1101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348393","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many citizens of other EU member states receive (a) disability living allowance and (b) personal independence payments.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 947","947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348394","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what clinical advice NHS England has sought in establishing best value prices and reference prices for implantable defibrillators and cardiac resynchronisation defibrillators.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 950","950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348395","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian grievance cases against his Department were initiated by contractors or manpower substitutes in each year since 2010; and how many such cases were successful.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 951","951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348396","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of cancer patients received (a) intensity modulated and (b) stereotactic radiotherapy in the latest month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 952","952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348397","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of hidradenitis suppurativa.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 962","962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348398","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people with hidradenitis suppurativa in the UK; how much his Department has spent on research into hidradenitis suppurativa in the last four years; and what guidance his Department gives on support to be given through the NHS for people with hidradenitis suppurativa.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 963","963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348399","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the care pathways for patients with hidradenitis suppurativa.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 964","964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348400","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to provide information to surgeons, dermatologists and general practitioners about hidradenitis suppurativa.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 965","965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348401","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of electrifying the Gospel Oak to Barking railway line; and what contribution his Department plans to make to that project.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 966","966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348402","2015-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to raise at (a) the UN and (b) UNESCO (i) the threat of destruction to the city of Palmyra in Syria from ISIS and (ii) ways in which the international community can intervene to protect valuable historical sites.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 967","967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348403","2015-06-08","Leader of the House","2015-06-03","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will bring forward proposals to amend the standing orders of the House to allow hon. Members to read out the names of fallen soldiers on the floor of the House.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 968","968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348404","2015-06-08","Leader of the House","2015-06-03","To ask the Leader of the House, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to change the rules for the election of the Speaker.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 969","969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348405","2015-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness with which the Hunting Act 2004 has been implemented.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 970","970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348406","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what organisations in Wirral South constituency have received funding from the Libor fund; and how much each such organisation has received.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 979","979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348407","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 4, what the reason was for the size of the reduction in the percentage of calls handled by HM Revenue and Customs contact centres within five minutes in the first two quarters of 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 984","984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348408","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 161, what estimate his Department has made of the efficient cost of those Control Period 5 projects that have completed the enhancement cost adjustment mechanism process; and what the estimated cost was of those projects before they began that process.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 985","985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348409","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 4, what steps he is taking to increase the proportion of calls handled by HM Revenue and Customs' Contact Centre within five minutes.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 976","976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348410","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish draft regulations defining coasting before the Second Reading of the Education and Adoption Bill.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1006","1006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348411","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Level Crossing Reform Action Plan.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1008","1008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348412","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England plans to establish reference prices for medical devices beyond those named in the Commissioning Intentions for 2015-16.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1018","1018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348413","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which National Clinical Directors and Clinical Reference Groups have been involved in establishing best value prices and reference prices for implantable defibrillators and cardiac resynchronisation defibrillators.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1019","1019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348414","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what modelling NHS England has done to determine (a) the effects of trends in NHS trusts' income on (i) provision of (A) implantable defibrillators, (B) cardiac resynchronisation defibrillators and (C) other high cost devices and (ii) service viability and (b) the effects of provision of high cost devices on the future financial positions of trusts.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1020","1020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348415","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is his policy that the proposed legislation requiring young people to earn or learn will extend to existing claimants of employment and support allowance under the age of 21.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1030","1030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348416","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to NHS England of the provision of fitness for work certificates as required by the Department for Work and Pensions in the period 2014-15.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1022","1022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348417","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England plans to establish reference prices as ceiling prices above which trusts will not be reimbursed.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1023","1023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349050","2015-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that a nuclear agreement with Iran includes military site inspections.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900189","900189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349051","2015-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support exchanges and trade missions between the UK and China.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900192","900192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349052","2015-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Saudi Arabian authorities on the effects on civilians of conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900195","900195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349053","2015-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to tackle extremist ideology and reduce the appeal of such ideology worldwide.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900190","900190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349054","2015-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with President Anastasiades and Mustafa Akinci on UN-brokered negotiations to secure a united federal Cyprus.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900199","900199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347944","2015-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of apprenticeship starts in Coventry for people aged (a) 16 to 24 and (b) aged 25 and older in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 892","892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347945","2015-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of total apprenticeship starts in Coventry begun by women in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 893","893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347946","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average clearing time is of employment and support allowance mandatory reconsideration appeals in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 894","894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347947","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of projected local government finance settlement spending for each of the next five years as (a) total expenditure and (b) a percentage of gross domestic product.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 895","895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347948","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of projected local government finance settlement spending in the West Midlands in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 896","896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347949","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has held with NATO and the EU on the effect of submarine activity on fishing in the Irish Sea in April 2015.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 813","813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347950","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which of the seven demonstrator sites the NHS National Diabetes Prevention Programme began operating.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 828","828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347951","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been identified as possibly diabetic by the NHS Health Check in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 829","829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347952","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether school nurses will have a role in the National Diabetes Prevention Programme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 830","830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347953","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been assessed by the NHS Health Check in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 831","831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347954","2015-06-04","Department for International Development","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes her Department is operating (a) in Yemen and (b) to address the implications of the conflict in that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 832","832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347955","2015-06-04","Department for International Development","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the number of refugees (a) within and (b) outside Yemen as a result of the ongoing conflict in that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 833","833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347956","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of human rights in Mexico.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 834","834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347957","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the government of Mexico on drug trafficking.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 840","840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347958","2015-06-08","Wales Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, when (a) he and (b) his Department have made (i) oral and (ii) written representations to the Secretary of State for Transport on the time taken of work carried out at the A55/A493 junction.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 752","752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347959","2015-06-08","Leader of the House","2015-06-02","To ask the Leader of the House, what consultation he has carried out in Wales on the Government's proposal to change the role of hon. Members representing constituencies in Wales in the scrutiny of legislation.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 753","753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347960","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of qualified heavy goods vehicle drivers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 751","751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347961","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the time taken by HM Revenue and Customs to answer telephone calls from members of the public; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 890","890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347962","2015-06-04","Department for International Development","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid her Department provided to the (a) health sector, (b) education sector and (c) other sectors (i) globally and (ii) in Africa in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 926","926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347963","2015-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to remove onshore wind turbine subsidies.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 712","712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347964","2015-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the removal of subsidies will extend to consented onshore turbines with grid connections not yet constructed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 713","713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347965","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Treasury has sought assurances from Transport for London that the invitation to tender for Bridge Design Consultancy Services (ITT reference: tfL/00711) was undertaken in a fair and transparent manner.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 897","897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347966","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of the decision by the Cancer Drugs Fund not to fund olaparib for patients with BRCA-mutated ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 704","704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347967","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to offer personalised medicines to women with BRCA-mutated ovarian cancer with limited treatment options.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 705","705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347968","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patients benefit from scientific research into personalised medicines.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 706","706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347969","2015-06-08","Women and Equalities","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals in relation to caste discrimination in the UK.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 928","928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347970","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what regulations apply to asbestos in buildings; when such regulations are laid; and for what duration those regulations are in force.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 709","709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347971","2015-06-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) licensed dog breeders and (b) pet shops licensed to sell puppies there are in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 741","741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347972","2015-06-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under section 3(1) of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 in England in 2014.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 857","857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347973","2015-06-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under section 2 of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1871 in England in 2014.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 858","858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347974","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on allowing physician associates to independently prescribe in the NHS.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 807","807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347975","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the number of physician associates employed in the NHS in (a) Hertfordshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 808","808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347976","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the statutory regulation of physician associates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 809","809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347977","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the workings and processes of the Egyptian government's judicial process.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 727","727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347978","2015-06-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will begin an investigation into the liability of ScottishPower and the alleged mis-selling of cashback warranties.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 728","728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347979","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the diagnosis process and reduce the time taken of children going through paediatric care pathways.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 749","749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347980","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to promote in primary and secondary schools (a) participation in home economics by and (b) the catering industry as a career for boys.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 816","816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347981","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many gastric band operations the NHS has carried out in each of the last five years; what the cost to the public purse was of such operations in each of those years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 825","825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347982","2015-06-04","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many accidents have been reported during the transportation of workers to North Sea oil rigs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 876","876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347983","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training standards are required for workers on North Sea oil rigs prior to their deployment on these oil rigs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 877","877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347984","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been (a) arrested and (b) prosecuted for the possession of skunk cannabis in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 878","878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347985","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been hospitalised from the effects of consuming skunk cannabis in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 879","879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347986","2015-06-04","Cabinet Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have died from the effects of consuming skunk cannabis in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 880","880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347987","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in each age group were diagnosed with Type 1 diabetes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 870","870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347988","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the prevalence of salmonella in chicken sold in shops and restaurants in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 871","871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347989","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of food poisoning have been reported from salads containing (a) salmonella and (b) bacteria in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 872","872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347990","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) the BMA and (b) other medical bodies on recent developments in treating cancer with platinum-based therapy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 873","873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347991","2015-06-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to promote the economic and environmental benefits of shooting sports in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 874","874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347992","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) the BMA and (b) other medical bodies on the links between caesarean section births and obesity.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 875","875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347993","2015-06-04","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many incidences of criminal damage have been reported on trains in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 821","821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347994","2015-06-04","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the cost of criminal damage on trains in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 822","822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347995","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure ISIL does not have access to chemical weapons.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 823","823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347996","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on reviewing EU legislation on access to cancer drugs for children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 824","824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347997","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the NHS has to use the drug T-Vec for the treatment of skin cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 868","868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347998","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on (a) the treatment of and (b) research on Type 1 diabetes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 869","869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347999","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in each age group have been diagnosed with dementia in each of the last five years in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 826","826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348000","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people that have been trafficked to the UK to have their organs harvested in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 817","817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348001","2015-06-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on allergen requirements and restrictions for restaurants.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 818","818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348002","2015-06-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of red grouse in the UK; and what estimate she has made of the value of red grouse shooting to the UK economy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 819","819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348003","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) criteria and (b) conditions his Department has placed on the loan of weaponry from the armed forces to other countries in the last year.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 827","827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348004","2015-06-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will discuss with her Norwegian counterpart the decision of the Norwegian parliament to repeal that country's lead shot ban.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 820","820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348005","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has discussed or plans to discuss with her French counterpart the banning of wi-fi signals in nursery and primary schools in France; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 714","714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348006","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has issued guidance to nursery and primary schools on the installation of wi-fi in classrooms.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 715","715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348007","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will undertake research into medical conditions in young people arising from radiation emitted by wi-fi units, mobile phones and other wireless devices; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 716","716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348008","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with (a) Cheshire West & Chester Council, (b) Cheshire East Council and (c) East Cheshire NHS Trust on the provision of sexual health services in Cheshire in (i) 2014 and (ii) 2015 to date.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 708","708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348009","2015-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what funding his Department allocated for enhanced redundancy schemes for community rehabilitation companies following the privatisation of probation services.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 898","898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348010","2015-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of the funding his Department allocated for enhanced redundancy schemes following the privatisation of probation services was allocated to Sodexo.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 899","899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348011","2015-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department took to ensure that the funding allocated for enhanced redundancy schemes following the privatisation of probation services was used for that purpose.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900","900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348012","2015-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of the funding allocated by his Department for enhanced redundancy schemes following the privatisation of probation services was allocated to each company receiving such funding.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901","901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348013","2015-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to reclaim any of the funding allocated by his Department for enhanced redundancy schemes following the privatisation of probation services which is not used for the intended purpose.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902","902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348014","2015-06-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will allow public representations or petitions to be received directly by the Local Government Boundary Commission.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 841","841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348015","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the bombing of a church, school compound and priests' compound in Kauda, South Sudan, on 25 May 2015.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 758","758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348016","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were waiting to see a GP for more than one week in (a) Sheffield, Heeley constituency and (b) Sheffield in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 703","703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348017","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding she has provided to schools for the removal of asbestos in the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 710","710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348018","2015-06-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was borrowed by adults in (a) Sheffield, Heeley constituency and (b) England in 24+ advanced learning loans in the last year.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 771","771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348019","2015-06-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of money borrowed under 24+ advanced learning loans that will be repaid to the Exchequer.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 772","772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348020","2015-06-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of 24+ advanced learning loans on participation levels in further education.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 773","773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348021","2015-06-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to increase the number of advanced level apprenticeships.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 774","774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348022","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many STEM teachers remain in the teaching profession (a) two years and (b) five years after their initial qualification.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 851","851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348023","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Teach First teachers remain in the teaching profession after (a) two years and (b) five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 852","852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348024","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Teach First teachers in each (a) subject and (b) parliamentary constituency (i) began teaching and (ii) left the teaching profession in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 853","853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348025","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will reinstate the School Support Staff Negotiating Body.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 854","854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348026","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the number of teaching assistants who are performing a full teaching role in schools in England.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 855","855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348027","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average salary is for teaching assistants in (a) state maintained schools, (b) free schools and (c) academy schools.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 856","856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348028","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department will spend to remove asbestos from primary and secondary schools in the next financial year.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 845","845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348029","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the number of hours outside contracted hours worked by teaching assistants in (a) Sheffield and (b) England over the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 846","846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348030","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what records her Department keeps on the number of job applications for each advertised teaching position.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 847","847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348031","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how her Department assesses demand for teachers in each subject area.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 848","848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348032","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of levels of supply and demand for qualified teachers in STEM subjects.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 849","849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348033","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many qualified STEM teachers there are per (a) primary and (b) secondary school pupil in each parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 850","850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348034","2015-06-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of OFGEM's plans to re-examine the current gas mains replacement programme on long term stability of gas supply in the UK.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 781","781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348035","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many apprenticeship places were taken up by people (a) already in employment with the same employer, (b) already in employment with a new employer and (c) who were previously unemployed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 775","775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348036","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of those previously unemployed found work as a result of an apprenticeship in the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 776","776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348037","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people working in the retail sector are in receipt of tax credits.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 777","777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348038","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people working in the retail sector received working families tax credits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 778","778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348039","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in each parliamentary constituency who earn less than the living wage are in receipt of (a) working families tax credit and (b) child tax credit.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 779","779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348040","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total cost to the Exchequer has been of paying (a) working families tax credits and (b) child tax credit to those who earn less than the living wage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 780","780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348041","2015-06-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to fulfil his Department's responsibilities for the promotion of community cohesion.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 729","729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348042","2015-06-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to ensure that developments in the Thames Gateway area are sustainable, self-supporting and contribute to community cohesion and integration.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 730","730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348043","2015-06-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Government spending on the Troubled Families Programme.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 731","731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348044","2015-06-09","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to introduce HGV overtaking restrictions on two-lane motorways and on some A-roads to reduce light vehicle journey times; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 937","937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348045","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the daily cost of a (a) locum and (b) family GP.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 810","810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348046","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in each parliamentary constituency have benefitted from the Help to Buy scheme in each year since the launch of that scheme.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 891","891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348047","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the treatment of hidradenitis suppurativa cost the NHS in England in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 745","745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348048","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support patients with hidradenitis suppurativa.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 746","746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348049","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training is provided to people who carry out assessments for employment and support allowance or personal independence payment on sufferers of hidradenitis suppurativa.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 747","747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348050","2015-06-04","Women and Equalities","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she plans to reopen the Access to Elected Office fund in the present Parliament; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 699","699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348051","2015-06-04","Women and Equalities","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government has taken to evaluate the effectiveness of the Access to Elected Office fund between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 700","700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348052","2015-06-04","Women and Equalities","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the (a) average, (b) highest and (c) lowest award made to an individual candidate was by the Access to Elected Office fund between May 2010 and May 2015.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 701","701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348053","2015-06-04","Women and Equalities","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much was disbursed to political candidates (a) in each region, (b) of each political party, (c) of each gender and (d) of each ethnic group by the Access to Elected Office fund between May 2010 and May 2015.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 702","702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348054","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people his Department will assess for personal independence payment in each month from July 2015 to July 2016.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 768","768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348055","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what targets he has set for the time taken to process new applications for personal independence payment.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 769","769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348056","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people claiming disability living allowance who will cease to receive disability benefits after being assessed for personal independence payment in each month from July 2015 to July 2016.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 767","767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348057","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost was of housing benefit for 18 to 21 year olds who were (a) employed, (b) unemployed and (c) inactive in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 763","763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348058","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average duration was of housing benefit claims by 18 to 21 year olds who were (a) employed, (b) unemployed and (c) inactive in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 764","764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348059","2015-06-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the cost of full maintenance grants to households earning (a) more and (b) less than 17,000 per year was in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 765","765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348060","2015-06-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the cost of partial maintenance grants to households earning (a) more and (b) less than 17,000 per year was in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 766","766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348061","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the most recent findings from the Care Quality Commission Inpatient Survey.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 924","924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348062","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) chief executives, (b) deputy chief executives and (c) assistant chief officers of community rehabilitation companies have left their post since 1 January 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 694","694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348063","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request a report from the Chair of the Southend University Hospital NHS Foundation Trust on how much Southend University Hospital received from car parking charges in each of the last two years and what use was made of those funds by that hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 684","684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348064","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request a report from the Chair of the Southend University Hospital NHS Foundation Trust on how many press officers were employed by Southend University Hospital in each of the last two years and what the average cost was of employing each of those press officers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 685","685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348065","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on how many safety officers are employed by Essex Community Rehabilitation Company to help (a) female and (b) male victims of domestic violence.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 695","695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348066","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent by Southend University Hospital on employing locums in each (a) ward and (b) position in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 686","686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348067","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how much Southend University Hospital plans to spend on employing locums in each (a) ward and (b) position in each of the next two years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 687","687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348068","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints about Southend University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust have been received by his Department in each week since January 2014; what response his Department gave to each such complaint; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 785","785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348069","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints about Southend University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust have been received in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 786","786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348070","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the level of income received by Southend University Hospital from car parking operations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 836","836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348071","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the salary was of the (a) Chief Executive and (b) Chairman of Essex Community Rehabilitation Company in 2014; what each such salary will be in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 837","837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348072","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) recent discussions he has had and (b) discussions he plans to have with Southend University Hospital about its policy towards car parking charges; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 688","688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348073","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) recent discussions he has had and (b) discussions he plans to have with Southend University Hospital about its policy on the payment of bonuses to senior managers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 689","689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348074","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) recent discussions he has had and (b) discussions he plans to have with Southend University Hospital about its policy on away days for senior management; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 690","690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348075","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has (a) issued and (b) plans to issue on the use of agency staff at the Probation Service.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 691","691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348076","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department (i) have had since January 2015 and (ii) plan to have in the next six months with the Chief Executive of the Essex Community Rehabilitation Company; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 692","692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348077","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the budgeted annual expenditure is of the Essex Community Rehabilitation Company for this financial year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 693","693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348078","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency plans his Department has to respond to a (a) heatwave and (b) cold snap in (i) London North West Healthcare NHS Trust area and (ii) the NHS England area.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 732","732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348079","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to manage an increase in the birth rate in Ealing Local Authority Area.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 733","733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348080","2015-06-04","Church Commissioners","2015-06-02","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, how many members of the clergy in each of the last 10 years have been women.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 734","734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348081","2015-06-04","Church Commissioners","2015-06-02","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what statistics the Church Commissioners collect on the number of LGBT men and women in the clergy.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 735","735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348082","2015-06-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department took to celebrate World Milk Day on 1 June 2015.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 736","736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348083","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the introduction of a Bill of Rights to replace the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 867","867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348084","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to strengthen economic and political ties with the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 866","866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348085","2015-06-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans her Department has to sponsor alternative green energy projects in Wales in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 717","717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348086","2015-06-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the number of jobs created in the Swansea Bay region as a result of the construction of the proposed tidal lagoon.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 718","718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348087","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with (a) health bodies, (b) youth organisations, (c) local government and (d) the devolved administration on legal highs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 719","719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348088","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent research her Department has undertaken to ascertain the safety of legal highs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 720","720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348089","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of recent research by the Institute of Cancer Research into the effect of a genetically created herpes-based virus as a remedy against forms of skin cancer.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 721","721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348090","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what definition her Department uses of the term psychoactive substance.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 795","795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348091","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Neath constituency have been affected by the under-occupancy penalty in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 859","859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348092","2015-06-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the number of pre-pay gas and electricity meters installed in England, Wales and Scotland without the authority of the account holder in the last 12 months; if she will prohibit the installation of such pre-payment meters without such authority; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 860","860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348093","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to encourage reform of the Prisoners of Conscience Affairs Committee in Burma; and if he will seek the empowerment of that Committee to ensure the release of all political prisoners.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 737","737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348094","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of whether human rights violations against the Rohingya in Burma meet the international legal definitions of ethnic cleansing and crimes against humanity.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 738","738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348095","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2015 to Question 227404, if he will place in the Library a copy of (a) DCDS(MilCap)/14/01/10 dated 28 January 2014 and (b) MAA/DG/COMMS/SENIOR MOD ZD743/ZD812 dated 13 December 2013.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 789","789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348096","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many successful shipborne rolling vertical landings have taken place using the F-35B with (a) an empty weapons load and (b) the maximum weight weapons configuration to date.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 790","790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348097","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many successful night landings of the Joint Strike Fighter F-35B have been conducted by RAF pilots using night vision.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 791","791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348098","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Joint Strike Fighter F-35s are allowed to use (a) night vision and (b) the distributed aperture system when landing on an aircraft carrier at night.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 792","792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348099","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish details of the programme to install a Collision Warning System in the Typhoon aircraft.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 793","793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348100","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the document D/VCDS&2ndPUS/8/1/4 PR11 Tornado CWS Further Work, identified in paragraph 1.4.6.606 of the Report into the Tornado collision of 3 July 2012 undertaken by the Director-General of the Military Aviation Authority.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 794","794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348101","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Autonomous Minesweeping Capability will achieve (a) initial and (b) full operational capability; what the total cost of the programme is; and where the assets developed will be permanently based.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 811","811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348102","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the proportion of the value of the UK Ministry of Defence Autonomous Minesweeping Capability contract that will go to (a) Atlas Elektronik (b) BAE systems and (c) Babcock.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 812","812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348103","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the Government's response to the House of Lords Economic Affairs Committee's First Report of Session 2014-15, The Economics of High Speed 2, HL Paper 134.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 934","934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348104","2015-06-08","Department for International Development","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support anti-FGM measures.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 935","935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348105","2015-06-08","Department for International Development","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she plans to take to support the implementation of the ban on female genital mutilation in Nigeria.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 936","936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348106","2015-06-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to safeguard consumers who wish to keep their current telephone number when switching providers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 927","927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348107","2015-06-04","Cabinet Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on the abolition of the annual canvass undertaken by Electoral Registration Officers, as provided for in the Electoral Registration and Administration Act 2013 c. 6 Part 1, Section 7(2)(b), during the course of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 696","696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348108","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will consult on a British Bill of Rights before its introduction; if he will publish the terms of reference for such a consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 697","697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348109","2015-06-04","Cabinet Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to alter the procedure by which the recommendations of the Boundary Commissions take effect upon the conclusion of their periodic reviews of constituency boundaries.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 698","698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348110","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that the Edith Cavell commemorative coin recently issued by the Royal Mint can be purchased by members of the public at an affordable price.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 711","711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348111","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will revise the guidance offered to LEAs regarding the choices available to parents who seek a place for their child at both grammar and LEA schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 750","750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348112","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 126, when he expects to be able to place in the Library the correspondence between his Department and Public Health England in relation to use of Lariam or Mefloquine and reports of (a) hallucinations, (b) psychosis and (c) suicidal thoughts in personnel prescribed those medications for the period 2010 to 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 739","739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348113","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK is able to identify those responsible for human rights violations in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea; and what steps the Government is taking to impose sanctions on North Korean officials similar to the financial sanctions imposed by HM Treasury on people responsible for serious human rights violations in Iran and Ukraine.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 726","726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348114","2015-06-10","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will commission an independent review of the Government's stake in the Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 754","754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348115","2015-06-10","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that any review of the Government's stake in the Royal Bank of Scotland (a) includes representation and consultation with all stakeholders and (b) assesses the costs and benefits of all available options, including alternatives to reprivatisation.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 755","755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348116","2015-06-10","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Royal Bank of Scotland on plans to close further branches; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 756","756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348117","2015-06-10","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will take steps to prevent further closure of branches of the Royal Bank of Scotland pending a review of such closure.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 757","757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348118","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from Welsh Assembly Ministers about the (a) Dyfed Powys Police Helicopter and (b) National Police Air Service.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 760","760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348119","2015-06-04","Wales Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what representations he has received from Ministers in the Welsh Government about the (a) Dyfed Powys Police Helicopter and (b) National Police Air Service.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 761","761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348120","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what human rights conditions are required of the government of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea for European-funded aid projects in that country; if he will press for greater use of such conditions; and what assessment he has made of the effect of such projects.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 782","782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348121","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what human rights conditions are attached to the UK's cultural engagement projects inside the Democratic People's Republic of Korea.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 783","783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348122","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what monitoring mechanisms there were of the effect on the people of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea of engagement projects funded by his Department in that country between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 784","784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348123","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has a mechanism in place to monitor whether foreign buyers of UK property are occupants, landlords, UK business owners or absentee property investors.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 799","799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348124","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many combined employment and support allowance and personal independence payment claimants with mental ill health have had their application undergo a mandatory reconsideration since October 2013.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 800","800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348125","2015-06-08","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Warrington North constituency are in receipt of child benefit for three or more children.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 805","805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348126","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children living in poverty in each ward of Warrington North constituency.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 806","806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348127","2015-06-04","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on replacing pacer trains on rail services in the north of England.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 838","838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348128","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce a Long Service Medal to recognise the contribution of long-serving police officers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 839","839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348129","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the future of A-levels and GCSEs for (a) Turkish, (b) Greek, (c) Gujarati, (d) Modern Hebrew, (e) Panjabi, (f) Polish, (g) Bengali and (h) other community languages; and if she will outline steps that will be taken in pursuit of that policy.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 842","842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348130","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his Department's report, Democratic People's Republic of Korea - Country of Concern, published on 12 March 2015, what steps the British Embassy in Pyongyang has taken to challenge widespread sexual abuse and domestic violence against women in that country.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 844","844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348131","2015-06-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress has been made in relation to the construction of Hinckley C nuclear power station; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903","903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348132","2015-06-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects the Smartmeter rollout to be completed.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904","904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348133","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 157, on the right of armed forces personnel to make a complaint following their illegal punishment following the receipt of a police caution in the last year and with reference to the contribution of the hon. Member for Broxtowe on 2 February 2015, Official Report, column 64, in which she gave a commitment to place notices in the usual places such as websites and magazines, if he will make a similar commitment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 905","905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348134","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the treatments for pancreatic cancer listed by the Cancer Drugs Fund will continue to be made available to patients on the NHS.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 917","917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348135","2015-06-08","Home Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to raise awareness of the dangers of legal highs amongst young people.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 931","931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348136","2015-06-08","Home Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to being forward legislation to ban the sale of so-called legal highs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 932","932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348137","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the value of UK property sold to foreign buyers between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 933","933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348138","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has recently received a revised draft of the National Rail Conditions of Carriage from the Association of Train Operating Companies for his approval.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 885","885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348139","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will amend her Department's Governors' handbook and the Academy Converter Checklist for Schools to better highlight the requirements of regulation 46 of the School Governance (Federations)(England) Regulations 2012 (SI 2012/1035).","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 815","815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348140","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18-21 year olds who (a) are care leavers, (b) have young children and (c) are in employment he has estimated would no longer receive housing benefit under the Government's proposals to restrict access for that age group.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 886","886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348141","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18-21 year olds he has estimated would be affected by plans to replace out-of-work benefits for that age group with a youth allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 887","887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348142","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people he has estimated will no longer receive housing benefit under the Government's proposals to restrict access for that age group to that benefit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 888","888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348143","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people under the Government's proposals for a youth allowance he has estimated will be expected to undertake community work from the commencement of an employment and support allowance claim.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 889","889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348144","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Pakistan on the issue of religious freedom (a) in relation to the case of Asia Bibi and (b) in general.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 835","835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348145","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with (a) ministerial colleagues and (b) representatives from the steel industry on Tata Steel's plans to close the British Steel pension scheme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 843","843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348146","2015-06-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on repeal of the Hunting Act.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 906","906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348147","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many (a) single-parent households, (b) households with dependent children, (c) households with a disabled member, (d) pensioner households and (e) households with one or more person employed in Camberwell and Peckham constituency are subject to the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 907","907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348148","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many households in the London Borough of Southwark have downsized as a result of the under-occupancy penalty since April 2013.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 908","908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348149","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of (a) single-parent households, (b) households with dependent children, (c) households with a disabled member, (d) pensioner households and (e) households with one or more person employed in the London Borough of Southwark are subject to the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 909","909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348150","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether minutes exist for each meeting of the Specialised Commissioning Oversight Group undertaken to date; if he will publish the agendas for and minutes of each such meeting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 910","910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348151","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many citizens of other EU member states with Parkinson's disease receive disability living allowance or personal independence payments.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 911","911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348152","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the names and positions are of the members of NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 912","912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348153","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the names and positions are of the members of NHS England's Specialised Commissioning Oversight Group.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 913","913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348154","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what systems and procedures exist between the Child Maintenance Service (CMS) and the Child Support Agency (CSA) to ensure that where, following a six-month warning notice of CSA case closure, a parent with care applies in advance to the CMS, the new application is not processed prematurely and a case opened by the CMS, prior to the CSA case being closed.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 914","914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348155","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in how many cases the Child Maintenance Service opened a new case in error before a case subject to the Child Support Agency case closure process was closed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 915","915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348156","2015-06-04","Cabinet Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the Government was of the inquiry into the leaking of a memorandum relating to the First Minister of Scotland during the General Election campaign.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 861","861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348157","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 223811, what progress has been made in completing the new Data Warehouse required by his Department to provide full IT functionality to support the 2012 Child Maintenance Scheme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 916","916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348158","2015-06-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the rationale was for the Government's decision to introduce a directly-elected mayor in Manchester; and what account was taken in that decision of the result of the referendum on the introduction of a mayor in Manchester in 2012.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 862","862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348159","2015-06-04","Prime Minister","2015-06-02","To ask the Prime Minister, what his policy is on reform of the political honours system.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 863","863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348160","2015-06-04","Cabinet Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date he expects the report of the Chilcot inquiry to be published.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 864","864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348161","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of conditions and the performance of staff at Rainsbrook Secure Training Centre.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 865","865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348162","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the National Employment Savings Trust is exempt from the requirements for improved governance of workplace pensions schemes set out in his Department's publication, Better workplace pensions: Putting savers' interests first, Cm 9000.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 918","918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348163","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the National Employment Savings Trust plans to complete (a) the independent assurance audit and (b) the other constituent parts of the voluntary assurance framework.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 919","919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348164","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what forecast he has made of when his Department's loan to meet the scheme implementation costs for the National Employment Savings Trust will be repaid; and what the process is for that repayment.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 920","920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348165","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in the London Borough of Southwark are currently receiving discretionary housing payment.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 929","929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348166","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households are currently claiming housing benefit in the London Borough of Southwark.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 930","930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348167","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what period of time parents who were formerly in receipt of Child Support Agency maintenance via that agency's collection service will experience a gap in child maintenance payments before their new applications to the Child Maintenance Service made within the six-month notice period are processed and a new payment schedule notified to the paying parent.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 921","921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348168","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 10 March 2015 to Question 227026, when he expects NHS England to publish the minutes of all meetings of the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group held to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 922","922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348169","2015-06-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if the Government will bring forward proposals to require broadcasters to provide subtitles and audio description for on-demand programmes for the benefit of people with sensory loss; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 923","923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348170","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulance vehicles there were in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 925","925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348171","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the 1.2 million spent on research by National Employment Savings Trust in fiscal year 2013-14.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 707","707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348172","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of people who are in receipt of (a) employment and support allowance (ESA), (b) the work related activity component of ESA, (c) jobseekers allowance and (d) income support who will be affected by reducing the benefit cap from 26,000 to 23,000 per year.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 742","742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348173","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of people who have a child aged under (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four and (e) five who will be affected by reducing the benefit cap from 26,000 to 23,000 per year.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 743","743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348174","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of people in temporary accommodation who will be affected by reducing the benefit cap from 26,000 to 23,000 per year.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 744","744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348175","2015-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 24 March 2015 to Question 228133, how much has been claimed in hardship payments in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 748","748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348176","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will be affected by the under-occupancy penalty between 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 722","722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348177","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will announce details of how his Department will reduce spending on social security by 12 billion by 2017-18.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 723","723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348178","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the number of working people claiming housing benefit on housing benefit spending.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 724","724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348179","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect on the number of families living in temporary accommodation of reducing the benefit cap from 26,000 to 23,000 per year.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 725","725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348180","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative research his Department has made on the incidence of Hepatitis B and HIV infection in the population of (a) men who have sex with men (MSM) and (b) the MSM population in civil partnerships or same sex marriages; what assessment his Department has made on this incidence in respect of the safety of blood donation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 740","740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348181","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of (a) HSBC, (b) Barclays and (c) Standard Chartered about allegations that their banks have been involved in money laundering by senior officials in world football administration.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 759","759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348182","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what power the Government has to investigate private banks registered in British Overseas Territories for alleged money laundering.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 762","762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348183","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish details of each (a) meeting and (b) overnight stay by Tony Blair in each UK embassy in each year between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 770","770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348184","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people and of what gender in each North Wales police force area committed an offence resulting in immediate custody in each year since 2011; and what the offence type and length of sentence was in each such year.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 787","787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348185","2015-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of sentenced women in each police force area in Wales were sentenced to immediate custody in each year since 2011.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 788","788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348186","2015-06-04","Cabinet Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 3 March 2015 to Question 225989, how many people (a) under the age of 18 and (b) aged 18 or over died as a result of asthma in England and Wales in 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 796","796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348187","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time at the Accident and Emergency Unit of the Queen Elizabeth Hospital was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 797","797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348188","2015-06-08","Department of Health","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of accident and emergency services at the Queen Elizabeth Hospital in Birmingham.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 798","798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348189","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) single-headed households, (b) households with children, (c) households with pensioners, (d) households where one or more person is employed and (e) households with a disabled member were placed in temporary accommodation by the London Borough of Southwark in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 801","801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348190","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households that were placed in temporary accommodation in the last 12 months by the London Borough of Southwark were housed (a) outside and (b) within that Borough.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 802","802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348191","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households that were placed in temporary accommodation in the last 12 months by the London Borough of Southwark outside the London Borough of Southwark were households with dependent children.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 803","803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348192","2015-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households that were placed in temporary accommodation in the last 12 months by the London Borough of Southwark were permanently rehoused within that borough.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 804","804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348193","2015-06-08","Department for Education","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what advice the Regional Schools Commissioner for the South East and South London gave to the Head Teacher Board on the statutory requirements on applications on behalf of federated schools for academy status in regulation 46 of the School Governance (Federations) (England) Regulations 2012 (SI 2012/1035) before approving the Academy Orders Prendergast, Prendergast Vale  and Prendergast Ladywell Schools in Lewisham on 26 February 2015.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 814","814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348194","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to make a decision on whether to appoint a Special Director to Network Rail's Board.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 881","881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348195","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish HS2 Ltd's jobs and skills strategy.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 882","882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348196","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Shareholder Executive's high-level Board effectiveness review of Network Rail has been completed; and if he will publish the conclusions of that review.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 883","883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348197","2015-06-08","Department for Transport","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which projects the Department has committed to include in the Control Period 6 High Level Output Statement.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 884","884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348550","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports he has received of flights by Russian military aircraft over Lancashire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900131","900131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348764","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of support provided by his Department to the Army Cadet Force.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900130","900130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348765","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that small and medium-sized manufacturers benefit from his Department's procurement of defence equipment.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900133","900133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348766","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to invest in new equipment for the armed forces.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900137","900137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348767","2015-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the safety of the reactors in the SSBN fleet.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900132","900132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349443","2015-06-10","Scotland Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make an assessment of the implications of the results in Scotland of the General Election for the mandate of the Government.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900159","900159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349444","2015-06-10","Scotland Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential costs and benefits to Scotland of operating a separate postal network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900164","900164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349445","2015-06-10","Scotland Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what information his department holds on the number of undergraduates studying at Scottish universities from (a) Scotland (b) the rest of the UK and (c) other EU member states.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900161","900161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349446","2015-06-10","Scotland Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the effect on democratic participation of the extension of the franchise in the Scottish independence referendum to 16 and 17 year olds.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900160","900160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349447","2015-06-10","Scotland Office","2015-06-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of reductions in welfare spending on child poverty in Scotland.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900163","900163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347630","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many UK supply chain (a) jobs and (b) apprenticeships were created in the renewable energy sector in each year from 2009 to 2014.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 596","596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347631","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's policy is on the potential sell-off by National Grid of its (a) gas distribution networks and (b) metering business.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 597","597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347632","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on (a) local economies, (b) customer service and (c) safety of any sell-off of National Grid (i) gas distribution networks and (ii) metering business.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 598","598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347633","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what meetings have taken place between representatives of her Department and National Grid about any sale of National Grid assets or businesses.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 599","599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347634","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what comparative assessment she has made of the benefits and disbenefits of (a) UK and (b) foreign ownership of energy infrastructure; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 600","600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347635","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many jobs will be created by investment in the planned Rampion wind farm; and what steps she is taking to ensure that UK supply chains benefit from such investment.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 601","601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347636","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what level of investment her Department plans to make in the development of carbon capture and storage.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 608","608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347637","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) jobs and (b) apprenticeships were created in the development of carbon capture and storage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 609","609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347638","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of coal used in UK energy generation is imported; and from which countries coal is imported.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 610","610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347639","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the value of work accruing to UK manufacturing companies in each region from the development of the Rampion wind farm.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 602","602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347640","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential for northern cities to benefit from (a) Rampion wind farm and (b) other investment in renewable energy sources.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 604","604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347641","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the potential benefit to the economy of each UK region of investment in the Rampion wind farm.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 603","603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347642","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the benefits and disbenefits of UK ownership of energy infrastructure in relation to the security of energy supply.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 605","605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347643","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people are classed as living in fuel poverty in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) Sheffield, Brightside and Hillsborough constituency.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 606","606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347644","2015-06-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many children live in households that are classed as being in fuel poverty in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) Sheffield, Brightside and Hillsborough constituency.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 607","607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347645","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of his Department's budget for each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 667","667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347646","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made his Department's budget for each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 668","668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347647","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effects of the proposed resettlement of Bedouin in Southern Israel on the peace process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 669","669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347648","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on official discrimination against Tamils in Sri Lanka; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 670","670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347649","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received from the government of Sri Lanka about allegations of war crimes in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 671","671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347650","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the roadworks on the M1 between junctions 15 and 19 will be completed.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 628","628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347651","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse is of the roadworks taking place on the M1 between junctions 15 and 19.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 629","629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347652","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he last discussed the progress of the A483 upgrade with Highways England; and what the outcome of that discussion was.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 586","586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347653","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from local (a) authorities and (b) businesses on delays to the A55/A483 upgrade project.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 587","587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347654","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the cost of the delays to the A55/A483 upgrade project to (a) the public purse and (b) businesses within 10 miles of the project.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 588","588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347655","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had about the economic effect of the delays to the A55/A483 upgrade project on the area with (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 589","589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347656","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he is satisfied with the quality of the information that his Department has given to motorists during the A55/A483 upgrade project.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 590","590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347657","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 25 February 2015 to Question 225319, for what reasons the A483 upgrade project missed its extended deadline.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 630","630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347658","2015-06-03","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 228104, what his Department's current plans are for reorganisation of HM Revenue and Customs in Wales.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 631","631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347659","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 228104, what progress his Department has made on the consultation process Building our Future, on HM Revenue and Customs reorganisation.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 650","650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347660","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 228104, what the outcomes have been of the conversations his Department has had with hon. Members and Welsh Assembly Members on HM Revenue and Customs reorganisation since October 2014.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 651","651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347661","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 228104, on which occasions he or other representatives of his Department met staff from the Wrexham HM Revenue and Customs office to discuss the future of that office; and what the outcomes were of those meetings.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 652","652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347662","2015-06-03","Wales Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, when he or his Department has made (a) oral and (b) written representations to the Secretary of State for Transport on the delays in the work carried out at the A55/A493 junction.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 663","663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347663","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what process his Department undertook to scrutinise the business case for the proposed Garden Bridge project.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 544","544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347664","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits of a new Thames pedestrian bridge at alternative locations to that of the proposed Garden Bridge project.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 545","545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347665","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what dates he has met Joanna Lumley to discuss the proposed Garden Bridge project in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 546","546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347666","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what dates officials in his Department have met Joanna Lumley to discuss the proposed Garden Bridge project in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 547","547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347667","2015-06-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects the TTIP negotiations between the EU and the US to be concluded.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 657","657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347668","2015-06-04","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-06-01","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which parliamentary constituencies have electorates more than 10 per cent (a) greater and (b) smaller than the UK average.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 658","658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347669","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she expects to respond to the letter from Dorset County Council seeking to prevent St Ives School increasing its age range.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 659","659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347670","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will place in the Library a copy of the letter from Dorset County Council seeking to prevent St Ives School increasing its age range.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 660","660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347671","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will commission an independent audit of the economic costs and benefits of UK membership of the EU.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 661","661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347672","2015-06-04","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding has been allocated to Network Rail for the electrification of the Barking to Gospel Oak line.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 550","550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347673","2015-06-04","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects work to (a) start and (b) be completed on the electrification of the Barking to Gospel Oak line.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 551","551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347674","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have left the employment of immigration centres in Scotland in each year since 2006; and for what reasons those people have left that employment.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 539","539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347675","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been detained in immigration removal centres in Scotland in each year since 2006; and what the capacity of such centres was in each of those years.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 540","540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347676","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many detainees in immigration removal centres in Scotland have taken their own life since 2006.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 541","541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347677","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was spent on training for (a) staff and (b) detainees in immigration removal centres in Scotland in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 542","542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347678","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reported (a) incidents, (b) assaults and (c) serious assaults there were on staff in immigration removal centres in Scotland in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 543","543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347679","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the latest position regarding training of the Syrian moderate opposition is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 662","662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347680","2015-06-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to ensure that elderly people without sufficient means can block calls from call centres on PPI claims, accident claims and claims against banks without cost.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 678","678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347681","2015-06-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions the Sports Minister has had with FIFA on the recent FBI investigation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 679","679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347682","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect on intelligence gathering as a result of the withdrawal of maritime patrol aircraft.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 680","680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347683","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department is of HMS Bulwark rescuing migrants in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 681","681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347684","2015-06-04","Cabinet Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many nominations for honours were made through the Northern Ireland Assembly in each year since its inception; and whether the nomination was successful in each such case.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 682","682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347686","2015-06-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to reform funding of the BBC.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 560","560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347687","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to publish the report Distressed Health Communities in East Cheshire NHS Trust.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 537","537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347688","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the financial viability of East Cheshire NHS Trust.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 538","538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347689","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to promote tourism and develop the tourism industry in England.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 585","585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347690","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the three clinical commissioning groups in Leeds not included in the Schedule to the draft directions on care.data submitted to NHS England for approval will be included in the pathfinder process.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 581","581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347691","2015-06-03","Department for International Development","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent reports she has received on the work of the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition; what steps she is taking to ensure that the Alliance's work does not contribute to the takeover of land belonging to small farmers by multinational corporations; and what steps she is taking to ensure that the Alliance does not prioritise growing food for export over producing food to feed local people.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 573","573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347692","2015-06-03","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consideration HM Revenue and Customs gave to the reputational risk of contracting to companies which are alleged to use aggressive debt collection techniques when it decided to outsource the collection of working tax credit overpayments to external debt collection agencies.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 574","574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347693","2015-06-03","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what quality standards HM Revenue and Customs applies when deciding to which external debt collection agencies the collection of working tax credit overpayments is outsourced.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 575","575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347694","2015-06-03","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what impact assessment was made of the decision by HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) to outsource the collection of working tax credit overpayments to external debt collection agencies; and what estimate HMRC made of the cost of (a) recovering overpayment by HMRC and (b) selling the debts.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 576","576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347695","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to subject to income tax the income HRH The Prince of Wales receives from the Duchy of Cornwall.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 557","557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347696","2015-06-03","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints HM Revenue and Customs has received about the decision to outsource the collection of working tax credit overpayments to external debt collection agencies.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 577","577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347697","2015-06-03","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons HM Revenue and Customs decided to outsource the collection of working tax credit overpayments to external debt collection agencies.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 578","578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347698","2015-06-03","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who signed off the decision that HM Revenue and Customs would outsource the collection of working tax credit overpayments to external debt collection agencies; what consultation with stakeholders was undertaken before the decision was taken; and whether expert advice was sought.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 579","579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347699","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the publication of the updated GP clinical code specification referred to in Annex 1 of the care.data Directions, whether any patient communications for care.data will be sent in June 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 580","580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347700","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Israeli government about forced evictions and harassment of the inhabitants of the village of Susya on the West Bank.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 555","555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347701","2015-06-04","Prime Minister","2015-06-01","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will provide an update on the progress of the Chilcot inquiry; and when he expects the Maxwellisation process to be completed.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 556","556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347702","2015-06-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy before the proposed referendum takes place to publish a study of the implications of UK exit from the EU.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 624","624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347703","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NHS England to take a decision on the draft clinical commissioning policy for Duodopa.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 531","531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347704","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how NHS England will communicate the decision on the draft clinical commissioning policy for Duodopa to (a) clinicians and (b) patients.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 532","532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347705","2015-06-03","Home Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on reinstatement of the Tier 1 visa route.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 582","582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347706","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve the matching of donated lungs with people waiting for lung transplants.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 621","621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347707","2015-06-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the merits of (a) the Prism reactor, (b) Areva Mox, (c) Canmox, and (d) immobilisation for the disposition of plutonium; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 559","559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347708","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will (a) sign the Safe Schools Declaration and (b) support implementation of that declaration in countries where armed conflict is taking place.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 653","653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347709","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of A&E departments likely to close in each region in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 654","654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347710","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of maternity units likely to close in each region in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 655","655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347711","2015-06-04","Home Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the likely number of officers in the Metropolitan Police Service (a) overall and (b) in Redbridge in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 656","656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347712","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he taking to improve rail connectivity to major rail lines from in East Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 638","638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347713","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had on investment in the East Durham section of the coastal railway line between Sunderland and Hartlepool.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 639","639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347714","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of the potential  effect of three private proton therapy centres becoming operational in England in 2016 on University College Hospital London and the Christie Hospital Manchester's plans to build NHS proton therapy centres.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 664","664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347715","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on electrification of the TransPennine rail line; and what the likely completion date is.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 665","665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347716","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the condition of the Woodhead Tunnels and their suitability for potential transport use in future; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 666","666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347717","2015-06-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained Army Reserve personnel were recruited in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 672","672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347718","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to alter the restrictions on the premises which can be licensed to have fixed-odds betting terminal machines.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 523","523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347719","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to decriminalise non-payment of the television licence fee.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 524","524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347720","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he proposes to continue top-slicing in the next television licence fee settlement.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 525","525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347721","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to publish a green and white paper on the BBC Charter renewal and draft Charter and Framework Agreements.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 526","526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347722","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to publish a consultation document on the BBC Charter renewal before Parliament rises for the summer recess.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 527","527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347723","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish his timetable for the BBC Charter renewal.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 528","528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347724","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has had discussions with the Attorney General regarding allegations of corruption at FIFA.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 529","529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347725","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to alter the number of fixed-odds betting terminal machines allowed in each betting shop.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 530","530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347726","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with content creators about the European Commission's Digital Single Market proposals.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 571","571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347727","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that tickets for the Rugby World Cup and Ashes cricket tests are sold at face value in the secondary ticketing market.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 572","572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347728","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the expected delivery date is for the completion of Horden Railway Station.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 584","584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347729","2015-06-03","Home Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests were made by the police for access to communications data relating to investigations into (a) drug offences, (b) people trafficking, (c) fraud, (d) other organised crime, (e) pornography and paedophile offences and (f) other offences in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 593","593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347730","2015-06-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on developing the next Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 594","594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347731","2015-06-03","Cabinet Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the Government has made on developing the next National Security Strategy; and when he expects that Strategy to be completed.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 595","595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347732","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to monitor the effect of the secondary ticketing market on the cost of attending major sporting events.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 561","561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347733","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations his Department has made to the European Commission on its Digital Single Market proposals.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 562","562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347734","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many masts have been built by the Mobile Infrastructure Project; and how much his Department has spent on that project.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 563","563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347735","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish the Statement of Commitment signed with the mobile network operators in December 2014.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 564","564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347736","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to investigate whether any bribery related to the FIFA allegations took place within the UK's jurisdiction.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 565","565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347737","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure the Premier League meets its commitment to fund grassroots sport.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 566","566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347738","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with Richard Scudamore about the Premier League's contribution to grassroots sport.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 567","567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347739","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will set up an independent review panel for the BBC Charter Renewal.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 568","568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347740","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to ensure that the Charter Renewal process is conducted on a cross-party basis.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 569","569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347741","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to make the allocation of funding by the National Lottery more open and transparent.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 570","570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347742","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of premises (a) has access to and (b) is using superfast broadband; what the total number of premises is; and what proportion of that total has been provided with access to superfast broadband under the Government's rollout programme.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 611","611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347743","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the (a) major road network and (b) rail network that is a complete not-spot.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 612","612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347744","2015-06-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of the procurement of the A400M.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 552","552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347745","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many libraries (a) closed and (b) switched to being run by volunteers between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 613","613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347746","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many public libraries do not have free wifi; by what date he plans that all public libraries will have access to free wifi; and what the cost to his Department will be of providing all remaining libraries with free wifi.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 614","614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347747","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the liquidation of the Museums, Libraries and Archives Council will be complete.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 615","615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347748","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on local authority funding for sports and cultural facilities.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 616","616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347749","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to consult on business rate relief for local newspapers.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 617","617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347750","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to introduce age-restriction controls for websites.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 618","618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347751","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will introduce an independent regulator for website age-restriction controls in 2015.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 619","619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347752","2015-06-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many premises are in complete not-spots.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 620","620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347753","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what factors he took into account in deciding the timing of the announcement of the closure of accident and emergency services at King George Hospital.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 558","558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347754","2015-06-04","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken pursuant to the meeting between the Isle of Wight Clinical Commissioning Group and the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Care Quality on 18 March 2015.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 643","643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347755","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals in England have used stereotactic radiosurgery (SRS) to treat both benign and malignant tumours of the brain; which of those hospitals have contracts with NHS England to deliver SRS; and which non-contracted hospitals have received payment from NHS England for delivering SRS since 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 634","634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347756","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England will publish the results of its review of stereotactic radiosurgery; and for what reasons NHS England is not publishing all submissions to that review.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 635","635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347757","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timescale is for the withdrawal of pacer trains from rail services in East Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 636","636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347758","2015-06-03","Department for Transport","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what level of investment his Department plans to make in rail services in East Durham over the next five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 637","637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347759","2015-06-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports have been prepared in the last 12 months on joint US-UK technical co-operation on nuclear arms control; and what circulation has been arranged for each such report.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 533","533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347760","2015-06-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK-US authentication workshops have been held since 2000 in the (a) UK and (b) US under the auspices of the 1958 US-UK Mutual Defense Agreement on atomic energy matters; which British experts participated in each such workshop; and what public version reports have been published on each such workshop.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 534","534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347761","2015-06-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the purposes, progress and funding of the joint UK-US Portal to Monitor Arms Control.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 535","535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347762","2015-06-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information the Atomic Weapons Establishment has received from Brookhaven National Laboratory under the 1958 US-UK Mutual Defense Agreement on atomic energy matters on the Controlled Intrusiveness Verification Technology  measurement system since January 2007.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 536","536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347763","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what organisation his Department has awarded contracts or sub contracts to for the provision of welfare to work programmes in Scotland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 548","548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347764","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Yemen on the safety of British citizens in that country.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 549","549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347765","2015-06-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Burma regarding implementation of the Declaration on Preventing Sexual Violence in the last six months; and at what levels these discussions took place.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 583","583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347766","2015-06-03","Home Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost is of policing the badger cull.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 591","591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347767","2015-06-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many badgers have been culled; and what the cost to the public purse is of the badger cull.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 592","592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347768","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 60 of background briefing notes to the Queen's Speech 2015, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) British citizens living overseas for more than 15 years in the (i) EU and (ii) rest of the world and (b) EU citizens resident in the UK who will not be eligible to vote in the upcoming European Union referendum.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 553","553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347769","2015-06-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has received a report from Ray Noble relating to the Mozes community energy co-operative.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 554","554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347770","2015-06-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the working paper by Jeronim Capaldo on the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership, entitled European Disintegration, Unemployment and Instability.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 622","622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347771","2015-06-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of research commissioned by the European Commission into the economic effect of the Trans-Atlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 623","623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347772","2015-06-04","Attorney General","2015-06-01","To ask the Attorney General, whether criminal investigations are being carried out to determine whether UK financial institutions have been used to carry out illegal transactions related to FIFA.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 626","626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347773","2015-06-03","Attorney General","2015-06-01","To ask the Attorney General, what discussions (a) Ministers in his Department and (b) the Serious Fraud Office have had with (i) the Swiss authorities and (ii) the US Justice Department about the investigation of fraud, racketeering and money laundering at FIFA.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 625","625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347774","2015-06-04","Attorney General","2015-06-01","To ask the Attorney General, when the Serious Fraud Office first became aware that UK financial institutions may have been used to carry out illegal transactions relating to FIFA; what action was taken; and when he was first made aware of this possibility.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 627","627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347775","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the Care Quality Commission publishes more of its inspection reports on time.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 633","633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347776","2015-06-03","Department of Health","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NHS England has to reduce the cost of agency staff to the NHS in England.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 632","632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347777","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions (a) Ministers in his Department and (b) the Financial Services Authority have had with the (i) Swiss authorities and (ii) US administration's Justice Department on the investigation of fraud, racketeering and money laundering at FIFA.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 640","640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347778","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to discover whether UK financial institutions have been used to carry out illegal transactions related to FIFA.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 641","641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347779","2015-06-04","HM Treasury","2015-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Financial Services Authority was informed of the possibility of UK financial institutions being used to carry out illegal transactions related to FIFA; what steps the Authority took to investigate; and when he was informed about that possibility.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 642","642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347780","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of comments by a spokesman from her Department in Schools Week of 29 May 2015 that there is a technicality which needs resolving in the process of applying for an Academy Order on behalf of a federated school; and if she will revise Regulation 46 of the School Governance (Federations) (England) Regulations 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 648","648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347781","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Academy Orders made on behalf of a federated school have been made on or after 1 September 2012; and how many such applications (a) she has approved and (b) have an Academy Agreement in place.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 649","649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347782","2015-06-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of the following households in the London Borough of Southwark with (a) dependent children, (b) a single person, (c) pensioners, (d) one or more people employed and (e) a disabled member are claiming housing benefit.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 644","644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347783","2015-06-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will bring forward proposals to allow 16 and 17 year olds to vote in any referendum on EU membership.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 645","645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347784","2015-06-04","Department for Education","2015-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information is sought from the applicant for an Academy Order for a federated school to ensure that it complies with Regulation 46 of the School Governance (Federations) (England) Regulations 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 646","646"
