"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92642","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in how many immigration or asylum cases during the last 12 months where a person has claimed to be under the age of 18, that person has been treated as an adult on the basis that their appearance or demeanour strongly suggests they are significantly over the age of 18.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 210006","210006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92643","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued as part of Operation Skybreaker on effective engagement with community groups, faith leaders, local police safer neighbourhood panels, safer neighbourhood boards and others.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209313","209313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92644","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will discuss with the (a) Minister for Women and Equalities and (b) the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government the implications for the Government's policies on the protection of victims of domestic violence of the recommednations of the Women's Aid SOS campaign on new models of funding for the national network of specialist women's refuges; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 210005","210005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92645","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Graduate Entrepreneur Tier 1 visas have been issued for use by each UK higher education institution since April 2013.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209966","209966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92646","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money her Department has generated through immigration control in each of the last five years; and what proportion of such money was (a) retained by her Department and (b) returned to HM Treasury in each such year.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209955","209955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92647","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, under what criteria it was decided to deploy Operation Skybreaker in Brent, Ealing, Greenwich, Newham and Tower Hamlets; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209310","209310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92648","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many sponsors of Tier 2 general visas in each region and constituent part of the UK have been issued with such visas in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209962","209962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92649","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Tier 2 visas were granted to people who were previously students in the UK in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209961","209961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92650","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which countries the UK has readmission agreements for the return of nationals found illegally in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209994","209994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92651","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the sale of illegal tobacco on the trade of legitimate tobacconists and newsagents.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209891","209891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92652","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who entered the UK in 2014 and claimed to have been trafficked were subsequently found to have no leave to remain in the UK.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209279","209279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92653","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of money spent by her Department on victim support is spent on direct theraupeutic counselling to victims of abuse.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209995","209995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92654","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many British children were recorded as having been trafficked for sex and labour in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209897","209897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92655","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spends annually to fund victim support.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209996","209996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92656","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal immigrants without passports from (a) India, (b) Bangladesh, (c) Pakistan and (d) China have been re-documented in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209993","209993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92657","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what average length of time it currently takes for documentation necessary to return home to be issued to an illegal immigrant found in the UK without such documentation who is from (a) India, (b) Bangladesh, (c) Pakistan, (d) Nigeria and (e) China.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209992","209992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92658","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Lancashire were wrongfully arrested in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209942","209942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92659","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will establish dedicated entry gates for Commonwealth citizens at UK ports and airports.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209925","209925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92660","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 October 2014, Official Report, column 464W, on creative industries, how many employers in (a) advertising, (b) architecture, (c) the art and antiques market, (d) crafts, (e) design, (f) designer fashion, (g) film and video, (h) interactive leisure software, (i) music, (j) performing arts, (k) publishing, (l) software and computer services and (m) television and radio currently hold a Tier 2 general sponsor license.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209948","209948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92661","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints have been received on the charge for using the 101 non-emergency police number in the last three years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209287","209287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92662","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the 101 non-emergency police number on the number of non-essential 999 calls.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209288","209288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92663","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 667W, on official visits, what domestic visits she has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209268","209268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92664","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the money spent by her Department on direct therapeutic counselling of victims of abuse is spent on people now adults and whose abuse occurred in their childhood.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209997","209997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92665","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps are being taken to reduce the administration associated with police stop and search procedures.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209273","209273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92666","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many alleged victims of human trafficking have been deported since 1 May 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209272","209272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92667","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who has been appointed to the role of Designate Anti-Slavery Commissioner, advertised in August 2014; and on the basis of what job description they were appointed.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209271","209271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92668","2014-10-17","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that asylum seekers receive face-to-face advice when making or following up a complaint.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209289","209289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92669","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests for sexual offences have been made in Barnsley East constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209813","209813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92670","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to enable interested parties to have access to appropriately redacted Project Licence applications made under the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 prior to approval being given for consultation on scientific and animal welfare grounds; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209976","209976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92671","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of progress on meeting (a) the Millennium Development Goal of ensuring all children receive an education by 2015 and (b) other Millennium Development Goals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209822","209822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92672","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the UK upholds its international obligations to prevent the illegal trade of ivory and rhino horns.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209928","209928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92673","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to prevent famine in South Sudan.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209989","209989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92674","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of EU aid to Angola is spent on improving the food supply.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209282","209282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92675","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful prosecutions there have been for the illicit sale of tobacco in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209893","209893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92676","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 19 January 2010 to Question 311921, what recent reports he has received about the progress of the Solicitors Regulation Authority investigation into Burges Salmon LLP.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209890","209890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92677","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will assess the merits of the court system assuming responsibility for reviewing power of attorney judgements.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209861","209861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92678","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary and the Secretary of State for Defence on the embargo on Government-held files relating to the Guildford Four.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209905","209905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92679","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what procedures are in place for power of attorney to be removed from a person who has abused that power; and what procedures there are for people to complain about someone who has joint power of attorney who may be abusing the fund.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209849","209849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92680","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many agency staff have been employed by the South Yorkshire Probation Service in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209814","209814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92681","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will assess the merits of requiring people applying for power of attorney to attend court and swear on oath to uphold power of attorney conditions.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209850","209850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92682","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the current national population is of (a) HM prisons and (b) privately-run prisons.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209853","209853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92683","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on consultancy staff by the South Yorkshire Probation Service in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209815","209815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92684","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what comparative assessment he has made of the incidence of bullying in prisons run by (a) HM Prison Service and (b) private sector bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209851","209851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92685","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what oversight mechanisms are in place to ensure that prisoners in private prisons are safe from violence.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209852","209852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92686","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what safeguards are in place to prevent misuse of funds when a (a) single and (b) joint power of attorney is obtained.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209854","209854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92687","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what programmes are in place to help prisoners to become digitally literate.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209841","209841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92688","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2014, Official Report, column 425, on sentencing: females, which offences were classed within the miscellaneous crimes against society offence class for which female offenders aged 18 and over were sentenced to immediate custody for a first offence in England and Wales in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013; and how many people of each such ethnicity served what sentence length under each such offence.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209947","209947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92689","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average hourly rate is paid to (a) external solicitors and (b) Treasury Solicitor staff working on developing the residence test for legal aid.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209963","209963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92690","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy that any contracts signed with private sector companies until May 2015 for the provision of probation services do not contain clauses that provide for compensation for loss of profit in the event of the termination of those contracts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209296","209296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92691","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours have been spent by (a) external solicitors, (b) external barristers, (c) Treasury Solicitor staff and (d) Treasury Counsel engaged by his Department for advice on the legal aid residence test policy.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209964","209964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92692","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much in total has been paid to (a) each external solicitor, (b) each external barrister, (c) Treasury Solicitor staff and (d) Treasury Counsel engaged by his Department for advice on the policy development of the legal aid residence test.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209965","209965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92693","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will bring forward legislative proposals to tighten minimum safety requirements for HGVs by removing exceptions for construction vehicles.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209960","209960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92694","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on road safety through driver distraction of inbuilt, in-car infotainment systems; and what plans he has to regulate the use of such systems.","Biography information for Mrs Linda Riordan","Mrs Linda Riordan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209299","209299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92695","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on fatigue in long distance coach and lorry drivers.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209957","209957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92696","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on the adequacy of the current Highway Code lane restrictions on heavy goods vehicles on motorways with over three lanes.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209278","209278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92697","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Exceptional Hardship Scheme applications in each constituency (a) were approved, (b) were rejected and (c) are still under consideration in the last year.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209304","209304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92698","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what organisations or individuals were specifically invited to respond to his Department's consultation on changing merchant shipping regulations: weighing of goods vehicles and emergency equipment lockers, published on 16 June 2014; and when he plans to publish his Department's response to that consultation.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209303","209303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92699","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department is undertaking on the road safety effects of advanced driver assistance systems; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect in the UK of decisions to deploy such systems in commercial and public sector fleets made in other countries.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209277","209277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92700","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, columns 661-2W, on official visits, what domestic visits he has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209267","209267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92701","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the EY Transport, Telecommunications and Energy Council decision to adopt a general approach, what provisions of the draft directive on the cross-border exchange of information on road traffic offences the UK will have to implement by 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209306","209306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92702","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost was of relocating HS2 Ltd from Eland House, Bressenden Place to 1 Canada Square.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209305","209305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92703","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time taken was by drivers to travel (a) clockwise and (b) anti-clockwise between junction 29 and junction 2 of the M25.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209885","209885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92704","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current average waiting time is for personal independence payments from application to the date of award.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209886","209886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92705","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current average waiting time is for applicants for personal independence payments for a face-to-face assessment if required.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209887","209887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92706","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of cases in which disability living allowance payments have ceased before personal independence payment is received; and what steps he is taking to ensure that people are not left without either benefit.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209866","209866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92707","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that work search and work availability requirements under universal credit are applied in a way that respects the particular training, skills, work patterns and  job search methodology of performers.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209838","209838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92708","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what pilot or feasibility studies were carried out by his Department on managing the change over from disability living allowance to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209868","209868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92709","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will introduce sector-specific guidance to his Department's decision-makers on work patterns and job searching in the entertainment industry.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209836","209836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92710","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have had their employment and support allowance stopped due to delays in processing medical certificates in (a) Bishop Auckland constituency and (b) Spennymoor in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209835","209835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92711","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the ratio of doctor health care professionals to nurse or physiotherapist health care professionals currently carrying out work capability assessments is in (a) Hemsworth constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209865","209865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92712","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that private sector job search providers delivering under universal credit are aware of the typical work patterns and job search methodology of performers in the entertainment industry.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209837","209837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92713","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many enquiry forms for assessment for personal independence payments have been sent to people in (a) Hemsworth constituency and (b) the UK; and how many of those who have applied have been waiting for a decision for longer than 26 weeks.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209867","209867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92714","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Dartford constituency and (b) Kent have claimed jobseeker's allowance in each of the last five years; and if he will estimate the annual cost to the public purse of such claims.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209883","209883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92715","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the value of help for funeral costs is calculated; what factors those calculations take into account; and what account is taken in such calculations of the income of the next of kin.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209863","209863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92716","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to monitor the average costs of funerals; and what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of funeral payments to meet the average cost of a funeral.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209862","209862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92717","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will extend the start-up period under universal credit for entertainers and other groups whose chosen profession has a large lead-in time before they have an established business.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209834","209834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92718","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the (a) demand and (b) waiting times for work capability assessments conducted by a (i) doctor and (ii) nurse or physiotherapist health care professional.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209864","209864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92719","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when universal credit will begin accepting claims for families.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209324","209324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92720","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have met the (i) First or Deputy First Minister for Northern Ireland or officials from their departments and (ii) Northern Ireland Minister for Social Development in the last two years.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209999","209999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92721","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will begin to publish the quarterly surveys carried out by the Child Maintenance Options Service on the child maintenance outcomes for parents who use its service.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209906","209906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92722","2014-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason a benefit sanction was imposed on Mr David Clapson in June 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209266","209266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92723","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average length of time is taken to process medical certificates of people in (a) Bishop Auckland constituency and (b) Spennymoor.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209845","209845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92724","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are currently waiting to see a doctor health care professional for the purposes of a work capability assessment in (a) Hemsworth constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209855","209855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92725","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are currently waiting to see a nurse or physiotherapist health care professional for the purposes of a work capability assessment in (a) Hemsworth constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209856","209856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92726","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what limit his Department has set on waiting times for work capability assessments; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure this limit is not exceeded.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209857","209857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92727","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in the London Borough of Brent have been subject to the household benefit cap for (a) less than one month, (b) between one and three months, (c) between three and six months and (d) more than six months.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 210007","210007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92728","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment cases are in payment; and how many applications for such payments have been made.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 210018","210018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92729","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the processing times are for an appeal where an individual is contesting a personal independence payment decision from the start of the appeal to its conclusion.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 210019","210019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92730","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each Welsh parliamentary constituency will no longer receive the Independent Living Fund from 30 June 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209958","209958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92731","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average time was taken between an employment and support allowance applicant undergoing a work capability assessment and advice being submitted to a decision maker for decision in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209953","209953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92732","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the causes of delays by his Department in providing paperwork to the HM Courts and Tribunal Service; and what guidance his Department issues on the number of times an appeal case may be delayed before it is deemed unreasonable.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 210020","210020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92733","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeal cases are delayed because his Department has not submitted the required information to HM Courts and Tribunal Service in time.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 210021","210021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91881","2014-10-14","Attorney General","2014-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many stalking and harassment cases were recorded in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209434","209434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91882","2014-10-14","Attorney General","2014-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to the Law Officers' Departments are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209462","209462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91883","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2014 to Question 206108, whether UK law and export control regulations place any restrictions on allowing companies which have previously been ejected from the DSEI arms fair for selling equipment which could be used for torture to exhibit at future DSEI events in London, or whether that decision is entirely a matter for Clarion Events.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209456","209456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91884","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many small and medium-sized businesses in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England and Wales have (i) applied for and (ii) been granted loans by the British Business Bank in the last year.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209441","209441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91885","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the current pricing structure of cross-border mail between the UK and Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209442","209442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91886","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2014 to Question 207177, who is responsible for drafting the text of the prudential carve-out in the Trade in Services Agreement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209430","209430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91887","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2014 to Question 207177, whether the text of the prudential carve-out will be published before the Trade in Services Agreement is finalised.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209431","209431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91888","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2014 to Question 207177, how the text of the prudential carve-out in the Trade in Services Agreement will be agreed.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209432","209432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91889","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the proposed changes to the disabled students' allowance on the participation in higher education of students with high needs.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209505","209505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91890","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in Barnsley East constituency are enrolled in adult skills sessions.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209561","209561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91891","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total volume was of mail (a) dispatched to and (b) received from the Republic of Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209570","209570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91892","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many projects in Barnsley East constituency have (a) applied for funding, (b) been selected to receive funding and (c) received final offer letters from the Regional Growth Fund in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209384","209384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91893","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department plans to have with representatives of the Chinese government about innovation, manufacturing or investment in the next year.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209373","209373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91894","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Chinese government about innovation, manufacturing and investment.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209377","209377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91895","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of people earning less than the national minimum wage in the care sector in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209411","209411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91896","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many employers in the care sector who failed to comply with the national minimum wage have been named to date.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209412","209412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91897","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he was consulted on the decision to restrict the last collection time at Royal Mail post boxes to 9 am; and how many post boxes across the country are subject to this decision.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209447","209447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91898","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change there has been in median gross weekly pay for (a) men and (b) women in Barnsley East constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209397","209397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91899","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people owned their own home in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209401","209401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91900","2014-10-15","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) England and Wales were paid the minimum wage in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209568","209568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91901","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209463","209463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91902","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will wait until the Government publishes its response to the Review of Property Conditions in the Private Rented Sector before taking forward the Deregulation Bill.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209508","209508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91903","2014-10-15","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the UK voted against UN General Assembly Resolution A/68/L.57/Rev. 1, Towards the establishment of a multilateral legal framework for sovereign debt restructuring processes.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209454","209454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91904","2014-10-15","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claimants of (a) child tax credit and (b) working tax credit reported a change of circumstances in 2013-14; in how many such cases payments were suspended while the change of circumstances was processed; and what the average amount per claimant was of such suspended payments.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209533","209533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91905","2014-10-15","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209496","209496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91906","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid in corporation tax by businesses registered in Barnsley East constituency in each of the last five years; and what proportion of that tax was paid by small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209388","209388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91907","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to National Minimum Wage Compliance in the Social Care Sector published by HM Revenue and Customs in November 2013, what steps he has taken since that date to tackle low pay in the social care sector.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209409","209409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91908","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley local authority, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) England have completed the purchase of a house through the Help to Buy scheme.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209383","209383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91909","2014-10-15","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he has taken to attract inward investment and create jobs in the tourism sector.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209448","209448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91910","2014-10-15","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he has taken to support tourism in the devolved administrations.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209435","209435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91911","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to National Minimum Wage Compliance in the Social Care Sector published by HM Revenue and Customs in November 2013, what proportion of workers found to be receiving less than the national minimum wage were women.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209410","209410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91912","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of workers in the care sector on zero hours contracts in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion of such workers were women.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209408","209408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91913","2014-10-14","Church Commissioners","2014-09-26","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, how many food banks are supported by the Church of England in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and Humber in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209393","209393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91914","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the proposed minimum space standards for adoption can be applied by local authorities to prior approval requests for conversions of offices to residential accommodation.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209429","209429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91915","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many businesses in (a) Barnsley East constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber have qualified for the full business rates discount to date.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209387","209387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91916","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many affordable homes have been built in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley local authority area, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209389","209389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91917","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in Barnsley East constituency were homeless in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209402","209402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91918","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of completed new houses were built on brownfield land in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209511","209511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91919","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what criteria his Department used to determine which councils received an (a) increase and (b) decrease in funding in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209518","209518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91920","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effects of the proposed changes to funding for Birmingham Council on deprivation and poverty in Birmingham.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209519","209519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91921","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209464","209464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91922","2014-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether there will be a consultation by the Homes and Communities Agency over plans for the Venture Quays building in East Cowes.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209576","209576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91923","2014-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what basis the Homes and Communities Agency determined the market value of the Venture Quays site in East Cowes.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209577","209577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91924","2014-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Homes and Communities Agency has made of the (a) value to the Isle of Wight economy of and (b) number of jobs protected or created by expressions of interest in the Venture Quays site in East Cowes.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209578","209578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91925","2014-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps Ofcom is taking to encourage new entrants in the market for mobile and fixed wireless services in the London area.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209499","209499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91926","2014-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many households in (a) England and Wales, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) Barnsley East constituency do not have access to (i) a fibre optic broadband connection, (ii) high speed broadband and (iii) the internet.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209400","209400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91927","2014-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Arts Council has spent per head of population in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209390","209390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91928","2014-10-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with children's privacy campaigners.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209438","209438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91929","2014-10-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Lord Chancellor and Secretary of State for Justice and the Secretary of State for Education about the protection of children from unwarranted press intrusion.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209439","209439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91930","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Ministerial Working Group announced in the White Paper National Security Through Technology, Cmd 8278.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209329","209329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91931","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness of the arrangements and (b) capacity to provide international training by the UK armed forces to support exporters of defence equipment.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209330","209330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91932","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the new approach towards engagement with overseas-based defence suppliers set out in the White Paper National Security Through Technology, Cmd 8278.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209331","209331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91933","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's communication to industry of its future requirements.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209332","209332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91934","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who the heads are of the (a) Saudi Arabia National Guard Communications Project and (b) Ministry of Defence Saudi Armed Forces Project.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209358","209358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91935","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the new Type 26 frigates will be named after cities; and when he plans to announce the names of the frigates.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209509","209509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91936","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209465","209465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91937","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the UK has to include gender advisory capacity as part of its recognised military capability; whether the UK plans to contribute any full-time gender advisers to (a) the rapid reaction force announced by the Prime Minister on 8 September 2014 and (b) other NATO operations and missions in the near future; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209498","209498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91938","2014-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2014, Official Report, column 687W, on Afghanistan, whether his Department has undertaken any comparative research on the civilian casualty rates of remotely piloted air systems, fast jet and rotary wing platforms.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209531","209531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91939","2014-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2014, Official Report, column 687W, on Afghanistan, what proportion of battle damage assessments are carried out from the air.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209532","209532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91940","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK plans to (a) bid to fill any of the nine gender adviser positions that are part of the Afghanistan Operation Resolute Support Force structure and (b) appoint an O7 rank or above to lead the Gender Advisory Unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209500","209500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91941","2014-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2014, Official Report, column 525W, on intelligence services, whether the principles published in the Consolidated Guidance to Intelligence Officers and Service Personnel 2011 are applied to assessment of the risk that shared data may be used for targeted killing by foreign states.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209540","209540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91942","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the Scout vehicles built under contract by General Dynamics will be built in that company's (a) UK factories and (b) Spanish factories; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209501","209501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91943","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2014, Official Report, column 359W, on unmanned air vehicles, whether there is a designated UK officer at Creech airbase responsible for ensuring that embedded UK officers comply with Joint Services Publication 398.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209502","209502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91944","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, column 245W, on Afghanistan, whether UK personnel embedded at Creech airbase have flown US aircraft outside Afghan airspace in support of NATO International Security Assistance Force missions in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209504","209504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91945","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2014, Official Report, column 359W, on unmanned air vehicles, whether an endorsed Rules of Engagement profile has been applied to a designated area that includes any part of Pakistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209503","209503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91946","2014-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 9 April 2014 to Question 194985, whether the Government has had any discussions with the government of Afghanistan about future basing of UK unmanned aircraft systems in that country since April 2014.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209575","209575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91947","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any UK Reapers or personnel from the UK Reaper Force Squadron have moved from Afghanistan to Qatar or another location in the Gulf in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209545","209545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91948","2014-10-15","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who the Chairs of Kings Free Schools and Academies Trust have been since its establishment; and on what dates each such Chair took took up and relinquished office.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209567","209567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91949","2014-10-15","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to her Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209495","209495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91950","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start centres there were in South Yorkshire in (a) May 2010 and (b) September 2014.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209398","209398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91951","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the recommendation of the World Health Organisations' European report on preventing child maltreatment, published in 2013, that national governments adopt a preventative and public health approach to child maltreatment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209349","209349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91952","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what total amount her Department spent on all measures aimed at tackling child abuse and neglect in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209347","209347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91953","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of professional social work placements required in 2013-14, excluding the Step Up programme, in order to meet the needs of social workers in training.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209350","209350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91954","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what total amount her Department spent on primary preventative measures aimed at preventing child abuse and neglect in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209348","209348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91955","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on extending ring-fencing of the five to 16 years schools budget to include funding for young people aged 16 to 18.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209381","209381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91956","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the average cost to a family of supporting a young person aged 16 to 18 in full-time education or training.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209382","209382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91957","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship starts there were in each academic year in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley local authority area, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) England since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209392","209392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91958","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people in Barnsley East constituency have received Green Deal funding.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209396","209396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91959","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria are applied by his Department to determine whether new electricity transmission cables should be laid below or above ground.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209337","209337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91960","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether customers who refuse to have a smart meter will be expected to pay for manual meter readings.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209352","209352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91961","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many smart meters have been installed.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209353","209353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91962","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many of the smart meters installed are SMETS 2 compliant.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209354","209354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91963","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209466","209466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91964","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department has taken to encourage schools to install solar panels since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209516","209516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91965","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to her Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209467","209467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91966","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to preserve stocks of sea bass in UK waters.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209565","209565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91967","2014-10-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) her Department, (b) the Biotechnology and Biological Sciences Research Council and (c) other public bodies spent on each category of agricultural research in each of the last 10 years; what estimate she has made of public expenditure on research and development on agriculture as a proportion of total spending on research and development in each of those years; and what proportion of publicly-funded research and development related to agriculture is (i) basic and (ii) applied research.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209587","209587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91968","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes to the best practice guidelines for shooting badgers made between 2013 and August 2014 on public safety.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209380","209380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91969","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of increased ties between North Korea, Iran, Venezuela, Cuba, the People's Republic of China and the Russian Federation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209370","209370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91970","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Iranian government on its approach to lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people; what recent representations he has received on the treatment of lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209365","209365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91971","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of UN sanctions in deterring Iran's nuclear programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209366","209366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91972","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the nuclear weapons capability of (a) North Korea and (b) Iran.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209369","209369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91973","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assurances about the death penalty the Government sought from the authorities in (a) California, (b) Dubai and (c) Japan before permitting UK police forces and other agencies to support criminal investigations in those jurisdictions; and if he will publish those assurances.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209436","209436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91974","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the government of India about the trial of Mr Richard de Wit.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209335","209335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91975","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether staff from his Department have attended the trial of Mr Richard de Wit in Kashmir.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209336","209336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91976","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote dialogue between the People's Republic of China and Taiwan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209360","209360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91977","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received from groups representing the Tibetan people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209361","209361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91978","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the UK's relations with (a) Cuba, (b) North Korea, (c) Venezuela, (d) Russia and (e) Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209367","209367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91979","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the range of the ballistic missiles possessed by (a) North Korea and (b) Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209368","209368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91980","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received from pro-democracy groups in Hong Kong; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209362","209362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91981","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has participated in discussions on resolving tensions between the People's Republic of China and Japan over the Senkaku Islands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209363","209363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91982","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from groups in the People's Republic of China about human rights in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209364","209364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91983","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Israeli government following the announcement of further settlement building on Palestinian land in the West Bank.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209579","209579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91984","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had with EU counterparts following the Israeli government's announcement of further settlement building on Palestinian land in the West Bank.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209580","209580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91985","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the principles published in the Consolidated Guidance to Intelligence Officers and Service Personnel 2011 are applied to assessment of the risk that shared data may be used for targeted killing by foreign states.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209539","209539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91986","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209468","209468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91987","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports his Department has received on the situation of the kidnapped schoolgirls in Nigeria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209525","209525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91988","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the NHS of treating obesity and its related diseases in (a) Harlow constituency, (b) Essex and (c) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209528","209528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91989","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many young poeple have been referred to specialist paediatric psychiatric services in Harlow in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209510","209510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91990","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions were issued for antidepressant medication in Harlow constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209512","209512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91991","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209469","209469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91992","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of section 39 of the Immigration Act 2014 on the level of immunisations amongst children against the infectious diseases listed in Schedule 1 of The National Health Services (Charges to Overseas Visitors) Regulations 2011.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209460","209460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91993","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS England internal taskforce currently reviewing specialised commissioning plans to seek input from internal stakeholders.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209453","209453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91994","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to enhance preparedness to isolate and contain instances of Ebola in England.","Biography information for Duncan Hames","Duncan Hames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209459","209459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91995","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) young people under 18 and (b) children under five have been admitted to hospital after ingesting methadone or buprenorphine in the last five years; and how many such ingestions were fatal.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209451","209451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91996","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had in the last six months with NHS England's Executive Team on the review of specialised commissioning.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209452","209452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91997","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what monitoring is undertaken to ensure that prescribers carry out adequate safeguarding of children living in families in which someone is undergoing opioid substitution therapy.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209450","209450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91998","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills and Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer on homecare workers receiving less than the minimum wage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209597","209597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91999","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the effect of charging VAT on the installation, repair or replacement of heating systems in the homes of people with (a) Parkinson's and (b) other progressive conditions in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209564","209564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92000","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to improve awareness of dementia among (a) NHS staff, (b) GPs and (c) the public.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209356","209356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92001","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on implementing the recommendations of the Independent Palliative Care Funding Review, published on 1 July 2011.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209379","209379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92002","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve (a) the diagnosis of dementia and (b) treatment for people with dementia.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209355","209355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92003","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost-per-quality adjusted life year threshold used by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and its predecessor bodies to determine the cost-effectiveness of medicines has been in each year since 1999; and what that threshold has been in each year in real terms (a) using the gross domestic product deflator, (b) adjusting for health pay and price inflation and (c) adjusting for the health component of the consumer price index.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209346","209346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92004","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's Child Protection Information Sharing project, what guidance will be given to NHS staff on sharing information with relevant local authorities, police forces and care homes.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209338","209338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92005","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for people with mental health problems in Birmingham to access talking therapies after being referred by a doctor.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209339","209339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92006","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to inform young people aged 16 and over about joining the bone marrow donor register.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209340","209340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92007","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department and (b) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence is taking to ensure that patients have access to drugs and treatments for ultra-rare diseases.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209351","209351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92008","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents have been recorded by the NHS of Citalopram leading to the deterioration of a patient's health in the last five years.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209345","209345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92009","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which clinical commissioning groups and local authorities did not submit a compliant application to the Better Care Fund by the deadline of 19 September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209343","209343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92010","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any changes proposed as a result of the current review of the commissioning of specialised services will be subject to public consulation.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209449","209449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92011","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints he received about waiting times to see a GP in the Barnsley East primary care trust area in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209395","209395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92012","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of the illegal use of controlled substances in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and Humber, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Barnsley East constituency.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209391","209391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92013","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many domestic violence arrests were made in Barnsley East constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209399","209399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92014","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in Barnsley East constituency were prosecuted for breaches of anti-social behaviour orders in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209394","209394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92016","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of correspondence from hon. Members to each UK Visas and Immigration regional account management team was responded to within the 20 working day target in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209546","209546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92017","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of couples who have polygamous marriages in (a) England and (b) Wales where one partner is married to another in a legal ceremony and where at least one partner is simultaneously also married to a third party in an unregistered religious ceremony.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209506","209506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92018","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether education will be a priority sector for her Department's disability framework; and whether her Department's country offices will recieve training and support to implement the framework.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209513","209513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92019","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is taking steps to ensure that extractive industry transparency is a key component of the forthcoming G20 Anti-Corruption Action Plan.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209515","209515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92020","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds on a proposed lending programme to Argentina from the World Bank.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209517","209517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92021","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to her Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209470","209470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92022","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many infrastructure projects worth more than 1 million funded by her Department were undertaken by (a) UK and (b) US companies in each of the last four years; and what the value was of each such project.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209574","209574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92023","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many of the tenders issued by her Department for infrastructure projects were awarded to UK companies in each of the last four years.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209571","209571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92024","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many tenders her Department has issued for infrastructure projects worth more than 1 million in each of the last four years.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209572","209572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92025","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with the South African government about the integration of black and minority ethnic groups into the wealth creating process; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209359","209359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92026","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to increase the availability of contraceptives to prevent the spread of HIV/AIDS as part of her Department's programme in South Africa; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209413","209413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92027","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the success of her Department's efforts to combat HIV/AIDS in Africa through the aid progamme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209414","209414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92028","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in what country the fund managers for the CP3 Asia Fund will be based.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209376","209376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92029","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many  freedom of information requests his Department received in each month since January 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209375","209375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92030","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many freedom of information requests received by his Department were (a) responded and (b) not responded to within the statutory period in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209378","209378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92031","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of confiscation of (a) knives, (b) firearms and (c) other weapons in (i) magistrates and (ii) Crown courts there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209372","209372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92032","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of confiscation of (a) mephedrone, (b) BZP, (c) spice and (d) ketamine there were in prisons in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209374","209374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92033","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of confiscation of legal highs there were in prisons in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209371","209371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92034","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) permanent full-time staff, (b) temporary full-time staff, (c) part-time staff, (d) agency staff and (e) consultants have been recruited by the National Probation Service headquarters since 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209422","209422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92035","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) permanent full-time, (b) temporary full-time and (c) agency staff have been recruited by each National Probation Service Division since 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209415","209415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92036","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many marriages have taken place in which one of the couple was in prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209416","209416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92037","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many marriages between two prisoners have taken place in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209417","209417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92038","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil partnerships have taken place in which one partner was in prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209418","209418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92039","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2014 to Question 199480, on what occasions prisons have used detached duty staff from other establishments since 1 April 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209423","209423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92040","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) permanent, (b) temporary, (c) agency staff and (d) consultants there were at the headquarters of the National Probation Service on 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209421","209421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92041","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil partnerships between two prisoners have taken place in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209419","209419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92042","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) permanent, (b) temporary and (c) agency staff there were in each division of the National Probation Service on 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209420","209420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92043","2014-10-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2014 to Question 202937, when he expects to provide the information requested.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209446","209446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92044","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff of each grade were used as part of the detached duty arrangements in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209424","209424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92045","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff of each grade were available for detached duty arrangements in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209425","209425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92046","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons have received how many detached duty staff of each grade in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209426","209426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92047","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on accommodation and subsistence for prison officers providing detached duty in prisons in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209427","209427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92048","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many responses to freedom of information requests have been subject to an internal review in each year since 2010; and how many such requests initially refused were subsequently granted in each of those years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209428","209428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92049","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of changes in collection rates of fines set by the criminal courts since HM Revenue and Customs data relating to defaulters was made available to court staff.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209357","209357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92050","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copy of the most recent National Offender Management Service report on homicides in prisons.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209341","209341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92051","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many murders there have been in English prisons in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209342","209342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92053","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officers in his Department received on the court reform programme.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209520","209520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92054","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209471","209471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92055","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the court reform programme has considered the case for improvement work at Sunderland Court.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209521","209521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92056","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria his Department's court reform programme uses to determine the case for court rebuilding works; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209522","209522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92057","2014-10-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department last reviewed the laws protecting children from press intrusion; and if he will commission such a review before the end of the present Parliament.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209534","209534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92058","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding his Department has provided for the upkeep of and refurbishment of courts that are over 100 years old in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209523","209523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92059","2014-10-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of violence were recorded in (a) magistrates' courts and (b) Crown courts in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209535","209535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92060","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the capital building budget is for the court reform programme.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209524","209524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92061","2014-10-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of (a) adult and (b) youth secure estate establishments have imams.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209538","209538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92062","2014-10-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of trial outcomes were (a) effective, (b) ineffective and (c) cracked in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209536","209536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92063","2014-10-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison chaplains there are of each faith.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209537","209537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92064","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how old each magistrates' court is.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209526","209526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92065","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will list the initiatives taken by the UK while holding the Chair of the UN Security Council; and which such initiatives received support from the full Security Council.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209566","209566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92066","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the annual savings to the public purse from the phasing out of the paper vehicle tax disc; and what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of changes in the level of vehicle tax evasion since that phasing out.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209563","209563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92067","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of motorists who will be unaware of changes to the requirement to display a tax disc in a vehicle after 1 October 2014.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209530","209530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92068","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve road safety on the A12 from Junction 28 of the M25 to Ipswich.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209573","209573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92069","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with particular reference to autism, what information his Department holds on the changes to Blue Badge criteria in Scotland and Wales; and whether he plans to bring forward proposals for similar changes in England.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209569","209569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92070","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road traffic accidents there were on the A12 from Junction 28 of the M25 to Ipswich in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209598","209598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92071","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure motorists are aware of changes to the requirements to display a tax disc in a vehicle from 1 October 2014.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209529","209529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92072","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the requirement to display a tax disc in a vehicle on (a) enforcement activities, (b) the number of untaxed cars on the road and (c) the level of vehicle tax evasion in the UK in 2014-15.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209514","209514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92073","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has undertaken on driverless cars and their effect on the HS2 Business Case.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209461","209461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92074","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average increase was in (a) regulated and (b) unregulated passenger rail fares for (i) peak and (ii) off peak rail services provided under franchise by London and South East Railway Limited in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209433","209433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92075","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the written Statement of 11 September 2014, by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Transport, Official Report, column 42WS, on rail franchising (Southeastern), what contractual guarantees have been secured from Govia on (a) on-station, (b) on-train and (c) ticket office staffing levels during the term of the directly awarded franchise.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209333","209333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92076","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the written Statement of 11 September 2014, by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Transport, Official Report, column 42WS, on rail franchising (Southeastern), what contractual guarantees have been secured from Govia about training for existing staff during the term of the directly awarded franchise.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209334","209334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92077","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of safe, affordable areas for heavy goods vehicle drivers to park and rest at night and access to toilet facilities and good quality food; and if he will take steps to ensure that capacity in such facilities is in line with demand.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209344","209344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92078","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average (a) regulated and (b) unregulated passenger rail fare was for (i) peak and (ii) off peak rail services provided under franchise by London and South East Railway Limited in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209404","209404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92079","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the all day public performance measure (PPM) of punctuality was for London and South East Railway Limited's franchised rail passenger services in each month since March 2010; and what the national average PPM was in each such month.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209405","209405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92080","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the negotiations between his Department and London and South East Railway Limited for the direct award of the South Eastern rail passenger franchise to June 2018.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209406","209406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92081","2014-10-14","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the levels of (a) total public subsidy, (b) premium payments to his Department from the train operator, (c) Network Grant, (d) passenger revenue and (e) revenue support during the life of the contract directly awarded by his Department to London and South East Railway Limited for rail passenger services on the South Eastern line to June 2018.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209407","209407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92082","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Barnsley East constituency have found employment lasting more than six months through the Work Programme since its inception; how many such people were aged under 24; and how many such people had a disability.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209403","209403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92083","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Barnsley East constituency have received the new enterprise allowance; how many such people have since claimed (i) jobseeker's allowance, (ii) income support as a lone parent and (iii) employment and support allwance; and how many of those were (A) women and (B) men.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209386","209386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92084","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) South Yorkshire, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber and (d) the UK received council tax benefit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209385","209385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92085","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have taken part in the mandatory attendance centre pilot announced in October 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209445","209445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92086","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2014 to Question 207491, whether second attachment fees will be paid for people transferred from Newcastle College to new providers; and whether the cost of those fees will be borne by his Department.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209437","209437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92087","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of applicants for employment and support allowance in (a) England and Wales, (b) South Yorkshire, (c) Barnsley Local Authority and (d) Barnsley East constituency who do not receive a decision within the target waiting time of 35 days; and what steps he is taking to expedite such applications.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209440","209440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92088","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people referred to the Help to Work scheme are (a) on a community work placement, (b) attending the jobcentre every day and (c) receiving intensive jobcentre support since April 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209443","209443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92089","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people referred to the Help to Work scheme who (a) participated in a community work placement, (b) attended the jobcentre every day and (c) received intensive jobcentre support have moved into employment since April 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209444","209444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92090","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on sanctioning employment and support allowance claimants who have a mental health condition or learning difficulty.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209457","209457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92091","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether jobseeker's allowance claimants who are required to attend the jobcentre daily will be provided with help for their travel expenses.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209458","209458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92092","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2014 to Question 207549, if his Department will publish the number of employment and support allowance claims which are awaiting action by (a) a work capability assessment provider and (b) his Department.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209455","209455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92093","2014-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) workers in agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209497","209497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92094","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many requests for a departure direction were made in the latest period for which figures are available; and how many were granted.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209527","209527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92095","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of British state pensioners live outside the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209507","209507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92096","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many unresolved Child Support Agency, Child Maintenance and Enforcement Commission and Child Maintenance Service cases have been closed or are inactive, without a request from the claimant.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209542","209542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92097","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of Child Support Agency, Child Maintenance and Enforcement Commission and Child Maintenance Service cases involving self-employed non-resident parents result in disputes between the parties over alleged earnings.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209543","209543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92098","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of Child Support Agency, Child Maintenance and Enforcement Commission and Child Maintenance Service cases involve self-employed non-resident parents.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209544","209544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92099","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proof of self-employed earnings is required for child support cases; and whether he is satisfied with those requirements.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209541","209541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92100","2014-10-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of British state pensioners living overseas do not receive annual pension increases.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209562","209562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92101","2014-10-14","Attorney General","2014-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many officials in the Law Officers' Departments of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209473","209473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92102","2014-10-14","Attorney General","2014-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, what targets have been set for the release of The Law Officers' Departments' material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in The Law Officers' Departments are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209604","209604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92103","2014-10-14","Attorney General","2014-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many officials in the Law Officers' Departments completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209643","209643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92104","2014-10-14","Attorney General","2014-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many officials in the Law Officers' Departments who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209621","209621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92105","2014-10-14","Attorney General","2014-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many companies have been prosecuted for not paying minimum wage in each of the last nine years.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209683","209683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92106","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Government's proposed changes to the disabled students' allowances on the drop-out rate of students who will no longer be eligible for funding.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209677","209677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92107","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Government's proposed changes to the disabled students' allowances on the employment prospects of students who will no longer be eligible for funding.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209678","209678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92108","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consultation his Department undertook with universities, providers of support and students prior to the announcement of 7 April 2014 on proposals to change the disabled students' allowance.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209679","209679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92109","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2014, Official Report, column 730W, on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership, who carried out the independent analysis; what their terms of reference were; and what the cost of that analysis was.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209676","209676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92110","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials in his Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209472","209472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92111","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials in his Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209620","209620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92112","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what targets have been set for the release of his Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in his Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209603","209603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92113","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials in his Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209642","209642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92114","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Government's representative at the meeting of the EU Trade Policy Committee on 12 September 2014 supported the European Commission's inclusion of the Investor-State Dispute Mechanism in the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209693","209693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92115","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that ethnic minority applicants for an apprenticeship are fairly treated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209721","209721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92116","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) female, (b) disabled, (c) black and minority ethnic and (d) other people have started on a traineeship in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209717","209717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92117","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that companies providing homecare services pay at least the minimum wage.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209744","209744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92118","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what service the British Business Bank offers to the manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209752","209752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92119","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Business Taskforce's publication Cut EU Red Tape, published in October 2013, what steps have been taken to reduce the barriers to overall competitiveness.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209792","209792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92120","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Business Taskforce's publication Cut EU Red Tape, published in October 2013, what steps have been taken to reduce the barriers to starting a company and employing people.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209793","209793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92121","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Business Taskforce's publication Cut EU Red Tape, published in October 2013, what steps have been taken to reduce the barriers to expanding a business and employing people.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209794","209794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92122","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Business Taskforce's publication Cut EU Red Tape, published in October 2013, what steps have been taken to reduce the barriers to trading across borders and employing people.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209795","209795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92123","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage the uptake of (a) e-commerce and (b) other online tools among (i) businesses and (ii) consumers.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209776","209776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92124","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Business Taskforce's publication Cut EU Red Tape, published in October 2013, what steps have been taken to reduce the barriers to innovation.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209796","209796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92125","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the adult skills budget has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209797","209797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92126","2014-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to ensure that the forthcoming UK-Colombia bilateral investment treaty includes adequate protection for UK investors.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209779","209779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92127","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many death certificates HIV has been mentioned in each year since 1985.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209702","209702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92128","2014-10-15","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions in (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013 and (d) 2014 to date the Charity Commission (i) opened and (ii) did not open an inquiry into a charity after having engaged with that charity on a regulatory issue.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209725","209725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92129","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) deaths and (b) injuries occurred as a result of road traffic accidents on the A12 from Junction 28 of the M25 to Ipswich in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209599","209599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92130","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials in his Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209644","209644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92131","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what targets have been set for the release of his Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in his Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209605","209605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92132","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Big Society community organisers living in Barnsley East constituency have been trained to date.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209560","209560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92133","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials in his Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209474","209474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92134","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials in his Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209622","209622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92135","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of changes in median household real income before housing costs in Barnsley East constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209559","209559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92136","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials in his Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209492","209492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92137","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials in his Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209661","209661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92138","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials in his Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209639","209639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92139","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the tax gap was in each of the last nine years; and what estimate he has made of the tax gap that was due to tax evasion in each of the last nine years.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209681","209681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92140","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs spent on dealing with tax evasion in each of the last nine years.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209682","209682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92141","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what targets have been set for the release of his Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in his Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209618","209618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92142","2014-10-15","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what changes there have been in the number of households in each constituency in Northern Ireland in receipt of child benefit between January 2009 and January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209592","209592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92143","2014-10-15","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what change there has been in the number of people paying income tax at the (a) basic and (b) higher rate in each constituency in Northern Ireland between January 2009 and January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209593","209593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92144","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the report by Nevin Associates Ltd, entitled The fiscal impact of lower VAT rates on visitor accommodation and attractions in the United Kingdom: Final Report, published in July 2014, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the conclusion on page 29 of that report that a reduction in VAT on tourism would generate a positive net present value of 3.9 billion for his Department over the course of 10 years and would create 123,000 jobs in the tourism sector.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209740","209740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92145","2014-10-14","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the incidence of financial crime in the Cayman Islands.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209742","209742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92146","2014-10-15","HM Treasury","2014-09-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of homecare workers in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Warrington who are being paid less than the minimum wage because they are not being paid for travel time between appointments.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209743","209743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92147","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reason Birmingham council's funding in 2015 will be reduced by a greater amount than the national average reduction.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209745","209745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92148","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many officials in his Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209475","209475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92149","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what targets have been set for the release of his Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in his Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209606","209606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92150","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many officials in his Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209645","209645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92151","2014-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many officials in his Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209623","209623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92152","2014-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials in his Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209624","209624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92153","2014-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials in his Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209646","209646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92154","2014-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what targets have been set for the release of his Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in his Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209607","209607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92155","2014-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials in his Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209476","209476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92156","2014-10-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that newspapers only publish photographs of children when they have parental consent to do so.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209781","209781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92157","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British service personnel are serving in (a) Afghanistan and (b) other countries.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209788","209788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92158","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library a copy of (a) the current text of the 1958 UK-US Mutual Defence Agreement and its annexes, as subsequently amended since the Agreement originally entered into force and (b) any amendments to the Agreement and its annexes that the Government proposes for when they are renewed.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209761","209761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92159","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current mission tasking is for HMS Defender; and how long she has been assigned to this task.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209756","209756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92160","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what UK armed forces assets and personnel are currently based at al-Udeid.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209757","209757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92161","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 14 January 2013, Official Report, column 601W, on Trident, how much his Department has spent to date on studies of whether to refurbish or replace the existing Trident warhead design.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209770","209770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92162","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the maximum daily sortie rate is for six Tornado fast jets configured for ground attack missions.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209758","209758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92163","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what UK armed forces (a) assets and (b) personnel will be used in attacking ISIL targets in Iraq.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209771","209771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92164","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the planned out-of-service date is for Tornado fast jets.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209759","209759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92165","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what UK armed forces assets and personnel are stationed in Iraq.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209772","209772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92166","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether forward air controllers are directing airstrikes in Iraq.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209773","209773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92167","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the UK's role is in Arctic security; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209767","209767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92168","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether targeting intelligence gathered by (a) Rivet Joint and (b) ISTAR assets has been provided to allies for targets within Syria.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209755","209755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92169","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the titles and objectives are of all enhanced collaborations under way under the auspices of the UK-US Mutual Defence Agreement.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209762","209762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92170","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of posts at the Ministry of Defence Police complement at the Atomic Weapons Establishment, Burghfield, are currently vacant.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209763","209763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92171","2014-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the organisations interested in leasing the Sea Monitoring Centre site at Marchwood in New Forest East constituency have been issued with his Department's invitation to negotiate; and what his policy is on the circumstances under which issues of commercial confidentiality inhibit revealing information.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209791","209791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92172","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2014, Official Report, column 222W, on the Atomic Weapons Establishment, what the conclusions and recommendations are of the investigation into shortfalls in policing standards and neglect of duties at the Atomic Weapons Establishment, Burghfield; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the report of the investigation.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209764","209764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92173","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officials in his Department work exclusively on Arctic issues; and what the (a) title of position and (b) grade is of each such official.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209765","209765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92174","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in how many training exercises HM Armed Forces have participated in (a) Norway, (b) Finland, (c) Sweden, (d) the US, (e) Canada, (f) Greenland, (g) Russia and (h) Iceland; how many personnel took part in each exercise; and how many such exercises were held (i) above and (ii) below the Arctic Circle.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209766","209766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92175","2014-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost was to his Department of Operation Patwin, by (a) humanitarian supplies delivered by ship, (b) non-physical humanitarian support and (c) all other costs.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209714","209714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92176","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what targets have been set for the release of his Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in his Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209608","209608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92177","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officials in his Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209477","209477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92178","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Service Complaints have been made in the Royal Navy Reserve in the last three years; and how long it has taken to investigate each case.","Biography information for Mr Charles Kennedy","Mr Charles Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209553","209553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92179","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officials in his Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209647","209647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92180","2014-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officials in his Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209625","209625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92181","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many officials in her Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209626","209626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92182","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many officials in her Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209648","209648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92183","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to encourage schools to instal solar panels; and whether she plans to allow schools to borrow money to finance the purchase of solar panels.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209685","209685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92184","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to help schools invest in solar panels.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209684","209684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92185","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many professional social work places will be required by the Step Up and Frontline social work training programmes in 2014-15.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209551","209551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92186","2014-10-15","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what organisations she has approved to be potential sponsors of future sponsored academies in Sheffield.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209594","209594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92187","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of professional social work placements provided by (a) local authorities, (b) third sector organisations and (c) other bodies in 2014-15.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209550","209550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92188","2014-10-15","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department received an application from the Kings Free Schools and Academies Trust to establish a new free school in Darnall, S9 in Sheffield; and if she will publish it.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209601","209601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92189","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department made of the effect of the Step Up and Frontline social work training programmes on the availability of social work placements for other trainees.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209549","209549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92190","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many professional social work placements were provided by (a) local authorities, (b) third sector organisations and (c) other bodies in 2013-14.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209548","209548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92191","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of professional social work placements required to meet the needs of social workers in training, other than in the Step Up programme, in 2014-15.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209547","209547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92192","2014-10-15","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department received an application from the Kings Free Schools and Academies Trust to establish a new free school in Milner Fields in Bradford.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209600","209600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92193","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many officials in her Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209479","209479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92194","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary school and (b) infant school pupils in (i) Barnsley East constituency, (ii) South Yorkshire, (iii) Yorkshire and the Humber and (iv) the UK received free school meals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209556","209556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92195","2014-10-14","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what targets have been set for the release of her Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in her Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209609","209609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92196","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the budget of the employer ownership fund has been in each year since 2011; what proportion of that budget has been spent in each such year; and how many apprenticeship starts have been created in each such year.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209719","209719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92197","2014-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department has spent on adult skills in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209751","209751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92198","2014-10-15","Department for Education","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the planned local completion site visit to Vaughan School in the hon. Member for Harrow West's constituency by the Education Funding Agency on 22 September 2014 was cancelled at less than a working day's notice; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209790","209790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92199","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what targets have been set for the release of his Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in his Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209610","209610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92200","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many officials in his Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209480","209480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92201","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, under what timetable electrical interconnectors will be allowed to participate in the capacity market auctions on an equal basis with domestic generators.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209674","209674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92202","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions officials in his Department have had with the European Commission on the principle of electrical interconnectors being allowed to bid in the new capacity market auctions.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209675","209675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92203","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many officials in his Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209649","209649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92204","2014-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many officials in his Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209627","209627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92205","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many officials in her Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209628","209628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92206","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many officials in her Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209650","209650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92207","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many officials in her Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209481","209481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92208","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 1 September 2014 to Question 206013, what the reasons are for the delay in publication of the study commissioned by her Department.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209555","209555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92209","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many of the species in the UK's Overseas Territories have had their conservation status assessed.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209783","209783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92210","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Foreign and Commonwealth Office publication, Overseas Territories, Security, Success and Sustainability, published in November 2012, what progress her Department has made on each of the environmental Priorities for Action in that paper; and what further steps she plans to take to deliver those priorities.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209787","209787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92211","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will designate sea bass as a species which can only be fished during recreational angling.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209741","209741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92212","2014-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2014 to Question 193828, what steps she has taken to ensure the accuracy of data collected by the Food Standards Agency on mis-stunning of animals for slaughter.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209694","209694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92213","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from the government of Ukraine on membership of the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209673","209673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92214","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will make recommendations to the UN Universal Periodic Review of the human rights record of Iran to encourage that state to cease its policies of persecution of members of the Bah community; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209697","209697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92215","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts on defence of the eastern borders of the Alliance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209692","209692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92216","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contribution the UK plans to make to the Universal Periodic Review of Iran's human rights record due to be considered by the UN Human Rights Council on 27 October 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209698","209698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92217","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received on human rights in Belarus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209668","209668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92218","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Uzbekistan on reports of human rights abuses.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209713","209713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92219","2014-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what military training the UK armed forces have (a) received from and (b) provided to the Israeli Defence Force in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209806","209806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92220","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made in bringing to justice those responsible for the destruction of Malaysian Airlines flight MH17 on 17 July 2014.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209807","209807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92221","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to raise the issue of forced repatriations to North Korea with the Chinese government.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209778","209778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92222","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials there were in the UK delegation to the 2013 Arctic Council Ministerial meeting in Kiruna, Sweden; and what the (a) title of position and (b) grade was of each such official.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209769","209769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92223","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials in his Department work exclusively on Arctic issues; and what the (a) title of position and (b) grade is of each such official.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209768","209768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92224","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the goals of the UK are, as an Arctic Council observer state, for the Canadian chairmanship of the Arctic Council from 2013 to 2015.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209760","209760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92225","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions officials in his Department have had with the Chinese government on upholding the religious freedom of Christians in the Wenzhou, Zhejiang Province.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209774","209774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92226","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will review the decision to move the BBC Tamil Service from London to Delhi; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209789","209789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92227","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials in his Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209482","209482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92228","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the government of Israel about potential breaches of international law by that country.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209581","209581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92229","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what personnel and frontline fighter aircraft from Middle Eastern States will participate in the coalition against ISIL.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209591","209591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92230","2014-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had with the Bangladeshi Prime Minister on (a) international recognition of her recent election, (b) alleged human rights violations preceding that election and (c) the promotion of free, fair and inclusive elections in Bangladesh in future during her visit to the UK in January 2014.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209602","209602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92231","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the authorities in South Sudan over the need for the NGO Bill in that country to ensure that citizens and civil society organisations can engage in humanitarian activity, enjoy freedom of association and use monitoring and accountability systems in accordance with the general assumptions of the New Deal.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209554","209554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92232","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with African Union governments to end the recruitment of children into the national armed forces of countries where this practice takes place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209687","209687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92233","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with his counterparts in the EU to ensure that the upcoming parliamentary elections in Moldova are free and fair; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209669","209669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92234","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials in his Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209651","209651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92235","2014-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials in his Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209629","209629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92236","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials in his Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209631","209631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92237","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials in his Department of each (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209484","209484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92238","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials in his Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209653","209653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92239","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the development of a patient experience survey for HIV has been considered as part of NHS England's review of patient experience.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209664","209664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92240","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for publishing the outcomes of NHS England's review of patient experience.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209665","209665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92241","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to raise awareness of the Middle East Respiratory Syndrome coronavirus.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209666","209666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92242","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the effect of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence's three-month end-of-life threshold on the number of treatments for advanced pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209582","209582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92243","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what targets have been set for the release of his Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in his Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209611","209611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92244","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the level of demand for haematology services in (a) England and (b) the North East of England; and what steps he is taking to ensure that resources are able to meet demand.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209775","209775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92245","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the haematology department at North Tees and Hartlepool NHS Foundation Trust is retained and that vacancies at that trust are filled; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209785","209785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92246","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to address the problem of obesity arising from the over-concentration of hot-food outlets.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209784","209784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92247","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of haematology specialists working in (a) England and (b) the North East; and how that number has changed since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209782","209782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92248","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to address the problem of fast food takeaways near schools having a damaging effect on the health of children.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209805","209805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92249","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of vacant and unfilled posts for haematology specialists working in (a) England and (b) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209780","209780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92250","2014-10-14","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions officials in his Department have had with their counterparts in the Home Department about steps to identify and segregate travellers entering the UK who may be carrying a virulent communicable disease.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209703","209703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92251","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library data on (a) the number of people diagnosed with HIV, (b) the number of HIV deaths and (c) HIV prevalence in England since 1985.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209726","209726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92252","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2014 to Questions 201000, 201001 and 201002, what progress has been made on the Healthcare Quality Improvement Partnership  one year feasibility study to inform the development of a future national clinical audit of HIV and sexually transmitted infections; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209727","209727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92253","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2014 to Questions 201000, 201001 and 201002, what the timetable is for the publication of the Healthcare Quality Improvement Partnership one year feasibility study to inform the development of a future national clinical audit of HIV and sexually transmitted infections.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209728","209728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92254","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library data on the change in the number of patients with HIV living in England since 1985.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209729","209729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92255","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adverse drug reaction reports have been received relating to the use of (a) nicotine replacement therapies, (b) varenicline and (c) e-cigarettes by school children.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209711","209711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92256","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how many fatalities have been reported in other countries arising from the use of (a) nicotine replacement therapies, (b) varenicline and (c) e-cigarettes.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209710","209710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92257","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress NHS England has made on its review of patient experience; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209709","209709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92258","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many drugs were approved by the Cancer Drugs Fund and subsequently rejected by NICE in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209753","209753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92259","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of progress by the British Standards Institute towards the creation of a publicly available specification for e-cigarettes.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209746","209746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92260","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to reply to the letter of the hon. Member for Bishop Auckland dated 26 August 2014.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209718","209718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92261","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission a review of the application process for Parkinson's disease Duodopa treatment, with a view to simplifying and speeding up applications.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209724","209724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92262","2014-10-15","Department of Health","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2014 to Question 206979, with reference to the finding that the number of serious suspected adverse drug reaction reports arising from use of nicotine replacement therapies and varenicline is significantly higher than that arising from the use of e-cigarettes, if his Department will require more prominent health warnings to be displayed for those drugs than for e-cigarettes.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209716","209716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92263","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has put in place to ensure that UK Border staff identify and segregate travellers suspected of entering the UK whilst carrying a virulent communicable disease.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209708","209708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92264","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which UK police forces have (a) provided and (b) received training from Israeli police or security services in each of the last five years; and what that training consisted of in each such case.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209808","209808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92265","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officials in her Department of what (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209485","209485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92266","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets have been set for the release of her Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in her Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209612","209612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92267","2014-10-15","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the extent of official corruption in Brazil; what the implications of such corruption are for the inclusion of Brazil on the list of safe countries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209586","209586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92268","2014-10-14","Cabinet Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of polygamous marriages in (a) England and (b) Wales.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209680","209680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92269","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officials in her Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209654","209654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92270","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officials in her Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209632","209632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92271","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many officials in her Department who received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark under the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System (i) had a disability, (ii) worked full-time and (iii) worked part-time in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209633","209633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92272","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many officials in her Department completed the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System in 2013-14; how many and what proportion of those officials received the (a) exceeded, (b) met and (c) must improve performance mark; and how many and what proportion (i) did and (ii) did not qualify for a bonus under that process.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209655","209655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92273","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to begin providing foreign aid to Venezuela; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209688","209688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92274","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many dedicated air bridges her Department has established for the movement of personnel and equipment for the Ebola crisis within West Africa.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209590","209590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92275","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of isolation centres with sustained support to deal with the Ebola outbreak in West Africa.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209589","209589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92276","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what targets have been set for the release of her Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in her Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209613","209613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92277","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many officials in her Department of what (a) gender, (b) ethnicity and (c) age received the Civil Service Employment Policy Performance Management System's (i) exceeded, (ii) met and (iii) must improve performance mark in 2013-14.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209486","209486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92278","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to announce future programme partnership funding from her Department from 2015-16 onwards.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209786","209786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92279","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to (a) increase humanitarian aid and (b) provide development assistance for state building in Iraq; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209747","209747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92280","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the implications of UK military action in Iraq for UK humanitarian aid to the victims of the conflict in Syria; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209748","209748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92281","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what new initiatives her Department plans to take in partnership with the governments of countries in Africa and Asia to combat Islamist extremism.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209749","209749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92282","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of persistent malnutrition on the population of the Democratic People's Republic of North Korea; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209690","209690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92283","2014-10-14","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will review CDC investment policy to determine if the requirement that investee companies have non-discrimination policies in place effectively addresses the inclusion of disabled people as employees, customers and service users.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209700","209700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92284","2014-10-15","Department for International Development","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many people were assisted by Operation Patwin; what costs were incurred by her Department in supporting Operation Patwin, by category of expenditure; and if she will publish her Department's learning review of that operation.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209715","209715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92285","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many companies have been successfully taken to tribunal by employees for not complying with minimum wage legislation in each of the last nine years.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209707","209707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92286","2014-10-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what meetings he has had with children's privacy campaigners in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209798","209798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92287","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost of the court at Shire Hall in Bedford has been, by major cost category, in each of the last (a) 12 months and (b) five years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209777","209777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92288","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what targets have been set for the release of his Department's material to the National Archives; what progress has been made in meeting those targets; and how many staff in his Department are engaged in reviewing records for that purpose.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209614","209614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92289","2014-10-14","Home Office","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in (a) Barnsley East constituency and (b) South Yorkshire have been arrested for possession of (i) Class A, (ii) Class B and (iii) Class C drugs in the last year; and what steps her Department is taking to rehabiliate people convicted of drug-related offences.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209557","209557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/92290","2014-10-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have received legal aid in each constituency in South Yorkshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209558","209558"
