"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051447","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 2.2.3 of the draft Domestic Abuse Bill, what the timetable and scope will be of the Whole Housing Partnership Project pilot.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214658","214658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051448","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of claimants who will undergo natural migration from legacy benefits into universal credit in 2019 in (a) the Vale of Clwyd, (b) Wales, and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214510","214510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051449","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many mobile phones have been seized in prison establishments in (a) 2015-6, (b) 2016-7 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214508","214508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051450","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2001 to Question 144163 on Irish Sea (Pollution), if he will list the pollution incidents involving discharges above 0.01 tonnes in the Irish sea in each of the last 4 years, with the (a) date of the incident, (b) the size of the incident, (c) the name of the company that reported the spill and (d) the name of the company responsible in each case.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214511","214511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051451","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the removal of bursaries for undergraduate nurses on the number of people choosing to study nursing.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214460","214460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051452","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to fill staff vacancies in the NHS.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214461","214461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051453","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the disabilities that students who qualified for the Disabled Students Allowance in each year since 2014-15.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214462","214462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051454","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the Government's timescale is for (a) acknowledging the concluding observations from the UN convention on the rights of persons with disabilities and (b) responding to that convention's recommendations.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214659","214659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051455","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help improve relations between Eritrea and Ethiopia.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214458","214458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051456","2019-02-04","Cabinet Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions the Reducing Regulation Committee has met; what decisions have flowed from those meetings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214449","214449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051457","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on the ongoing conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214588","214588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051458","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the change has been in the number of (a) looked after children and (b) children who were in foster placements between 2013 and 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214518","214518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051459","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the recommendations on improving fire safety tests made by the Association of British Insurers will be incorporated into any future test his Department commissions the Building Research Establishment to undertake to check the fire safety of building materials.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214559","214559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051460","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps his Department is taking to ensure the protection of the Kurdish population in (a) Syria and (b) Northern Iraq.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214589","214589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051461","2019-02-04","Home Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 4 January 2019 to Questions 205232, 205233 and 205235, if he will take steps to ensure timely visa application processes for invited participants in Parliamentary events.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214528","214528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051462","2019-02-04","Treasury","2019-01-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the contribution of the Chief Secretary to the Treasury of 29 January 2019, Official Report, Column 637, to which (a) initial and (b) final financial year she referred to in relation to official estimates of the change in the number of children in absolute child poverty.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214529","214529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051463","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Bahrain after the recent verdict against Nabeel Rajab and the hunger strike of Ali AlHajee and Naji Fateel while in Bahraini prison.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214590","214590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051464","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of UK-trained oversight bodies in Bahrain in investigating allegations of the torture of prisoners while in custody.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214591","214591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051465","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the further testing to check the fire safety of building materials that his Department is commissioning with the Building Research Establishment will include a large-scale test on standard high-pressure laminate cladding and plastic foam insulation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214560","214560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051466","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to Saudi counterparts on the humanitarian situation in Yemen and access for humanitarian supplies from the port of Hodeidah.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214592","214592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051467","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the further testing to check the fire safety of building materials that his Department is commissioning with the Building Research Establishment will include a large-scale test on fire retardant high-pressure laminate cladding and plastic foam insulation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214561","214561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051468","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January 2019 to Question 205785 on New Monks Farm: Construction, whether he has issued a holding direction to delay Adur District Council's granting of planning permission for the Monks Farm development; and what the timeframe is for determining whether to call in that decision.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214448","214448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051469","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2019 to Question 212352 on Mental Health Inter-ministerial Group, on what date the inter-ministerial group for mental health will next meet.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214539","214539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051470","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the further testing to check the fire safety of building materials his Department is commissioning with the Building Research Establishment will include a large-scale test on zinc composite material cladding with a polyethylene core and plastic foam insulation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214562","214562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051471","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 211319 on Accident and Emergency Departments, what mechanisms his Department will put in place to ensure a higher share of NHS funding is allocated to geographies with high levels of health inequality.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214540","214540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051472","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the further testing to check the fire safety of building materials his Department is commissioning with the Building Research Establishment will include a large-scale test on external wall insulation incorporating Expanded Polystyrene insulation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214563","214563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051473","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the delay to the proposed doubling of places on the PrEP Impact Trial on his Department's commitment to ending new HIV transmissions by 2030.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214541","214541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051474","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to introduce the doubling of places on the PrEP Impact Trial.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214542","214542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051475","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, by what date the proposed doubling of places on its PrEP Impact Trial will be achieved.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214543","214543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051476","2019-02-04","Cabinet Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2019 to Question 204484 on Interserve and the Answer of 24 January 2019 to Question 204485, for what reason the information provided does not include the number of meetings held by (a) Ministers in his Department and (b) Cabinet Office Markets and Suppliers team with representatives of Interserve plc in 2018.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214537","214537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051477","2019-02-04","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she last chaired round table talks between the leaders of the main political parties in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214519","214519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051478","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Abbott FreeStyle Libre flash glucose monitoring devices and sensors local clinical commissioning groups prescribed in (a) 2017-18 (b) 2018-19 to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214470","214470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051479","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to recoup the cost of regulating drones from their users or manufacturers.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214515","214515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051480","2019-02-04","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans she has to appoint an independent mediator to chair discussions with the main political parties in Northern Ireland to restore devolution.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214520","214520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051481","2019-02-04","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she plans to further reduce the salaries of Members of the Legislative Assembly in the continued absence of a functioning Northern Ireland Assembly.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214521","214521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051482","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average length of time taken is for the FreeStyle Libre sensors to be issued to people with diabetes through the NHS.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214471","214471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051483","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what is the cost to the NHS is of each FreeStyle Libre flash glucose monitoring device.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214472","214472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051484","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the technical feasibility of requiring drones to be fitted with geofencing software which prevents their operation around certain sites including airports, high-population density areas and national security sites.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214516","214516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051485","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations his Department has made to the pharmaceutical company Abbott on the availability of FreeStyle Libre being issued to people with Type 1 diabetes from April 2019.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214473","214473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051486","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2018 to Question 122517 on children: social services, whether the six local authorities named in that answer are still exempt from statutory guidance.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214567","214567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051487","2019-02-04","Treasury","2019-01-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 28th January to Question 210062 on Loans: Mozambique, what information UK-based lenders to foreign governments have to disclose and to whom under UK prudential disclosure requirements.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214660","214660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051488","2019-02-04","Treasury","2019-01-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January to Question 210062 on Loans: Mozambique, who conducts the independent assessment of compliance with those requirements; and where those assessments are published.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214661","214661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051489","2019-02-04","Treasury","2019-01-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January to Question 210062 on Loans: Mozambique, whether those prudential disclosure requirements were complied with in the case of the $2 billion of loans from UK-based banks to three state owned companies in Mozambique.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214662","214662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051490","2019-02-04","Home Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January to Question 210062 on Loans: Mozambique, whether UK authorities plan to take action under the 2010 Bribery Act in relation to the allegations of K-based banks role in the $2 billion of loans to three state-owned companies in Mozambique.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214663","214663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051491","2019-02-04","Cabinet Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2019 to Question 211108, whether Interserve FM ltd are contractually required to pay their employees the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214493","214493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051492","2019-02-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to his oral contribution of 29 January 2019, Official Report, column 755, on the EU (Withdrawal) Act 2018, which experts he proposes to consult on the technical points raised in the proposals of the hon. Member for North West Hampshire; and if he will make a statement on their response.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214481","214481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051493","2019-02-04","Department for International Development","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2019 to Question 211150 on Department for International Development: contracts, whether cleaning staff paid the London Living Wage or the National Living Wage as appropriate refers to the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214494","214494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051494","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2019 to Question 211667 on private rented housing: housing benefit, how many local authorities in the Liverpool City Region have imposed fines of £30,000.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214495","214495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1051495","2019-02-04","Home Office","2019-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Iranian citizens able to apply for visas to visit the UK at the Visas and Immigration Centre in Tehran.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214474","214474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050003","2019-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many accidents have occurred at funfairs and amusement parks in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213367","213367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050025","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing an inland checking facility to ensure the smooth functioning of Portsmouth International Port in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213448","213448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050060","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the results of the study entitled Characterisation of elemental in PM2.5 in a medium sized Swedish city dominated by a modern waste incinerator plant published in X-Ray Spectrometry in 2006 which showed that between 17 per cent and 32 per cent of PM2.5 emissions landed within 1km of the site.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213204","213204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050098","2019-01-30","Department for International Development","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the number of international aid workers operating in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213217","213217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050099","2019-01-30","Department for International Development","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the number of international aid workers killed while operating in Yemen in each year since 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213218","213218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050104","2019-01-30","Cabinet Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average annual earnings were of the bottom five deciles in Leicester in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213221","213221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050147","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of lowering import tariffs on agricultural products on the domestic food and drink industry in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213404","213404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050317","2019-01-29","Treasury","2019-01-29","What fiscal steps he is taking to support the high street.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Jones","Mr Marcus Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908879","908879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050318","2019-01-29","Treasury","2019-01-29","What progress he has made on reducing the amount of income tax that people pay.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908882","908882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050319","2019-01-29","Treasury","2019-01-29","What discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on reviewing the adequacy of funding for social security benefits.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908885","908885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050320","2019-01-29","Treasury","2019-01-29","What discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on the personal finances of claimants.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908886","908886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050323","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to tackle the spread of disinformation on social media.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908935","908935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050364","2019-01-29","Treasury","2019-01-29","What discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Scotland on providing additional support for low-income households in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908888","908888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050375","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether financial assistance is available for students from the lowest-income households who qualify for the disabled student allowance to help with the £200 required to access specialist equipment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213927","213927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050376","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with mental health issues receive support to access social housing.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213928","213928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050377","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations his Department has made to foreign Governments on ending the practice of fur farming.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214043","214043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050378","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of availability of the 2018-19 seasonal flu vaccine.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214044","214044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050379","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to include community groups in the planned consultation on a deposit return scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214045","214045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050380","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of measles there have been since 7 July 2018.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214046","214046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050381","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Government plans to respond to its consultation entitled Ending the sale of energy drinks to children, published on 30 August 2018.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214047","214047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050382","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many investigations resulting from information being passed to the police by Action Fraud have taken place in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213951","213951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050383","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2018 to Question 182114 on Universal Credit, what definition of genuine hardship is used by her Department to determine whether exceptional circumstances apply to a claim for an advance payment of (a) legacy benefits, (b) personal independence payment and (c) universal credit.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213954","213954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050384","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timeframe is for the publication of the recommendations of the consultation entitled, Leasehold home ownership: buying your freehold or extending your lease, published by the Law Commission in September 2018.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213955","213955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050385","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2018 to Question 174628 on Leasehold, what the timeframe is for bringing forward the legislative proposals to tackle unfair leasehold practices for existing leaseholders.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213956","213956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050386","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many responses the Law Commission received from existing leaseholders to the consultation entitled, Leasehold home ownership: buying your freehold or extending your lease, published in September 2018.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213957","213957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050387","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2018 to Question 203779 on Disabled Students Allowances, what the timetable is for the (a) commencement and (b) conclusion of that research project.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213929","213929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050388","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of Santander's proposal to close 140 branches in the UK on people's access to money.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214048","214048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050389","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support British citizens driving in EU countries after 29 March 2019 who do not hold a green card.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214040","214040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050390","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the decrease in the pass rate for GCSE English and maths resits between 2017 and 2018.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213952","213952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050391","2019-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many checks for radioactive contamination are carried out on each person after they have left the reactor compartment tunnel at HM Naval Base Clyde, Faslane.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214023","214023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050392","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the White Paper entitled The UK's future skills-based immigration system, published in December 2018, Cm 9722, published on 19 December 2018, what plans are in place for conversations with people and businesses over the next twelve months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214041","214041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050393","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with unions representing rail staff on safeguarding (a) staff and (b) passengers at stations between Blackpool North and South and Preston.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213953","213953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050394","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to support community energy generation after the closure of the feed-in-tariff scheme in March 2019.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214049","214049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050395","2019-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January 2019 to Question 205862 on HMS Mersey: English Channel, whether he has received confirmation from the Home Office that they will be funding the cost of HMS Mersey's deployment to the English Channel.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214009","214009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050396","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the BBC on the Corporation increasing the number of programmes it broadcasts on television to appeal to people in the 15-30 demographic.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214014","214014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050397","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to prevent social media platforms accessing individual's personal data and internet history for the purposes of generating advertising revenue.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214015","214015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050398","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to improve mobile phone coverage in Northern Ireland for those who cannot receive any phone reception.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214016","214016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050399","2019-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with NATO on the UK’s role in EU defence programmes after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214017","214017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050400","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has plans to prohibit the use of sound-producing anti-loitering devices without a licence.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214050","214050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050401","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the accuracy of advice given to claimants by Jobcentre staff on moving on to universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213884","213884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050402","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the revenue accrued as a result of the 15 pence per minute charge for a 101 telephone call is retained by his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214051","214051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050403","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of the 15 pence per minute 101 call charge on the finances of lower-income families.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214052","214052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050404","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many herds in (a) Area 01, Gloucestershire and (b) Area 02, West Somerset badger control areas were tested with interferon gamma in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213909","213909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050405","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many interferon gamma tests were conducted on herds in (a) Gloucestershire and (b) Somerset in each year since 2010; and how many cattle in each of those herds tested positive.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213910","213910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050406","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many herds in Area 03, Dorset (03) badger control areas were tested with interferon gamma in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213911","213911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050407","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many interferon gamma tests were conducted in each herd in Dorset in each year since 2012; how many positive cattle in each herd tested positive.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213912","213912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050408","2019-02-04","Department for International Development","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has provided humanitarian assistance to Brazil as a result of the collapse of the damn in Minas Gerais.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213969","213969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050409","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 20610 on Road Traffic Control: West Sussex, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government to prevent a scheme from going ahead in the event that the WCHAR's findings indicate that it contravenes these policies or design standards.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213877","213877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050410","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of climate change on the UK's diplomatic relations with states in Asia.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214053","214053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050411","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of climate change on the UK's diplomatic relations with African countries.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214054","214054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050412","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of spending by his Department's Integrated Activity Fund in Bahrain.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214055","214055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050413","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) his Department, (b) Public Health England and (c) the Committee on the Medical Effects of Air Pollutants have (i) made, (ii) commissioned and (iii) received assessments on the comparative levels of toxicity of (A) PM 0.1, (B) PM1 and (C) PM2.5 from different sources of emissions.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213913","213913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050414","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons the Clean Air Strategy 2018 does not discuss PM1 and PM0.1; and what evidence his Department has on the safety to human health of (a) those particles and (b) urban air quality.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213914","213914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050415","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of filter bags in waste incinerators in safely capturing pollutants (a) PM 0.1 and (b) PM1.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213915","213915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050416","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 206215 on Air Pollution, if he will publish the evidence held by (a) his Department and (b) Public Health England of the effect on human health of ultrafine particles (i) PM0.1 and (ii) PM1.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213916","213916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050417","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 206215 pn Air Pollution, if he will direct Public Health England to make an assessment of the effect on respiratory and cardiovascular health of exposure to ultrafine particles (a) in and (b) outside the vicinity of waste incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213917","213917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050418","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for his policies of the Fundació ENT study entitled Air Pollution from Waste Disposal: Not for Public Breath, published in November 2015, which concluded that the current design of the EU legal framework allows for emission limit values that face an unavoidable allocation of health and environmental risks to those citizens living nearby incineration and co-incineration activities.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213918","213918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050419","2019-02-04","Department for International Trade","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress he has made in laying statutory instruments related to EU exit preparedness; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213981","213981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050420","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on laying statutory instruments relating to EU exit preparedness; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213982","213982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050421","2019-01-31","Wales Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what progress he has made on laying statutory instruments relating to EU exit preparedness; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213983","213983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050422","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made in laying statutory instruments related to EU exit preparedness; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213984","213984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050423","2019-02-04","Cabinet Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 211865 on Census: Sikhs, how many of the 53 focus group participants supported the introduction of a Sikh ethnic tick box.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214056","214056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050424","2019-02-04","Cabinet Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans his Department has to develop the National Cyber Security Strategy beyond 2021.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213970","213970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050425","2019-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) the Royal Navy and (b) the manufacture of the Type 26 frigate of General Electric's proposed relocation of its works from Rugby to France.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214057","214057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050426","2019-02-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on the UK steel sector of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214010","214010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050427","2019-02-04","Department for International Trade","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of EU measures to limit imports of steel into the EU in response to the imposition of metal tariffs by the United States; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK steel industry of being excluded from those measures after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214011","214011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050428","2019-02-04","Department for International Trade","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what contingency plans his Department has made to ensure the maintenance of protections for UK steel producers introduced by the European Commission's definitive safeguard measures on imports of certain steel products, published on 16 January 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214012","214012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050429","2019-02-04","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have (a) been removed and (b) have left the UK as a result of English language tests administered by ETS in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213885","213885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050430","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria her Department uses to override a decision of a magistrates' court in relation to the value of deductions in claimants’ universal credit awards; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213886","213886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050431","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is her Department’s policy to sanction claimants of jobseeker's allowance who decline to accept a job with a zero hours contract; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213887","213887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050432","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department spent from the public purse on campaigns to promote the cessation of smoking in 2017-18.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214029","214029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050433","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions each local authority has been subject to legal action for the provision of inaccurate advice on universal credit to claimants in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213888","213888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050434","2019-02-04","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his oral contribution of 28 January 2019, Official Report, column 504, whether it is his policy that there will be no immigration limits on the number of international students.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214058","214058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050435","2019-02-04","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to undertake a review of his Department's policy on the inclusion of international students within the net migration target.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214059","214059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050436","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has plans to monitor the (a) export and (b) economic value of education at the (i) national, (ii) regional and (iii) local authority level.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214060","214060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050437","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on including education in the Government's trade strategy for bilateral agreements.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214061","214061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050438","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has plans to improve the quality of its monitoring of the long-term employment destinations of overseas students that graduated at UK universities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214062","214062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050439","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the volume of disposable nappies in household waste; and what assessment he has made of the (a) environmental and (b) financial merits of the introduction of reusable nappy schemes by local authorities.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214063","214063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050440","2019-02-04","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, at which locations the UK Visa and Citizenship Application Service Centres will be based after services are moved out of Oldham Post Office.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214064","214064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050441","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding (a) in total and (b) per head of population has been allocated to transport infrastructure in each region in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213949","213949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050442","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were required to attend residential detoxification facilities as a condition of their sentence in each year since 2010 for which information is available.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214065","214065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050443","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on residential detoxification facilities provided to individuals required to attend such facilities as a condition of their sentence in each year since 2010 for which information is available.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214066","214066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050444","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of prisoners being released on a (a) Friday and (b) Saturday to ensure that they are able to access housing and employment-related services on the day of release.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214067","214067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050445","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of pension credit claimants in (a) Warrington, (b) Warrington North constituency and (c) the North West who have a partner of working age and will be affected by forthcoming changes to the rules on pension credit.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213950","213950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050446","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which companies his Department has contracted to deliver electronic tagging services; and what the (a) value and (b) duration is of each of those contracts.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214068","214068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050447","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking through the Cross-government suicide prevention workplan to help prevent loneliness and other underlying factors associated with suicide in children and young people.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214035","214035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050448","2019-01-31","Attorney General","2019-01-29","To ask the Attorney General, how much of the £3 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213891","213891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050449","2019-01-31","Cabinet Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much of the £108 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been  allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213892","213892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050450","2019-02-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 207549 on Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy: Brexit, how much of the £375 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213893","213893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050451","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much of the £56 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213894","213894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050452","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the courts closures programme on the financial cost of travelling to court for (a) witnesses, (b) victims of crime and (c) court staff.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214022","214022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050453","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 207553 on Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Brexit, how much of the £720 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213895","213895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050454","2019-01-31","Department for International Trade","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much of the £202 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213896","213896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050455","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 208748 on Department for Transport: Brexit, how much of the £101 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213897","213897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050456","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 207547 on Department of Health and Social Care: Brexit, how much of the £71 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213898","213898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050457","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 207551 on Department for Work and Pensions: Brexit, for what reason her Department is unable to estimate the amount of funding her Department has allocated to prepare for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213899","213899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050458","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much of the £75 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213900","213900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050459","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 207546 on Treasury: Brexit, how much of the £60 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213901","213901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050460","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints have been made to the Police in England and Wales in relation to section 4A on stalking of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997; how many complaints have resulted in charges being made; how many charges have resulted in convictions; and how many convictions have resulted in custodial sentences in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214069","214069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050461","2019-02-04","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 207552 on Home Office: Brexit, how much of the £875 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213902","213902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050462","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints the police in England and Wales have received in relation to the offence of coercive control; how many complaints have resulted in the accused being charged; how many charges have resulted in a prosecution; how many prosecutions have resulted in a conviction; and how many people convicted have been given custodial sentences in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214070","214070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050463","2019-02-04","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 207548 on Northern Ireland Office: Brexit, for what reason calculating a specific allocation would be disproportionately difficult in relation to estimating the amount of funding her Department has allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213903","213903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050464","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has for the introduction of an appeal process to the EU Settled Status scheme.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214071","214071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050465","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of current preparations for the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the road haulage sector.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213941","213941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050466","2019-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 207550 on Ministry of Defence: Brexit, how much of the £25 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213904","213904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050467","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 207561 on Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Brexit, for what reason his Department does not hold data on funding allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213905","213905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050468","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of the £47 million allocated to his Department for Brexit preparations in 2018-19 and 2019-20 has been allocated to preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213906","213906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050469","2019-01-31","Scotland Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 207564 on Scotland Office: Brexit, for what reason his Department holds no estimate of what it has spent on no deal preparations, which cannot readily be separated from other EU exit and devolution functions in general.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213907","213907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050470","2019-01-31","Wales Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 207565, Wales Office: Brexit, for what reason his Department holds no information on allocation of funding for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213908","213908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050471","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle incidents of knife crime on the railways.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214072","214072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050472","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Zimbabwean counterpart to ensure that Evan Mawarire is given a fair trial in accordance with international law.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213985","213985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050473","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prisoners have been diagnosed with a mental illness while in prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213942","213942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050474","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the effect of universal credit on people's ability to pay upfront childcare costs without incurring debt.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214036","214036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050475","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) South Africa, (b) Botswana, (c) Namibia and and (d) Malawi on the situation in Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213986","213986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050476","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to provide low-income families with financial support for childcare when that childcare is paid for.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214037","214037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050477","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Zimbabwean counterpart to ensure that individuals detained by the military and the police during the recent unrest are given a fair trial in accordance with international law.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213987","213987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050478","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much compensation was paid to landowners and developers for delays in completing Crossrail in accordance with the contract timetable in (a) each compensation category and (b) total up to 31 December 2018; and what recent estimate he has made of the total compensation that will be paid to landowners and developers for the failure to deliver Crossrail in accordance with the contract timetable by the completion of the scheme.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213947","213947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050479","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US Government counterparts on the International Criminal Court; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213943","213943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050480","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to publish its response to the recommendations of the independent review into the application of sharia law in England and Wales.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214073","214073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050481","2019-02-04","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made representations to the Financial Conduct Authority on investigating whether payday loan companies are applying affordability checks to applicants.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213971","213971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050482","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of levels of funding for Natural England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213944","213944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050483","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of political stability in the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213945","213945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050484","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the dry weather in summer 2018 on farm productivity levels.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214074","214074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050485","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has raised with his Chinese counterpart reports of the alleged use of forced confessions on China Central Television.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214075","214075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050486","2019-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which of his Department's surplus aircraft, by aircraft type, were disposed of by sale or gifting since January 2013; and what the military registrations were of each those surplus aircraft so disposed.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214076","214076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050487","2019-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's disposal of surplus aircraft by sale or gifting since January 2013, which of those surplus aircraft so disposed were advertised as being for sale by competitive bid; and whether those surplus aircraft so advertised were procured by a preferred purchaser.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214077","214077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050488","2019-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's disposal of surplus aircraft by sale or gifting since January 2013, what the (a) average price paid by the buyer, (b) total cost of commissions paid to third-party agencies and (c) total revenue returned to the public purse was for each type of those surplus aircraft so disposed.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214078","214078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050489","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has had discussions with (a) Ofcom and (b) the Foreign and Commonwealth Office on reports of the alleged use of forced confessions on China Central Television.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214079","214079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050490","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking with football clubs to help identify perpetrators of antisemitic hate crimes on match days.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214080","214080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050491","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of football clubs on the use of antisemitic chants at football matches.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214081","214081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050492","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the police and (b) other relevant authorities on the monitoring of antisemitism at football matches.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214082","214082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050493","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Norway, (b) Finland and (c) Sweden on antisemitism.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214083","214083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050494","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to record data on education as an (a) export and (b) economic value (i) nationally, (ii) regionally and (i) locally.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214018","214018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050495","2019-02-04","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will make an estimate of the amount of money that the EU has spent on the (a) Republic of Ireland and (b) island of Ireland to date; and if he will make an estimate of the amount of money the UK has contributed to those bodies that formed part of that spending.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214013","214013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050496","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Trade on including education in its strategy for future bilateral agreements; and what the outcome of those discussions has been.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214019","214019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050498","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to improve the recording of the long-term employment destination of international graduates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214021","214021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050499","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow East of 17 December 2018, reference DL2671.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214084","214084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050500","2019-01-31","Department for International Development","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments required Ministerial approval by her Department in the financial years (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214085","214085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050501","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs,  whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a centralised system for recording Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214086","214086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050502","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will allocate further additional resources to the Independent Case Examiner to reduce (a) waiting times for decisions and (b) the number of cases outstanding.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214028","214028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050503","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to give Metro Mayors a formal role in the (a) design and (b) delivery of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214087","214087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050504","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if the Government will make it its policy to make funding for the UK Shared Prosperity Fund available at the same level as EU Structural Fund spending after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214088","214088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050505","2019-01-31","Cabinet Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether representatives from (a) Guinea, (b) Chile, (c) Cameroon, (d) Angola, (e) Bulgaria and (f) Pakistan were called to give evidence to the Chilcot Inquiry.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214089","214089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050506","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when EU citizens living in the UK who have paid the £65 settled status fee will receive their refund.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214090","214090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050507","2019-01-31","Scotland Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on tackling fuel poverty in Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214091","214091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050508","2019-02-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 39 of the Government white paper entitled National Security and Investment, published in June 2018, whether the proposed Government powers will permit the exclusion of a company supplying UK telecoms critical national infrastructure with equipment on national security grounds.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214092","214092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050509","2019-02-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 39 of the Government white paper entitled National Security and Investment, published in June 2018, who he plans to consult when determining whether to exclude a company on national security grounds.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214093","214093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050510","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has read the report by the Conservative Party Human Rights Commission on human rights in Russia; and what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the recommendations in that report.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214024","214024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050511","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to increase support for civil society and human rights defenders in Russia.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214025","214025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050512","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that GP surgeries are supplied with adequate guidance for patients on their medication in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213939","213939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050513","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) initial and (b) additional allocated budgets for special needs provision in West Sussex schools have been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213878","213878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050514","2019-02-04","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the IR35 reforms, how much extra tax is payable by the firm in addition to the fees paid to the worker when a firm classes someone as an employee for tax purposes; and what that tax payable would be for a worker charging £400 per day for their services.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214094","214094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050515","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of (a) trends in the level of betting on football, (b) the effect of in-play betting on gambling levels and (c) the adequacy of existing regulations on gambling advertising in relation to sport.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213940","213940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050516","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish the information that his Department holds on local authorities that undertake separate food waste collections.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213976","213976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050517","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which local authorities in England undertake separate food waste collections.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213977","213977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050518","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to make an assessment of the effect on babies of (a) glyphosate and (b) other chemicals used in disposable nappies.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214095","214095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050519","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to record which local authorities in England have yet to undertake separate food waste collections.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213978","213978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050520","2019-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 211684 on Chinook Helicopters: Accidents, whether the Government has preserved records relating to the crash of the RAF helicopter Chinook that were closed between the date of the accident on 2 June 1994 and 1995.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213973","213973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050522","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what legal aid will be available for (a) applications and (b) appeals in relation to the EU settlement scheme.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213988","213988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050523","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether victims of modern slavery are exempt from the requirement to take an annual work capability assessment; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213946","213946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050524","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers (a) started and (b) completed the National Professional Qualification in Headship in each of the last five years; and whether he made an assessment of methods for improving head teacher recruitment and retention as part of his recently published recruitment and retention strategy.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214096","214096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050525","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when scoping is planned to start for the review of NICE technology appraisal methods set out in the 2019 voluntary scheme for branded medicines pricing and access.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214097","214097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050526","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Saudi Arabian authorities to (a) release female human rights defenders detained in since May 2018 and (b) bring to justice those suspected of their torture.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214026","214026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050527","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the UN Human Rights Council (a) condemning the detention and torture of female human rights activists in Saudi Arabia and (b) requesting the release of those women.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214027","214027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050528","2019-02-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2018 to Question 203356 on Innovation and Science, what the reason is for the delay in publication of the third wave of Science and Innovation Audits.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214098","214098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050529","2019-02-04","Department for International Trade","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many arms licences have been (a) granted and (b) refused to Saudi Arabia since 9 August 2018.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213966","213966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050530","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the viability of bringing forward to 2030 the target year for phasing out diesel and petrol-fuelled cars.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214099","214099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050531","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Saudi counterpart on the detention of female human rights activists detained in that country.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213967","213967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050532","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to announce departmental targets for the reduction of PM 2.5 pollutants.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214100","214100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050533","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to reduce air pollutants from motor vehicle fumes.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214101","214101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050534","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum cases his Department has identified as complex in Lanark and Hamilton East constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214102","214102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050535","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department takes to assess the income of paying parents who are company directors in child maintenance service cases.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214103","214103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050536","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the needs of people with fibromyalgia who are making claims for (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment support allowance.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214104","214104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050537","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on (a) the poultry meat sector and (b) the cost of British poultry meat products in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213919","213919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050538","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the provision of non-UK labour to staff the poultry meat industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213920","213920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050539","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether companies that gain contracts to run outsourced (a) cleaning and (b) security services in his Department will be required to (i) recognise Trades Unions and (b) pay the Real Living Wage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214105","214105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050540","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to meet with representatives of fibromyalgia (a) charities and (b) action groups in February 2019.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214106","214106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050541","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress she has made in enabling greater access to (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment support allowance for people with mental health difficulties.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214107","214107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050542","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the use of cannabidiol treatment for people with fibromyalgia.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214108","214108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050543","2019-02-04","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will place in the Library a copy of his letter to the Chief Inspector of Ofsted, dated 15 November 2018, on Steiner independent schools and other matters.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213979","213979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050544","2019-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many herds have been subject to interferon gamma testing in each of the (a) low, (b) edge and (c) high-risk bovine tuberculosis control areas in 2018.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213921","213921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050545","2019-02-04","Attorney General","2019-01-29","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2018 to Question 194050 on Crown Prosecution Service: Staff, what the figure was for prosecutions for minor motoring offences (a) at the beginning of that period (b) at the end of that period.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213930","213930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050546","2019-02-04","Attorney General","2019-01-29","To ask the Attorney General, what the change has been in the overall case load for the CPS in the West Midlands between May 2010 and November 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213931","213931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050547","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the situation of the G11 group of Eritrean parliamentarians, who have been detained in Eritrea since 2001.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213922","213922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050548","2019-02-04","Attorney General","2019-01-29","To ask the Attorney General, what the change has been in the overall case load for the Crown Prosecution Service in the West Midlands in each year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213932","213932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050549","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Eritrean Government on the Eritrean Parliamentarians detained incommunicado in Eritrea since 2001.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213923","213923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050550","2019-01-31","Attorney General","2019-01-29","To ask the Attorney General, what the change has been in the overall caseload for the Crown Prosecution Service in each year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213933","213933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050551","2019-01-31","Attorney General","2019-01-29","To ask the Attorney General, how many staff were employed in each department within the CPS on (a) 30 May 2010 and (b) 30 September 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213934","213934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050552","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for research into methods for (a) treating and (b) curing Trimethylaminuria.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214109","214109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050553","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Safety at Ports and Borders to prevent counterfeit electrical goods from entering the UK (a) currently and (b) after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214110","214110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050554","2019-01-31","Attorney General","2019-01-29","To ask the Attorney General, how many staff were employed in each Department in the CPS in the West Midlands on (a) 30 May 2010 and (b) 30 September 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213935","213935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050555","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to prepare for the UK potentially leaving the EU without a deal in relation to perishable goods being exported.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214111","214111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050556","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the answer of 7 January 2019 to question 203778 on Designated Public Places Orders: Prosecutions, how many prosecutions there were for the offence of consumption of alcohol in a designated public place under the Criminal Justice and Police Act 2001 by location of the court in each year from 30 May 2009.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213936","213936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050557","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government plans to take to do to simplify bureaucracy and support small businesses exporting goods in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214112","214112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050558","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of perishable goods checked at customs have (a) exited and (b) entered the UK in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214113","214113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050559","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what precautions customs officers are taking when checking perishable goods exiting the country to avoid the waste of products.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214114","214114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050560","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled Room to Manoeuvre, published by Arthritis Research, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recommendations made in that report.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214115","214115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050561","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing legislative proposals for further regulation to tackle online (a) platforms and (b) retail sites that allow the sale of counterfeit and substandard electrical goods.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214116","214116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050562","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of  the potential merits of providing additional funding to Safety at Ports and Borders to prevent counterfeit and substandard electrical goods from being imported.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214117","214117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050563","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will make an estimate of the (a) number of fulfilment houses that are operating in the United Kingdom that are selling counterfeit and substandard electrical goods and (b) cost to the UK economy of such fulfilment houses.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214118","214118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050564","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he made of the cost to the UK economy of the sale of counterfeit and substandard electrical products.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214119","214119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050565","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with online platforms on preventing sales of counterfeit and substandard electrical goods on their websites.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214120","214120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050566","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Italian Government on that Government's decision not to allow the Sea-Watch crew and the refugees that it has picked up dock.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213924","213924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050567","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the full delivery of the commitment to run two trains an hour between Mid-Cheshire and Manchester as set out in the current Northern Rail franchise agreement.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214121","214121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050568","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has held with bus companies on disability awareness training for all bus drivers.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213995","213995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050569","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the level of discrimination experienced by disabled people when travelling by taxi.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213996","213996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050570","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that baggage handlers at UK airports are trained to handle wheelchairs.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213997","213997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050571","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on reducing health inequalities for people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213998","213998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050572","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on increasing the number of learning disability nurses in the NHS.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213999","213999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050573","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect that the provision of social care has on the level of hospital admissions by people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214000","214000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050574","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that reasonable adjustments are provided to people with a learning disability when using the NHS.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214001","214001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050575","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2019 to Question 210599, on Buildings: Insulation, how his Department categorised the other 884 samples.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214122","214122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050576","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment he has made of the merits of community-based social care and assessment and treatment units.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214002","214002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050577","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on decreasing the number of people with a learning disability in assessment and treatment units.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214003","214003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050578","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an estimate of the level of unmet need for social care in England.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214004","214004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050579","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to tackle the level of unmet need for social care in England.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214005","214005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050580","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department plans to publish its response to the consultation entitled Pre-paid funeral plans, launched in June 2018.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214123","214123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050581","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the future immigration system will allow temporary short-term workers on a 12-month visa from EU member states to access (a) primary care and to register with a GP, (b) NHS secondary care services; and whether those workers will be obliged to pay the health surcharge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214042","214042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050582","2019-02-04","Attorney General","2019-01-29","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the number of people (a) the CPS employs and (b) who were employed by the CPS in May 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213937","213937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050583","2019-02-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will increase funding to councils to support the provision of council tax support.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214124","214124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050584","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the role of the voluntary and community sector in supporting the implementation of the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214006","214006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050585","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England on the role of non-clinical interventions in achieving the ambitions set out in the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214007","214007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050586","2019-01-31","Attorney General","2019-01-29","To ask the Attorney General, what the change has been in the overall case load for the Crown Prosecution Service between May 2010 and September 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213938","213938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050587","2019-02-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of personal insolvencies in each local authority area in the UK in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213964","213964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050588","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to increase the mental health workforce to achieve the ambitions set out in the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214008","214008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050589","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to extend the Community Housing Fund beyond 2020.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214125","214125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050590","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the outcomes of pancreatic cancer diagnoses in line with the NHS England 2015 cancer strategy.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214126","214126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050591","2019-02-04","Department for Transport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Wolverhampton train station has been accredited under the Secure Stations Scheme.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214038","214038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050592","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any claimants featured in her Department's promotional materials have received payment for doing so in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213965","213965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050593","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many animals have been experimented on in the UK in the last 12 months for household product ingredients.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213980","213980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050594","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of claims of housing disrepair made in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213948","213948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050595","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2019 to Question 210500 on Local Growth Deals, how much funding from the public purse was allocated to each (a) city and (b) growth deal announced in (i) 2017, (ii) 2018 and (iii) 2019 in (A) Northern Ireland, (B) Wales and (C) Scotland.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213974","213974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050596","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to Answer of 29 January to Question 210499 on Capital Investment, if he will publish the amount of funding allocated by (a) central government for each capital project, (b) each devolved administration for each capital project either fully or partially funded in (i) 2017, (ii) 2018 and (iii) 2019; and what the total cost to the public purse was for each such project in each of those years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213975","213975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050597","2019-02-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 112 of the Civil Society Strategy published in August 2018, whether his Department has provided training for central government commercial buyers in how to take account of social value in commissioning and procurement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214127","214127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050598","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all prisons that house sexual offenders have a strategy developed for managing those offenders.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213958","213958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050599","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans for strategies for sexual offenders to be implemented in all prisons that house them.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213959","213959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050600","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to take to ensure that Her Majesty’s Prisons and Probation Service implement a national needs analysis for people serving both custodial and community sentences; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213960","213960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050601","2019-02-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 112 of the Civil Society Strategy published in August 2018, when his Department plans to publish a guide to selling to government for voluntary, community, and social enterprise organisations, including social value.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214128","214128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050602","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sexual offenders were not moved to a local resettlement prison in their area of release due to a lack of spaces available for vulnerable prisoners at those sites in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213961","213961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050603","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners released from training prisons whose sentences were for sexual offences did not receive (a) Community Rehabilitation Company resettlement and (b) Through the Gate services on release in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213962","213962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050604","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many trainee probation officers were trained to work with sexual offenders in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213963","213963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050605","2019-02-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 112 of the Civil Society Strategy, published in August 2018, whether The Crown Representative has undertaken an awareness campaign to encourage use of Contracts Finder and Mystery Shopper services to promote early engagement and co-design and to hold authorities to account for poor practice.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214129","214129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050606","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2018 to Question 208247 on the regular reporting of mental health spend to the NHS dashboard, when the Government plans to publish the next quartile of data.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214030","214030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050607","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2018 to Question 210680 and with reference to the Backbench Business Committee debate on Mental Health First Aid on 17 January 2019, Official Report columns 1366-1395, what the main outcomes were of the Work Leadership Council on the 17 January 2019.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214031","214031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050608","2019-01-31","Cabinet Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) violent crimes and (b) sexual offences were committed in Wolverhampton in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214039","214039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050609","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2018 to Question 210677 on Mental Health and Employers Independent Review and with reference to the Backbench Business Committee debate on Mental Health First Aid on 17 January 2019, Official Report columns 1366-1395, whether the Government has plans to make the recommendations of the Farmer-Stevenson review binding for private business.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214032","214032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050610","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 211320, if the Government will increase public health funding for local authorities to retain sexual health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214033","214033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050611","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 211319 on the Nuffield Trust Paper, whether healthcare services in deprived areas will receive support to recruit more staff.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214034","214034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050612","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department holds figures on how many UK citizens below pension age living in the European Union utilise the S1 form certificate of entitlement to access healthcare.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214130","214130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050613","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Category C Prisons there are in England and Wales; and how many of those prisons routinely accommodated prisoners of a higher risk category in 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213972","213972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050614","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Article 24 of the United Nations Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities, what recent steps the Government has taken to support the (a) inclusive education of disabled children and young people and (b) progressive removal of barriers to education and participation in mainstream education.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214131","214131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050615","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's obligations under Article 24 of the UN Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities of the free school programme; and how many special schools have opened under that programme.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214132","214132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050616","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve the (a) speed of diagnosis and (b) treatment of lipoedema.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213925","213925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050617","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) quality and (b) reliability of research into lipoedema.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213926","213926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050618","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on reports of the indefinite detention of senior political opponents in the Ritz-Carlton hotels and other places; and whether the Government will support a legal process to help bring those who are alleged to have committed illegal acts to justice.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213880","213880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050619","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations the Government has made to the Government of Saudi Arabia on providing proof of life for (a) political detainees held in places such as the Ritz-Carlton and (b) female activists held in Riyadh.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213881","213881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050620","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government provides to Saudi Arabian civil society to help them uphold the rule of law and fundamental human rights in the country.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213882","213882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050621","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effectiveness of imposing trade sanctions on Saudi Arabia to tackle human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213883","213883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050622","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many disposable nappies have been recycled in the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214133","214133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050623","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) certified enforcement and (b) high-court officers have lost their licence to enforce debts since April 2014.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214134","214134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050624","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant of the Answer of 11 January 2019 to Question 204365 on Clinical Commissioning Groups: Finance, for what reason Harrow CCG has been placed into financial directions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213889","213889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050625","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to ensure there is sufficient funding for (a) public health, (b) mental health services and (c) social care since Harrow Clinical Commissioning Group has been placed in financial directions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213890","213890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050626","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of magistrates’ court closures on access to justice.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214135","214135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050627","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of leaving the EU on the UK’s legal sectors.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214136","214136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050628","2019-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of non-appearances by (a) defendants and (b) witnesses in magistrates’ courts over the last three years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214137","214137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050629","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking ensure that there is sufficient public awareness of the changes to universal credit entitlement for mixed-aged couples among people who are affected by that change.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214138","214138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050630","2019-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the date of completion is of the most recent equality impact assessment carried out on the changes to universal credit entitlement for mixed-aged couples.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214139","214139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050631","2019-02-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people under the age of 18 have presented at A&E departments requiring treatment for self-harm in CCG areas covering the (a) Greater Birmingham (b) the West Midlands metro area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213968","213968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050632","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to reduce the number of incidences of misdiagnosis of kidney cancer.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213989","213989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050633","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government plans to take in the next five years to reduce the number of patients with kidney cancer who are misdiagnosed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213990","213990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050634","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits of allocating funding to research into the development of a national screening programme for kidney cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213991","213991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050635","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, what recent steps he has taken to implement the target of diagnosing 75 per cent of cancers at stage one or stage two by 2028; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213992","213992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050636","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the evidential basis was for his Department's target of  diagnosing 75 per cent of cancers at stage one or stage two by 2028 and if he made an assessment of the feasibility of setting that target at 2025.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213993","213993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050637","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether cryoablation needles will remain available through the High Cost Tariff Excluded Device List with no changes to current funding arrangements in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213994","213994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050643","2019-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on regional security of the Israeli Government's decision not to renew the mandate of the international observatory task force in Hebron; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214157","214157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049329","2019-01-30","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-28","What plans her Department has to enable Northern Ireland to reduce its public sector fiscal deficit.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908812","908812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049378","2019-01-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","What steps his Department is taking to help ensure fire safety in buildings.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908851","908851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049379","2019-01-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","What steps he is taking to ensure that adequate infrastructure is put in place to support the proposed increase in housing in the Swale borough council area.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908852","908852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049380","2019-01-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","What progress his Department has made in its review of the rules that require carbon monoxide alarms to be fitted in homes across England.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908853","908853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049984","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 207224 on Universal Credit: Support for Mortgage Interest, how much Support for Mortgage Interest has been (a) paid, (b) recouped and (c) left outstanding since April 2018.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213323","213323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049985","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the long-term effect of Frontline on the number of people engaging in social work research.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213377","213377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049986","2019-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what military training the UK has provided to the armed forces of Ecuador since 2014; and what plans his Department has to provide military training to the armed forces of Ecuador in the future.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213337","213337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049987","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce underage drinking.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213353","213353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049988","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of people experiencing insulin resistance.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213354","213354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049989","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when stem cell treatments for wet age-related macular degeneration will be made available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213355","213355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049990","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when haematopoietic stem cell transplantation treatment will be made available on the NHS for people with multiple sclerosis.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213356","213356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049991","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce levels of obesity among (a) Asian and (b) other BAME children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213357","213357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049992","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with glaucoma in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213358","213358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049993","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce NHS waiting times for (a) hip and (b) knee operations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213359","213359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049994","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the finding of Public Health England's news story of 18 July 2018, Flu vaccine effectiveness in 2017 to 2018 that the flu vaccine was 15 per cent effective in all age groups, what steps he is taking to improve the effectiveness of the flu vaccine.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213360","213360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049995","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on the living standards of benefit claimants of the rate at which repayments of overpayments are repaid to her Department.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213410","213410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049996","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons (a) his Department uses different indices to measure inflation and (b) benefit increases are pegged to the lower index.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213258","213258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049997","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it a requirement that all care home providers routinely check the blood sugar levels of their diabetic occupants.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213361","213361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049998","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have a diagnosis of cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213362","213362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1049999","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been living with a diagnosis of scoliosis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213363","213363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050000","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have a diagnosis of incontinence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213364","213364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050001","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been living with a diagnosis of diabetes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213365","213365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050002","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with anaemia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213366","213366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050004","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the draft Invasive Non-native Species (Amendment etc.) (EU Exit) Regulations 2019 (a) makes policy changes, (b) will lead to a change in operational delivery, (c) will impose additional costs on (i) business, (ii) individuals, or (iii) the public sector, (d) makes changes to primary legislation, (e) will result in any additional environmental impacts compared with the legislation being amended or replaced, and (f) is only required in the event the UK leaves the EU with no deal.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213194","213194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050005","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the draft Fisheries (Amendment) (EU Exit) Regulations 2019 (a) makes policy changes, (b) will lead to a change in operational delivery, (c) will impose additional costs on (i) business, (ii) individuals, or (iii) the public sector, (d) makes changes to primary legislation, (e) will result in any additional environmental impacts compared with the legislation being amended or replaced, and (f) is only required in the event the UK leaves the EU with no deal.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213195","213195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050006","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 208362 on Buildings: Insulation, what assessment his Department has made of the compatibility with building regulations of the 1,421 non-aluminium composite material cladding samples submitted to the Building Research Establishment.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213373","213373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050007","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason his Department charges more for applications for passports accepted through post offices compared with online applications.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213411","213411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050008","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the terms of reference are for the High Court's judicial review into the implementation of the Pension Act 1995 and Pension Act 2011.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213338","213338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050009","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the National Action Plan for the Sustainable Use of Pesticides will include a strategy for (a) minimising overall pesticide use and (b) supporting the wider use of integrated pest management.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213316","213316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050010","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's transparency data, Police funding: special grant applications: 2017 to 2018, updated on 4 June 2018, for what reason his Department's policy is to fund 85 per cent of the investigation costs requested by police forces for large scale child sexual exploitation cases and not the full costs of such investigations.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213414","213414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050011","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's transparency data, Police funding: special grant applications: 2017 to 2018, updated on 4 June 2018 and the Grenfell Tower investigation, for what reason his Department's policy is to fund 85 per cent of large scale investigations that are a Government top priority and not the full costs of such investigations.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213415","213415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050012","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many local authorities have (a) volunteered to support unaccompanied asylum-seeking children and (b) published the number of children who have been successfully rehomed since the launch of the National Transfer Scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213369","213369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050013","2019-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of pension credit claimants in (a) Cardiff South and Penarth, (b) the Vale of Glamorgan and (c) Wales who have a partner of working age and will be affected by forthcoming changes to the rules on pension credit.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213370","213370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050014","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he is taking steps to ensure people can access Skymkevi through the NHS.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213277","213277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050015","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will ensure Metro Mayors in England will have a formal role in the consultation on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213368","213368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050016","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the link between areas of deprivation and health service usage.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213320","213320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050017","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Iran on legal and political restrictions on human rights campaigners.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213344","213344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050018","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Russia on the reported abduction of Oleg Kozlovsky.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213345","213345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050019","2019-01-31","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the total amount of funding provided to businesses by UK Export Finance; and what proportion of that support was provided to SMEs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213462","213462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050020","2019-01-30","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will place in the Library a copy of his letter to the Chief Inspector of Ofsted, dated 15 November 2018, on the subject of Steiner independent schools and other matters.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213278","213278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050021","2019-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his December 2018 report on the Modernising Defence Programme, what the (a) timescale and (b) plans are for implementing the international civilian defence cadre; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213286","213286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050022","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many high street retail shops have closed in (a) the UK, (b) Hampshire and (c) Portsmouth since 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213447","213447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050023","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to support lotteries.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213468","213468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050024","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of raising the prize limit for society lotteries.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213469","213469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050026","2019-01-30","Department for Transport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the processing time of freight at Portsmouth International port.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213449","213449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050027","2019-01-30","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average state school class size is in (a) the UK, (b) Hampshire and (c) the city of Portsmouth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213450","213450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050028","2019-01-30","Department for Transport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Portsmouth International port on the effect of peak ferry times on the processing capability of the port in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213451","213451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050029","2019-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many hearings in the first tier tribunal in the social entitlement chamber took place where her Department was a respondent; and at how many of those hearings a representative of the Department was in attendance in each month in 2018.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213407","213407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050030","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department will take to prevent the closure of major high street retailers in (a) the UK, (b) Hampshire and (c) Portsmouth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213452","213452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050031","2019-01-31","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he plans to seek the inclusion of investor protection clauses in trade agreements that he transposes with (a) Canada and (b) Japan.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213426","213426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050032","2019-01-31","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade whether he plans to consult publicly on the inclusion of investor protection clauses and (b) other investment provisions in trade agreements that he seeks to transpose with (i) Canada, (ii) Japan and (iii) other countries with which the EU has yet to ratify an agreement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213427","213427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050033","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to support biomedical research into the diagnosis and treatment of ME.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213339","213339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050034","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he will take to reduce the use of single-use plastic.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213257","213257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050035","2019-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy,  if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the report of 18 January 2018 by the Centre for Social Investigation entitled Are employers in Britain discriminating against ethnic minorities.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213155","213155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050036","2019-01-30","Women and Equalities","2019-01-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals on extending civil partnerships to heterosexual couples.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213156","213156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050037","2019-01-30","Treasury","2019-01-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the go-live operational date is scheduled for the new Customs Declaration Service to take over from CHIEF system.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213157","213157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050038","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Consolidated Guidance is applied to information sharing where there is a serious risk of the use of lethal force.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213158","213158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050039","2019-01-31","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which countries have assented to their existing free trade agreements with the UK as a result of UK membership of the EU being immediately rolled over once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213159","213159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050040","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the estimated operational cost of the EU settlement scheme is.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213160","213160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050041","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made contingency plans for an outbreak of African swine flu in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213196","213196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050042","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which countries that export meat to the UK have experienced outbreaks of African swine flu.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213197","213197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050043","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has recently commissioned research into a cure for African swine flu; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213198","213198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050044","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Tobacco Products and Nicotine Inhaling Products (Amendment etc.) (EU Exit) Regulations 2018, whether products produced before the UK leaves the EU will still be legal to sell after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213284","213284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050045","2019-01-30","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what role the devolved Administrations will have in developing the UK’s trade policy after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213467","213467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050046","2019-01-30","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has to promote high environmental standards with the UK's trading partners in (a) current and (b) future trade negotiations.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213280","213280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050047","2019-01-30","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, (a) how many staff have been appointed to prepare and (b) what the cost to the public purse has been of preparing his Department for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213281","213281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050048","2019-01-30","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what trade agreements he expects the UK to have agreed and will be in force on 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213282","213282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050049","2019-01-31","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has plans to introduce legislative proposals for the Parliamentary oversight of new trade agreements.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213161","213161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050050","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of including the use of skylark plots in his Department's future environmental land management scheme.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213456","213456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050051","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims of slavery who are no longer receiving support through the asylum system (a) have applied for a subsistence rate back payment and (b) are yet to apply for a back payment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213236","213236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050052","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of victims of slavery who are due a subsistence rate back payment are no longer receiving support through the asylum system.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213237","213237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050053","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has held with BMW on the future of production at its Oxford plant in the event that the UK leaves the EU; and whether those discussions included the possibility of moving production away from the UK.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213457","213457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050054","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to replicate the provisions of Article 13 of the Lisbon Treaty on animal sentience in UK law in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213458","213458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050055","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174612 on Air pollution, what evidence he is using to assess the safe limit for public health of inhalation of PM0.1 and PM1 particles.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213199","213199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050056","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  pursuant to his Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174612, Air Pollution, as the COMEAP study to which he refers was carried out in 2012, if he will (a) ask that body to conduct a further study on the effects of particulate air pollution on mortality in the UK and (b) will ensure that such a new study includes PM0.1 and PM1.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213200","213200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050057","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ask Public Health England to carry out a study of where emissions of (a) PM0.1, (b) PM1 and (c) PM2.5 from municipal waste incinerators land.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213201","213201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050058","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the recent National Atmospheric Emissions Inventory point source data for municipal solid waste incinerators that shows that in 2016 waste incinerators emitted 8996 Kg of PM0.1 and 51,042 Kg of PM1, if (a) his Department or (b) Public Health England will make an assessment of the effects of those emissions on (i) human health and (ii) air quality in the vicinity of those incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213202","213202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050059","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps Public Health England has taken to assess air quality in the vicinity of waste incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213203","213203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050061","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) his Department and (b) Public Health England has made an assessment of the effect on (i) air quality and (ii) human health of different stack heights of waste incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213205","213205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050062","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in (a) England and (b) England and Wales were transferred to a bed in an NHS mental health facility because they had (i) psychosis, (ii) schizophrenia or (iii) any other condition in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213294","213294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050063","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) average, (b) highest and (c) lowest number of weeks is which have passed between a doctor recommending transfer of a prisoner to a bed in a mental health facility and the prison’s eventual transfer of that prisoner in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213295","213295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050064","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has issued to the Court of Protection on the use of Section 49 of the Mental Capacity Act 2005 to ensure that (a) NHS bodies are not disproportionately affected and (b) clinicians are not called away from front-line services at short notice.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213296","213296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050065","2019-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times the Court of Protection has asked NHS bodies for reports under Section 49 of the Mental Capacity Act 2005 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213297","213297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050066","2019-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which NHS bodies have been asked to provide reports under Section 49 of the Mental Capacity Act 2005 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213298","213298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050067","2019-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has given to NHS bodies on how to respond to requests for reports by the Court of Protection issued under Section 49 of the Mental Capacity Act 2005.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213299","213299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050068","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 31 of the NHS Long Term Plan, published in January 2019, what additional social care funding the Government plans to provide to meet the commitment that adult social care funding does not impose any additional pressure on the NHS over the coming five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213300","213300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050069","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 14 of the NHS Long Term Plan, published in January 2019, how many of the one million hospital bed days to be freed up by that plan are planned to be used for patients with dementia.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213301","213301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050070","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, published in January 2019, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that digitised health services proposed in that plan are accessible for people living with dementia.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213302","213302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050071","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 15 of the NHS Long Term Plan, published in January 2019, whether the revised GP Quality Outcomes Framework (QOF) proposed in that plan will effect QOF indicators for dementia including (a) new diagnoses, (b) care plans or memory assessment reviews and (c) named carers on records.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213303","213303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050072","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to 63 of the NHS Long Term Plan, published in January 2019, what estimate he has made of the number of the target 150,000 cases of heart attack, stroke and dementia to be prevented that will be cases of (a) heart attacks, (b) strokes and (c) dementia; and whether any interim targets will be set over the ten year period of that plan.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213304","213304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050073","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether EU nationals undertaking an apprenticeship in the UK will be able to complete their apprenticeship in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213351","213351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050074","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what account his Department takes of inflation when allocating funding for apprenticeships.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213352","213352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050075","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using bacteriophages as an alternative to antibiotics.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213453","213453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050076","2019-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential for hypersonic flight to be included in the design of the next generation fighter jet.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213287","213287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050077","2019-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what has been the contribution to the public purse from the sale of courts in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213419","213419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050078","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2019 to Question 210039 on Social Workers: Training, how many bidders submitted a tender application.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213378","213378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050079","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether combination treatments will be assessed in the review of NICE technology appraisal methods set out in the 2019 voluntary scheme for branded medicines pricing and access.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213317","213317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050080","2019-01-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff of his Department are working wholly or predominantly on preparing for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213226","213226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050081","2019-01-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff in each directorate of his Department have been moved from previous roles to work wholly or predominantly on preparing for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213227","213227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050082","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of regional trends in the level of funding changes experienced by local authorities since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213209","213209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050083","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to improve the quality of health and social care services for disabled children.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213463","213463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050084","2019-01-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to help elderly people learn digital skills in (a) the East Midlands and (b) England.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213464","213464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050085","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to raise public awareness of the vulnerability of keyless cars to theft.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213210","213210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050086","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department has allocated directly to (a) Keep Britain Tidy and (b) other anti-litter initiatives in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213350","213350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050087","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers have moved down the pay scale in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213211","213211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050088","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many prosecutions Companies House has brought in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213394","213394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050089","2019-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to the UN to arrange prisoner swaps between warring sides in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213214","213214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050090","2019-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies have been struck off the companies register as a result of action by Companies House in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213395","213395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050091","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to respond to the September 2018 report of the Task and Finish Group on Taxi and PHV Licensing; and whether he plans to bring forward primary legislation to implement that report’s recommendations.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213212","213212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050092","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the adequacy of travel arrangements for football fans.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213213","213213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050093","2019-01-30","Department for Transport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to respond to the September 2018 report of the Task and Finish Group on Taxi and PHV Licensing; and whether he plans to bring forward primary legislation to implement that report’s recommendations.","Biography information for Julia Lopez","Julia Lopez","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213442","213442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050094","2019-01-30","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) teaching assistants and (b) specialist support staff have been employed in primary schools in (i) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (ii) the London borough of Lewisham, (iii) London and (iv) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213417","213417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050095","2019-01-30","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) teaching assistants and (b) specialist support staff have been employed in secondary schools in (i) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (ii) the London Borough of Lewisham, (iii) London and (iv) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213418","213418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050096","2019-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an estimate of the revenue that accrued to Iran from fuel exports that (a) complied and (b) did not comply with international sanctions in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213215","213215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050097","2019-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the volume of imports into Yemen which have been in breach of sanctions on (a) weapons and (b) fuel in each year since in 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213216","213216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050100","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 134294 on Haematological Cancer, when he plans for the evaluation of the rapid diagnostic centres to be published; and he plans for that evaluation to inform the national roll-out of the centres as proposed in the NHS Long-Term Plan.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213321","213321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050101","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2019 to Question 207238 on Asparaginase, what steps Porton Biopharma will take to increase capacity of erwinase and better supply the (a) UK and (b) world market for the remainder of 2019.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213322","213322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050102","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been prosecuted in relation to illegal immigration in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213219","213219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050103","2019-01-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of homeless in Leicester in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213220","213220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050105","2019-01-30","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that School Special Educational Needs Co-ordinators have enough (a) time and (b) resources to provide support to every child.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213454","213454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050106","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has plans to provide financial assistance to individuals from low-income households to enable them to retrofit their older diesel vehicles to reduce emissions of nitrogen dioxide.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213390","213390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050107","2019-01-30","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the January 2019 survey of members of the National Education Union, what steps he is taking to respond to concerns raised in that survey on the effect of reductions in the number of teaching assistants and learning support assistants on the quality of teaching.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213455","213455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050108","2019-01-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2019 to Question 206818 on Air Pollution, which of the eight local authority groupings that have submitted air quality plans to his Department have submitted (a) a final plan and (b) an outline business case.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213391","213391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050109","2019-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 206022 on European Aircraft: safety measures, how the mandatory requirement, based on industrial standards and internationally agreed definitions, for the Typhoon aircraft to be compliant with Part 13 sub paragraph 1.1.9.1 of MAA/Def Stan 00-970 (Aircraft Collision Avoidance System) is satisfied.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213440","213440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050110","2019-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the mandatory requirement, based on industrial standards and internationally agreed definitions, for the F35 Lightening aircraft to be compliant with Part 13 sub paragraph 1.1.9.1 of MAA/Def Stan 00-970 (Aircraft Collision Avoidance System) is satisfied.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213441","213441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050111","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has in place to ensure that Highways England takes steps to reduce levels of nitrogen dioxide on the strategic road network which exceed statutory limits.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213392","213392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050112","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps Highways England is taking to reduce levels of nitrogen dioxide on the strategic road network which exceed statutory limits.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213393","213393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050113","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the policing precepts in increasing police funding in areas with a low base of council tax.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213324","213324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050114","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of (a) the importance of Welsh ports to the UK economy and (b) the role of Welsh ports in the Maritime 2050 strategy.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213291","213291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050115","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason references to the South Wales ports of (a) Newport, (b) Cardiff, (c) Barry, (d) Port Talbot and (e) Swansea were not included in his Department’s strategy document entitled Maritime 2050: Navigating the Future.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213292","213292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050116","2019-01-31","Department for Transport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's document entitled Maritime 2050: navigating the future, published in January 2019, for what reason there are no references to the South Wales ports of Newport, Cardiff, Barry, Port Talbot and Swansea in that document.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213293","213293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050117","2019-01-31","Cabinet Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the healthy life expectancy is for people living in (a) Easington constituency, (b) County Durham and (c) England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213325","213325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050118","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of changing the legislation on compulsory purchase orders to allow such orders to be used in a cost efficient and timely manner by local authorities proposing housing regeneration schemes in areas with high rates of (a) absentee landlords, (b) poor housing quality and (c) low housing demand.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213326","213326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050119","2019-01-31","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will conduct an inquiry into the future of housing in former coalfield communities to develop a bespoke housing policy for constituencies experiencing (a) poor housing quality and (b) low housing demand.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213327","213327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050120","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will link the funding of local authority children's services to levels of demand.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213328","213328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050121","2019-01-30","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will (a) set a recommended social worker caseload figure and (b) provide funding to reduce the average caseloads of such workers.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213329","213329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050122","2019-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will add prison photographic ID to the list of documents that can be used to verify a universal credit claim.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213330","213330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050123","2019-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the standard time is for a work coach to reply to a journal message.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213331","213331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050124","2019-01-30","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked after children have been transferred into County Durham from other local authorities.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213332","213332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050125","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will provide additional funding to Durham Constabulary to reverse the central funding reduction since 2010.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213333","213333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050126","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he is taking steps to use Durham Constabulary as an example of best practice to improve national policing services.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213334","213334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050127","2019-01-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many leasehold (a) houses and (b) flats have been bought using the Help to Buy equity loan scheme  by region since 2013.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213228","213228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050128","2019-01-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Digital and the Creative Industries of 15 November 2018, Official Report column 545, whether it is his policy that the use of the term fibre in the advertising of part-copper broadband represents misleading advertising.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213437","213437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050129","2019-01-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Digital and the Creative Industries of 15 November 2018, Official Report column 545, what steps he is taking to tackle the misleading advertising of fibre broadband.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213438","213438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050130","2019-01-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Digital and the Creative Industries of Thursday 15 November 2018, Official Report column 545, whether he plans to include proposals to tackle the misleading advertising of fibre broadband in his forthcoming Statement of Strategic Priorities to Ofcom.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213439","213439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050131","2019-01-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the levels of non-payment of Help to Buy equity loans repayments by recipients for whom interest on their loans is now payable in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213229","213229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050132","2019-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that sensitive military technologies in use by the armed forces cannot be purchased on the open market from UK-based auctioneers; and whether he plans to undertake a review to prevent such situations occurring again.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213347","213347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050133","2019-01-31","Treasury","2019-01-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason HMRC has introduced new guidance on the payment of VAT on costs for the provision of site-based staff at (a) sheltered units of accommodation and (b) other such developments.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213206","213206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050134","2019-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to undertake an assessment of the potential effect on the capabilities of the armed forces of sensitive military technologies in use by those forces being sold at auction to hostile agents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213348","213348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050135","2019-01-30","Department for International Trade","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the Local to Global podcast (a) since its launch and (b) in the next (i) six, (ii) 12, (iii) 18 and (iv) 24 months.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213459","213459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050136","2019-01-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he is meeting the Government's commitment to replace homes sold through the council right to buy scheme.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213230","213230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050137","2019-01-30","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants in his Department have been seconded to the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs to work on programmes related to the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213460","213460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050138","2019-01-30","Cabinet Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the second phase of the Grenfell Inquiry is planned to (a) start and (b) conclude.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213231","213231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050139","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimates his Department has made of the comparable costs of the (a) recommendations of the School Teachers’ Pay Review Body that all pay and allowance ranges for teachers and school leaders are uplifted by 3.5% from September 2018 and (b) his Department's pay package introduced following the that School Teachers’ Pay Review Body report.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213396","213396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050140","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2018 to Question 147920 on NHS: Dental Services, what the total expenditure was on NHS dental services (a) gross and (b) net of patient charge revenue in 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213397","213397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050141","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June to Question 147920 on NHS: Dental Services, what the expenditure was on NHS dental services net of patient charge revenue per head of population in 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213398","213398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050142","2019-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 5 June to Question 147921 on NHS: Dental Services, what the patient charge revenue was in 2017-18 (a) in total and (b) as a proportion of the total expenditure on NHS dental services.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213399","213399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050143","2019-01-30","Treasury","2019-01-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department plans to publish the schedule of applied tariff rates for imports and exports in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213400","213400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050144","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department has provided to assist food and drink businesses with preparedness for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213401","213401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050145","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs what assessment his Department has made of the preparedness of the food and drink industry for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213402","213402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050146","2019-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the food and drink industry.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213403","213403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050148","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will provide the same national funding for the Emergency Services Day as the Ministry of Defence does for Armed Forces Day.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213233","213233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050149","2019-01-31","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will fund a position for somebody to work on the Emergency Services Day as the Ministry of Defence does for Armed Forces Day.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213234","213234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050150","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will make a financial donation to the National Emergency Services Memorial.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213235","213235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050151","2019-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on the development of large-scale onshore wind projects in England; and whether that policy applies to (a) Wales and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213162","213162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050152","2019-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Energy and Clean Growth of 08 January 2019, Official Report, column 153 and with reference to the Minister's oral contribution to the Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy Committee on 28 November 2017, whether his Department will support onshore wind in those areas of the UK that want to deploy it.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213163","213163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050153","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of child sexual abuse images online in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213275","213275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050154","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his department is taking to prevent the availability and distribution of child sexual abuse material online; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213276","213276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050155","2019-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of suicides among young people under 21 in each of the last five years that had a link to content seen on social media.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213273","213273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050156","2019-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether (a) he (b) Ministers of his Department and (c) officials of his Department have met representatives of Pinterest over the last two years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213274","213274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050157","2019-01-31","Department for Education","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there is a sustainable future for children’s services in West Lancashire.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213285","213285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050158","2019-01-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the accuracy of reports that climate change is exacerbating conflict in Mali; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213279","213279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050159","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department plans to take to directly contact elderly citizens to inform them that they must make online Biometric applications for settled status.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213250","213250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050160","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the funding for advertising the settled status scheme was spent on online advertising in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213251","213251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050161","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that (a) elderly people and (b) disabled people are able to apply for settled status if they do not have access to a computer or smartphone.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213252","213252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1050162","2019-01-30","Home Office","2019-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he will ensure that elderly people residing in the UK without UK citizenship are provided with information on the need to apply for settled status.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213253","213253"
