"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37922","2014-02-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow all (a) social and (b) private tenants to switch from prepayment to credit meters for gas and electricity supplies.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187678","187678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37923","2014-02-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187638","187638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37924","2014-02-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each supplier following the contract award.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187590","187590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37925","2014-02-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each supplier following the contract award.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187591","187591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37926","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of whether a vaccination programme against TB would be cheaper per infected badger than culling.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187666","187666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37927","2014-02-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what flood prevention measures have been undertaken in Shrewsbury in the last three years; and how many staff of (a) his Department and (b) the Environment Agency have been so employed.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197616","197616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37928","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187639","187639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37929","2014-02-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent on flood defences and flood prevention measures in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Shrewsbury in each of the last three years; and if he will provide additional funding to dredge the River Severn at Shrewsbury.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197615","197615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37930","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with landowners and farmers about deer management groups.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187694","187694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37931","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to eradicate grey squirrels.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187695","187695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37932","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that all agricultural environmental programmes include strict predator control on a condition.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187686","187686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37933","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of trees that have been planted in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187698","187698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37934","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the role of tree planting in flood prevention.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187699","187699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37935","2014-02-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he will reply substantively to the letter from the hon. Member for Mid Worcestershire of 25 July 2013, acknowledged by his Department on 2 October 2013, about Hartlebury Parish Council and the proposed main burn incinerator.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187545","187545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37936","2014-02-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department issues to the Planning Inspectorate on what it should accept as the minimum proximity between anaerobic digester plant developments and non-agricultural residential properties.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187580","187580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37937","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funds are available for heightening of sea walls to protect against flooding.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187450","187450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37938","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of likely increases in sea levels affecting Bournemouth East constituency in the next (a) 25, (b) 50 and (c) 100 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187454","187454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37939","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Nigerian government about including James Ibori in a prisioner transfer agreement.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187446","187446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37940","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the initiation of an independent, international war crimes inquiry in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187499","187499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37941","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the accountability process in Sri Lanka; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187500","187500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37942","2014-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to stop Japan's large-scale killing of whales and breaching of international treaties.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187489","187489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37943","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his US counterpart on Linda Carty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187490","187490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37944","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that citizens moving from the British Overseas Territories to Britain are settled as quickly and comfortably as possible.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187564","187564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37945","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department is providing in the process of installing democratic systems in Libya.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187561","187561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37946","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Prime Minister on allowing British Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies to lay individual wreaths at the Cenotaph on Remembrance Sunday.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187562","187562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37947","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage participation in sport in the British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187563","187563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37948","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on continued US-South Korean military drills in and around South Korea.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187559","187559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37949","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the British Overseas Territories are bound into the British constitution beyond any reasonable doubt.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187560","187560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37950","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on bringing an end to the civil war in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187558","187558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37951","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to take steps to ensure that UK aircraft comply with China's air defence zone.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187557","187557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37952","2014-02-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when Ministers in his Department last met representatives of the All Party Parliamentary Group in International Religious Freedom.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187538","187538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37953","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Ukranian counterpart aimed at bringing to an end the recent restrictions on human rights following protests in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187668","187668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37954","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187640","187640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37955","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what action he is taking to develop the UK's trading relationship with other Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187667","187667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37956","2014-02-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 196W, on re-employment, what the total cost was of those retirements.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187586","187586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37957","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that endangered species in the British Overseas Territories are protected.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187567","187567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37958","2014-02-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise the failure of the Tanzanian government to take action in relation to the seizure of Silverdale Farm by Mr Benjamin Mengi in his upcoming meeting with the President of Tanzania.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187581","187581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37959","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of (a) hospital costs, (b) care maintenance costs, (c) litigation costs, (d) morbidity costs, (e) other categories of cost and (f) total costs including all allowances of bacterial meningitis in each year from 2008 to 2013.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187579","187579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37960","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential annual cost of providing meningitis B vaccine to all 15-year-olds.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187585","187585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37961","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many confirmed cases of (a) bacterial meningitis and (b) meningitis B there were in each of the last five years for which data is available; and how many cases of each such category resulted in death.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187584","187584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37962","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health staff were employed by the NHS in each NHS trust in London in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187624","187624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37963","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many operations were cancelled on or after the day of admission in each NHS trust in London in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187625","187625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37964","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health and wellbeing boards include representatives of the criminal justice community.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187626","187626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37965","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when required standard operating procedures for independent sector abortion providers were first released; when updates to those procedures were released; and when the provision that it is good practice that one of the two certifying doctors has seen the woman, though this is not a legal requirement first appeared in those procedures.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197614","197614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37966","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many out-patient appointments were cancelled in each NHS trust in London in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187630","187630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37967","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people (a) entered and (b) completed drugs treatment in the last 12 months for which figures are available; and in each case how many people were treated for (i) opioid, (ii) cocaine, (iii) cannabis and (iv) amphetamine addiction.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187627","187627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37968","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187642","187642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37969","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in the UK have had age-related macular degeneration in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187684","187684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37970","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2014, Official Report, columns 650-1W, on abortion, when the issue with extracting data from the HSA4 form first started to occur; and what steps the Government is taking to address the problem.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187682","187682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37971","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2014, Official Report, columns 650-1W, on abortion, if he will publish the available data on how many women seeking an abortion met the authorising medical practitioner in each year since 1984.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187683","187683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37972","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of (a) the number and (b) the age groups of tinnitus sufferers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187687","187687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37973","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had about use of EMA40 to treat shingles.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187688","187688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37974","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss post-operation joint replacements for elderly people with the BMA and other medical bodies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187700","187700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37975","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of cases of shingles in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187689","187689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37976","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of elderly people who have had post-operation problems with joint replacements in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187701","187701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37977","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discretion GPs will have not to make patients records automatically available to NHS schemes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187690","187690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37978","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had about use of the Eylea form of aflibercept.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187685","187685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37979","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on access to treatment for patients of pseudoxanthoma elasticum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187535","187535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37980","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many East of England Ambulance Trust vehicles were diverted to hospitals in North London between 1 January and 9 February 2014.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187532","187532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37981","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to rename the Department of Health as the Department for Public Health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187572","187572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37982","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change about the effects of cold homes on (a) individual health and (b) NHS services.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187554","187554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37983","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions Barnet and Chase Farm Hospital Trust Maternity unit at Barnet Hospital was put on divert between 1 January and 9 February 2014.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187534","187534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37984","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions Barnet and Chase Farm Hospital Trust Accident and Emergency unit at Barnet Hospital was put on divert between 1 January and 9 February 2014.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187533","187533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37985","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on public health of youth violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187574","187574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37986","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average (a) length and (b) cost was, including all intensive care and surgical on-costs, of a hospital admission owing to a case of bacterial meningitis in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187578","187578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37987","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the average cost to the public purse of treating repeated episodes of depression by (a) drugs, (b) individual counselling and (c) mindfulness-based therapy in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187485","187485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37988","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to tackle neknomination.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187487","187487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37989","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the projected rise in cancer cases.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187478","187478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37990","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the quantity and capacity of NHS dental provision is determined; and what requirement there is to plan provision based on population.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187464","187464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37991","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the outpatient follow-up ratio average across all specialties was in each (a) NHS acute trust in Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) government region in England in (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12, (iv) 2012-13 and (v) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187444","187444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37992","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on retaining access to free diagnosis and treatment for every resident in England for all the diseases included in Schedule 1 of the National Health Service (Charges to Overseas Visitors) Regulations 2011.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187447","187447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37993","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of introducing safe staffing levels for (a) accident and emergency units, (b) doctors, (c) midwives and (d) social workers comparable to current nursing standards.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187471","187471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37994","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Cancer Outcomes and Services dataset is complete; and whether the symptom first noted date section of that dataset is available for use by clinical researchers.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187472","187472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37995","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for changes in the number of people being detained under the Mental Health Act 1983 over the last five years; and what plans he has to reduce instances of mental health patients being detained in police custody rather than a healthcare setting.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187473","187473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37996","2014-02-12","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many former care staff and teachers who worked in approved schools or community homes with education in the 1970s and 1980s in (a) England and Wales and (b) North Wales have been arrested for offences of (i) physical assault and (ii) sexual offences against former residents of the institutions in the last 30 years; how many such people have been (A) subsequently charged, (B) tried, (C) found guilty and (D) had convictions overturned on appeal.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187494","187494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37997","2014-02-13","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Migrant Help will have an office in Wrexham to assist in giving advice to asylum seekers there as part of its contract to assist and advise asylum seekers.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187577","187577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37998","2014-02-12","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many claimants who sent Pre-Action Protocol letters to her Department in relation to immigration decisions which were not responded to within three months have subsequently sought judicial review proceedings.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187555","187555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37999","2014-02-13","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date officials in her Department were first made aware that the hon. Member for Forest of Dean had concerns over the immigration status of his cleaner.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187536","187536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38000","2014-02-13","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individuals detained in immigration removal centres have been transferred to hospital following sectioning under the Mental Health Act 1983 from (a) Colnbrook Immigration Removal Centre, (b) Hammondsworth Immigration Removal Centre, (c) Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre and (d) all other immigration removal centres in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187527","187527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38001","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners have been sentenced (a) for drug offences and (b) under section 1(1) of the Street Offences Act 1959 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187526","187526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38002","2014-02-12","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Pre-Action Protocol letters in relation to immigration decisions have been received by her Department in each of the last five years; and how many such letters have been responded to within (a) 14 days and (b) three months.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187497","187497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38003","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made on the enquiry by Judge Macur into the Waterhouse (North Wales Tribunal) enquiry; and when this report is planned to be released.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187496","187496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38004","2014-02-12","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to enable minimum pricing for alcohol.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187693","187693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38005","2014-02-12","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187643","187643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38006","2014-02-13","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications are currently on hold pending the outcome of the High Court judgment on the minimum income threshold for sponsoring non-EEA partners and dependent children applying in the family route.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187587","187587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38007","2014-02-13","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the guidance on the UK Border Agency's website entitled, Checks for staff employed from 1 May 2004 to 28 February 2008 was last updated.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187602","187602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38008","2014-02-13","House of Commons Commission","2014-02-10","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the average wait time is for callers to the PICT helpdesk.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187524","187524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38009","2014-02-13","Department for International Development","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's and non-departmental public body's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps her Department has taken to monitor the performance of each supplier following the contract award.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187592","187592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38010","2014-02-13","Department for International Development","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether funding has been provided to the Ugandan parliament's Committee on Human Rights Affairs through the Deepening Democracy programme Phase 2; and whether such funding will be so provided during the remainder of the programme.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187634","187634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38011","2014-02-13","Department for International Development","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of aid pledged to Haiti by her Department following the earthquake in January 2010 has arrived in that country to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197623","197623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38012","2014-02-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of reports of discriminatory practices towards the Tamil people in Sri Lanka relating to (a) political rights, (b) education and (c) appropriation of land.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197620","197620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38013","2014-02-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking in Sri Lanka to create lasting peace and reconciliation.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197621","197621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38014","2014-02-13","Department for International Development","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of aid pledged to Pakistan by her Department following the floods in July and August 2010 has arrived in that country to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197622","197622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38015","2014-02-13","Department for International Development","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of aid pledged by her Department to the Philippines following Typhoon Haiyan has arrived in that country to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197618","197618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38016","2014-02-12","Department for International Development","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187644","187644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38017","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187645","187645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38018","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2013, Official Report, column 324W, on employment tribunal services, if he will publish the analysis sought in that question.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197617","197617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38019","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria will be used to award transforming rehabilitation contracts in respect of women's services.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187665","187665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38020","2014-02-13","Home Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her Answer of 20 January 2014, Official Report, column 26W, on human trafficking: victim support schemes, what support services are provided by local authorities to victims of human trafficking after 45 days in shelters; what other mainstream support provisions are available; what support is provided to a person who wishes to return to their home country; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187656","187656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38021","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure women released from prison into a different-contract package area receive high quality and holistic rehabilitation services and support.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187568","187568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38022","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that the proposed General European Data Protection Regulation does not prevent health research involving personal data from taking place.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187610","187610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38023","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders who (a) breached their licence conditions and (b) re-offended while on licence were recalled to prison in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187481","187481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38024","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 61W, on procurement, when the information sought by the original question will be provided.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187523","187523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38025","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps Ministers in his Department took when first informed of allegations of mistreatment at Medomsley Detention Centre.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187521","187521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38026","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support his Department is providing to the victims of mistreatment at Medomsley Detention Centre.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187520","187520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38027","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when Ministers in his Department were first informed of allegations of mistreatment at Medomsley Detention Centre.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187522","187522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38028","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of reducing the number of mother and baby units from three to one on the ability of women in prison to maintain family contact.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187493","187493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38029","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) male and (b) female prison officers have been convicted of (i) any criminal offence and (ii) a criminal offence relating to their role as a prison officer by offence type in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187482","187482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38030","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prison officers working in (a) male and (b) female prisons are (i) male and (ii) female.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187484","187484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38031","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) male and (b) female prison officers have been the subject of internal disciplinary action in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187483","187483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38032","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what projections his Department has made of the female prison population over the next five years.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187442","187442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38033","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria he plans to use to award Transforming Rehabilitation contracts in respect of women's services.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187443","187443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38034","2014-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the likely number of appeals against decisions on entitlement to (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment in the next two years.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187469","187469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38035","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the closure of open women's prisons on reoffending rates.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187506","187506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38036","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of women who will be recalled to custody under his Department's Transforming Rehabilitation proposals.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187505","187505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38037","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to balance the legal rights and responsibilities of employees and employers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187546","187546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38038","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the budget of the Office of the Public Guardian will be in 2014-15.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187548","187548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38039","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many parliamentary questions for answer on a named day were answered by his Department (a) on the named day, (b) after the named day with prior notification to the hon. Member concerned and (c) after the named day without prior notification to the hon. Member concerned between 1 November 2013 and 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187474","187474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38040","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many parliamentary questions for written answer on a named day answered by his Department after the named day without prior notification to the relevant hon. Member concerned between 1 November 2013 and 31 January 2014 were answered (a) one, (b) two to five, (c) six to 10, (d) 11 to 20 and (e) 21 or more days after the named day.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187475","187475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38041","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was for his Department to provide an answer to parliamentary questions for answer on a named day that were answered after the named day without prior notification to the hon. Member concerned between 1 November 2013 and 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187476","187476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38042","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) ordinary written questions and (b) questions for answer on a named day were received by his Department between 1 November 2013 and 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187477","187477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38043","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision to close two of the three mother and baby units in prisons on the distance women are held from their families.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187531","187531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38044","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions have been secured for trespassing on the railway in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187529","187529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38045","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women will be recalled to custody under the Transforming Rehabilitation proposals.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187530","187530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38046","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the three probation level input indicators due to be published in autumn 2012.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187569","187569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38047","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average full apportioned cost to probation of delivering a community order or suspended sentence order to the service definition in the National Offender Management Service specification was for the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187570","187570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38048","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were sentenced to (a) less than one month imprisonment, (b) between one and two months imprisonment, (c) between two and three months imprisonment, (d) between three and six months imprisonment, (e) between six and nine months imprisonment and (f) between nine and 12 months imprisonment in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187571","187571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38049","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals against decisions on entitlement to (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment there were in each month in each of the last three years in each court and in each local authority area.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187550","187550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38050","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the potential effect of the proposed General European Data Protection Regulation on medical research.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187540","187540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38051","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many notifications were sent by a court or fixed penalty office to the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency following the accumulation of six penalty points by a new driver within the two year probationary period in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187576","187576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38052","2014-02-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many notifications of endorsement from a court or fixed penalty office of a driver who meets the criteria of the Road Traffic (New Drivers) Act 1995 were sent to the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency following the accumulation of six penalty points by a new driver within the two year probationary period in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187575","187575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38053","2014-02-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187646","187646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38054","2014-02-12","Scotland Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187647","187647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38055","2014-02-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent discussions the Electoral Commission has had with the Electoral Registration Officer for Denbighshire on what lessons can be drawn from his success in increasing registration in the Vale of Clwyd.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187543","187543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38056","2014-02-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the accuracy and fairness of media coverage of electoral registration fraud.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187542","187542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38057","2014-02-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what steps the Electoral Commission is taking to correct misconceptions held by the public about levels of electoral registration fraud.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187541","187541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38058","2014-02-12","Department for Transport","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans there are to improve disability and pushchair access to Pokesdown for Boscombe Railway Station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187449","187449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38059","2014-02-12","Department for Transport","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187648","187648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38060","2014-02-13","Department for Transport","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each supplier following the contract award.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187593","187593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38061","2014-02-13","Department for Transport","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2014, Official Report, column 319W, on motor vehicles: registration, what the changes in 2013 to the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency's vehicle registration processing system were; and what the purpose of those changes was.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187609","187609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38062","2014-02-13","Department for Transport","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's Consultation on Local authority parking, published in December 2013, whether primary legislation would be needed to abolish the use of fixed or mobile closed circuit television cameras for parking enforcement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187628","187628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38063","2014-02-13","Department for Transport","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the likely level of underspend in respect of the Office of Low Emission Vehicles up to 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197619","197619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38064","2014-02-12","Wales Office","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187650","187650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38065","2014-02-12","Women and Equalities","2014-02-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187641","187641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38066","2014-02-12","Women and Equalities","2014-02-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what targets she has set for the representation of women on Government departmental boards.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187508","187508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38067","2014-02-12","Women and Equalities","2014-02-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of whether the recruitment process for non executive directors of Government departments meets equality and diversity guidance used in the wider Civil Service.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187509","187509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38068","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans she has to review the Gender Recognition Act 2004 to remove the spousal veto for gender reassignment.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187510","187510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38069","2014-02-12","Women and Equalities","2014-02-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether her Department operates a video relay telephony service to those for whom British Sign Language is their first language.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187511","187511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38070","2014-02-12","Women and Equalities","2014-02-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what guidance her Department has provided to other Departments on the provision of video relay telephony services to those for whom British Sign Language is their first language.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187512","187512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38071","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claiming employment and support allowance and issued with a sanction did not keep their claim live in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187528","187528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38072","2014-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for changes in the number of appeals against decisions on entitlement to (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment (i) over the last three years and (ii) as predicted to occur over the next two years.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187470","187470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38073","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of employment and support allowance claimants who appealed against a work capability assessment decision in 2012-13 were (a) eligible for and (b) received Crisis Loan payments.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187455","187455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38074","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 421W, on unemployed people: basic skills, how many of the people referred who started on Skills Conditionality activities between August 2011 and August 2013 completed their course.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187466","187466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38075","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are currently awaiting a work capability assessment in (a) Chelmsford constituency and (b) Essex.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187467","187467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38076","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for the collection of the under-occupancy penalty of the decision of the Upper Tribunal (Administrative Appeals Chamber) on 10 January 2014, Appeal No. CH/140/2013, to dismiss the appeal against the decision of the appeal tribunal sitting at Bolton on 18 September 2012.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187515","187515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38077","2014-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have disputed a sanction of their benefit in each of the last five years have had their sanction overturned following appeal.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187495","187495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38078","2014-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK have disputed a sanction of their benefit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187492","187492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38079","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2014, Official Report, column 732W, on jobseeker's allowance, on which date in each of the months referred to in the Answer his Department conducted its count of the number of individuals with an adverse jobseeker's allowance decision.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187463","187463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38080","2014-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on whether requirements similar to those on landlords under Regulation 36 of the Gas Safety (Installation and Use) Regulations 1998 should also apply to the leaseholder market.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187488","187488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38081","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2014, Official Report, column 732W, on jobseeker's allowance: York, how many people in York Central constituency who had their benefit suspended as a result of an adverse jobseeker's allowance (JSA) sanction decision had their JSA restored (a) at the end of and (b) earlier than the end of their sanction period in (i) October 2012 and (ii) each month since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187460","187460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38082","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2014, Official Report, column 732W, on jobseeker's allowance: York, how many individuals there were with an adverse jobseeker's allowance sanction decision in (a) City of York, (B) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) England in (i) October 2012 and (ii) each month since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187462","187462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38083","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2014, Official Report, column 732W, on jobseeker's allowance: York, what the average period was for which jobseeker's allowance (JSA) was suspended for the 960 individuals from York Central constituency whose JSA was subjected to an adverse sanction decision between 22 October 2012 and 30 June 2013; and what the average period of suspension was for sanctioned JSA claimants in the UK over the same period.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187461","187461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38084","2014-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187651","187651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38085","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department uses to evaluate mandatory skills conditionality interventions.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187582","187582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38086","2014-02-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what course content the Skills Conditionality interventions made between August 2011 and August 2013 consisted of.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187583","187583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38101","2014-02-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage an increase in on-farm anaerobic digestion.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902559","902559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/38651","2014-02-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote economic growth in rural areas.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902571","902571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37689","2014-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child (UNCRC) when making new policy and legislation, if he will place in the Library all assessments of how new policy and legislation from his Department since January 2013 has given due consideration to the UNCRC.","Biography information for Natascha Engel","Natascha Engel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187399","187399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37690","2014-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to support start-up businesses in Barnsley.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187429","187429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37691","2014-02-11","Cabinet Office","2014-02-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for access to which public services photo ID is required.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187411","187411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37692","2014-02-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-07","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the effect on the size of the electorate of the removal from the electoral register of electors who fail to fill in the household registration form for two successive years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187379","187379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37693","2014-02-12","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the assessment by the Office of Tax Simplification of his proposals for a transferable tax allowance.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187393","187393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37694","2014-02-12","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff HM Revenue and Customs expects to dedicate to administering the transferable tax allowance (a) in its first year of operation and (b) each year thereafter.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187394","187394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37695","2014-02-12","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to HM Revenue and Customs of administering the transferable tax allowance in (a) its first year of operation and (b) each year thereafter.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187395","187395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37696","2014-02-12","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will become higher rate taxpayers between 2010-11 and 2014-15 as a result of changes to income tax rate thresholds.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187396","187396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37697","2014-02-11","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the average annual benefit to households and individuals in each constituent part of the UK and each region in England of reducing the rate of value added tax on (a) books and periodicals, (b) food and (c) children's clothing to zero.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187426","187426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37698","2014-02-12","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time taken by his Department is to answer a freedom of information request.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187439","187439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37699","2014-02-12","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of how much more VAT a couple with two children and earning 20,000 a year have paid in (a) cash terms and (b) as a proportion of their household income as a result of the increase in the standard rate of value added tax to 20 per cent.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187436","187436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37700","2014-02-12","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the net effect in (a) cash terms and (b) as a proportion of the average annual income of the 2.5 per cent increase in the standard rate of value added tax on (i) pensioner couples, (ii) single pensioners, (iii) couples with children and (iv) single parents with children.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187437","187437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37701","2014-02-12","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many firms benefited from the regional employer national insurance contributions holiday in each region.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187438","187438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37702","2014-02-11","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of levels of personal debt people resident in Scotland held in unsecured personal loans, secured personal loans, credit cards, store cards, hire purchase agreements and other unsecured personal borrowings in each of the last four financial years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187433","187433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37703","2014-02-11","HM Treasury","2014-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the average annual cost to consumers in Scotland of servicing personal debt held in the form of unsecured personal loans, secured personal loans, credit card debt, store card debt, hire purchase agreements and other unsecured personal borrowing; and if he will estimate the effect on such costs of lenders increasing their rates by (a) one per cent, (b) two per cent and (c) three per cent above present levels.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187434","187434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37704","2014-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he, Ministers or officials of his Department have had with the Mayor of London and officials or members of the Greater London Authority and the London Borough of Bromley on development of the upper site at Crystal Palace; and what the outcome of those discussions was.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187428","187428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37705","2014-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to promote the Green Investment Bank loan available to finance local authorities to convert to low energy street lighting.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187409","187409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37706","2014-02-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential benefit to consumers in the communications sector of the Government's proposals to streamline regulatory and competition appeals.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187440","187440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37707","2014-02-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her timetable is for reform of the regulatory and competition appeals processes in the communications sector.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187441","187441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37708","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what initiatives his Department is undertaking to monitor and raise educational attainment among children of minority ethnic origin.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187427","187427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37709","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many young people in Birmingham, Hall Green constituency will be affected by the reduction in funding for 18-year-olds at further education colleges.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187432","187432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37710","2014-02-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government about extending the Community Energy Scheme to local authorities in Scotland.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187413","187413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37711","2014-02-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with which local authorities his Department has had discussions regarding taking part in the Community Energy Scheme announced in December 2013.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187414","187414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37712","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of rape, sexual violence and murder of rape victims by members of the military in Burma; and what assessment he has made of whether such crimes amount to a crime against humanity.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187397","187397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37713","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent meetings HM Ambassador to Cambodia has had with family members of Cambodian political prisoners who remain in jail.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187417","187417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37714","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings he has had with Cambodian political and civil society leaders since May 2010.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187418","187418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37715","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Cambodian counterpart on (a) land grabs, (b) human rights, (c) free and fair elections and (d) freedom of expression in that country.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187419","187419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37716","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Cambodia.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187420","187420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37717","2014-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the UK took (a) unilaterally and (b) through the EU prior to elections in Cambodia in July 2013 to ensure they were free and fair.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187421","187421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37718","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of selective dorsal rhizotomy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187398","187398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37719","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has the Department made of a link between levels of deprivation and incidence of meningitis.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187391","187391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37720","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans that his NHS patient data sharing initiative will be applied to privately-provided primary care.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187405","187405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37721","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on GPs who decide to operate an opt-in rather than opt-out procedure for their patients in relation to his NHS patient data-sharing initiative.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187406","187406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37722","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients have received proton beam therapy at (a) the facility in Villigen, Switzerland and (b) each of the two US facilities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187374","187374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37723","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost of providing proton beam therapy to an NHS patient is at (a) the facility in Villigen, Switzerland and (b) the two facilities in the US.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187375","187375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37724","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures are in place to ensure that NHS patients who require proton beam therapy are able to access it within a clinically appropriate timeframe.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187376","187376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37725","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients have required proton beam therapy in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187377","187377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37726","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the number of people who would benefit from mindfulness-based therapies approved by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE); and how many people were being treated by mindfulness-based therapies approved by NICE in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187382","187382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37727","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by what process the post of Director of Immunisation will be filled when the incumbent Director's contract expires.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187383","187383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37728","2014-02-11","Home Office","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how UKBA monitors contractual levels of staffing provided by GEO Group UK Ltd at Harmondsworth and Colnbrook Immigration Removal Centres.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187415","187415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37729","2014-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the anticipated underspend for the financial year 2013-14 for each of the 35 probation trusts in England and Wales is.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187387","187387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37730","2014-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of trainee probation officers that the National Probation Service will need to recruit for financial years 2014-15 and 2015-16.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187388","187388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37731","2014-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to ensure that there will be sufficient experienced probation officers allocated to the 21 community rehabilitation companies to assess risk escalation of offenders who are supervised by those companies.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187389","187389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37732","2014-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what funds he will make available to the National Probation Service after 1 June 2014 for the recruitment of trainee probation officers in England and Wales.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187390","187390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37733","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if the Government will undertake a full review of the sentencing guidelines relating to dangerous driving offences.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187435","187435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37734","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many safeguarding referrals remained unprocessed by the Office of the Public Guardian on the first day of each month from 1 May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187422","187422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37735","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many safeguarding referrals were (a) received and (b) processed by the Office of the Public Guardian in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187423","187423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37736","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by the Office of the Public Guardian in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187424","187424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37737","2014-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the publicised (a) opening and (b) closing date was of each recruitment campaign for a magistrate vacancy since May 2010; for which of those recruitment campaigns the application process was closed early; and on what date each such early closure took place.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187425","187425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37738","2014-02-11","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-07","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which council ward in Denbighshire had the biggest decrease in electorate from 1997 to 2013; and what the electorate in that ward was for each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187380","187380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37739","2014-02-11","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-07","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if he will place in the Library a copy of the minutes of the meeting of the Electoral Commission held at 9.00am on 18 September 2013.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187381","187381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37740","2014-02-11","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-07","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the potential effect the introduction of photo ID as a prerequisite for voting would have on turnout in each (a) socio-economic group, (b) ethnic group and (c) 10-year cohort from 18 years old.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187412","187412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37741","2014-02-11","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-07","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2014, Official Report, columns 468-0W, on electorate, if he will publish in full the minutes in Annex B of the Electoral Commission's letter, extracts from minutes of meetings held with hon. Members.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187378","187378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37742","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of long-term trends in (a) training and (b) employment in the shipping industry to the decline in the total number of UK seafarers between 2012 and 2013.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187384","187384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37743","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of long-term trends in (a) training and (b) employment in the shipping industry to the decline in the total number of UK ratings between 2012 and 2013.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187385","187385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37744","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of long-term trends in (a) training and (b) employment in the shipping industry to the decline in the total number of UK certificated officers between 2006 and 2013.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187386","187386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37745","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish the invitation to tender document for the new long Greater Anglia franchise expected to commence in October 2016; and when he expects to award that new franchise.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187407","187407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37746","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what service improvements he plans to incorporate into the new short Greater Anglia franchise from July 2014 to October 2016.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187408","187408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37747","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to ensure (a) refurbishment or (b) replacement of the rolling stock on (i) commuter and (ii) intercity services on the Greater Anglia franchise in the (A) short Greater Anglia franchise to October 2016 and (B) long Greater Anglia franchise after October 2016.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187400","187400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37748","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure any rolling stock refurbishment programmes in the short Greater Anglia franchise provide significant upgrades for customers.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187401","187401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37749","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will direct Network Rail to use National Journey Time Improvement Funding to ensure that infrastructure improvements to reduce journey times on the Great Eastern Main Line begin in Control Period 5 (2014-19).","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187402","187402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37750","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his estimate is of the number of commuters who will use Greater Anglia services at peak time in each of the next 20 years; and what plans he has to increase capacity (a) between London and Colchester and (b) on other key sections.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187403","187403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37751","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of employment trends in the shipping industry.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187404","187404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37752","2014-02-11","Department for Transport","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to bring forward the major upgrade of the Felixstowe to Nuneaton route including electrification into Control Period 5 for the purposes of supporting freight customers and passenger services in the East of England and on the Great Eastern Main Line.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187431","187431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37753","2014-02-11","Wales Office","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much Wales will receive in Barnett consequentials following the Government's announcement of a programme of 55 new flood defence improvement projects for 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187392","187392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37754","2014-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the annual (a) staffing and (b) other costs are of conducting medical interviews for employment and support allowance and disability living allowance applicants.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187410","187410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37755","2014-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will waive the 104 weeks' residency requirement for disability living allowance claimants who (a) have refugee status, (b) made their claim before this requirement was brought in and (c) are under 18 years old.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187416","187416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37756","2014-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claiming jobseeker's allowance who were sanctioned in 2013 subsequently found full-time employment within (a) one, (b) three, (c) six and (d) 12 months in each local authority in England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187430","187430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37292","2014-02-10","Attorney General","2014-02-06","To ask the Attorney General, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by the Law Officers' Departments since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187071","187071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37293","2014-02-10","Attorney General","2014-02-06","To ask the Attorney General, which paid public appointment contracts the Law Officers' Departments has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187010","187010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37294","2014-02-10","Attorney General","2014-02-06","To ask the Attorney General, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187238","187238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37295","2014-02-10","Attorney General","2014-02-06","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of staff of (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187260","187260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37296","2014-02-10","Attorney General","2014-02-06","To ask the Attorney General, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) the Law Officers' Departments and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187279","187279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37297","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187259","187259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37298","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187278","187278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37299","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187009","187009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37300","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187070","187070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37301","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the majority of Government services are still available throughout the sub-post office network.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187042","187042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37302","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent meetings he has had with representatives of Post Office Limited to discuss investment in the sub-post office network to allow sub-postmasters to grow their businesses.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187043","187043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37303","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) women and (b) men applied for the 24+ advanced learning loan in the 20013-14 academic year.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187046","187046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37304","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) women and (b) men aged 24 years old and above applied for Government financial assistance for further education in each of the academic years between 2008 and 2013.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187048","187048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37305","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer on state aid to Lord Stoddart of Swindon, House of Lords Official Report, 23 January 2014, WA column 166, what the subject is of each of the UK state aid cases currently before the European Commission for approval.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187055","187055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37306","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which colleges have incorrectly advertised eligibility and access to Student Loans Company services in the last year.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187134","187134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37307","2014-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many non-UK EU students studying at private universities used the Student Loan Company in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187157","187157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37308","2014-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students in each private university (a) have access to the student loan system, (b) are studying HNCs and HNDs and (c) are non-UK EU students using the Student Loan Company.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187158","187158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37309","2014-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the regulatory tests are for (a) public and (b) private institutions seeking to acquire degree awarding powers.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187200","187200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37310","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which Local Enterprise Partnerships shared a first draft of their Strategic Economic Plans with his Department by the end of December 2013; whether his Department provided feedback on each of these plans by the end of January 2014; and which such plans included specific proposals relating to (a) funding for skills provisions and (b) capital funding for further education colleges.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187172","187172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37311","2014-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the financial effect on small and medium-sized businesses of the requirement for CE marking of structural steel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187202","187202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37312","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of businesses with an annual rental value of 50,000 or less a year are owned by (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187174","187174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37313","2014-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to reduce the impact on small and medium-sized businesses of the requirement for CE marking of structural steel.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187203","187203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37314","2014-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when in the last 12 months he has met bodies from the steel industry to discuss the requirement for CE marking of structural steel.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187204","187204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37315","2014-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the RAB charge on loans made to students at alternative providers.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187207","187207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37316","2014-02-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187237","187237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37317","2014-02-11","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 216W, on re-employment, what the total cost was of those redundancies.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187208","187208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37318","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which of the public appointments made by Government in each department between 1 April and 30 September 2013 were to remunerated posts; and in what pay band each such appointment was.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187121","187121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37319","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the differences in registration rates between (a) the black and Asian communities and (b) the white community.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187133","187133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37320","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will commission research on the effect of (a) media coverage of electoral registration fraud, (b) politicians' comments on electoral registration fraud and (c) the Electoral Commission's coverage of electoral registration fraud on the public's perception of electoral fraud.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187129","187129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37321","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many regulations made since May 2010 contain a sunset clause.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187103","187103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37322","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many chairs of public bodies were (a) men and (b) women in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187049","187049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37323","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of chairs of public bodies appointed since 5 May 2010 are (a) men and (b) women.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187047","187047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37324","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187011","187011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37325","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187072","187072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37326","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which central government office estate buildings are currently (a) unoccupied and (b) under-occupied.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187257","187257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37327","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress has been made on relocating civil servants from expensive city centre locations since the publication of the Government's Estate Strategy in June 2013.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187258","187258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37328","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187239","187239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37329","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187261","187261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37330","2014-02-10","Cabinet Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187280","187280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37331","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2013, Official Report, columns 803-4W, on electoral register, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the reduction in the number of attainers registered to vote between 2009 and 2012; what steps he has taken to address that reduction; and how successful they have been.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187348","187348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37332","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187275","187275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37333","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187253","187253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37334","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187294","187294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37335","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of UK labour productivity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187305","187305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37336","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the European Commission on the rural fuel rebate scheme.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186985","186985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37337","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has held with members of the European Parliament representing (a) English, (b) Scottish, (c) Welsh, (d) Northern Ireland constituencies and (e) the European Committee of the Regions on the rural fuel rebate scheme.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186986","186986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37338","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187089","187089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37339","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187029","187029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37340","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what reports he has received on whether the Colombian mining industry, including companies listed on the London Stock Exchange, is contracting army units for private security purposes in Colombia.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187141","187141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37341","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the additional revenue secured since 2010 as a result of changes to the IR35 tax regulations affecting the self-employed.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187119","187119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37342","2014-02-10","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost of enforcement of the IR35 rules since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187120","187120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37343","2014-02-11","HM Treasury","2014-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what Barnett consequentials arise from the Government's proposals for High Speed Rail 2.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187205","187205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37344","2014-02-10","Church Commissioners","2014-02-06","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, when he last met the Rural Affairs Group of the Church of England.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187221","187221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37345","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 47 of the National Planning Policy Framework, whether local authorities are required to include greenbelt land in their five-year supply of deliverable housing sites if no other sites are available.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187222","187222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37346","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187240","187240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37347","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187262","187262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37348","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the full actuarial cost of fire deaths was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187224","187224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37349","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many fire deaths there were in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187225","187225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37350","2014-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library details of all transactions recorded by his Department under the Catering and Hospitality expenses types in the calendar year 2013 including (a) copies of invoices and (b) proof of payment, including date of payment.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187235","187235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37351","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for consideration of applications to the Bellwin Fund of the fact that the winter floods are still ongoing, making the extent of damage difficult to assess.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187301","187301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37352","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to extend the deadline for applications to the Bellwin Fund beyond the end of March 2014 in respect of damage caused by and recovery measures relating to the recent winter floods.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187300","187300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37353","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187281","187281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37354","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much has been collected in business rates in (a) Hyndburn constituency and (b) Rossendale in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187352","187352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37355","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many properties have been sold under the preserved Right-to-Buy scheme in each of the last five years; what the average discount given to house buyers was under the scheme in those years; and if he will list this information by local authority area.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187334","187334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37356","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of trends in local government procurement from small, local businesses.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187306","187306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37357","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many properties were sold under the Right to Buy scheme in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13; and what the average discount given to house buyers was under that scheme in those years in each local authority area.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187163","187163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37358","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of preserved right-to-buy sales on rental incomes for housing associations which were part of large-scale voluntary transfer schemes.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187165","187165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37359","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many replacement homes (a) are under construction or (b) have completed as a result of all right-to-buy sales subsequent to the enhanced discount introduced on 2 April 2012, by local authority.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187167","187167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37360","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what total amount of discount has been applied as part of the preserved right-to-buy sales in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187169","187169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37361","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to replace housing stock as a result of preserved right-to-buy sales.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187170","187170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37362","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total amount of discount is that has been applied as part of all right-to-buy sales in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187171","187171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37363","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many replacement homes (a) are under construction or (b) have completed as a result of preserved right-to- buy sales subsequent to the enhanced discount introduced on 2 April 2012, by local authority.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187166","187166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37364","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of preserved right-to-buy sales on affordable housing policy.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187164","187164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37365","2014-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 601W, on council tax, which local authorities have increased council tax and by what percentage amount in 2013-14.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187210","187210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37366","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to gain a more accurate representation of gypsy and traveller numbers in South Staffordshire constituency; and what steps he is taking to ensure that the duty of pitch provision is more evenly spread across all nearby local authority areas.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187181","187181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37367","2014-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, column 17, what assessment he has made of the number of properties offered under the help-to-buy scheme which are in areas insurance companies deem to be at high risk of flooding; and what discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on including such properties in the Flood Re insurance scheme.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187155","187155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37368","2014-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the proportion of private landlords renting to tenants in receipt of housing benefit; and what steps he is taking to ensure people in receipt of benefits are not excluded from the private rented sector.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187145","187145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37369","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will consider introducing an exemption for extending permitted development rights in national parks.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187057","187057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37370","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187012","187012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37371","2014-02-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187073","187073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37372","2014-02-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with Ofcom on the position of local television stations in Wales and Scotland on the electronic programme guide.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187004","187004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37373","2014-02-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by her Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187074","187074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37374","2014-02-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which paid public appointment contracts she has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187013","187013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37375","2014-02-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance her Department has issued to the Arts Council on its distribution of funds across urban and rural communities.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187179","187179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37376","2014-02-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) her Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to her.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187282","187282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37377","2014-02-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of staff of (a) her Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to her work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187263","187263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37378","2014-02-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) her Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to her.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187241","187241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37379","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187242","187242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37380","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Defence on 3 February 2014, Official Report, column 14, on European Defence Agency, what types of expenditure by the Agency fall into (a) its operational budget and (b) its functional budget; what the purpose is of the Agency's functional expenditure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187223","187223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37381","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187264","187264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37382","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187283","187283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37383","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that the Ministry of Defence Police adhere to the College of Policing standards.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187329","187329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37384","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve cyber security at Ministry of Defence sites.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187307","187307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37385","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many attempted cyber attacks on his Department were recorded in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187308","187308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37386","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British service personnel have been killed in live fire exercises in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187309","187309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37387","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 37 of his Department's Safety and Environmental Protection Assurance Report 2012-13, what the life-limiting features that cannot be mitigated through life extension programmes are for existing nuclear-powered submarines.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187336","187336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37388","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether plans to establish a Navy Safety Centre have been approved; and where this centre will be located.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187337","187337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37389","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps have been taken to install a buoyancy aid for embarked Apache attack helicopters.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187338","187338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37390","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many safety critical posts exist in Defence Equipment and Support; and how many such posts are currently vacant.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187339","187339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37391","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve the safety of personnel during live fire exercises.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187310","187310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37392","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on armed forces recruitment post-2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187311","187311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37393","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential implications of Scottish independence on recruitment to the armed forces.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187312","187312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37394","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many citizens of the Republic of Ireland are currently serving in the (a) Army and (b) Royal Navy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187313","187313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37395","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of Army officers are recruited from (a) Scotland, (b) England and Wales and (c) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187314","187314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37396","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of Royal Navy officers are recruited from (a) Scotland, (b) England and Wales and (c) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187315","187315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37397","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the Army is recruited from (a) Scotland, (b) England and Wales and (c) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187316","187316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37398","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what involvement UK armed forces currently have in Libya.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187321","187321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37399","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times the Movement and Transport Safety Regulator has identified instances of dangerous goods being transported from Afghanistan in each of the last five years; what the nature and risk was in each incident; and when each incident occurred.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187234","187234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37400","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which defence establishments are subject to Dangerous Substances and Explosive Atmosphere Regulations; and which establishment received a (i) stage 1 risk assessment and (ii) stage 2 risk assessment in the most recent period for which data are available.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187233","187233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37401","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent redundancies on the level of suitably experienced and qualified personnel.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187232","187232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37402","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for the outsourcing of Defence Munitions Plymouth.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187092","187092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37403","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual expenditure on the Trident nuclear weapons system, including all capital expenditure at HMNB Clyde, AWE Aldermaston and AWE Burghfield, has been since 2000.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187138","187138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37404","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the cost at outturn prices of the Trident replacement programme.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187135","187135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37405","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the cost at outturn prices of the D5 missile extension programme.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187136","187136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37406","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of developing and procuring a replacement missile for the Trident D5 missile for the remainder of the replacement submarine service life after 2042.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187137","187137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37407","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimated annual expenditure and percentage share of his  Department's procurement budget the design and construction of the Astute-class submarines will represent in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187143","187143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37408","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the (a) expenditure and percentage share of his Department's procurement budget that the design and construction of the Trident replacement submarines will represent and (b) what the running costs and percentage share of his Department's overall spending of the existing Trident nuclear weapons system will be in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187142","187142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37409","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of nuclear liabilities associated with berthing and decommissioning submarines, decontamination of associated sites and storage of related nuclear materials, including disaggregation by (a) out-of service submarines, (b) in-service submarines and (c) Trident replacement submarines.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187144","187144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37410","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many such posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187014","187014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37411","2014-02-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187075","187075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37412","2014-02-11","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 413W, on redundancy, what the cost to the public purse was of redundancies for officials who have subsequently been rehired by his Department.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187005","187005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37413","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Office since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187076","187076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37414","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which paid public appointment contracts his Office has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187015","187015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37415","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, columns 386-7W, on electoral register, how many local authorities inspect their own council tax records to find eligible electors.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187228","187228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37416","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, columns 181-2W, on electoral register, if he will make it his policy to collect data intended to improve efficiency in registration of electors.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187229","187229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37417","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 386W, on electoral register, on what dates the student forums established by his Department for the purpose of promoting registration have met in each region; and what the main collective outcomes of these meetings were.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187350","187350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37418","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 386W, on electoral register, if he will place a copy of the best practice to increase voter registration turnout in the Library.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187351","187351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37419","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 387W, on electoral register, if he will relay this information to hon. Members and local councillors on a regular basis.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187371","187371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37420","2014-02-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, columns 386-87W on electoral register, how his Department encourages local authorities to use their own council tax records to find eligible electors.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187227","187227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37421","2014-02-13","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will place in the Library a copy of the initial advertisement which was published in the Official Journal of the European Union for the priority schools building programme.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187373","187373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37422","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will consider reversing the reductions in funding for full-time education places for 18 year olds announced by his Department in January 2014.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187366","187366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37423","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2014, Official Report, column 52W, on private education: offences against children, on what date the inspector subject to direct allegations was suspended.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187369","187369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37424","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2014, Official Report, column 189W, on private education: offences against children, how many allegations of cases of child abuse at independent schools he is aware of.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187370","187370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37425","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effects of the reduction in funding for full-time education places for 18-year-olds on students from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187347","187347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37426","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187284","187284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37427","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in England in 2012-13 failed to get a GCSE grade A*-C in both English and mathematics.","Biography information for Mr Jeremy Browne","Mr Jeremy Browne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187302","187302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37428","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187265","187265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37429","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools were built (a) with and (b) without fire sprinklers in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187226","187226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37430","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on increasing the number of children adopted in England.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187220","187220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37431","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187243","187243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37432","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with HM Chief Inspector of Schools about the performance of free schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187196","187196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37433","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received from local authorities about overprovision of school places in areas where a free school or schools are (a) established or (b) proposed.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187197","187197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37434","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children being educated in free schools who qualify for free school meals.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187195","187195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37435","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many additional school places have been created by the free schools that (a) have been provided to date and (b) are projected to be provided in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187188","187188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37436","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received from any local authorities with a projected school place shortage that will not be met by free school provision.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187198","187198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37437","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consideration his Department has given to allowing local authorities to open a new school to meet school place demand; and what representations he has received on this issue.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187199","187199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37438","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the per pupil place value for money of free schools; and what effect the acquisition of sites (a) in London and (b) outside London has on that value for money.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187184","187184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37439","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupil vacancies there are in free schools in (a) London and (b) England; and what proportion of free schools opened in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013 have vacancies.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187185","187185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37440","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether any consented free school applications have been withdrawn to date by (a) the proposers in the community or (b) the proposed provider.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187186","187186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37441","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the capital and revenue costs of free schools that (a) have been provided to date, (b) are to be provided in 2013-14 and (c) are projected to be provided in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187187","187187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37442","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department's estimate of December 2012 that the 79 open free schools would create at least 34,000 additional school places was accurate.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187189","187189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37443","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average class size is in free schools open to date.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187190","187190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37444","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the parental complaints he has received connected with the termination of inspectors working for the Independent Schools Inspectorate relate to concerns over the treatment of children within the schools inspected.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187216","187216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37445","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the capacity of existing multiple academy trusts to take on the remaining community schools in (a) England and (b) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187191","187191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37446","2014-02-25","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many inspectors working for the Independent Schools Inspectorate have ceased to be deployed for reasons connected with statutory notices being served on schools to date.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187217","187217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37447","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children with a statement of special educational needs being educated in free schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187192","187192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37448","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children with (a) dyslexia and (b) dyspraxia being educated in free schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187193","187193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37449","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of free schools which participate in the relevant local authority's admissions process to enable pupil place planning.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187194","187194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37450","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers he expects to receive training under the Year of Code campaign.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187206","187206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37451","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff will be employed on the Year of Code Campaign; how many such staff were appointments from outside his Department; and where such jobs were advertised.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187156","187156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37452","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his response of 29 January 2014 to the hon. member for Cardiff West, Official Report, column 934, if he will release the qualifications of the teachers at the Al Madinah Free School in Derby at the beginning of the September 2013 school term.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187153","187153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37453","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the head of the Year of Code Campaign was appointed; where this vacancy was advertised prior to appointment; how the successful candidate was chosen; and what their salary is.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187160","187160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37454","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that free schools demonstrate compliance with the Public Sector Equality Duty by publishing their equality information and objectives.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187140","187140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37455","2014-02-13","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 60W, on schools: construction, which schools (a) have started construction and (b) will start construction before May 2015 under the current timetable.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187069","187069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37456","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 213W, on foster care, what activities local authorities are undertaking to support recruitment and retention of foster carers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187067","187067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37457","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer from the Minister for Housing of 22 January 2014, Official Report, column 212W, on families: disadvantaged, what criteria his Department uses to assess the success and value for money of its contribution to that programme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187100","187100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37458","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187016","187016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37459","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) capital and (b) revenue funding has been allocated by his Department to (i) Coventry City Council and (ii) each local authority in the West Midlands in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187038","187038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37460","2014-02-10","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187077","187077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37461","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's withdrawal of bursaries for trainee religious education teachers on the level of recruitment of religious education teachers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187097","187097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37462","2014-02-11","Department for Education","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funds were provided for bursaries for trainee religious education teachers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187098","187098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37463","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the UK-France Declaration on Nuclear Energy of 31 January 2014, what the dates and themes have been of the joint meetings held between respective national ministries, regulators, the Civil Nuclear Constabulary and the Gendarmerie to date; what decisions were taken and what actions arose; and what the cost has been of such co-operation since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186979","186979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37464","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reasons his Department supported the five-year contract award to Nuclear Management Partners to manage the Sellafield site.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186996","186996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37465","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department submitted its application to the European Commission for approval of providing state support for the financed radioactive waste and decommissioning plans for new build nuclear power plants; when he expects the decision on this application to be made; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the application.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186997","186997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37466","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187078","187078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37467","2014-02-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the average level of savings made by customers in each socio-economic group from each collective switching scheme supported by the Cheaper Energy Together fund.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187039","187039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37468","2014-02-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the (a) number of switches and (b) number of switches according to different indicators of vulnerability in each collective switching scheme supported by the Cheaper Energy Together fund.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187037","187037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37469","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187017","187017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37470","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187244","187244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37471","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187266","187266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37472","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187285","187285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37473","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will assess whether there was a benefit to the local supply chain in West Cumbria from the work of Nuclear Management Partners at Sellafield.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187345","187345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37474","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Scottish Government on storage of waste from Hunterston nuclear power station.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187343","187343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37475","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of contracts connected to decontamination work at Sellafield have been awarded to parent companies of Nuclear Management Partners; and what the value of those contracts is.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187344","187344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37476","2014-02-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that the Atomic  Energy Authority Police adhere to the College of Policing standards.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187330","187330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37477","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what on-the-ground inspections have been planned by the Environment Agency for the two new proposed shale gas drilling sites in Fylde.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187304","187304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37478","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187286","187286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37479","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187267","187267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37480","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187245","187245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37481","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187018","187018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37482","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187079","187079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37483","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what investigation his Department has carried out on the effects of neonicotinoids on waterways; and what monitoring the Government undertakes on the effects of the neonicotinoids moratorium on the aquatic environment.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187007","187007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37484","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the UK has taken towards achieving an international agreement under the UN Convention on the Law of the Sea including a globally accepted mechanism for designation of high seas marine protected areas before the end of the 69th Session of the UN General Assembly this year.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187008","187008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37485","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward winter fuel payments in order to protect pensioners from the price rise associated with off-grid energy at the onset of winter.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187116","187116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37486","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring off-grid energy within the remit of the energy regulator.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187114","187114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37487","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support people who move from a liquid petroleum gas boiler to a conventional boiler.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187115","187115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37488","2014-02-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of fuel price rises on households using liquefied petroleum gas.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187113","187113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37489","2014-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what provision exists for the recycling of plastic bags (a) nationally and (b) in Gloucestershire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187211","187211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37490","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to protect Christians in Syria.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187123","187123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37491","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the regional effect of the Government's approach to trade with Israel.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187173","187173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37492","2014-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his Ministerial colleagues the potential effect of the Government's response to the report on UK housing by the UN Special Rapporteur on adequate housing on the UK's relations with the Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187068","187068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37493","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the implementation of his Department's commitment to work with Colombia on the design of a business and human rights strategy; and how his Department is designing this strategy in consultation with a wide variety of civil society organisations.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187139","187139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37494","2014-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had on human rights during his recent visit to the Philippines; and what representations he made to his interlocutors in support of the UN Convention Against Torture and the rule of law in that country.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187146","187146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37495","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will commission a review of the operation of the Schengen Agreement and the UK's non-participation in the Schengen area arrangements.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187106","187106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37496","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will investigate the reasons for the gender pay gap at senior management structures 2, 3 and 4 of his Department.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186982","186982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37497","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187080","187080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37498","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187019","187019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37499","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of North Korea on the treatment of Christians in that country.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187054","187054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37500","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187246","187246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37501","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187268","187268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37502","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187287","187287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37503","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library all assessments of new policy and legislation from his Department since January 2013 which give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187317","187317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37504","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what current financial aid commitments the UK has in Libya.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187319","187319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37505","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place a copy of the accounts of the Ascension Island government for financial years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13 in the Library.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187324","187324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37506","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which vessels purchased commercial fishery licences for the waters off Ascension Island in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187322","187322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37507","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many fish of each species were caught in Ascension Island's commercial fishery in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187323","187323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37508","2014-02-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what talks his Department has had with the current Egyptian government on restoring democratic elections in Egypt.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187320","187320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37509","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2013, Official Report, column 648W, on National Clinical Excellence Awards, what consideration he has given to offering awards to those performing clinical roles other than that of consultant in medical teams.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187353","187353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37510","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2013, Official Report, column 648W, on National Clinical Excellence Awards, what proportion of NHS consultants are women; and what proportion of recipients of the awards are women.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187354","187354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37511","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS hospitals have been recorded as having general and acute bed occupancy in excess of 95 per cent on any one day in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187355","187355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37512","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of people are not registered with either an NHS dentist or a private dentist in each region.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187358","187358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37513","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reason was for his Department's decision not to introduce Enriched Culture Medium testing for Group B Strep on 1 January 2014. despite Ministers' previous commitment to do this; and who took that decision.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187359","187359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37514","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what visits Dame Carol Black has made since her appointment to promote the Public Health Responsibility Deal partners to (a) small and medium size enterprises, (b) other private companies, (c) public sector bodies and (d) third-sector organisations.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187357","187357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37515","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of calls made on (a) higher rate and (b) 0845 telephone numbers to GP surgeries in England in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187362","187362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37516","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients presented at (a) GP surgeries and (b) accident and emergency departments with dental problems in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187361","187361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37517","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Minister in his Department is a member of the inter-ministerial group on gang culture; and on what dates that Minister has attended meetings of the group.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187335","187335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37518","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) name, (b) location, (c) floor space, (d) tenure status and (e) value is of properties (i) owned and (ii) occupied by (A) his Department and (B) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187288","187288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37519","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times he has made an official visit to a hospital in Yorkshire and Humber.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187327","187327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37520","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him work outside of London; and in which local authorities such staff are located.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187269","187269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37521","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many civil servants are on each pay grade in (a) his Department and (b) agencies and public bodies accountable to him.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187247","187247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37522","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) district nurses, (b) health visitors, (c) community psychiatric nurses, (d) community matrons and (e) community learning disabilities nurses were employed by the NHS in each Clinical Commissioning Group area in London in (i) the latest period for which figures are available and (ii) the period 12 months prior to this; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187061","187061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37523","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health staff were employed by the NHS in each NHS trust in London in the last five years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187052","187052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37524","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which paid public appointment contracts he has (a) renewed and (b) not renewed since May 2010; and how many posts were held by (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187021","187021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37525","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many out-patient appointments were cancelled in each NHS trust in London in the last five years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187051","187051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37526","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many operations were cancelled on or after the day of admission in each NHS trust in London in the last five years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187050","187050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37527","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people detained under the Mental Health Act were transferred from Northern Ireland to hospitals in England in 2012-13.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186984","186984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37528","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by his Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187082","187082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37529","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2013, Official Report, column 147WH, what progress the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has made in developing guidance relating to trauma.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186980","186980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37530","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Contribution of the Minister of State for Care and Support of 4 September 2013, Official Report, column 148WH, what assessment he has made of how the work of clinical commissioning groups complies with NHS England guidelines.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186981","186981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37531","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the health budget in Crawley constituency was in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186994","186994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37532","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many errors in handling patient data resulting in breaches of confidentiality took place in the NHS in each of the last five years for which data are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186990","186990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37533","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether information on the treatment and diagnosis of sensitive health conditions will be excluded from the care.data extraction of patient data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186991","186991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37534","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures his Department has to audit the usage and security of patient data disclosed to third parties by the Health and Social Care Information Centre; whether any audits have been carried out on such usage; and whether any confidentiality breaches have taken place in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186992","186992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37535","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue guidance to (a) midwives and (b) GPs on reduced fetal movements during the third trimester of pregnancy to ensure that (i) appropriate measures are taken by healthcare professions, (ii) expectant mothers receive the best advice on precautions and (iii) best practice is shared throughout the health service.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 186999","186999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37536","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps heis taking to improve education on pregnancy and maternity for the prevention or avoidance of (a) stillbirths, (b) children born with fetal alcohol syndrome and (c) infant deaths due to pregnant women (i) smoking, (ii) having a high body mass index, (iii) drinking six or more units of alcohol at one time and (iii) bad nutrition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187000","187000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37537","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of introducing a universal 30 week pregnancy scan on identifying placenta complications leading to stillbirths; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187001","187001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37538","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the mandatory introduction of a bereavement policy on all businesses available to a parent whose child had died.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187002","187002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37539","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many healthcare assistants there were in each NHS trust in London in the last five years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187065","187065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37540","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished admissions episodes there were at (a) North West London Hospitals NHS Trust and (b) all other London hospitals in the last five years for which figures are available; what the (i) mean and (ii) median time waited was in days for cholecystectomy procedures in each such area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187063","187063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37541","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered nurses there were in each NHS trust in London in the last five years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187064","187064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37542","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received from ambulance trusts on the provision of stab vests for ambulance personnel.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187058","187058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37543","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished admissions episodes there were in the last five years for which figures are available in each NHS trust in London; what the (a) mean and (b) median time waited was in days for (i) hip replacement, (ii) hysterectomy and (iii) cataract removal procedures in each such area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187062","187062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37544","2014-02-10","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to ambulance trusts on the provision of stab vests for ambulance personnel.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187059","187059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37545","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS is of patients who require emergency dental treatment presenting at accident and emergency departments.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187154","187154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37546","2014-02-12","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has (a) taken and (b) plans to take in the next 12 months against IVF clinics which have destroyed embryos in error without patient consent; how many incidences of such destruction of embryos have occurred in each of the last five years; what action was taken under section 17(1)(c) of the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Act 1990; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187161","187161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37547","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 160W, on re-employment, what the total cost was of that redundancy.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187209","187209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37548","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the five point pregnancy plan developed by Tommy's; what recent assessment he has made of the benefits of a national campaign on pregnancy health to reduce rates of perinatal mortality; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187201","187201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37549","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with professional practitioner groups about screening ovarian cancer patients for the BRCA1 gene.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187213","187213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37550","2014-02-13","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with professional practitioner groups about guidelines for ovarian cancer diagnosis and treatment.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187214","187214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37551","2014-02-11","Department of Health","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Home Department on youth violence.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187212","187212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37552","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that speed limits are adhered to in rural constituencies.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187180","187180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37553","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of a link between the consumption of highly alcoholic beverages and anti-social and criminal behaviour; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187178","187178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37554","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date the proposed ban on khat will come into force.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187094","187094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37555","2014-02-10","Home Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the titles are of the individual public appointments that have been made by her Department since May 2010; and which of those appointees were women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187083","187083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/37556","2014-02-11","Home Office","2014-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures are in place to enable individuals to offer accommodation to refugees from Syria under the Government's recently announced scheme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 187099","187099"
