"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576763","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Brimstone missiles have been used in Syria in each month since December 2015.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45266","45266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576764","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2016 to Question 43906, what forecast he has made of the amount that will be spent on UK defence attachés in each country in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45291","45291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576765","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Northern Ireland University Air Squadron has reached its capacity of student places planned when it was set up.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45109","45109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576766","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to end payment of the operational allowance to armed forces personnel serving in South Sudan.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45090","45090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576767","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of physical training provided at the Infantry Battle School in Brecon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45101","45101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576768","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent under each cost heading by UK defence attachés in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45190","45190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576769","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the strength was of the Royal Navy Reserve in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45253","45253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576770","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what works took place on the engines of the Type 45 Destroyers while they were collectively docked during the summer of 2016.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45254","45254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576771","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which of the Type 45 Destroyers are (a) available for operations, (b) being used for training, (c) preparing to deploy and (d) being refitted.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45255","45255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576772","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many sailors have been recruited to the Royal Navy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45256","45256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576773","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to expand the Royal Naval Reserve.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45257","45257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576774","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to renew the capabilities provided by the former RFA Diligence for repair and maintenance of Royal Navy and Royal Fleet Auxiliary vessels.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45203","45203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576775","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure serving Scottish soldiers' qualifications are recognised by civilian contractors when they wish to undertake trade training while stationed in England.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45191","45191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576776","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what vessels of all types are available to the Royal Naval Reserve for training.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45176","45176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576777","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) reservists, (b) Cadet Forces adult volunteers and (c) cadets of the three services there are in West Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45177","45177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576778","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the strategic military importance of Gibraltar to the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45163","45163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576779","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraphs 5.36 to 5.38 of the Cabinet Manual, what the Government's policy is on whether the convention that a debate in Parliament should be held before troops are committed in military action applies if troops are deployed in a non-combat role but then subsequently become involved in sustained and proactive combat activities as a result of a change in circumstances or a change in mission.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45137","45137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576780","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to increase the level of defence spending that goes to small firms.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45161","45161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576781","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the change in defence spending has been since May 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45162","45162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576782","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK's vote to leave the EU on the relationship between the European Investment Bank and UK universities.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45180","45180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576783","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial resources are available to schools from (a) her Department and (b) local authorities for the installation of automatic fire sprinklers.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45189","45189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576784","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will hold discussions with HM Treasury on the potential to fully fund apprenticeships for 16 to 18 year olds from savings accrued as a result of the introduction of the Apprenticeship Levy.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45105","45105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576785","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with large employers on the effect on their take-up of apprenticeships of the new funding arrangements proposed for apprenticeships for 16 to 18 year olds, published on 12 August 2016.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45106","45106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576786","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on safety of buildings on pupils of removing the expectation from guidance that most new schools should have automatic fire sprinkler systems fitted.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45102","45102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576787","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the impact assessment for her Department's proposals for changes in funding rates for colleges and providers, published on 12 August 2016.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45104","45104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576788","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make a statement about the implications for apprenticeship take-up by 16 to 18 year olds of her Department's proposals for changes in funding rates for colleges and providers, published on 12 August 2016.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45107","45107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576789","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the proportionate level of effect of her Department's proposals for changes in apprenticeship funding, published on 12 August 2016, on (a) small employers, (b) young people in deprived areas and (c) apprenticeships offered in the service and tourism sectors.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45108","45108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576790","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been allocated from the Condition Improvement Fund for 2016-17; and how much from that Fund was allocated in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45243","45243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576791","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the contract of employment of the Chief Executive of the Education Funding Agency expires.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45211","45211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576792","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils on the National Schools Database are not assigned to a specific school or registered for home tuition.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45288","45288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576793","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the ability of maintained nursery schools and children's centres to remain financially viable following recent changes to their funding.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45260","45260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576794","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school leavers in each of the local authorities of the Liverpool City Region who were (a) entitled and (b) not entitled to free school meals went to university in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45287","45287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576795","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) nursery schools, (b) day-care facilities and (c) children's centres in (i) Birmingham, Erdington constituency, (ii) the West Midlands and (iii) the UK have (A) declared insolvency and (B) closed due to funding shortages in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45259","45259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576796","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academies have been removed from their multi academy trust on the initiative of (a) Regional School Commissioner and (b) Minister in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45322","45322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576797","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the procedures are for people involved in assessing applications for the Condition Improvement Fund to contact applicants seeking further information when required.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45244","45244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576798","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2016 to Question 43735, how many of the applications received in 2015 and subsequently approved the Regional School Commissioner initially recommended to be declined.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45247","45247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576799","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff at the Education Funding Agency assist with assessing applications to the Condition Improvement Fund; and how many staff assisted with such applications in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45240","45240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576800","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications were made for funding for substantial building repair work at (a) secondary and (b) primary schools in 2015-16; and how many such applications for such funding there were in 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45241","45241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576801","2016-09-12","Department for Education","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions the Chief Executive of the Education Funding Agency met her predecessor in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45242","45242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576802","2016-09-12","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to mark Anti-Slavery Day 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45299","45299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576803","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dairy farmers there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45330","45330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576804","2016-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many Rural Payments Agency staff have been tasked with responding to telephone enquiries from farmers on the Basic Payments Scheme in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45230","45230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576805","2016-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what UK representation there is at the International Union for Conservation of Nature World Conservation Congress.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45333","45333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576806","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations she has received from scientists and other experts on the use of neonicotinoids and their effect on the bee population.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45289","45289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576807","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent research her Department has undertaken on the link between neonicotinoids and bee populations.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45290","45290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576808","2016-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the number of badgers to be culled in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45110","45110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576809","2016-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the press release by Natural England of 29 July 2016 to issue a licence permitting the control of up to 10 buzzards, if her Department will take steps to ensure that the granting of such licences does not endanger the buzzard population.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45114","45114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576810","2016-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's policy is on future funding of the LEADER and Countryside Stewardship schemes; what discussions she has had with her Ministerial colleagues on the funding of those schemes; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45127","45127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576811","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the (a) effectiveness and (b) value for money of the badger cull.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45099","45099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576812","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what grants her Department has paid to the RSPB in each of the last five years; and for what purpose each such grant was paid.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45082","45082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576813","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to eradicate bovine tuberculosis.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45173","45173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576814","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on the maintenance of current restrictions on the use of neonicotinoids once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45172","45172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576815","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations she has received from scientists and policy experts on her policy on the badger cull.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45174","45174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576816","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Sudan on bringing peace to South Sudan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45206","45206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576817","2016-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2016 to Question 43364, what steps the Government has taken to work with international partners to hold Daesh to account for its crimes since 21 July 2016.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45154","45154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576818","2016-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 24 March 2016 to Question 31582, whether the Government has offered support to the government of Iraq on collecting forensic evidence of genocide committed against the Yazidis and other religious minority groups.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45151","45151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576819","2016-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings have taken place between ministers of his Department and their Saudi Arabian counterparts since 25 March 2015; and at how many of those meetings concerns were discussed about alleged breaches of International Humanitarian Law in Yemen by air strikes.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45152","45152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576820","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Chinese government on banning organ tourism to China.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45143","45143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576821","2016-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) consultants and (b) seconded staff (i) are working and (ii) have been recruited to work at his Department in the last three years; and from which (A) companies, (B) departments and (C) other organisations such staff were recruited or seconded.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45153","45153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576822","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Chinese government on disputed islands in the South China Sea.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45205","45205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576823","2016-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of his Department's staff have resigned in the last six months.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45229","45229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576824","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 June 2016 to Question 40553, whether (a) local Health and Wellbeing Boards, (b) Clinical Commissioning Groups, (c) NHS Trusts, (d) hon. Members and (e) members of the public will be consulted ahead of the implementation of Sustainability and Transformation Plans.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45277","45277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576825","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the report of the Decision Support Unit commissioned by NICE, Assessing technologies that are not cost-effective at zero price, published in July 2014, what progress has been made on the appraisal of combination medicines; and how policy for dealing with such medicines has changed as a result of that report.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45231","45231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576826","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidelines his Department issues to NHS Foundation Trusts on the publication of board papers.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45278","45278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576827","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans (a) his Department and (b) NHS England have to report on the outcome of the process to consider the future of the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45232","45232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576828","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the NHS Sustainability and Transformation Plan for Coast, Humber and Vale.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45274","45274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576829","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the feedback NHS England gave to the Coast, Humber and Vale footprint area on the first draft of their Sustainability and Transformation Plan which was submitted on 30 June 2016.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45276","45276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576830","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent from the public purse on printing and postage of employees' payslips in the last year for which figures are available; and if he will take steps to ensure that NHS employees receive their payslips electronically.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45227","45227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576831","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent staff from (a) his Department, (b) NHS England, (c) NHS commissioners, (d) NHS providers and (e) local authorities are working on the NHS Sustainability and Transformation Plan (STP) for Coast, Humber and Vale; and how much has been spent to date on the Coast, Humber and Vale STP.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45275","45275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576832","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS is of using agency nurses from overseas.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45316","45316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576833","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he anticipates an increase in the uptake of medical thrombectomy for the treatment of acute stroke in NHS hospitals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45317","45317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576834","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many premature babies were born in (a) England and (b) each local authority in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45215","45215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576835","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the funding gap between research spending on adult autism and other health conditions.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45216","45216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576836","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has received a copy of the report by the Westminster Commission on Autism, entitled A Spectrum of Obstacles, published in July 2016; and what plans he has to implement that report's recommendations.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45217","45217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576837","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of making selective dorsal rhizotomy surgery available on the NHS for young people with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45210","45210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576838","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons restrictions on advertising and promotional deals on unhealthy foods were not included in the Government's childhood obesity plan.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45212","45212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576839","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has further to centralise the delivery of acute stroke services in metropolitan areas.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45318","45318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576840","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished admission episodes there were with a primary diagnosis of mental and behavioural disorder for patients aged 0 to 18 years in 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45294","45294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576841","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were admitted to adult inpatient mental health wards in 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45295","45295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576842","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children and (b) adults spent time in a police station as a place of safety due to their mental health condition in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45296","45296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576843","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the psychological support available for people with dystonia and other neurological conditions; and if he will take steps to improve the process of such support.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45245","45245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576844","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients aged 0 to 18 years attending accident and emergency departments in 2015-16 had a psychiatric condition.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45293","45293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576845","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons his Department did not include the eight key actions, recommended by Public Health England in its report, Sugar reduction: the evidence for action, published in October 2015, in the Government's childhood obesity plan.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45246","45246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576846","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which of the vanguard sites for the new care models programme under the NHS England Five Year Forward View have (a) considered Hepatitis C as part of their programme and (b) engaged with operational delivery networks for Hepatitis C.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45249","45249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576847","2016-09-13","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what activities have been undertaken by (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department at (i) Richmond House, London and (ii) Quarry House, Leeds to promote breastfeeding during World Breastfeeding Week 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45286","45286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576848","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish a timetable for the roll-out of the General Practice Resilience Programme to support GP practices in Mid Sussex constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45262","45262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576849","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, to what extent NICE has involved external stakeholders and charities in reviewing how well the incremental cost effectiveness ratio is working in making new cancer medicines available to patients on the NHS.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45233","45233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576850","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of mobile surgical health theatres; and whether such centres are included in the Sustainability and Transformation Plans.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45270","45270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576851","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are registered with diabetes in (a) Burnley constituency and (b) Lancashire.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45239","45239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576852","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reusing dispensed but unused returned drugs in the NHS.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45077","45077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576853","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding there has been for (a) practice nurses, (b) physician assistants, (c) practice managers and (d) receptionists in Mid Sussex constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45078","45078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576854","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that women suffering from metastatic HER2 breast cancer receive (a) the Kadcyla form of Trastuzumab emtansine and (b) other required medication.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45079","45079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576855","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the NHS of dispensed but unused prescription drugs.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45086","45086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576856","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2016 to Question 42381, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the immigration status of NHS employees from other EU countries when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45083","45083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576857","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the merits of offering unused returned drugs to developing countries.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45085","45085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576858","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has paid BT for the licensing, deployment and support of acute IT systems in the south of England.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45133","45133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576859","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS mental health trusts have been rated by the Care Quality Commission as (a) inadequate and (b) requiring improvement since the new rating system was introduced in April 2015.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45134","45134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576860","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what new investment NHS England has approved for the provision of additional Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services and eating disorder beds since April 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45135","45135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576861","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many additional practice-based mental health therapists have been appointed to GP practices in Mid Sussex constituency since 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45125","45125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576862","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on delivering the integration of primary and community services with seven-day access in Mid Sussex constituency since 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45095","45095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576863","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings he has had with the BMA in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45131","45131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576864","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals he has visited in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45132","45132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576865","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the effect of the vote to leave the EU on his policy to provide full seven-day NHS services.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45130","45130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576866","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with multiple sclerosis aged (a) 0-10, (b) 11-20, (c) 21-40, (d) 41-60, and (e) 61+ years old in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45142","45142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576867","2016-09-12","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England is operating a moratorium on the opening of new mental health beds in the areas of Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services and eating disorders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45136","45136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576868","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges on the use of simple home-cooked food to reduce diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45140","45140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576869","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with opticians' associations on opticians spotting illness when carrying out eyesight checks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45141","45141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576870","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 22 January 2016 to Question 22462 and 28 June 2016 to Question 40748, when NHS England plans to publish findings from its review of individual funding requests for palivizumab; whether that review will include details of the number of individual funding requests submitted, accepted and declined; and what the reason is for the time taken to publish the findings from that review.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45146","45146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576871","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people by age have been diagnosed with sepsis in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45207","45207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576872","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average cost for each patient of second allogeneic haematopoietic stem cell transplants for relapsed disease in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45182","45182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576873","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total number of patients who have received a second allogeneic haematopoietic stem cell transplant for relapsed disease in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45181","45181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576874","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people to be resettled through the Vulnerable Persons Relocation programme in each of the next 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45184","45184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576875","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to speed up the process of family reunification for unaccompanied refugee children in Europe.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45175","45175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576876","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been resettled through the Vulnerable Persons Relocation programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45183","45183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576877","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hate crimes were committed against disabled people in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45208","45208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576878","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that self-employed tutors are subject to criminal records checks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45209","45209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576879","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what annual change there has been in the number of BAME people serving in the police in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45202","45202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576880","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to support diversity champions in the police force.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45201","45201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576881","2016-09-12","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications were made by (a) EEA nationals for registration certificates and (b) EEA family members and extended family members for residence cards in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45158","45158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576882","2016-09-12","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the feasibility of processing applications for registration certificates and residence cards through an online system; and if she will estimate the potential savings in administration costs to the public purse of such a system.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45159","45159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576883","2016-09-12","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on the granting of visas to Syrian passport holders to enter the UK on a short term basis.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45123","45123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576884","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce (a) trolling and (b) cyber-bullying.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45144","45144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576885","2016-09-12","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is her Department's policy to immediately reject visa applications based on the applicant's nationality.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45126","45126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576886","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government's chief fire and rescue advisor was consulted on changes to policy on fire safety policy for new school buildings.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45103","45103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576887","2016-09-12","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passenger interviews were undertaken with people of each (a) ethnicity, (b) religion and (c) nationality by UK Border Agency officials at each UK airport in the last five years; and whether each of those passengers was permitted to continue their journey after that interview.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45251","45251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576888","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect on community cohesion of the presence of (a) Mufti Hanif Qureshi, (b) Muhammad Naquib ur Rehman and (c) Hassan Haseeb ur Rehman in the UK in 2016.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45264","45264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576889","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of the cost of private-rented sector accommodation on the ability of London boroughs to resettle vulnerable Syrian refugees under the Vulnerable Persons Resettlement programme.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45199","45199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576890","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking with Police and Crime Commissioners to improve diversity in police forces.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45200","45200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576891","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to simplify the citizenship application process for EU nationals.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45198","45198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576892","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that social media websites remove abusive and threatening posts.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45167","45167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576893","2016-09-12","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of locating the Security Industry Authority outside London; and what alternative locations have been considered for that authority.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45220","45220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576894","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to lay guidance on licensing functions under taxi and private hire vehicle legislation before Parliament.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45309","45309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576895","2016-09-12","Department for International Development","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings at official level her Department has had with the Department for Exiting the EU in which her Department's budget was discussed.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45301","45301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576896","2016-09-12","Department for International Development","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings at official level her Department has had with the Department for International Trade in which her Department's budget was discussed.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45302","45302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576897","2016-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many women's organisations the Minister for Middle East and Africa met during his recent visit to Somalia.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45298","45298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576898","2016-09-12","Department for International Development","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many full-time equivalent staff of her Department, at what grades, have been seconded to the Department for International Trade.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45300","45300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576899","2016-09-13","Department for International Development","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what activities have been undertaken by Ministers of her Department to promote breastfeeding during World Breastfeeding Week 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45285","45285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576900","2016-09-12","Department for International Development","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to page 135 of her Department's Annual Reports and Accounts 2015-16, for what reasons the budget allocation to South Sudan has decreased from £188,184 in 2015-16 to £145,000 in 2017-18.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45119","45119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576901","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what restrictions the Government has put in place to prevent threatening and intimidating behaviour on the part of bailiffs.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45098","45098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576902","2016-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of whether the level of tribunal fees acts as a disincentive to women pursuing a sex discrimination claim.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45124","45124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576903","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to ensure that any future UK Bill of Rights covers all of the UK.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45168","45168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576904","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what requirements are in place to ensure that the mental health of a defendant is fully considered before sentencing.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45166","45166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576905","2016-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeal hearings were cancelled in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) the first eight months of 2016 at the (i) First-tier Tribunal and (ii) Upper-tier Tribunal due to documents from the Home Office not being submitted before the hearing date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45321","45321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576906","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on the implementation of Part 2 of the Leveson inquiry.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45329","45329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576907","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Written Statement WS368 of 8 December 2015, when the review into the care and management of transgender offenders will be published.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45328","45328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576908","2016-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to (a) improve public awareness of the law and (b) make it easier for the law to be understood by people without legal expertise.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45310","45310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576909","2016-09-12","Leader of the House","2016-09-06","To ask the Leader of the House, when he plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Walsall North, dated 8 August 2016, on the renewal and restoration of the Commons building; and what the reason is for no reply having yet been sent.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45118","45118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576910","2016-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps his Department has taken to encourage the growth of and strength of local business associations and trade partnerships in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45097","45097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576911","2016-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether he has taken steps to support the Northern Ireland Executive in the regeneration of coastal areas in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45096","45096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576912","2016-09-12","Home Office","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to mark Anti-Slavery Day and to acknowledge the work of non-governmental organisations, local authorities and people involved in tackling slavery; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45234","45234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576913","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 April 2016 to Question 35329, whether the development of a plan to progress the initial feasibility and business case work for a Euston Station masterplan has been completed.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45248","45248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576914","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer given by the then Prime Minister, on 29 June 2016, Official Report, column 1294, when his Department will confirm details of the additional compensation to be offered to Southern Rail passengers following the recent strikes and disruption to the regular timetable.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45235","45235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576915","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will provide compensation to non-season ticket holders on Southern Rail for the result of strike action in 2016 and for the effect on such ticket holders of the reduced timetable in operation since 11 July 2016.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45237","45237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576916","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess the merits of establishing a working group on future planning of Crossrail 2 which includes representatives from Transport for London and affected local authorities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45320","45320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576917","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to ensure that local authorities are (a) kept informed on and (b) can contribute to Transport for London's work on business cases for future development of Crossrail 2.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45319","45319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576918","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to simplify rail fares for journeys between London and Scotland and reduce the fare anomalies that lead to split ticketing.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45193","45193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576919","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve the (a) connectivity and (b) affordability of rail travel between Stoke-on-Trent and London.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45312","45312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576920","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of whether the Government's Go Ultra Low scheme to deliver 750 more charging points in UK towns and cities by 2020 will reach its target.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45225","45225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576921","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 8 of the Government's report entitled, Childhood Obesity: a Plan for Action, published in August 2016, how much the Government has invested in (a) walking to school and (b) cycling to school in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45087","45087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576922","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2016 to Question 40558, from which sources other than vehicle excise renewals his Department receives credit card fees from people paying for services offered by his Department and its agencies; and what the total amount so received was in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45129","45129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576923","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to launch his Department's public consultation on new Taxi and Private Hire Vehicle Licensing Practice Guidance.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45094","45094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576924","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the size of (a) rail franchises and (b) the Govia Thameslink rail franchise on the efficient delivery of rail services.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45089","45089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576925","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 8 of the Government's report entitled, Childhood Obesity: a Plan for Action, published in August 2016, whether the clear target to increase the number of children walking to school in the Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy will be quantifiable.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45088","45088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576926","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals related to the recommendations of the Law Commission's report on level crossings, published in September 2013.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45156","45156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576927","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to respond to his Department's consultation on the Hendy Report, published in January 2016.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45155","45155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576928","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total spend on High Speed 2 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45120","45120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576929","2016-09-12","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what section 54 undertakings have been given for which rolling stock fleets; and what the (a) owning group and (b) terminating date is for each such undertaking.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45157","45157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576930","2016-09-13","Women and Equalities","2016-09-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government Equalities Office is taking to implement the actions identified for it in the Government's Ending Violence against Women and Girls 2016-2020, published in March 2016; and when a member of staff from the Government Equalities Office last attended a Violence against Women and Girls Stakeholder Meeting chaired by the Home Office.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45283","45283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576931","2016-09-13","Women and Equalities","2016-09-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what activities (a) she and (b) officials of the Government Equalities Office have undertaken to promote breastfeeding during World Breastfeeding Week 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45284","45284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576932","2016-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the reviews carried out by his Department on the deaths of social security claimants since 2014.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45252","45252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576933","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what response he plans to make to the serious concerns raised by the recent UN Committee on the Rights of the Child in its concluding observations to its Fifth Period Report.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45292","45292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576934","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 27 June 2016 to Question HL691, if the Government will publish the information it holds on the proportion of claimants affected by the lower benefit cap who are in receipt of (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance and (c) income support.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45327","45327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576935","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 32920, where the allegations of fraudulent benefit claims are collected.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45323","45323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576936","2016-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the closure of the independent living fund on people who received payments from that fund prior to its closure.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45315","45315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576937","2016-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable for publication is of the Freud Review into housing benefit changes and their impact on supported accommodation.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45224","45224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576938","2016-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the Government plans to announce the outcome of its review into future funding for supported housing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45221","45221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576939","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department is providing to pensioners who depend on charities and families to pay household bills.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45139","45139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576940","2016-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the living wage on the earnings threshold for carers allowance; and if he will bring forward proposals to raise the existing threshold.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45121","45121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576941","2016-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to exempt domestic violence refuges from proposals to cap housing benefit.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45122","45122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576942","2016-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department plans to issue to its staff on the application of residency tests to refugees applying for disability living allowance.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45160","45160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576943","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the Government's welfare reforms on deprivation in (a) Glasgow East constituency, (b) the city of Glasgow and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45084","45084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576944","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) investigations and (b) prosecutions overseen by Trading Standards have related to (i) the mis-selling of vehicles and (ii) the tampering of mileage on vehicles in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45092","45092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576945","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to incentivise energy companies to assist people in (a) fuel poverty and (b) fuel debt.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45093","45093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576946","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to complete the roll-out of smart meters.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45091","45091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576947","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to continue to support Government investment in (a) new energy sources and (b) tidal energy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45145","45145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576948","2016-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many officials in his Department are working on climate change policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45149","45149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576949","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of his Department's budget in each of the next three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45185","45185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576950","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to improve the performance of the Feed-in Tariff scheme for solar power.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45178","45178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576951","2016-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress has been made on the accelerated decommissioning programme for nuclear waste in the UK.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45307","45307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576952","2016-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the remaining total cost to the public purse will be of construction at Hinkley Point C should that project receive approval.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45306","45306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576953","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect that a possible Heathrow Airport expansion will have on UK industry.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45281","45281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576954","2016-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the period of maternity leave for mothers of premature babies.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45213","45213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576955","2016-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what role his Department played in drafting the Government's childhood obesity plan.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45304","45304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576956","2016-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the renewables industry in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45305","45305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576957","2016-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to improve security measures at sites containing nuclear waste.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45308","45308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576958","2016-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the speech of the then Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on 18 November 2015, on a new direction for UK energy policy, when the terms of reference of the review into coal will be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45332","45332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576959","2016-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of recent changes in business rates on corporate demand for rooftop solar power.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45169","45169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576960","2016-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations his Department has made to the Valuation Office Agency on the effect of planned business rate increases for solar power on the solar industry.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45250","45250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576961","2016-09-12","Department for International Trade","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff at what civil service grades his Department employs.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45238","45238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576962","2016-09-12","Department for International Trade","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many flights (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have taken as part of their official duties since his Department was set up on 14 July 2016.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45236","45236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576963","2016-09-12","Department for International Trade","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, on what trade deals his Department has begun the negotiation process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45314","45314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576964","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the importance of direct long-haul air links with a hub airport when opening trade discussions around the world.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45280","45280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576965","2016-09-08","Department for International Trade","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with the government of Japan on increasing trade links with that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45204","45204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576966","2016-09-12","Department for International Trade","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many meetings have been held between Ministers of his Department and their international counterparts on future trade deals since his Department was created; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45148","45148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576967","2016-09-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff his Department (a) employs and (b) plans to employ in the next 12 months; and how many such staff will be located in (i) London, (ii) Brussels and (iii) elsewhere.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45150","45150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576968","2016-09-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the budget of his Department in each of the next three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45147","45147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576969","2016-09-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent steps he has taken to decide the immigration system to be implemented upon the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45324","45324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576970","2016-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on retaining the EU's professional qualifications directive after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45313","45313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576971","2016-09-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he plans for the UK to initiate Article 50; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45218","45218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576972","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on future collaboration with the EU on consumer protections in relation to e-commerce; if he will make it his policy to ensure UK consumers who access e-commerce firms located in the EU single market continue to be offered the protections currently provided by the Directive on Consumer Rights of 25 October 2011 (2011/83/EC).","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45265","45265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576973","2016-09-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make it his policy to ensure the UK maintains the requirements of Council Directive 1999/74/EC on battery hens.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45267","45267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576974","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on the devolution of the policy and administration of agricultural subsidies to the devolved administrations once the UK exits the Common Agricultural Policy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45268","45268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576975","2016-09-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on future UK membership of Europol.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45269","45269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576976","2016-09-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make it his policy to continue UK access to the Schengen Information System for law enforcement purposes once the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45272","45272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576977","2016-09-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on future UK participation in the EU cybersecurity strategy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45273","45273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576978","2016-09-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on future UK involvement in the European Arrest Warrant.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45271","45271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/581259","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the range of international operations being undertaken by the armed forces.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906260","906260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/581260","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, What the Government's commitments are to fulfil its obligations under Article 5 of the NATO Treaty.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906254","906254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/581261","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the future of volunteer gliding schools in Wales.","Biography information for Lord Davies of Gower","Byron Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906255","906255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/581262","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on delivering the UK's contribution to NATO's enhanced forward presence in eastern Europe; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906258","906258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/581263","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy to keep open the Kinloss army barracks.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906261","906261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/581264","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to improve nuclear safety at the Atomic Weapons Establishment to ensure that it no longer requires enhanced regulatory attention from the Office of Nuclear Regulation.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906253","906253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/581265","2016-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent representations he has received on the work of SSAFA, the armed forces charity.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906256","906256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576352","2016-09-07","Attorney General","2016-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, how many offenders have had their sentence increased under the unduly lenient sentence scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44884","44884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576353","2016-09-07","Attorney General","2016-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, what plans he has to extend the unduly lenient sentence scheme.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44885","44885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576354","2016-09-07","Attorney General","2016-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, what plans he has to extend the scope of the unduly lenient sentence scheme.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44886","44886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576355","2016-09-07","Attorney General","2016-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have applied for sentences to be reviewed under the unduly lenient sentence scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44887","44887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576356","2016-09-07","Attorney General","2016-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, how many sentences referred to the Court of Appeal under the unduly lenient sentence scheme were (a) increased and (b) kept the same in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44888","44888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576357","2016-09-07","Attorney General","2016-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, how many applications under the unduly lenient sentence scheme have been rejected due to falling outside the remit of that scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44889","44889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576358","2016-09-08","Cabinet Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to change the staff headcount across the Civil Service in each of the next four years; and what the projected expenditure on staff is in that time period.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44983","44983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576359","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will bring forward proposals to bring prison officers' retirement age into line with that of staff in the police force, fire service and armed forces.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44981","44981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576360","2016-09-07","Cabinet Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, from which sources does the Government receive credit card fees from people paying for services offered by its departments and agencies; and what the total amount received was in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45025","45025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576361","2016-09-08","HM Treasury","2016-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will continue to make funding available for new and existing LEADER and Countryside Stewardship schemes when the UK ceases to be a participant of the Common Agricultural Policy on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45072","45072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576362","2016-09-08","HM Treasury","2016-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 4.3.2 of the Open Banking Standard report published in February 2016, what assessment the Government has made of the (a) cyber security, (b) data protection and (c) fraud risks an open banking environment introduces.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45073","45073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576363","2016-09-08","HM Treasury","2016-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Open Banking Standard report published in February 2016, how the Government plans to ensure that customers provide informed consent when using open banking services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45074","45074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576364","2016-09-08","HM Treasury","2016-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to ensure that the LEADER and Countryside Stewardship schemes continue to be funded when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44984","44984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576365","2016-09-08","HM Treasury","2016-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse was of providing the married couples allowance in each financial year since 2001.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44906","44906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576366","2016-09-08","HM Treasury","2016-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many couples claimed the married couples allowance in each financial year since 2001.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44905","44905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576367","2016-09-07","HM Treasury","2016-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax and national insurance revenue was received from the self-employed courier sector in each of the last three years; and how much tax credit expenditure that sector received in each of those years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44938","44938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576368","2016-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to enable communities with neighbourhood plans that are (a) complete and (b) being developed to appeal against planning decisions that conflict with that plan.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44881","44881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576369","2016-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has given to support children and young adults in social care in (a) St Helens North, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45022","45022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576370","2016-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support the work of anti-racism groups in North East England and celebrate the support shown for migrants and refugees in Newcastle following the vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45075","45075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576371","2016-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the Government's policy is on the maximum threshold for council tax increases in England in (a) 2019-20, (b) 2020-21 and (c) 2021-22.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45063","45063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576372","2016-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Government has made of the (a) amount and (b) proportion that net revenue expenditure by local authorities will increase in England in (i) 2017-18, (ii) 2018-19 and (iii) 2019-20.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45034","45034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576373","2016-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding per head his Department has given to support children and young adults in social care in (a) St Helens North, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45021","45021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576374","2016-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Government has made of the  potential annual proportion increase in yield from business rates available for local authorities in Dorset, Poole and Bournemouth in (a) 2019-20, (b) 2020-21 and (c) 2021-22.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45035","45035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576375","2016-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued on whether responses from residents to public consultation questionnaires issued by local authorities should be anonymous or identified by name and address.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45036","45036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576376","2016-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities in England have held referendums seeking increases in council tax beyond the maximum threshold in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45037","45037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576377","2016-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many social houses were (a) built and (b) sold under the Right to Buy scheme in (i) Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency, (ii) Cheshire West and Chester and (iii) England in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45027","45027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576378","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of wheelchair access at sports venues.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45033","45033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576379","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the role of her Department was in drafting the Government's childhood obesity plan.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44972","44972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576380","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of moving from the current system of rooftop valuation for mobile network base stations to a no scheme valuation model on (a) the supply of sites, (b) the revenues received by Newcastle City Council and other public sector organisations from rooftop rentals and (c) mobile phone operator profits.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44955","44955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576381","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Department for Communities and Local Government on how to replace the funding potentially lost to public sector organisations for rooftop rental as a result of the changes to rooftop valuation proposed in the Digital Economy Bill.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44956","44956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576382","2016-09-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Queen's Speech 2016, if her Department will publish detailed plans to create the right for every household to access high speed broadband.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44980","44980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576383","2016-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of the success of the London 2012 Olympic Games on the success of the competitors at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44915","44915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576384","2016-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had on the BBC's investment in Gaelic broadcasting as part of the BBC Charter Review; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44918","44918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576385","2016-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many serving personnel will return from Germany as part of the planned rebasing in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44890","44890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576386","2016-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost of terminating and re-tendering the Carillion Amey housing contract.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44893","44893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576387","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent violence and instability in South Sudan on the deployment plan of British armed forces as part of the UN peacekeeping mission in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44909","44909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576388","2016-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many married quarter void properties are situated on each military base in the UK.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44891","44891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576389","2016-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 38976, on married quarters, what assessment his Department has made of the habitability of the 10,187 void properties.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44892","44892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576390","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many cyber-attacks there have been on the UK's national energy infrastructure in the past five years.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44904","44904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576391","2016-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British airstrikes have been conducted in (a) Iraq from September 2014 to September 2016 and (b) Syria from December 2015 to September 2016.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45023","45023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576392","2016-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the (a) criteria by which applicants are selected and (b) names of applicants who applied to host Armed Forces Day in 2017.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44988","44988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576393","2016-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department asked local authorities in Northern Ireland to apply to host Armed Forces Day in 2017.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44989","44989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576394","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the rate of UK Reaper drone strikes in Iraq and Syria by month since the mission was launched; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45010","45010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576395","2016-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the deadline for the receipt of applications for Armed Forces Day 2018 will be.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44990","44990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576396","2016-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK is currently using armed Reaper drones outside of Iraq and Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45011","45011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576397","2016-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times nuclear convoys travelled through (a) Glasgow East constituency, (b) the City of Glasgow and (c) Scotland from May 2015 to September 2016.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45030","45030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576398","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence the Government holds to demonstrate that merging further education colleges will create savings; and what assessment she has carried out on whether the policy of merging further education institutions in Scotland has been successful.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45024","45024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576399","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of how much her Department will spend on children's centres in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45052","45052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576400","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason her Department's review of further education institutions does not include sixth forms or universities.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45053","45053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576401","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of graduate teachers secured a permanent teaching post within a year of graduation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44998","44998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576402","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government plans to take to increase the number of (a) young people and (b) young men from deprived areas entering further education and taking up apprenticeships.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44997","44997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576403","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding per head is received for childcare in (a) St Helens North, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45020","45020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576404","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many one-on-one classroom assistant tuition hours were provided on average each week for children with special educational needs in state schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44992","44992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576405","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans the Government has for the distribution of funding from the soft drinks undertaking levy between schools across the UK for sporting activity.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44974","44974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576406","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on children's centres in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44978","44978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576407","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to promote closer links between UK and non-EU universities.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44879","44879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576408","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate her Department has made of the average number of cases being handled by individual social workers on a weekly basis.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44916","44916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576409","2016-09-08","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter of 1 August 2016 on behalf of a constituent concerning the teaching of mathematics.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44903","44903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576410","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage the recruitment of graduates into the social work sector.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44912","44912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576411","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase public awareness of the role of social workers.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44913","44913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576412","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department holds data on the (a) use and (b) prevalence of setting and streaming in schools in England.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44947","44947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576413","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to ensure that UK fisheries are managed at or below maximum sustainable yield by 2020; what steps she plans to take to maintain a sustainable fisheries policy after the UK leaves the EU; and if she will take steps to work with European partners to support sustainable fishing after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44902","44902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576414","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of putting in place a comprehensive system of environmental protection before deep sea mining operations are allowed to commence in oceans worldwide.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44959","44959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576415","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent on coastal defences for each UK region, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45019","45019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576416","2016-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is planning to take to assist farmers in the (a) North West and (b) Ribble Valley constituency with transitional funding after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45009","45009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576417","2016-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many racehorses (a) died and (b) were destroyed on British racecourses or shortly afterwards due to injury sustained in (i) flat, (ii) all weather and (iii) national hunt racing in (A) 2013, (B) 2014 and (C) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45068","45068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576418","2016-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many racehorses (a) died and (b) were destroyed as a result of training injuries in Britain in (i) 2013, (ii) 2014 and (iii) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45069","45069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576419","2016-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many racehorses (a) died and (b) were destroyed at each of Britain's 59 racecourses in (i) 2013, (ii) 2014 and (iii) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45070","45070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576420","2016-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many racehorses were slaughtered in abattoirs in Britain in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45071","45071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576421","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library all emails, notes, letters or other documents or records relating to his Department's exercise of reviewing all correspondence and parliamentary proceedings on the subject of allegations of breaches of international humanitarian law in Yemen by the Saudi-led Coalition and on the publication of the Written Ministerial Statement Corrections to Parliamentary Questions and Westminster Hall Debates, HCWS125.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45062","45062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576422","2016-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the human rights conditions in prisons in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45042","45042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576423","2016-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights record of the government of Bangladesh; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45040","45040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576424","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British nationals are currently detained in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44977","44977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576425","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government is making to the governments of India and Pakistan on finding a peaceful solution to the situation in Kashmir which fully involves the people of Kashmir in the process.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44958","44958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576426","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on British nationals detained in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44976","44976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576427","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the security of British Embassy employees returning to Juba, South Sudan after the attacks on civilians at the Terrain hotel in July 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44908","44908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576428","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his South Sudanese counterpart on tackling recent violence in Jonglei state in South Sudan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44907","44907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576429","2016-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations the Government has made to the government of Bahrain on reports of human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44882","44882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576430","2016-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 July 2016 to Question 42328, for what reasons his Department did not provide the schedule of documents requested in that Question relating to the disappearance of Rebecca Coriam.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44883","44883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576431","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage GPs to undertake collaborative work with Muscular Dystrophy UK to increase their knowledge of care and management of people with neuromuscular conditions.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44910","44910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576432","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with NICE on increasing capacity for highly specialised technology evaluations.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44911","44911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576433","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the ratio of medical staff to administrators is in the NHS.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44948","44948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576434","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish all sustainability and transformation plans that were submitted within the June 2016 deadline.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44970","44970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576435","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts use agency nurses who are brought in from other countries.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44960","44960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576436","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS is of using agency doctors who are brought in from other countries.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44961","44961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576437","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many performance meetings the Departmental Board has held since his appointment; and how many of those meetings he has attended.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44971","44971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576438","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the minutes of all the meetings his Department has held related to each of the 44 sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44968","44968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576439","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the eight key actions recommended in the Public Health England report entitled Sugar Reduction, the evidence for action, published in October 2015, for what reasons all of those actions were not included in the Government's childhood obesity plan.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44975","44975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576440","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the performance of Capita in delivering primary care support.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44969","44969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576441","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people who received redundancy payments from the NHS in 2015-16 were subsequently re-employed by the NHS on a (a) consultancy and (b) permanent basis; and what the cost to the NHS was of those redundancy repayments.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44966","44966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576442","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on primary care in (a) West Sussex and (b) Mid Sussex constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45008","45008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576443","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to improve access to GPs in Mid Sussex constituency.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45007","45007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576444","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent mental health inspectors are employed by the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45014","45014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576445","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to introduce new care models across the UK similar to those introduced in England to date.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44991","44991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576446","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health services he has visited in his capacity as Secretary of State since December 2015; and what the date was of each such visit.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45015","45015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576447","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings of the CLIC Sargent report, entitled Cancer costs: financial impact of childhood cancer revealed, published on 1 September 2016, if he will carry out an immediate review of travel assistance available to young cancer patients and their parents.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45001","45001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576448","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings of the report of CLIC Sargent, Cancer costs: financial impact of childhood cancer revealed, published on 1 September 2016, how he plans to ensure that his Department's guidance on hospital car parking is applied consistently across England.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45002","45002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576449","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 21 July 2016 to Question 42766, whether he has accepted the recommendation of the independent Mental Health Taskforce in its report published in February 2016 to bring together an expert group to examine the needs of children who are particularly vulnerable to developing mental health problems, including those with long-term conditions.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45031","45031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576450","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding has been provided to prevent and tackle Group B Strep infection among pregnant women in the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44993","44993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576451","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to prevent and tackle Group B Strep infection among pregnant women and unborn children.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44994","44994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576452","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to increase the number of nurses (a) qualifying and (b) subsequently working in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44995","44995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576453","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the primary care transformation fund will be invested in Mid Sussex constituency in the next four years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45006","45006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576454","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the CLIC Sargent report of 1 September 2016, entitled Cancer costs: financial impact of childhood cancer revealed, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of cancer on young people and their families.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45000","45000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576455","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals are forecast to (a) open and (b) close in each of the next five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45026","45026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576456","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Oxford University Hospitals NHS Trust has paid Cerner in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45043","45043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576457","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Royal Free London NHS Foundation Trust has paid Cerner in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45044","45044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576458","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government plans to take to (a) reduce the number of patients receiving an incorrect initial heart diagnosis and (b) provide the correct diagnosis and treatment for those patients.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45003","45003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576459","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Newcastle upon Tyne Hospitals NHS Trust has paid Cerner in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45048","45048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576460","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much to date the NHS has paid Cerner in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45049","45049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576461","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) job description and (b) salary is of the Head of the NHS England EU Transition Team.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45058","45058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576462","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much to date the NHS has paid Fujitsu for the licensing, deployment and support of acute IT systems in the South of England.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45050","45050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576463","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much to date the NHS has paid BT for licensing, deployment and support of acute IT systems in London.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45051","45051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576464","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual budget is of the NHS England EU Transition Team; and what the remit of that team is.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45059","45059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576465","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much West Suffolk NHS Foundation Trust has paid Cerner in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45047","45047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576466","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust has paid Cerner in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45045","45045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576467","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Homerton University Hospital NHS Foundation Trust has paid Cerner in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Richard Bacon","Mr Richard Bacon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45046","45046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576468","2016-09-07","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Sustainability and Transformation plans will be (a) made public and (b) fully consulted on before being implemented.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45067","45067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576469","2016-09-07","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to include Scottish universities in the Government's tier 4 Visa Pilot.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45029","45029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576470","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the application waiting times for people resident in Liverpool, Wavertree constituency who are seeking asylum.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45017","45017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576471","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 11 April 2016 to Question 32631 on human trafficking: females, if she will take steps to ensure that data referred to is collected.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45016","45016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576472","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken is for family reunification of unaccompanied refugee children in Europe.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44965","44965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576473","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her plans are to tackle trends in stress-related illnesses among police officers in Lancashire.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44962","44962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576474","2016-09-08","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what number and proportion of (a) overall visa applications and (b) applications from Syrian passport holders have been rejected by her Department in the last year.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45004","45004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576475","2016-09-07","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to contact visa and naturalisation applicants to ask those applicants to submit an up-to-date English Language Certificate if an application is to be refused solely on the grounds of the submission of an expired certificate.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44987","44987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576476","2016-09-07","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what statistics her Department holds on (a) convictions and (b) fines for mobile phone use while driving in each police force area.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44950","44950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576477","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on trends in the incidence of mobile phone use while driving since it was prohibited.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44933","44933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576478","2016-09-07","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the (a) ability and (b) willingness of police forces to catch those using their mobile phone while driving.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44935","44935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576479","2016-09-07","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department had with the Department for Education before the decision to withdraw government guidance that most new schools are expected to be fitted with automatic fire sprinkler systems.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44870","44870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576480","2016-09-07","Department for Education","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to include students from other EU countries in the eligibility criteria for student loans in the 2017-18 and 2018-19 admissions years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44877","44877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576481","2016-09-07","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to remove international students from the Government's migration targets following the decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44875","44875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576482","2016-09-07","Home Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to ensure EU nationals currently employed in UK universities will retain their positions after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44880","44880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576483","2016-09-07","Department for International Development","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what innovation start-up grants are available for charities that undertake water sanitation projects.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44869","44869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576484","2016-09-08","Department for International Development","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many days of holiday, on average, were awarded to departmental employees living and working overseas in 2015-16.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44957","44957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576485","2016-09-07","Department for International Development","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made on meeting the target of committing 0.7 per cent of national income to international aid.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45066","45066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576486","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government intends to publish its consultation relating to death by dangerous driving and driving without due care and attention.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44964","44964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576487","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was for fee remission in employment tribunal claims between receipt of such claims and final processing in the latest period for which figures are available; and what proportion of fee remission applications were successful in that period.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44963","44963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576488","2016-09-08","Department of Health","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure the efficient and timely transfer of prisoners to hospitals under the provisions of the Mental Health Act 1983; and how many prisoners have waited for more than 14 days for such a transfer in each quarter since April 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45018","45018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576489","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans she has to open new prisons.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45032","45032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576490","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to create a new legal status of guardian of the property and affairs of a missing person by 1 December 2016.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44982","44982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576491","2016-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals to the tribunal service from appellants in (a) Glasgow South West constituency, (b) Glasgow and (c) Scotland regarding (i) personal independence payments, (ii) employment and support allowance, (iii) income support, (iv) jobseeker's allowance and (v) tax credits were successful in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44896","44896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576492","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the penalties for mobile phone use while driving.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44934","44934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576493","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to help local authorities utilise data from the transport sector to improve local road networks.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44874","44874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576494","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vacant posts at each grade there are at the National Maritime Operations Centre in Fareham.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44922","44922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576495","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times in the last two years the Northern Maritime Operations Centre in Fareham has had staffing levels below what is considered safe.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44919","44919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576496","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times one person has been left on (a) daytime and (b) night-time watch at Falmouth Coastguard Operations Centre in the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44923","44923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576497","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average length of time is from joining for an employee to qualify as a (a) maritime operations commander, (b) maritime operations controller, (c) senior operations officer and (d) maritime operations officer.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44932","44932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576498","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any requests from Falmouth Coastguard Operations Centre asking for assistance in running an incident have been turned down by (a) the National Maritime Operations Centre in Fareham and (b) any other station in the last two years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44939","44939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576499","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fully-qualified coastguard staff were on (a) daytime and (b) nighttime duty at Falmouth Coastguard operations centre on (a) 2 May and (b) 9 July 2015.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44920","44920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576500","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vacant posts at each grade there are at Falmouth Coastguard operations centre.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44921","44921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576501","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many callouts have been recorded for coastguard rescue teams in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44940","44940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576502","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times in the last two years Falmouth Coastguard Operations Centre has had staffing levels below what is considered safe.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44927","44927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576503","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average length of time is from joining for an employee to qualify as a (a) senior watch manager, (b) watch manager, (c) watch officer and (d) watch assistant.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44941","44941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576504","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether staff at the National Maritime Operations Centre in Fareham are required to record a reason for not calling on a lifeboat or coastguard team or another resource.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44928","44928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576505","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many unanswered telephone calls the National Maritime Operations Centre has each day.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44929","44929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576506","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fully-trained coastguard staff working at the National Maritime Operations Centre in Fareham were on the daytime watch covering the south coast from Plymouth to Selsey Bill on (a) 2 May 2015, (b) 9 July 2015, (c) 24 May 2016, (d) 29 May 2016 and (e) 4 June 2016.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44926","44926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576507","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the National Maritime Operations Centre in Fareham turned down requests from other Category 1 Responders for assistance in the last two years; and for each such request (a) what type of request it was, (b) what reason was recorded for it being turned down and (c) which coastguard station turned it down.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44925","44925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576508","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the coastguard has turned down requests from other Category 1 Responders for assistance in the last five years; and for each such request (a) what type of request it was, (b) what reason was recorded for it being turned down and (c) which coastguard station turned it down.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44942","44942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576509","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what change there has been in the number of incidents reported along the south coast from Plymouth to Selsey Bill in the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44943","44943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576510","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what maximum length of time is considered safe from when an emergency call is received in a coastguard control room to when the coastguard vehicle is ready to leave its station.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44944","44944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576511","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the coastguard turned down any request from any other service for assistance during inland floods in the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44945","44945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576512","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguard rescue teams have been deployed to inland flooding incidents in the past two years; and how many times those teams were called out to such incidents in the past two years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44946","44946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576513","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44873","44873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576514","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the DVLA on waiting times for HGV driving licence renewal; what the (a) rate of renewals, (b) number of new applications, (c) total number of renewals outstanding, (d) average waiting time from application to renewal and (e) number of staff processing renewals was for HGV driving licence renewals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45012","45012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576515","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many callouts have been recorded for each coastguard rescue team along the south coast from Plymouth to Selsey Bill in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44930","44930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576516","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many reports of tombstoning have been received and investigated by a coastguard team from Plymouth to Selsey Bill in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44931","44931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576517","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fully-trained staff are based at the National Maritime Operations Centre in Fareham.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44924","44924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576518","2016-09-08","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential economic effect of High Speed 2 on the local economy in Coventry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44979","44979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576519","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on delivering 750 more charging points in UK towns and cities by 2020 through the Go Ultra Low City scheme.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45057","45057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576520","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total amount paid in compensation to people affected by the High Speed 2 project was in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45041","45041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576521","2016-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is for the transition from one employment and support allowance entitlement to jobseeker's allowance in Fife.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44871","44871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576522","2016-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of people in the workfare programme in (i) Fife and (ii) Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency moved into full-time employment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44872","44872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576523","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for funeral payments were (a) made and (b) granted in Scotland in 2015-16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44895","44895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576524","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the average length of time a person making an initial inquiry claiming social security benefit spent on the telephone in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44894","44894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576525","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total expenditure from the public purse was for the social fund funeral payments scheme in 2015-16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44897","44897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576526","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with cancer applied for attendance allowance under the special rules for people with terminal illness in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44900","44900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576527","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on advertising the attendance allowance scheme in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44901","44901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576528","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people applied for attendance allowance under the special rules for people with terminal illness in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44899","44899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576529","2016-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on administration costs related to attendance allowance in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44898","44898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576530","2016-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to increase awareness of the Disability Confident campaign; and how his Department plans to measure the effectiveness of that campaign.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44951","44951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576531","2016-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on the introduction of transitional arrangements to assist women born on or after 6 April 1951 who have been adversely affected by changes to the state pension age.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44917","44917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576532","2016-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is for a decision to be made for a personal independence payment claim in (a) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) England.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45061","45061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576533","2016-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Scotland received support from Access to Work grants (a) in total and (b) for a mental health condition in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45060","45060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576534","2016-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to monitor the effect of the change from disability living allowance to personal independence payments on the standard of living of the recipients of those payments.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44986","44986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576535","2016-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides on the minimum number of days between benefit payments for a person ending an employment and support allowance claim and beginning a jobseeker's allowance claim; and what the average time between such benefit payments was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44952","44952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576536","2016-09-08","Cabinet Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are currently registered as self-employed in Westmorland and Lonsdale constituency; and what the average salary is earned by those people.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45013","45013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576537","2016-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to encourage and support graduates in finding a job.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44996","44996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576538","2016-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on making the pension age for Civil Nuclear Constabulary police officers the same as that for police forces under the responsibility of the Home Office.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44999","44999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576539","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the role of his Department was in drafting the Government's childhood obesity plan.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44973","44973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576540","2016-09-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many of the annual returns or confirmation statements submitted to Companies House since 1 July 2016 did not contain information on the relevant company's persons of significant control.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45005","45005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576541","2016-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress his Department has made on developing an Energy Innovation Strategy.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45054","45054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576542","2016-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many tonnes of carbon dioxide were displaced by renewable (a) electricity and (b) heat generation in (i) the UK, (ii) England, (iii) Scotland and (iv) Wales in 2015.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45055","45055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576543","2016-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of having the Civil Nuclear Constabulary retirement age at (a) 65 and (b) 68 on (i) the safety of the individual officer and (ii) national security.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44937","44937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576544","2016-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the contribution of the manufacturing industry to the UK economy in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44914","44914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576545","2016-09-07","HM Treasury","2016-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of recent increases in Financial Services Compensation Scheme levies on small businesses.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44949","44949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576546","2016-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many additional staff have been deployed to the UK's mission to the UN in Geneva to work on World Trade Organisation (WTO) policy and to renegotiate the UK's membership of the WTO since the EU referendum.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44953","44953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576547","2016-09-07","Department for Transport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the importance of direct long-haul air links with a hub airport for international trade.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44936","44936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576548","2016-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff were employed by the (a) Defence Growth Partnership and (b) UK Defence Solutions Centre on 1 April 2016.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45056","45056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576549","2016-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the cost to (a) government and (b) industry of the Defence Growth Partnership (i) was in 2014-15, (ii) was in 2015-16 and (iii) is for 2016-17.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45039","45039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576550","2016-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much (a) government and (b) industry funding the UK Defence Solutions Centre received in the financial year 2015-16; and how much such funding is projected for 2016-17.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45038","45038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576551","2016-09-07","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make it his policy to (a) establish a prosperity zone among countries with similar approaches to the UK to have trade, completion and property rights and (b) negotiate and inherit bilateral trade deals with nations whose markets are more distorted.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45028","45028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576552","2016-09-07","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans his Department has in place to include the devolved administrations in UK trade negotiations in the future.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45065","45065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576553","2016-09-07","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff worked for the Defence and Security Organisation on 1 April 2016; and what the budget for that organisation is for 2016-17.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 45064","45064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576554","2016-09-07","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the level of (a) imports and (b) exports between the UK and Norway by sector was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44985","44985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576555","2016-09-08","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department are currently engaged in (a) London and (b) Geneva on World Trade Organisation policy.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44954","44954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576556","2016-09-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what (a) meetings and (b) discussions he has had with Didier Seeuws, Head of the Brexit Taskforce at the European Council.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44967","44967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576557","2016-09-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make it his policy to ensure reciprocity of student access to higher education funding systems with other EU countries as part of negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44878","44878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/576558","2016-09-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make it his policy that access to EU science and research funding programmes is maintained as part of the UK's negotiations on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44876","44876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578462","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to tackle problems associated with the rise in availability of Fixed Odds Betting Terminals.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906194","906194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578463","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support tourism through increasing the number of UNESCO-recognised World Heritage sites in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906191","906191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578464","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she  has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on the devolution of responsibility for broadcasting policy.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906193","906193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578465","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the success of Team GB at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906192","906192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578466","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps her Department has taken to roll out superfast broadband; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906189","906189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578467","2016-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with UK Anti-Doping and its international partners on doping in sport.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906196","906196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578468","2016-09-08","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has to reform UK Trade and Investment.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906161","906161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578469","2016-09-08","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to ensure that the UK retains its research and development relationship with Israel after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906168","906168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578470","2016-09-08","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will estimate the potential cost to the economy of trade barriers between the UK and EU countries after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906164","906164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578471","2016-09-08","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential role of the Prime Minister's Trade Envoys in increasing future levels of UK exports.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906167","906167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578472","2016-09-08","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he plans to meet with UK automotive sector representatives to discuss that sector's role in future trade deals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906166","906166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/578473","2016-09-08","Department for International Trade","2016-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to secure a trade agreement with Israel after the UK ceases to be party to the EU-Israel Association Agreement.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906162","906162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573370","2016-09-06","Cabinet Office","2016-09-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to have targets for BAME representation in the Senior Civil Service.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44005","44005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573371","2016-09-06","Cabinet Office","2016-09-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answers of 25 July 2016 to Questions 43380 and 43381, for what reasons his Department does not hold information on the number of public sector contracts won by small businesses or on the number of companies bidding; and if he will take steps to collate that information.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44099","44099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573372","2016-09-06","Cabinet Office","2016-09-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 26 July 2016 to Question 43378, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of people by (i) region, (ii) county and (iii) parliamentary constituency are paid less than the Living Wage Foundation's living wage.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44109","44109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573373","2016-09-06","Cabinet Office","2016-09-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answers of 25 July 2016 to Questions 43380 and 43381, what proportion of that £12 billion was spent on (a) small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) winning contracts directly from government and (b) large companies winning contracts directly from government and then outsourcing parts of those contracts to SMEs.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44100","44100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573374","2016-09-06","Cabinet Office","2016-09-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions his Department has had with the Crown Prosecution Service on Operation Lydd.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44263","44263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573375","2016-09-06","Cabinet Office","2016-09-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to review progress towards commitments made at the 2016 Anti-Corruption Summit in London; and what the timetable is for further periodic reviews of that progress.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44131","44131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573376","2016-09-06","HM Treasury","2016-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of country-by-country reporting regulations on the competitiveness of the UK economy.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44141","44141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573377","2016-09-06","HM Treasury","2016-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of private landlords who will be affected by the tax relief change to higher rate taxpayers announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44101","44101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573378","2016-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much in housing benefit has been paid (a) to tenants in private-rented sector accommodation and (b) directly to private landlords in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44097","44097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573379","2016-09-06","HM Treasury","2016-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many widowed parents and bereaved cohabiting parents will be financially worse off as a result of the planned changes to the widowed parent's allowance.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44076","44076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573380","2016-09-06","HM Treasury","2016-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate how much air passenger duty was paid by passengers using Manchester Airport in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44066","44066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573381","2016-09-06","HM Treasury","2016-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate how much fuel duty was collected by filling stations in Greater Manchester in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44067","44067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573382","2016-09-06","HM Treasury","2016-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to monitor and regulate the liquidity ratio on property funds.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44009","44009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573383","2016-09-06","HM Treasury","2016-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to minimise the administrative effect on small businesses of information requests from the Financial Ombudsman.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44010","44010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573384","2016-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on plans to cap housing benefit and (b) assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed cap on housing benefit on people who live in supported housing and have mental illness; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44004","44004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573385","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the population in (a) Birmingham, Northfield constituency and (b) Birmingham city was homeless in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44006","44006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573386","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assistance his Department provides to local authorities to help tackle (a) homelessness and (b) the root causes of homelessness.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44007","44007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573387","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to provide employment and social enterprise opportunities for (a) the homeless and (b) those at risk of homelessness in (i) the West Midlands and (ii) Birmingham, Northfield constituency.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44008","44008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573388","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2016 to Question 42908, for what reasons he does not plan to release the Planning Inspector's report before issuing his decision on those appeals; and if he will make it his policy to publish that report in advance of the decision being issued.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44022","44022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573389","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19679, how much land in East Dorset District Council area is designated as green belt.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44057","44057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573390","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19683, how much land in Purbeck District Council area is designated as green belt.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44058","44058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573391","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to increase the powers of local authorities to (a) remove travellers camped illegally on public land and (b) recover site clean-up costs from those illegally settled on public land.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44038","44038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573392","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 3 May 2016 to Question 35113, what powers his Department can exercise if the Social Housing Regulator is failing to protect tenants from serious detriment by registered providers.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44077","44077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573393","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 July 2016 to Question 43423, on housing: construction, if he will publish statistics for net new dwellings in England for the years 1997-98 to 2005-06 comparable to those published for subsequent years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44064","44064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573394","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much central government funding has been (a) made available for tenant training in each of the last 10 years and (b) allocated, or he plans to make available, for tenant training in (i) 2016 and (ii) each subsequent year of the current Parliament.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44065","44065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573395","2016-09-06","Department for Transport","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to grant local authorities greater powers to resolve neighbour disputes arising from the reservation of parking spaces using traffic cones, refuse bins or other items.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44087","44087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573396","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government was involved in the legal agreement drawn up in 1998 to transfer the estates involved in the Tower Hamlets Housing Action Trust to Old Ford Housing Association.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44088","44088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573397","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library a copy of the advice provided to the Housing Minister prior to authorisation of the stock transfer of the Parkside estates to Old Ford Housing Association.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44089","44089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573398","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 5576, on social rented housing: EU nationals, whether it remains his Department's policy to introduce a four-year residency requirement for EU migrants following the decision of the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44098","44098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573399","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the causes of the increase in homelessness in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44128","44128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573400","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of indefinitely vacant properties.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Mr Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44153","44153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573401","2016-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has given to support children and young adults in social care in (a) Warwickshire and (b) Rugby constituency in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44147","44147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573402","2016-09-06","Department for Education","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were in the care of the local authority in (a) Warwickshire and (b) Rugby constituency in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44148","44148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573403","2016-09-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which agencies perform child protection checks prior to a self-employed adult being permitted to provide extracurricular activities to children for which activity or sport there is no governing body.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44158","44158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573404","2016-09-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the rollout of superfast broadband in the B91 1 postcode area.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44083","44083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573405","2016-09-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of National Lottery ticket sales revenues was (a) passed to the good causes funds and (b) spent on good causes in Scotland in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44041","44041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573406","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel in each of the armed forces were affected by the increase in the qualifying age for an armed forces pension.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44002","44002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573407","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what procedures his Department has in place for the regular receipt of information on non-combatant casualties arising from US airstrikes which are conducted from UK airbases.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44003","44003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573408","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how net pay deductions from the salaries of Ministry of Defence fire fighters and fire officers are calculated.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44081","44081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573409","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse of reviewing the level of net pay deductions from the salaries of Ministry of Defence fire fighters and fire officers was in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44082","44082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573410","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what arrangements will be made to provide submarine operational cover while HMS Ambush in undergoing repairs; and what risks have been identified as a result of those arrangements.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44090","44090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573411","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total amount of pay deducted from the salaries of Ministry of Defence fire fighter and fire officer grades through net pay deductions was in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44079","44079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573412","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the net pay deductions from the salaries of Ministry of Defence fire fighters and fire officers reflect the full difference in the value of pension benefits accrued compared with staff of similar grades working for local authorities.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44080","44080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573413","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how long HMS Ambush is expected to remain out of service while repairs are being conducted; and where that repair work will be carried out.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44091","44091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573414","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 2 March 2016 to Question 28220, which areas have locally determined arrangements for issuing iodine tablets in the event of a radiation emergency involving an operational nuclear reactor; to which nuclear reactors those arrangements are linked in (a) the UK, (b) other countries and (c) areas that have a pre-disposition to households in the detailed planning area; what other arrangements his Department has in place for issuing iodine tablets in areas that do not have pre-distribution to households; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44105","44105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573415","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the circumstances were of the collision involving HMS Ambush near Gibraltar on 20 July 2016; and whether there will be a board of inquiry investigation into that incident.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44092","44092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573416","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the rationale was for his Department's decision to allow soldiers who have completed only Phase One training to be called up to perform frontline tasks.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44104","44104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573417","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department or other bodies provide to help veterans experiencing mental health difficulties as a result of military service.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44139","44139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573418","2016-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps are being taken to prevent discrimination against people with dyslexia in the Armed Forces.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44156","44156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573419","2016-09-06","Department for Education","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to prevent self-employed adults with violent convictions providing extracurricular classes or sessions to children for sports or activities which have no governing body.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44157","44157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573420","2016-09-06","Department for Education","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what role Ofsted has in its (a) reports and (b) other work in monitoring the level of integration of asylum seekers and refugees in schools.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44165","44165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573421","2016-09-06","Department for Education","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether students from other EU member states who plan to start their studies in the UK in autumn 2017 will be considered eligible for student loans.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44136","44136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573422","2016-09-06","Department for Education","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department issues guidance on the proportion of a school's annual budget it considers prudent for a school to hold as a cash balance.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44117","44117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573423","2016-09-06","Department for Education","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to progress reforms to Disabled Student Allowances.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44084","44084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573424","2016-09-06","Department for Education","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total value of the repayments issued by the Student Loans Company to people who had overpaid their student loan was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44085","44085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573425","2016-09-06","Department for Education","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people who have already repaid their student loan in full are having loan repayments deducted from their pay.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44086","44086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573426","2016-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy that the UK will continue after the UK leaves the EU to recognise the professional qualifications of all people with professional qualifications from other European Economic Area member states whose qualifications are currently recognised and who are currently registered to provide professional services in the UK.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44025","44025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/573427","2016-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on the Government continuing to recognise professional qualifications obtained by citizens and residents of member states of the European Economic Area and members of their families from institutions (a) in other European Economic Area countries and (b) outside the European Economic Area under the same terms as now obtained when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 44027","44027"
