"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081848","2019-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost to the consumer of Ofgem's creation of Customer Engagement Groups in each energy network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Sir Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227971","227971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081849","2019-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department (a) owns or (b) leases the former Kodak processing unit at 26-38 Rylston road in Fulham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Greg Hands","Greg Hands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228047","228047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081850","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) facilities, (b) military manpower and (c)civilian manpower are based at (i) the British Defence Singapore Support Unit and (ii) the Joint Logistics Support Base, Duqm, Oman.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227935","227935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081851","2019-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department has made on reducing regulation.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227936","227936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081852","2019-03-07","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of additional carbon dioxide that has been emitted in each of the last five years as a result of UK Export Finance funding for fossil fuel projects overseas.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228121","228121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081853","2019-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what reassurances he has received from Ofgem on the selection of members to the gas network (a) Customer Challenge and (b) Customer Engagement Groups to ensure that no single body carries disproportionate influence over the outcomes from those groups.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Sir Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227972","227972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081854","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the evidential basis was for the DVLA's decision to classify autism spectrum disorders as a condition which must be declared.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228122","228122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081855","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 18 July 2017 and 23 July 2018 to Questions 4768 and 163751, how many Armed Forces personnel work as targeting advisers in the HQ of the Royal Saudi Airforce HQ; and whether those personnel remain present during strikes coordinated in that HQ in Yemen.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228123","228123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081856","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the DVLA has taken to ensure that people with autism spectrum disorders are aware of the recent changes that mean they need to declare their diagnosis.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228124","228124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081857","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 33 of the Government's August 2018 Civil Society Strategy, what steps his Department has taken explore further initiatives based on the learnings from the funding model adopted by the social sector during the Grenfell response.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228125","228125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081858","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 37 of the Government's August 2018 Civil Society Strategy, what progress has been made on his Department's target of training a further 3,500 people in community organising through a national network of Social Action Hubs and partnerships with public and social sector organisations by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228126","228126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081859","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which stakeholder groups the DVLA engaged with when deciding that autistic spectrum disorders needed to be declared.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228127","228127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081860","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 41 of the Government's August 2018 Civil Society Strategy, what steps his Department has taken with NHS England to strengthen volunteering within the NHS, spreading impact volunteering opportunities in priority areas across the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228128","228128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081861","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the new Radiotherapy Operational Delivery Networks announced by NHS England will be funded through the £20.5bn of extra funding announced in 2018.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228048","228048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081862","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 41 of the Government's August 2018 Civil Society Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to further embed and scale people taking action as a core part of how public services are delivered and explore how the government can best continue to back and scale high impact social value initiatives.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228129","228129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081863","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Department pays the salaries of liaison officers on secondment to Saudi Arabia; and from what budget those payments are made.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228130","228130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081864","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce wait times for Her Majesties Courts and Tribunals Service.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Sir Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227973","227973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081865","2019-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) charity shops and (b) other second hand retailers of plans to replace CE markings with a bespoke UK mark in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228049","228049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081866","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of recent bank branch closures on (a) rural and suburban communities and (b) the community of Sheffield Hallam constituency.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228131","228131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081867","2019-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the research and observation exemption claimed by people hunting deer with dogs under section 9 of the Hunting Act 2004 is legitimately claimed; and what information his Department holds on whether any such research has been published.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228132","228132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081868","2019-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what grace period is planned for retailers to adapt to the replacement of CE markings in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228050","228050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081869","2019-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure that any items in stock in charity shops on 29 March 2019 are not required to change their CE labels to bespoke UK labels in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228051","228051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081870","2019-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure that second hand goods can be sold in perpetuity by charity shops even if they only have a CE label in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228052","228052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081871","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of losing access to the network offered by the European University Institute will have on the UK's research capacity.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228133","228133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081872","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been excluded from (a) primary schools and (b) secondary schools in Bedford Borough in each year for which information is available; if he will publish those exclusions by school; how many of those exclusions were permanent exclusions; and what the national average in England is for school exclusions at primary and secondary level.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228134","228134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081873","2019-03-06","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has undertaken an impact assessment on (a) noise pollution and (b) air pollution that would be caused by the changes to flight paths proposed under the Heathrow Airspace and Future Operations Consultation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228135","228135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081874","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2019 to Question 221002 on Navy: Shipping, what the maximum (a) lifespan is of  newly constructed warships and (b) number of years commercial vessels can have been in service to be considered for military refurbishment.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228136","228136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081875","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the UK-Israel Free Trade Agreement will exclude Israeli settlements in the Occupied Palestinian Territories in line with current European Union differentiation.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228137","228137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081876","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities have (a) been granted permission to move (i) up to 0.5 per cent or (ii) in excess of 0.5 per cent of schools block funding to high needs block funding, (b) been denied permission to move schools block funding to high needs block funding and (c) made a request to move schools block funding to high needs block funding but no decision has yet been made; and what criteria his Department uses to determine such applications.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228138","228138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081877","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to Answer of 1 March 2019 to Question 224318 on Special Educational Needs: Finance, when plans to launch his Department's call for evidence looking into the financial incentives in the SEND system.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228139","228139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081878","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on the (a) eviction of the Abu Assab family and (b) potential eviction of a further 200 Palestinian families from their homes in East Jerusalem.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228140","228140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081879","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve response times within the Service Complaints Ombudsman.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228141","228141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081880","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of CCTV installed in taxi and private hire vehicles on improving passenger safety.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228053","228053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081881","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the procedure is for addressing complaints raised by black, Asian, minority ethnic and female military personnel.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228142","228142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081882","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of current lending conditions to (a) large, (b) medium, (c) small and (d) micro house builders in England.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228143","228143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081883","2019-03-06","Department for International Development","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the long-term strategy of the Government is with respect to sustainable support for the United Nations Relief and Works Agency for Palestine Refugees in the Near East.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228144","228144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081884","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of Israel’s decision to withhold $138 million in taxes from the Palestinian authorities on the economic situation in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228145","228145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081886","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government , what steps he will take to stimulate improved lending terms from high street banks to small and medium-sized house builders in England.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228147","228147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081887","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how responsibility for maintaining Victoria Tower Gardens will be divided between Royal Parks and the body responsible for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre once the Memorial and Learning Centre has been built.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227956","227956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081888","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of (a) the annual running costs of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre and (b) how much of that cost will be covered by visitor entrance fees and other income.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227957","227957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081889","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2018 to Question 203298, National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, what is the relevance of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre being located on the banks of the Thames.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227958","227958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081890","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question 225480, whether international students would be guaranteed a student visa under the new immigration system once their European Temporary Leave to Remain runs out, provided they pass an additional criminality check, without additional cost or administrative burden.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228054","228054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081891","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress he has made on recruiting probation officers in (a) England and (b) North West; and how many vacancies there are in each of those areas.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228148","228148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081892","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the report entitled, An inspection of North West Division National Probation Service, published by HM Inspectorate of Probation in February 2019, what steps he is taking to ensure that probation staff are trained on the policy requirements in relation to the use of remote technology.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228149","228149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081893","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the report entitled, An inspection of North West Division National Probation Service, published by HM Inspectorate of Probation in February 2019, what steps is he taking to ensure that the premises in the North West used by the Probation Service are of an adequate standard.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228150","228150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081894","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the report entitled, An inspection of North West Division National Probation Service, published by HM Inspectorate of Probation in February 2019, what steps is he taking to ensure that probation staff are able to use court staff facilities.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228151","228151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081895","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the report entitled, An inspection of North West Division National Probation Service, published by HM Inspectorate of Probation in February 2019, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) risk management plans in relation to domestic abuse and (b) the reporting to courts of plans are improved.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228152","228152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081896","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps are being taken to reduce the number of agency staff employed by the Probation Service.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228153","228153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081897","2019-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for each year since 2016-17, how many universal credit full service claimants submitted a DS1500 form to access universal credit under the special rules for terminal illness; and how many of those applications were (a) accepted and (b) rejected.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227959","227959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081898","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer  of 22 January 2019 to Question 207274 on Arms Trade: Saudi Arabia, whether the terms of the (a) 1985 and (b) 1986 Al Yamamah MOUs have been replicated in the Saudi British Defence Cooperation Programme.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228154","228154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081899","2019-03-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to Sporting Future: A Strategy for an Active Nation, published in December 2015, what progress the Inter-Ministerial Group for Healthy Living has made on implementing a joined-up approach to delivery and funding for sport and physical activity.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228155","228155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081900","2019-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of DS1500 forms issued to claimants of universal credit were not returned to the Department in each year since 2016-17.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227960","227960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081901","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applicants that were refused access to the universal credit special rules for terminal illness died within six months of that refusal in each year since 2016-17.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227961","227961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081902","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what consultation with stakeholders his Department undertook in advance of its decision to include a reasonable expectation of death within six months provision as a requirement for the issue of a DS1500 form.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227974","227974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081903","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on claimant wellbeing of the requirement to (a) declare a terminal illness and (b) declare a prognosis at the outset of a universal credit claim, as a precursor to accessing the special rules for terminal illness.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227975","227975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081904","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department has in place for claimants who have a terminal illness but have not declared this at the outset of their universal credit claim.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227976","227976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081905","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received in the last six months on the (a) level of charges levied by the DVLA to private parking companies seeking data on vehicle owners and (b) level of proof required by the DVLA before that data is released.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228156","228156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081906","2019-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions have taken place between the Governments of the United Kingdom and Republic of Ireland to resolve the issue of the two Northern Irish fishing vessels seized by the Irish Navy on 26 February 2019.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228157","228157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081907","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what support from the Coastal Communities Fund is available for Scotland.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228158","228158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081908","2019-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 124 of the High Court judgement of 10 July 2017, what (a) processes and (b) procedures are used by Saudi Arabia for UK and Saudi officials to report potential violations of international humanitarian law up the chain of command.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228159","228159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081909","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many incidents of racism were reported in schools in (a) England, (b) Essex, (c) Tendring and (d) Clacton constituency in (i) 2017 and (ii) 2018.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228160","228160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081910","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage anti-racism initiatives in schools.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228161","228161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081911","2019-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, in which month of 2018 the consignment of 31 reindeer was imported from Finland; who made the decision to permit the import of the reindeer; and whether the animals’ welfare was taken into account as part of that decision.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227943","227943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081912","2019-03-06","Cabinet Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an estimate of the net change in the number of people in the working age population as a result of ageing demographic trends in the UK and excluding in-year migrants in the (a) last five years and (b) next five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227977","227977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081913","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, for what reason the 9 March 2015 Open General Trade Control Licence to Saudi Arabia was denied.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228162","228162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081914","2019-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the consent process for acidising is the same as for fracking; how many applications for acidising have been granted in the last five years for which figures are available; and what health and safety critieria have to be met as part of that consent process.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227944","227944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081915","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to increase the accountability of the Financial Conduct Authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228163","228163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081916","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's policy is on the statutory immunity of the Financial Conduct Authority in cases where it is found to have acted negligently.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228164","228164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081917","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the availability of technetium and krypton generators for nuclear medicine procedures in hospitals.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228055","228055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081918","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Transport on transporting technetium and krypton generators by air instead of road in the event that the UK leaves the EU without deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228056","228056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081919","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the state of political and constitutional freedoms in Sierra Leone; and what steps his Department has taken in response to recent political and constitutional events in Sierra Leone.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228165","228165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081920","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions has he had with his counterpart in the Government of Eritrea on reducing the number of people conscripted into the (a) armed forces and (b) security services.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227945","227945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081921","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the weaponry owned by Russia is that has resulted in that country being in violation of its INF Treaty obligations; and what the location is of that weaponry.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227937","227937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081922","2019-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in which non-UK countries UK pensioners (a) receive and (b) do not receive an annual uprating to their state pension in accordance with the triple lock.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228166","228166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081923","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the level of educational outcomes of students attending Pupil Referral Units.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228167","228167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081924","2019-03-07","Cabinet Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the Government has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) billboards and (b) other physical advertisements on how the public should prepare for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228168","228168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081925","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the maintenance of freedom of expression in publicly funded educational establishments.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227978","227978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081926","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether a free trade deal with the United States is a priority for his Department.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227979","227979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081927","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic status the European Union will have to the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227980","227980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081928","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions for (a) carrying a knife and (b) knife-related crime resulted in a sentence of (i) up to six months, (ii) six to 12 months and (iii) over 12 months in the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227981","227981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081929","2019-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount of time spent looking for a job was  each week by individuals claiming (a) universal credit and (b) job seekers allowance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227982","227982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081930","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to increase trade between the UK and Tanzania.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227983","227983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081931","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many veterans have taken part in the Armed Forces to Teachers scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227984","227984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081932","2019-03-06","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the status of Gibraltar remains a red line for the UK in its negotiations on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227985","227985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081933","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of knife offences in Havering in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227986","227986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081934","2019-03-06","Department for International Development","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that aid spending supports the UK's political, commercial and diplomatic priorities.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227987","227987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081935","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential merits of increasing the minimum sentence for knife-related crime.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227988","227988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081936","2019-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the suitability of chlorinated chicken for the UK market.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227989","227989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081937","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential merits of introducing a compulsory custodial sentence for carrying a knife.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227990","227990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081938","2019-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to increase the rate of reduction in the UK's carbon emissions.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227991","227991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081939","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to reduce organised acquisitive crime in the outer London boroughs.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227992","227992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081940","2019-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are being taken to prevent methane leaking from the fracking site operated by Cuadrilla at Preston New Road.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227993","227993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079548","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the probation and courts IT systems failure that occurred in January 2019.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227391","227391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079549","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of estimated cost to the public purse of the probation and courts IT systems failure in January 2019 has been recovered from IT suppliers.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227392","227392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079550","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has undertaken a review into the causes of the probation and courts IT systems failure in January 2019.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227393","227393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079551","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Civil Service People Survey 2018, published in December 2018, what steps his Department is taking to address staff concerns on the HMCTS reform programme.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227394","227394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079552","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of court closures on the time taken for hearings to be listed.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227395","227395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079553","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court cases have proceeded in the absence of a defendant in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227396","227396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079554","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff in the Probate Service have applied to work in a Courts and Tribunal Service Centre in the last six months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227397","227397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079555","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what consultation with recognised trades unions his Department undertook on the proposal to use bulk scanning and printing services in the Probate Service before that contract had been signed with the supplier.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227398","227398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079556","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken was for (a) the issue of a divorce petition and (b) the issue of divorce petition to decree nisi in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227399","227399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079557","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts have closed since 1 January 2009; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of each of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227400","227400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079558","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question 223965 on Home Office: staff, how long each of the three contingent workers that have been employed in his Department for more than 24 months have worked to date to the nearest month.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227369","227369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079559","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of February 28 to Question 223969 on Home Office: Employment Agencies223969, what the (a) start and (b) end dates are for each of the contracts listed in that Answer.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227370","227370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079560","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question 223971 on Home Office: Staff, what the daily rate of pay was for each of the roles listed in that Answer.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227371","227371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079561","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 223140 on Home Office: Staff, if he will publish a list of the companies that are contracted as suppliers; and how many staff are provided by each of those suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227372","227372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079562","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 223140 on Home Office: Staff, whether a (a) Counter Terrorist Check, (b) Security Check and (c) Developed Vetting has been required for each of the staff contracted by suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227373","227373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079563","2019-03-05","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 223140 on Home Office: Staff, under which frameworks those suppliers were contracted.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227374","227374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079564","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Government response to the Disqualification criteria for councillors and mayors consultation, published in October 2018, when he plans to bring forward legislation to ensure that a person subject to (a) an anti-social behaviour injunction, (b) a Criminal Behaviour Order, (c) a Sexual Risk Order or (d) who is on the Sex Offenders’ Register will be disqualified from standing for elected office.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227382","227382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079565","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to respond to his Department's consultation on the regulation of society lotteries.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227389","227389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079566","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many FTE staff employed by HMRC work on issues related to tax mediation in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227384","227384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079567","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cases dealt with by HMRC involved the application of alternative dispute resolution in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227385","227385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079568","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many FTE staff employed by HMRC are working on issues related to international tax avoidance in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227386","227386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079569","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many FTE staff employed by HMRC are working on issues related to tackling smuggling in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227387","227387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079570","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) paid and (b) unpaid overtime hours worked by teachers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227364","227364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079571","2019-03-06","Department for International Development","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of measles cases throughout the world.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227365","227365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079572","2019-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has held with counterparts in the governments of Commonwealth member states on the payment of compensation to African veterans of the Second World War.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227366","227366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079573","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Administration on food standards in relation to a future trade deal after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227367","227367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079574","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government has plans to reform the cap on interchange rate fees for card payments introduced in the Interchange Fee Regulation 2016 from a percentage cap to a flat rate of 50p per transaction.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227415","227415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079575","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of children in the UK applying for a secondary school place who were accepted by their first choice every year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227368","227368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079576","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential correlation between the use of sunbeds for tanning the risk of skin cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227416","227416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079577","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, the proportion of cancer patients in England received radiotherapy as part of their primary treatment in 2018.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227381","227381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079578","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Development on improving the transparency and effectiveness of his Department’s aid programmes.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227378","227378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079579","2019-03-05","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to improve the transparency of his Department’s aid budget.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227379","227379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079580","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of (a) trends in fire-related deaths and (b) the adequacy of future funding for the Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227408","227408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079581","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the findings of Dame Judith Hackitt’s May 2018 Review of Building Regulations and Fire Safety, what steps his Department is taking to ensure adequate staffing of the Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227409","227409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079582","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps his Department has taken to tackle (a) wildfires and (b) other fires caused by environmental factors.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227410","227410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079583","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the findings of Dame Judith Hackitt’s May 2018 Review of Building Regulations and Fire Safety, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the Fire and Rescue Service is adequately resourced to conduct inspections of residential buildings.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227411","227411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079584","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the findings of Dame Judith Hackitt’s May 2018 Review of Building Regulations and Fire Safety, what steps his Department is taking to tackle shortages in fire engineering expertise.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227412","227412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079585","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people under 18 years old are serving life sentences due to convictions under joint enterprise law.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227375","227375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079586","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question 224315, for what reasons his Department has not made a recent estimate based on up to date prices of the cost to the NHS of treating injuries caused by excessive alcohol consumption.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227380","227380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079587","2019-03-06","Cabinet Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring the compatibility of registration officers’ systems for managing registration data between local authority areas.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227388","227388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079588","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons the contract for PET-CT scanning in Oxfordshire was awarded to InHealth and not Oxford University Hospitals Trust.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227413","227413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079589","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) accessibility, (b) cost and (c) quality of care of moving the PET-CT scanning service from Churchill Hospital in Oxford as a result of the decision to award the contract for scanning to InHealth.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227414","227414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079590","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to section 66 of the Immigration Act 2014, what the timeframe is for his Department to undertake a review of his powers to deprive individuals of their citizenship for the period from July 2015 to July 2018.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227383","227383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079591","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to include tackling the advertising of alcohol to children in the upcoming alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227390","227390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079592","2019-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding from the Housing Infrastructure Fund has been allocated to be spent in (a) St Albans and (b) North Hertfordshire district.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227406","227406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079593","2019-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many areas throughout England have passed Neighbourhood Plans.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227407","227407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079594","2019-03-05","Department for Education","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to calculate and update each year the amount of high needs funding to be allocated on the number of children being diagnosed with special needs; and what his policy is on directly correlating funding with need.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227363","227363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079595","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February to Question 218376 on Paramedical Staff: Small Claims, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of provisions for injured claimants who are unable to use the IT portal.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227402","227402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079596","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February to Question 218376 on Paramedical Staff: Small Claims, what the timeframe is for the roll-out the IT portal.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227403","227403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079597","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February to Question 218376 on Paramedical Staff: Small Claims, what plans his Department has to undertake testing of the IT portal in advance of its roll-out.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227404","227404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079598","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February to Question 218376 on Paramedical Staff: Small Claims, (a) who is designing and (b) what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of that new IT portal.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227405","227405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079599","2019-03-05","Department for Education","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) children and (b) children eligible for free school meals reached a Good Level of Development at age five in Huddersfield in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227376","227376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079600","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of increased probate fees on levels of charitable giving.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227377","227377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079601","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February to Question 222647 on HIV: Infection, what the timetable is for the review of the number of places available on the Pre-exposure Prophylaxis Impact trial by the PrEP Oversight Board.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227401","227401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079604","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the merits of the conclusion of the Institute of Legacy Management in November 2018 that changes to probate fees could cost charities in the region of £10 million annually in legacy income.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227417","227417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077730","2019-02-28","Department for International Development","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of trends in the level of food production in Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226112","226112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079315","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to ensure UK sports organisations are meeting commitments on athlete welfare.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227127","227127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079316","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department when drafting the Healthcare (International Arrangements) Bill made an assessment of the effect of implementing that legislation on the (a) EU-Canada Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement and (b) Trade in Services Agreement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227105","227105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079317","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of local town councils on coastal communities.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227165","227165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079318","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of stockpiling drugs so that patients can continue to have access to those drugs in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227166","227166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079320","2019-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will review the UK’s support for the current peace process in Myanmar.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227061","227061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079321","2019-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of diplomatic initiatives to prevent further violence between government forces and ethnic military groups in Karen and Rakhine states in Myanmar.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227062","227062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079322","2019-03-05","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the collective number of years of instutional experience is that HMRC has lost as a result of redundancies in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227116","227116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079323","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to replace EU funding for rural communities when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227054","227054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079324","2019-03-05","Department for Education","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has been made of the effect of high levels of air pollution near schools on school children.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227128","227128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079325","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to ensure NHS patients throughout England continue to receive liothyronine after recent price increase in the cost of that drug to the NHS.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227053","227053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079326","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many immigration appeals were (a) submitted and (b) determined in each of the last five years in relation to Home Office refusal, curtailment and removal decisions in ETS-linked cases.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227034","227034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079327","2019-03-05","Department for International Development","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding from the public purse the UK has provided to the Trust Fund for Africa in each year since its establishment.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227143","227143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079328","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral evidence of the HMRC director general of border co-ordination to the Public Accounts Committee on 5 November 2018, HC 1595, Question 51, what assessment has been made of the ability of the inland facilities to handle high-risk trade through (a) container and (b) roll-on roll-off ports across all four UK nations.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227122","227122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079329","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral evidence of the HMRC chief executive to the Public Accounts Committee on 5 November 2018, HC 1595, Question 53, what additional inland clearance facilities are being planned.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227123","227123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079330","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what deployments are proposed by the HMRC surge and rapid response team in respect of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227124","227124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079331","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions HMRC has had with the Government Race Disparity Audit Advisory Group in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227125","227125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079332","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral evidence of the HMRC director general for border co-ordination to the Public Accounts Committee on 20 November 2017, HC 558, Questions 78 and 111, what additional infrastructure is planned in each of the four UK nations to facilitate customs-related checks.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227126","227126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079333","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many criminal legal aid firms were in operation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227146","227146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079334","2019-03-05","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on steps schools can take to reduce the number of young people joining gangs.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227036","227036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079335","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions his Department has had with social media companies on the adequacy of the (a) age limits on users of their services and (b) checks that those companies have in place on the age of users.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227037","227037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079336","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children who have been prevented from receiving a vaccination due to a parent withholding their consent each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227038","227038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079337","2019-03-05","Cabinet Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost to the public purse of holding a second referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227039","227039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079338","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Sudanese counterpart on recent reports of the arrest by the Sudan police of fourteen academics in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227100","227100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079339","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the recommendation of the Joint Council for the Welfare of Immigrants that the Government grant all (a) EEA and (b) Swiss nationals and family members resident in the UK the automatic right to remain.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227101","227101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079340","2019-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of UK factories that used robots in the manufacturing process in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227040","227040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079341","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were unemployed in Ribble Valley in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227047","227047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079342","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the employment rate in the Ribble Valley constituency was in each year since 2016.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227048","227048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079343","2019-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the planned date for the Trafalgar-Class SSN to leave service.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227033","227033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079344","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the number of private landlords who do not conduct annual gas safety inspections; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227044","227044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079345","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to address the findings of the Public Health England report entitled Vaping in England: evidence update summary February 2019 that the number of children who have tried e-cigarettes has doubled since 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227132","227132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079346","2019-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland of 13 February 2019, Official Report, column 911, how much has been paid in salaries to Members of the Legislative Assembly since the collapse of the Northern Ireland Assembly in January 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227055","227055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079347","2019-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for the Cabinet Office of 27 February 2019, Official Report column 367, what preparations the Government is making to mark the 21st anniversary of the signing of the Belfast/Good Friday Agreement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227056","227056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079348","2019-03-05","Church Commissioners","2019-02-28","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what authority set down in the statutes of the Commissioners enabled the payment of £29,800 to meet damages and costs relating to the case of Bishop George Bell; and what steps the Commissioners took to scrutinise that settlement before they made over those funds.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227049","227049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079349","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what feasibility studies been completed in the last 12 months on the future of Cawdor Barracks part of the Better Defence Estates programme.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227073","227073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079350","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to introduce (a) 25p per coffee cup surcharge, (b) bottle deposit scheme and (c) refillable water bottle policy.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227078","227078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079351","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of changing the rules on prominence to support public service broadcasters on digital platforms.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227133","227133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079352","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on teaching digital skills in schools.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227134","227134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079353","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that human biases are not replicated in artificial intelligence technologies used in public services.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227135","227135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079354","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent progress he has made in commissioning the National Citizen Service 2.0.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227136","227136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079355","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 7 of the report entitled Paying to Breathe: Why unfair asthma prescription charges must be stopped, published in February 2019, what plans he has to change the Prescription Charges exemptions list as a result of the finding in that report that 57 per cent of people with asthma are skipping medication due to the cost.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227071","227071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079356","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 7 of the report entitled Paying to Breathe: Why unfair asthma prescription charges must be stopped, published in February 2019, what assessment he has made of the effect of prescription charges on people on low incomes who have asthma.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227072","227072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079357","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which (a) companies, (b) organisations and (c) Government Departments are liable for compensation claims for damage as a result of induced seismicity from hydraulic fracturing operations.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227147","227147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079358","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which (a) companies, (b) organisations and (c) Government Department's will be liable for the long-term (i) decommissioning of hydraulic fracturing wells and (ii) associated effects of hydraulic fracturing operations in the event that the licensed operator goes out of business.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227148","227148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079359","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the evidential basis is for the decision to suspension hydraulic fracturing operations for 18 hours as a result of induced seismic activity of >0.5 magnitude.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227149","227149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079360","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the cold venting of fugitive gasses is allowed to occur at hydraulic fracturing operations.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227150","227150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079361","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what regulatory conditions are in place to detect unrecovered fugitive gas and fluid from hydraulic fracturing operations.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227151","227151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079362","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what processes hydraulic fracturing operators have to follow to dispose of waste; and what the final resting location is for hydraulic fracturing waste.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227152","227152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079363","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether shale gas regulators have an agreed process for safe recycling of flowback from hydraulic fracturing operations.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227153","227153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079364","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons shale gas regulators do not conduct independent well integrity reports for hydraulic fracturing operations.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227154","227154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079365","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the traffic light monitoring system for regulating fracking-induced seismicity, for what reasons red events are allowed as part of an operator’s hydraulic fracturing plan.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227155","227155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079366","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the traffic light monitoring system for regulating fracking-induced seismicity, for what reason trailing events of over 0.5 magnitude are not categorised as red events.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227156","227156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079367","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Department's letter of 27 February 2019 to the hon. Member for Bridgend on the Health and Safety Executive, what is meant by the phrase centrally reported.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227063","227063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079368","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Department's letter of 27 February 2019 to the hon. Member for Bridgend, which notices of contravention placed on his Department related to the (a) Army, (b) RAF, (c) Royal Navy and (d) Royal Marines in each year between 2012 and 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227064","227064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079369","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Department's letter of 27 February 2019 to the hon. Member for Bridgend on the Health and Safety Executive, what the criteria are for determining whether notices of contravention placed on his Department by that Executive are to be reported (a) centrally and (b) elsewhere.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227065","227065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079370","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Department's letter of 27 February 2019 to the hon. Member for Bridgend on the Health and Safety Executive, whether (a) a policy change, (b) a staffing issue and (c) another reason constituted the reason why notices of contravention placed on the Ministry of Defence by the Health and Safety Executive were not reported centrally in the years (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227066","227066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079371","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Department's letter of 27 February 2019 to the hon. Member for Bridgend on the Health and Safety Executive, how his Department ensures that when notices of contravention are centrally reported (a) all appropriate follow-up action by the Health and Safety Executive to ensure compliance is completed, (b) lessons are learned, (c) remedial action is implemented, (d) lessons are cascaded across the armed forces and (e) lessons are not confined to one location.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227067","227067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079372","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Department's letter of 27 February 2019 to the hon. Member for Bridgend on the Health and Safety Executive, how his Department ensures that when notices of contravention are not centrally reported (a) all appropriate follow-up action by the Health and Safety Executive to ensure compliance is completed, (b) lessons are learned, (c) remedial action is implemented, (d) lessons are cascaded across the armed forces and (e) lessons are not confined to one location.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227068","227068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079373","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Department's letter of 27 February 2019 to the hon. Member for Bridgend on the Health and Safety Executive, to what (a) changes, (b) requirements, (c) staffing, (d) training and (e) other issues the notices of contravention placed on his Department in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014 and (iv) 2017 relate.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227069","227069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079374","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will share the eligibility criteria for the pupil premium with the (a) Department of Education and (b) schools.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227163","227163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079375","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 220226 on Genito-urinary Medicine, what the number of appointments for STIs has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227106","227106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079376","2019-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the ability of the new off-shore patrol vessels ships to have a UAV capability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227042","227042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079377","2019-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on members of the armed forces personnel that have reached retirement age but want to extend their service and are fit and capable enough to do so; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227043","227043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079378","2019-03-05","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the adequacy of his Department's policy on serving advisory notices on tyres found to be in a dangerous condition but which are not illegal at MOT examinations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227051","227051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079379","2019-03-05","Department for Education","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 222633 on Pre-School Education: Closures, what is involved in the network of English hubs in which there will be a £26 million investment.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227098","227098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079380","2019-03-05","Department for Education","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 222633 on Pre-School Education: Closures, if he will list £20 million investment in training and professional development for pre-reception early years’ staff in disadvantaged areas by (a) region and (b) local authority.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227099","227099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079381","2019-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to her Written Statement of 21 February 2019 on Employment and Support Allowance, Official Report HCWS 1348, which work streams the 1,200 staff working on underpayment cases have been taken from; and how many of those staff have been (a) moved from other areas of her Department and (ii) newly recruited.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227168","227168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079382","2019-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an estimate of the number of people who went into (a) rent arrears and (b) council tax arrears following the underpayment of their employment and support allowance; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227169","227169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079383","2019-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of staffing levels in universal credit centres; and what proportion of fixed-term staff working in universal credit centres are on (a) permanent contracts and (b) zero-hour contracts.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227130","227130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079384","2019-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has received representations on therapeutic radiographers and the forthcoming workforce implementation plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227070","227070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079385","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions the Government has had with (a) peer-to-peer lenders and (b) other organisations in the fintech sector on  proposals for regulation of the sector in the Financial Conduct Authority's July 2018 CP18/20 consultation paper.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227074","227074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079386","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the international competitiveness of the UK's fintech sector of the Financial Conduct Authority's proposals for regulation of the peer-to-peer lending sector in its July 2018 CP18/20 consultation paper.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227075","227075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079387","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions the Government has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the potential effect on the strength of the UK's peer-to-peer lending sector of the proposals on marketing restrictions in the FCA July 2018 CP 18/20 consultation paper.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227076","227076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079388","2019-03-05","Department for Education","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of secondary school school places that will be required in Mansfield in each year to 2025.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227164","227164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079389","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the shipping industry of compliance with the International Maritime Organisation’s 0.5 per cent cap on the sulphur content of shipping exhaust emissions from 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227080","227080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079390","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from the shipping industry on the International Maritime Organisation’s 0.5 per cent cap on the sulphur content of shipping exhaust emissions from 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227081","227081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079391","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the shipping industry’s compliance with the International Maritime Organisation’s 0.5 per cent cap on the sulphur content of shipping exhaust emissions from 1 January 2020 does not have a negative effect on seafarer (a) employment and (b) pay.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227082","227082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079392","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to allocate additional funding to the Maritime and Coastguard Agency to enabling the Agency to enforce the International Maritime Organisation’s 0.5 per cent cap on the sulphur content of shipping exhaust emissions from 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227083","227083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079393","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the investment required by ports to provide access to alternative fuel sources in order to comply with international regulations on the greenhouse gas content of exhaust emissions from merchant shipping.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227084","227084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079394","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which ports with waste reception facilities are compliant with the International Maritime Organisation’s mandatory guidelines on exhaust gas cleaning systems; and when each of those ports was last inspected for compliance.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227085","227085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079395","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many merchant vessels on the UK Ship Register use fuel which is compliant with the International Maritime Organisation’s 0.5 per cent cap on the sulphur content of shipping exhaust emissions from 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227086","227086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079396","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff have been employed by HMRC in each month since June 2016.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227157","227157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079397","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many merchant vessels on the UK Ship Register have been fitted with exhaust gas cleaning systems; and how many of those vessels have been inspected for compliance with the International Maritime Organisation’s 0.5 per cent cap on the sulphur content of shipping exhaust emissions to be introduced on 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227087","227087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079398","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the number of internationally registered merchant vessels using sea routes from UK ports that use fuel that is compliant with the International Maritime Organisation’s 0.5 per cent cap on the sulphur content of shipping exhaust emissions to be introduced on 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227088","227088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079399","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff have been employed by his Department in each month since June 2016.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227158","227158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079400","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the investment required in the national ports network to provide adequate access to alternative fuel sources in order to comply with international regulations on the greenhouse gas content of exhaust emissions from merchant shipping.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227089","227089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079401","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of High Speed Two; and what recent assessment he has made of the value for money of that project.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227137","227137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079402","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the number of internationally registered merchant vessels regularly using sea routes from UK ports that use fuel that is compliant with the International Maritime Organisation’s 0.5 per cent cap on the sulphur content of shipping exhaust emissions to be introduced on 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227090","227090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079403","2019-03-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff have been employed by his Department in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227159","227159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079404","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of using the budget allocated to High Speed Two to instead invest in (a) regional transport infrastructure projects, (b) upgrading existing rail lines and (c) reducing government expenditure.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227138","227138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079405","2019-03-04","Department for International Trade","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff have been employed by his Department in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227160","227160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079406","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the number of internationally registered merchant vessels regularly plying trade on routes from UK ports that use fuel which is compliant with the International Maritime Organisation’s 0.5% cap on the sulphur content of shipping exhaust emissions to be introduced on 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227091","227091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079407","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have been employed by his Department in each month since June 2016.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227161","227161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079408","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to ensure that (a) people on teacher training courses are trained in dealing with children with additional learning needs and (b) sufficient on-going training is offered to qualified teachers to ensure that an adequate level of training is maintained.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227052","227052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079409","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has allocated funding to the shipping industry to prepare for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227092","227092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079410","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vessels were re-registered from the UK Ship Register in each month between January 2018 and January 2019.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227093","227093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079411","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new vessels were registered on the UK Ship Register in each month between January 2018 and January 2019.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227094","227094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079412","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of (a) open and (b) closed loop scrubbers on annual levels of greenhouse gas content in exhaust fumes from merchant ships operating from UK ports.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227095","227095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079413","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of international trends in the regulation of exhaust gas cleaning systems in the shipping industry.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227096","227096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079414","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has issued to the shipping industry on (a) alternative fuels and (b) exhaust gas cleaning systems; and when that guidance was last updated.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227097","227097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079415","2019-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224346 on Buildings: Insulation, whether he has made a recent assessment of the dangers of toxic smoke from commonly used insulation materials in the event of a fire.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227107","227107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079416","2019-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224346 on Buildings: Insulation, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings on the toxicity of common insulation materials in the December 2018 study entitled Fire behaviour of modern façade materials–Understanding the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227108","227108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079417","2019-03-05","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff were transferred to HMRC to work on issues relating to the UK's withdrawal from the EU in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227117","227117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079418","2019-03-05","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were prosecuted by HMRC for fraudulently claiming gift aid payments in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227118","227118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079419","2019-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224346 on Buildings: Insulation, what criteria the expert panel will use to decide whether further large-scale testing is needed on cladding materials; and if his Department will publish those assessments.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227109","227109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079420","2019-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224346 on Buildings: Insulation, whether his Department still plans to conduct a BS 8414 test with a system incorporating High-Pressure Laminate cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227110","227110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079421","2019-03-05","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK nationals were deported back to the UK in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227077","227077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079422","2019-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224346 on Buildings: Insulation, whether he has made a recent assessment of (a) the combustibility of a range of common insulation materials and (b) the safety of those materials for use on buildings.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227111","227111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079423","2019-03-05","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff at HMRC work on issues related to tax and the overseas crown dependencies and territories.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227119","227119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079424","2019-03-05","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff at HMRC work on matters related to Value Added Tax.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227120","227120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079425","2019-03-05","Treasury","2019-02-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff at HMRC work on issues related to tax compliance.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227121","227121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079426","2019-03-05","Cabinet Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office,  what estimate the Government has made of the cost to the public purse of the planned television advertisements outlining how the UK's exit from the EU will affect the public.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227162","227162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079427","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 222020, how many migrant families were supported by local authorities under Section 17 of the Children Act 1989 in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227112","227112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079428","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 222021, how many changes of circumstance applications to gain recourse to public funds were granted by his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227113","227113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079429","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 222021, how many changes of circumstance applications to gain recourse to public funds were granted by his Department in 2016-17.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227114","227114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079430","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 222021, how many changes of circumstance applications to gain recourse to public funds were granted by his Department in 2017-18.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227115","227115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079431","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the HMPPS no-smoking policy will be extended to cover Immigration Removal Centres.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227139","227139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079432","2019-03-05","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to introduce a no-smoking policy at all UK Immigration Removal Centres.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227140","227140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079433","2019-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which premises controlled by his Department do not have a no-smoking policy.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227141","227141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079434","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which of his Department's premises do not operate a no-smoking policy.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227142","227142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079435","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to include asthma in the prescription charges exemptions list.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227045","227045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079436","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the level of asbestos in schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227031","227031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079437","2019-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department has closed since 1 January 2009; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value of each of those sales was.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227131","227131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079438","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security of UK citizens visiting Sharm el Sheikh; if he will review his travel advice on that area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227032","227032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079439","2019-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many tribunal cases on personal independence payment have taken place in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227103","227103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079440","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether there are any pensioners entitled to pensions credit who are not in receipt of that benefit.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227104","227104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079441","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing mandatory disability equality training for licensed taxicab and minicab drivers.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227079","227079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079442","2019-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to UK Citizens stranded abroad as a result of the grounding of flights following the escalation of tensions between India and Pakistan.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227129","227129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079443","2019-03-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he take steps to ensure that legal changes to the Northern Ireland backstop are a priority in the negotiations on the withdrawal agreement with the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227102","227102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079444","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Code of Practice for the Welfare of Laying Hens and Pellets.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227046","227046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079445","2019-03-05","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he undertook a review of security at Sharm El Sheikh Airport during the Prime Minister's recent visit to Egypt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227035","227035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079446","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce the results of his review of pavement parking which began in summer 2018.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227145","227145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079447","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the cost was of the construction of Richmond House.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227041","227041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079448","2019-03-05","Department for Education","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when organisations will be able to register on the Education and Skills Funding Agency register of training organisations.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227144","227144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079449","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals for the introduction of compulsory calorie information on restaurant menus.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227050","227050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079450","2019-03-05","Women and Equalities","2019-02-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Convention on the Elimination of all Forms of Discrimination Against Women, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on improving access for women's organisations and coalitions to engage with Government.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227057","227057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079451","2019-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to support the Centenary Global Action and global efforts for a strong International Labour Organisation Convention to end workplace harassment.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227058","227058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079452","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the average in-year bonus was for (a) male and (b) female staff in his Department at each grade in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227059","227059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1079453","2019-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to his Department's Gender Pay Gap Report 2018, for what reasons at Grade A 32.26 per cent of men received bonuses compared to 18.75 per cent of women.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227060","227060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078450","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department provides to help homeless applicants make a claim for universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226486","226486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078451","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2018 to Question 160779, how many (a) men and (b) women in private sector pensions schemes were contracted-out between 1978-79 and 1987-88; and how many of those (i) men and (ii) women (A) have reached state retirement age since the introduction of the single tier pension and (B) are still to reach state retirement age.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226688","226688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078452","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the effect on (a) value for money and (b) service provision of providing funding to local authorities through (i) long-term arrangements and (ii) one-off funding streams.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226662","226662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078453","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Government has been consulted on the proposals to be put forward by the US President in the plan entitled, Deal of the Century in relation to Israel.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226512","226512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078454","2019-03-04","Department for International Development","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether it remains the Government's policy to continue to support the United Nations Relief and Works Agency.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226513","226513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078455","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of naproxen on the NHS.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226707","226707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078456","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of stocks of naproxen held by the NHS in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226708","226708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078457","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the cost to the individual of becoming a victim of childhood sexual abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226672","226672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078458","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants have benefited from the provisions under section 119 (3) (a) and (b) of the Universal Credit Regulations 2013 that hardship payments cease to be recoverable in the event that such claimants have earnings above the thresholds specified in those regulations in each month since August 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226487","226487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078459","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training has been provided to Jobcentre Plus staff in the (a) UK and (b) Easington Constituency to support (i) people with autism and (ii) family carers looking after a child with autism to ensure they can access all necessary services.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226654","226654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078460","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many applications for products not yet on the market were made to NICE in each year from 2016 to 2018; and how many of those applications were granted.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226527","226527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078461","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the cost to the NHS of diabetes drugs prescriptions by CCG from 2018 to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226528","226528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078462","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Answer of 21 February 2019 to Question 222632, on Pre-school Education: Closures, what estimate he has made of the number of children with SEND affected by the closure of maintained nursery schools in the last five years.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226663","226663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078463","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Answer of 21 February 2019 to Question 222629, on Pre-school Education, for what reasons his Department did not refer to the reasons for the reduction in the number of maintained nursery schools since 2010 in that Answer.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226664","226664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078464","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 February 2019 to question 222631, for what reasons his Department did not refer to whether his Department has made an estimate of the cost to other public services in areas where maintained nursery schools have closed in that Answer.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226665","226665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078465","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2019 to Question 217588, Academies Enterprise Trust: Finance, how much of the £4.5 million provided to date is non-recoverable; and how much of the £3.06 million used for redundancies is non-recoverable.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226671","226671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078466","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to enable more midwifes to be qualified tongue tie practitioners.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226514","226514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078467","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2019 to Question 221779, High Speed Two: Lancaster, if he will meet (a) the hon. Member for Lancaster and Fleetwood and (b) Lancaster business leaders to discuss High Speed Two.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226699","226699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078468","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the amount of excessive and unnecessary packaging materials being used; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226515","226515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078469","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of whether the Information Sharing to Tackle Violence scheme is fully compliant with data protection legislation.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226507","226507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078470","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which hospitals with A&E Departments are not fully co-operating with the Information Sharing to Tackle Violence scheme.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226508","226508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078471","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that train companies have effective accessibility plans for passengers with (a) learning disabilities and (b) autism.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226509","226509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078472","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to introduce high-intensity focused ultrasound therapy for prostate cancer more widely through the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226582","226582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078473","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of bringing forward the increase of the maximum period for recovery of universal credit advance payments from 12 to 16 months, currently scheduled for October 2021.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226694","226694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078474","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the new minimum rate of monthly deductions towards repayment of universal credit advance payments will be as a proportion of a claimant’s standard allowance once the maximum repayment period has been extended to 16 months, as scheduled for October 2021.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226695","226695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078475","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department have carried out impact assessments on the requirement for universal credit advance payments to be repaid at a minimum rate of 10 per cent of the standard allowance.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226696","226696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078476","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing a means-tested income and expenditure assessment in respect of deductions from universal credit for the recovery of advance payments to ensure that repayment rates are based on a claimant's ability to pay.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226697","226697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078477","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the need for reasonable adjustments for vulnerable universal credit claimants, who cannot read or write, to have access to alternative means of communication with their work coach other than through the online journal.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226698","226698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078478","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of employment and support allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK have received a sanction of their benefit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226557","226557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078479","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of employment and support allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK have disputed a sanction to their benefit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226558","226558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078480","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of employment and support allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have disputed a sanction to their benefit in each of the last five years have had their sanction overturned after they were reconsidered.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226559","226559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078481","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of employment and support allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have received a sanction to their benefit in each of the last five years have had their sanction overturned following an appeal to a Tribunal.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226560","226560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078482","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of employment and support allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have disputed a sanction to their benefit in each of the last five years have had their sanction overturned after they were reconsidered or successful appeals were made.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226561","226561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078483","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of patients have been (a) treated by and (b) admitted to A&E departments in (i) four hours and (ii) more than four hours in (A) Jarrow constituency, (B) South Tyneside, (C) the North East and (D) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226562","226562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078484","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have been (a) treated by and (b) admitted to A&E departments in (i) four hours and (ii) more than four hours in (A) Jarrow constituency, (B) South Tyneside, (C) the North East and (D) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226563","226563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078485","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of patients have been treated or admitted to A&E departments in three hours in (a) the Jarrow Constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East, and (d) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226564","226564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078486","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have been (a) treated by and (b) admitted to A&E departments in three hours in (i) Jarrow constituency, (ii) South Tyneside, (iii) the North East and (iv) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226565","226565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078487","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of patients have been (a) treated by and (b) admitted to A&E departments in two hours in (i) Jarrow constituency, (ii) South Tyneside, (iii) the North East, and (iv) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226566","226566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078488","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have been (a) treated by and (b) admitted to A&E departments in two hours in (i) Jarrow constituency, (ii) South Tyneside, (iii) the North East and (iv) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226567","226567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078489","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of patients have been (a) treated by and (b) admitted to A&E departments in less than one hour in (i) Jarrow constituency, (ii) South Tyneside, (iii) the North East and (iv) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226568","226568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078490","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have been (a) treated by and (b) admitted to A&E departments in less than one hour in (i) Jarrow constituency, (ii) South Tyneside, (iii) the North East and (iv) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226569","226569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078491","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for universal credit in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and d) the UK were processed (i) within five weeks, (ii) between five and ten weeks and (iii) in ten weeks or longer in the most recent 12 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226570","226570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078492","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many starter homes have been completed to date.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226539","226539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078493","2019-03-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether extending Article 50 would lead to a requirement to hold elections in the UK to the European Parliament.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226525","226525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078494","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: measures to promote tax compliance, published on 6 February 2014, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after not meeting the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226745","226745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078495","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: measures to promote tax compliance, published on 6 February 2014, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after not meeting the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226746","226746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078496","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: measures to promote tax compliance, published on 6 February 2014, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after not meeting the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226747","226747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078497","2019-03-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: measures to promote tax compliance, published on 6 February 2014, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after not meeting the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226748","226748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078498","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: measures to promote tax compliance, published on 6 February 2014, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after not meeting the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226749","226749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078499","2019-03-04","Cabinet Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's Rapid Response Unit.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226754","226754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078500","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote LGBTI rights in Uganda.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226701","226701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078501","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote LGBTI rights in Kenya.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226702","226702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078502","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve support for autism in inpatient mental health facilities.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226553","226553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078503","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Wallasey constituency, (b) Wirral and (c) England that were (i) eligible and (ii) not eligible for free school meals attended a primary school rated as (A) good and (B) outstanding in the academic year ending August 2018.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226554","226554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078504","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Scottish limited partnerships have not registered a person of significant control.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226693","226693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078505","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking in response to reports of abuse of LGBTI refugees in Kenya's Kakuma refugee camp.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226703","226703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078506","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of schools in (a) Wallasey, (b) Wirral and (c) Merseyside with internet speeds of (i) less than 10 Mbps, (ii) between 10 and 30 Mbps and (iii) over 30 Mbps.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226555","226555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078507","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on consumer energy prices of the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226673","226673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078508","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Attorney General on the legal implications of the judicial review into complaints in relation to the equalisation of state pension age on the handling of complaints by (a) her Department, (b) the Independent Case Examiner and  (c) the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226520","226520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078509","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax tribunal appeals failed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226684","226684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078510","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cases of historical tax avoidance HMRC has outstanding.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226685","226685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078511","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with NATO allies on the security situation between India and Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226521","226521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078512","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies with (a) assets over £2 billion or (b) a turnover of over £200 million have published their tax strategy.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226686","226686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078513","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people (a) charged and (b) found guilty of traffic offences in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226522","226522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078515","2019-03-04","Cabinet Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what checks HMRC makes to ensure that the supply chains of government contractors are tax compliant.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226687","226687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078516","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support previous customers of Wonga who have outstanding complaints against that company since it entered administration.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226524","226524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078517","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 223144, which Minister is responsible for policy on play services for children aged six and over which is not part of the early years foundation stage statutory framework; and how much funding the Government allocated in support for play for children in (a) after-school clubs, (b) holiday play schemes, (c) adventure playgrounds and (d) play-ranger services in the last three years for which that information is available.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226700","226700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078518","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken in response to the recommendation of the Fourth Report of the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Committee, Fourth Report of the Environmental Audit Committee, Third Report of the Health and Social Care Committee, and Second Report of the Transport Committee of Session 2017–19 on Improving air quality, HC 433, that the Government aligns (a) climate change schemes, (b) urban planning, (c) public transport and (d) fiscal incentives with air quality goals to prevent its policy from working at cross-purposes.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226550","226550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078519","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to tackle the financial effect of the introduction of the Worldwide Harmonised Light Vehicle Test Procedure on company car drivers.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226551","226551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078520","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224343 on Buildings: Insulation, for what reasons there has been a period of six months between the bespoke test methodology being approved by his Department on 22 August 2018 and the start of non-Aluminium Composite material cladding testing taking place in March 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226674","226674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078521","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to collect and publish data on the ground rents paid by leaseholders.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226540","226540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078522","2019-03-04","Cabinet Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women aged 65 and over were diagnosed with cervical cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226679","226679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078523","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to extend routine cervical screening to women aged 65 and over.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226680","226680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078524","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department notifies surviving spouses about their entitlement to Bereavement Support Payment as a matter of routine; and how long after the death of a husband, wife or civil partner such notification is issued.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226681","226681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078525","2019-03-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 16 of the Government's August 2018 Civil Society Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to work with Big Lottery Fund to use £55 million from dormant accounts to fund a new, independent organisation which will work with partners across the private and social sectors to tackle financial exclusion.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226675","226675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078526","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the take-up rate for Bereavement Support Payment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226682","226682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078527","2019-03-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 113 of the Government's August 2018 Civil Society Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to explore the potential to use flexibilities in the law governing contracts (such as the Mutuals Reservation) to reserve some competitions to other social purpose vehicles.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226676","226676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078528","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have received their full entitlement to Bereavement Support Payment in each of the last five years; and how many people have received a reduced entitlement to that payment due to a late application.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226683","226683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078529","2019-03-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials from (a) his Department and (b) the Office for Civil Society have been moved from their normal duties to work on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226677","226677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078530","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the letter to the Rt. Hon. Member for Delyn, dated 21 January 2019 and deposited in the library, what the planned timescale is for the (a) completion of draft questions, (b) evidence gathering exercise, (c) closing date and (d) Government's response to the call for evidence on attacks against retail employees.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226571","226571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078531","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the letter to the Rt. Hon. Member for Delyn, dated 21 January 2019 and deposited in the library, what steps his Department is planning to take to deliver the targeted communications activity to raise awareness of the existing legislation that covers assaults against an individual when working in a retail environment; and what the budget is for that communications activity.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226572","226572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078532","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the letter to the Rt. Hon. Member for Delyn, dated 21 January 2019 and deposited in the library, when he plans to publish details on the outcomes of the retail group meeting held in February 2019.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226573","226573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078533","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the letter to the Rt. Hon. Member for Delyn, dated 21 January 2019 and deposited in the Library, what the (a) outcomes were and (b) response was to the letter to the Commissioner of the City of London Police on retail crime and attacks on retail employees.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226574","226574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078534","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to the letter from the Rt. Hon. Member for Delyn, dated 22 January 2019.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226575","226575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078535","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what meetings (a) Ministers, and (b) officials of his Department, have had with representatives working on behalf of Philip Morris International since 2018 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226630","226630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078536","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of services provided by local authorities to help people give up smoking.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226631","226631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078537","2019-03-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to respond to the letter of 14 January 2019 from the right hon. Member for North Norfolk on the security of the UK’s communications infrastructure.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226595","226595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078538","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations his Department has received from local authorities on services provided by councils to help people give up smoking in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226632","226632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078539","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to the letter of 14 January 2019 from the right hon. Member for North Norfolk on the security of the UK’s communications infrastructure.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226596","226596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078540","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to respond to the letter of 14 January 2019 from the right hon. Member for North Norfolk on the security of the UK’s communications infrastructure.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226597","226597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078541","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations his Department has received from local authorities on services provided by councils to help people give up smoking in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226633","226633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078542","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations his Department has received from the charity sector on services provided by councils to help people give up smoking in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226634","226634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078543","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the amount of money that would accrue to the public purse annually as a result of tariffs on imports from non-EU countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226516","226516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078544","2019-03-04","Cabinet Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking through its One Public Estate programme to identify and release surplus public sector land for local regeneration projects in (a) Crawley constituency and (b) West Sussex.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226651","226651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078545","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish the full guidance for part-time maintenance loans.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226530","226530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078546","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support people with fibromyalgia.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226750","226750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078547","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to make distance-learning maintenance loans available.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226531","226531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078548","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the take-up has been of part-time maintenance loans since that loan's inception.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226532","226532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078549","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships have been created in (a) Mansfield and (b) Nottinghamshire since 2015.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226751","226751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078550","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the Turkish Government’s treatment of (a) members of the Alevi community and (b) other religious minorities.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226491","226491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078551","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has his Turkish counterpart on (a) the treatment of Alevis in the Turkish prison system and (b) those people's access to Dedes.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226492","226492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078552","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to ensure that people with eating disorders are able to access treatment and support.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226752","226752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078553","2019-03-04","Department for International Development","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's press release entitled UK aid protecting women from trafficking in Burma – and helping them into jobs published on 18 February 2019, how UK aid has been used to help disadvantaged and conflict-affected people.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226729","226729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078554","2019-03-04","Department for International Development","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's press release entitled UK aid protecting women from trafficking in Burma – and helping them into jobs published on 18 February 2019, whether the Government has received assurances that UK aid provided to Sittwe General Hospital will not be used to underpin reported apartheid practices at that hospital.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226730","226730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078555","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the human rights implications of the four killings by Indian military and paramilitary forces in the town of Pulwama on 18 February 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226636","226636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078556","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the total spending under the Rough Sleeping Initiative in each month in the financial year 2018-19 in (a) London Boroughs and (b) England.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226713","226713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078557","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his department has made of the total amount in interim financial support loans given to NHS Trusts and Foundation Trusts and the associated interest rates in (a) London and (b) England in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226714","226714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078558","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) repayments and (b) interest paid on interim financial support loans by each NHS Trust and Foundation Trust in (i) London and (ii) England in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226715","226715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078559","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to reduce homelessness in London.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226716","226716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078560","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of reports of revenge violence and revenge evictions against people of Kashmiri origin in India after the suicide attack of 14 February 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226637","226637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078561","2019-03-04","Department for International Trade","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 220155, which countries from the human rights priority list were invited to and attended Defence and Security Equipment International 2017 as official delegations.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226638","226638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078562","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for the Social Mobility Commission’s statutory annual report entitled State of the nation 2018 to be published.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226639","226639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078563","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, who are the core members are of the Women’s Health Taskforce for England.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226640","226640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078564","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the terms of reference are for the women’s health taskforce for England.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226641","226641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078565","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how he plans to inform (a) the Campaign Against Painful Hysteroscopy and (b) other patient groups about the (i) agendas and (ii) minutes of the meetings of the women’s health taskforce for England.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226642","226642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078566","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will make it its policy to reinstate nurse bursaries.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226753","226753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078567","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how he plans to ensure that (a) the Campaign Against Painful Hysteroscopy and (b) other patient groups are able to influence the (i) agendas for meetings and (ii) work of the women’s health taskforce for England.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226643","226643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078568","2019-03-04","Cabinet Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department have been tasked with preparing Orders in Council to implement recommendations of the Boundary Commission.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226737","226737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078569","2019-03-04","Cabinet Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, by what date he has asked for Orders in Council to be prepared to implement recommendations of the Boundary Commission.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226738","226738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078570","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to support self-employed people who need to claim employment support allowance.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226720","226720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078571","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) collate and (b) publish data on the number of Britons poisoned by carbon monoxide when holidaying overseas.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226732","226732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078572","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will help to protect Britons holidaying overseas from carbon monoxide poisoning by establishing a programme advising them to take a portable carbon monoxide monitor on their trip.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226733","226733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078573","2019-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments have required ministerial approval from his Department in each financial year since 2015-16.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226635","226635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078574","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to extend the Community Housing Fund to 2023; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226644","226644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078575","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on the number of communities (a) bringing forward and (b) completing projects of the length of the period for which the Community Housing Fund is open to them; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226645","226645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078576","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Housing Communities and Local Government on extending the Homes England Community Housing Fund to 2023; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226646","226646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078577","2019-03-04","Attorney General","2019-02-27","To ask the Attorney General, how many cases have been passed to the CPS by the police which the CPS has decided not to pursue (a) in each region and (b) at CPS Direct in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226517","226517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078578","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Joint Incident Assessment Team in investigating breeches of international humanitarian law in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226493","226493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078579","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to allocate funding to local authorities to implement Local Cycling and Walking Infrastructure Plans.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226518","226518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078580","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the validity of the findings of the Joint Incidents Assessment Team investigation into the bombing of a Médecins Sans Frontières cholera treatment centre in Abs in Yemen on 11 June 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226494","226494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078581","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking help resolve the hostilities in Kashmir; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226534","226534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078582","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a online sales tax.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226576","226576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078585","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Liverpool City Region will receive funding from his Department to implement the local cycling and walking infrastructure plan.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226495","226495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078588","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to encourage cycling in Liverpool in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226496","226496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078591","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department will provide funding to  to hospital trusts to cover additional medical air freight costs for (a) radioisotopes for cancer treatment and (b) other treatments that cannot be stockpiled in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226647","226647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078595","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an estimate of the reduction in the level of revenue accruing to the public purse from an inability to recoup Help to Buy equity loans on leasehold houses due to those properties being (a) unsalable and (b) salelable only at a reduction on the initial purchase price; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226541","226541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078598","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make funding from Homes England available to local authorities in South East England for brownfield regeneration.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226711","226711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078599","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of gun and knife offences in Merseyside in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226497","226497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078600","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to discuss with his Indian and Pakistani counterparts the current situation in Kashmir; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226535","226535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078601","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will convene an emergency international summit, hosted in London, to co-ordinate a response to the attacks on Christians around the world.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226721","226721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078602","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold discussions with his Nigerian counterpart on (a) the rescue of Leah Sharibu and other people kidnapped by Boko Haram and (b) ending the violence against Christians in Nigeria’s middle belt.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226722","226722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078603","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will co-ordinate an international effort to encourage Christians and other religious minorities who have left Iraq and Syria to return to those countries to rebuild their lives.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226723","226723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078604","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to Christians on death row on charges of blasphemy in Pakistan  .","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226724","226724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078605","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to reduce domestic demand for palm oil in the biofuel and food industries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226536","226536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078606","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the rights of Christian minorities in Burma.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226725","226725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078607","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote religious tolerance and justice for Coptic Christians in Egypt.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226726","226726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078608","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of rail passenger numbers for each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for James Morris","James Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226656","226656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078609","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when will he bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a new offence of intentional trespass to tackle unlawful traveller encampments.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226712","226712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078610","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the sustainability of palm oil production; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226537","226537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078611","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help protect the rights of Christian workers in the Middle East.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226727","226727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078612","2019-03-04","Department for International Development","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that international NGOs consider religious vulnerability in their definition of need.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226728","226728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078613","2019-03-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to announce the next steps for the Rural Gigabit Connnectivity programme.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226648","226648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078614","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent international discussions he has had on the sustainable (a) supply and (b) use of palm oil; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226538","226538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078615","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 220908 on Nurses: Training, if he will place in the Library a list of the providers of nursing and midwifery courses in England; and how many nursing and midwifery applications there were to each provider of nursing and midwifery courses in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226670","226670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078616","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of trends in the level of Police Community Support Officers on incidences of crime in (a) Liverpool and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226498","226498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078617","2019-03-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made on its plans for an outside-in strategy to build full-fibre networks in rural areas.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226649","226649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078618","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there is no disruption to the quality assurance of radiotherapy clinical trials and the patients who have enrolled in those trials after the Secure File Transfer System is discontinued after 31 March 2019.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226655","226655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078619","2019-03-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what funding his Department has allocated to subsidise full-fibre networks in rural areas.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226650","226650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078620","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish the results of his Department's consultation on police pursuits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226499","226499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078621","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any records pertaining to the historical arrears-only cases from the 1993 and 2003 Child Maintenance Schemes been destroyed, deleted or removed from the Child Maintenance Service since the Child Maintenance (Miscellaneous Amendments) Regulations 2018 came into force on 14 December 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226667","226667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078622","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much in arrears accrued under the historical arrears-only cases from the 1993 and 2003 Child Maintenance Schemes has been written-off since the Child Maintenance (Miscellaneous Amendments) Regulations 2018 came into force on 14 December 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226668","226668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078623","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what long-term funding is available for tackling homelessness in Liverpool City Region.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226556","226556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078624","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many historical arrears-only cases from the 1993 and 2003 Child Maintenance Schemes have been closed since the Child Maintenance (Miscellaneous Amendments) Regulations 2018 came into force on 14 December 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226669","226669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078625","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to prevent loss of biodiversity in the UK.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226587","226587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078627","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a comprehensive review of the town centre first policy.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226577","226577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078628","2019-03-04","Northern Ireland Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the security situation in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226588","226588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078629","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to increase the amount of green space in cities.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226589","226589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078630","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to reduce building on green field sites.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226590","226590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078631","2019-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on the identification of next-of-kin where they assume responsibility for a public health funeral and the deceased has left no will.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226533","226533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078632","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding has been allocated to research on fracking in 2019.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226591","226591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078633","2019-03-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps he has to support the arts in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226592","226592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078634","2019-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans her Department has to increase financial support for single-parent families.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226593","226593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078636","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to make childcare more accessible in North Herefordshire.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226594","226594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078637","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to undertake a public consultation on the proposed review of NHS performance times.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226519","226519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078638","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding academy sponsors have committed to provide in capital funding to academies in England; and how much of that funding has been provided in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226678","226678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078639","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with local authorities on ensuring the adequacy of the provision of guidance for the most vulnerable people on their entitlement to free dental health care in certain circumstances.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226579","226579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078640","2019-03-04","Department for International Trade","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment has he made of the effect on businesses of the new rules in India preventing online retailers from selling products through vendors in which they hold an equity stake.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226580","226580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078642","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Phillipines on the steps being taken to support an end to violence against Christians in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226581","226581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078643","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Targeted Charging Review on the business case for renewable energy to be merchantable without subsidy.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226482","226482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078644","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of a reduction in speed limits outside schools from 30 mph to 20 mph on the level of road traffic incidents.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226501","226501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078645","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many supported internships have been completed by local authority.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226704","226704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078646","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many supported internships are available in each local authority.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226705","226705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078647","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has been made of the adequacy of the availability of supported internships in each local authority.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226706","226706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078649","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the of the effect of air passenger duty on (a) developing and (b) maintaining aviation routes to (i) priority and (ii) emerging markets.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226652","226652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078650","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of trains on the Southeastern rail network have been delayed in the last 12 months; and what proportion of those delayed trains were the fault of (a) Southeastern and (b) Network Rail.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226578","226578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078651","2019-03-04","Treasury","2019-02-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Department for International Trade on the importance of developing new aviation routes to new and emerging markets.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226653","226653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078653","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he is making to the Zimbabwean Government on respecting the rights of protesters.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226526","226526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078654","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pedestrians were (a) killed and (b) seriously injured in traffic incidents outside of schools in (i) Merseyside and (ii) England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226502","226502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078655","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has plans to update his Department’s assessment of the levelised cost of electricity across all generation sources.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226483","226483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078656","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he last carried out an assessment of the levelised cost of electricity across all generation sources.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226484","226484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078657","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224343 on Buildings: Insulation, for what reason the bespoke test methodology was not subject to a full consultation.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226734","226734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078658","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224343 on Buildings: Insulation, for what reason the bespoke test methodology was not made available in the public domain when it was agreed in August 2018.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226735","226735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078659","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224346 on Buildings: Insulation, what plans his Department has to help ensure the removal of insulation materials that have been deemed unsafe.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226736","226736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078661","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will set out his Department’s most recent assessment of the levelised cost of electricity from (a) onshore wind, (b) offshore wind, (c) large scale solar photovoltaic and (d) nuclear energy sources.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226485","226485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078662","2019-03-04","Department for Education","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on educating young people on road safety.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226503","226503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078663","2019-03-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what legislation will give effect to advances in EU employment rights being replicated in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226552","226552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078664","2019-03-04","Home Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the additional cost to police forces in 2020-21 of employer contributions to the police pension scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226504","226504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078666","2019-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to protect outdoor workers from ambient air pollution in Scunthorpe; which locations have been found to have fine-particle air pollution levels that exceed the WHO limit of 10 micrograms per cubic metre in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226666","226666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078667","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to promote awareness of road safety for children in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226505","226505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078668","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent diplomatic steps he has taken to help secure the release of (a) human rights activists, (b) political opponents and (c) other people detained illegally in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226717","226717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078670","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi counterpart on the human rights situation in that country.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226718","226718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078671","2019-03-04","Department for International Trade","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department makes assessments of countries' human rights records when negotiating trade deals with those countries.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226719","226719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078672","2019-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of (a) security and (b) the humanitarian situation in (i) Sa'dah, Yemen and (ii) Hajjah, Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226506","226506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078673","2019-03-04","Department for International Trade","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he plans to publish the UK's (a) tariff schedules and (b) tariff-rate quotas as part of Government preparations for leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226488","226488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078674","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 206853 on Cherwell Valley Railway Line: Electrification, for what reasons that answer did not specify when he expects the publication of the timetable for a decision to be made on the future electrification of the railway line between Oxford and Didcot Parkway.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226739","226739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078676","2019-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what contingency plans his Department has put in place in the event of future probation and courts IT systems failure.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226709","226709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078677","2019-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to prevent a further HM Courts and Tribunals IT systems failure.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226710","226710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078678","2019-03-04","Department for Transport","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many complaints his Department has received in each of the last five years on mini cab drivers refusing service to customers with guide dogs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226489","226489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078679","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons people with asthma are charged for their medication; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226740","226740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078681","2019-03-04","Department for International Trade","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the Exporting is Great publicity campaign in the last year in (a) digital and (b) physical advertising.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226741","226741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078682","2019-03-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential health benefits of extending free prescriptions to people with asthma.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226742","226742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078683","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2019 to Question 202108 on Multiple Occupation, what estimate he has made of the number of houses of multiple occupation in Birmingham Edgbaston as at 27 February 2019.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226731","226731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078684","2019-03-04","Department for International Trade","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the setup and maintenance of the great.gov.uk website (a) in the 12 months and (b) since its launch.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226743","226743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1078685","2019-03-04","Department for International Trade","2019-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of his Department organising (a) UK, (b) overseas events, (c) overseas missions and (d) webinars for UK companies.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226744","226744"
