"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759383","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on developing advertising powers to enable that government to protect children from junk food marketing.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9911","9911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759384","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to allow the Scottish Government to restrict junk food advertising to children.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9912","9912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759385","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which properties NHS Property Services has sold in each of the last five financial years; and who the purchasers were for each of those properties.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9913","9913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759386","2017-09-13","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to prevent subscription to Islamic extremist groups or ideology within the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9991","9991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759387","2017-09-13","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what services her Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9968","9968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759388","2017-09-13","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been classified as having no recourse to public funds in (a) Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle constituency, (b) Hull City Council area and (c) the East Riding of Yorkshire Council area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9894","9894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759389","2017-09-14","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide a list of her official engagements since the commencement of the current Parliament when the constituency's hon. Member was (a) invited and (b) not invited.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9848","9848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759390","2017-09-14","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 4201, what the reasons are for the delay in the publication of the independent review into deaths and serious incidents in police custody.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9832","9832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759391","2017-09-14","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total budget of each police and crime commissioner was in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9847","9847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759392","2017-09-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure that dangerous dogs are chipped in (a) Vale of Clwyd constituency, (b) Wales and (c) England.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9744","9744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759393","2017-09-14","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of her Department's staff had a pay increase (a) above, (b) at and (c) less than one per cent in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9759","9759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759394","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the extent of the potential use of cryptocurrencies for criminal purposes; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 10018","10018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759395","2017-09-14","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations her Department has received from representatives of churches and other faith groups on time limits for immigration detention; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 10012","10012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759396","2017-09-13","Department for International Development","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what monitoring her Department undertakes to ensure that aid granted to specific areas is used for the purposes for which it was intended; and if she will liaise with religious missionaries in the destination country to ensure that UK aid is effectively distributed.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 10005","10005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759397","2017-09-13","Department for International Development","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to uphold the commitment it made at the 9th Commonwealth Youth Ministers meeting outlined in point 4 of the Final Communiqué to take meaningful and concrete actions to empower and address the specific needs of marginalised young people in Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9777","9777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759398","2017-09-13","Department for International Development","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the Sustainable Development Goals and the Addis Ababa Action Agenda commitments towards children and youth by 2030 are achieved.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9740","9740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759399","2017-09-13","Department for International Development","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that young people in developing countries are able to access social services and work opportunities.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9741","9741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759400","2017-09-14","Department for International Development","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent progress she has made on the recapitalisation of the Commonwealth Development Corporation (CDC); and what plans she has to enable parliamentary scrutiny of the CDC Business Case and its recapitalisation.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9751","9751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759401","2017-09-13","Department for International Development","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to uphold the commitment it made at the 9th Commonwealth Youth Ministers meeting outlined in point 2 of the Final Communiqué to ensure that young people play a central role in achieving inclusive and sustainable development and in helping the global community to achieve the 2030 Agenda for Sustainable Development.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9778","9778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759402","2017-09-13","Department for International Development","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what services her Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9969","9969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759403","2017-09-13","Department for International Development","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) short-term emergency and (b) medium-term reconstruction aid her Department has provided to people affected by Hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9952","9952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759404","2017-09-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9970","9970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759405","2017-09-14","Home Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what Government-commissioned or run inquiries into child sexual abuse are open; and what the (a) start and (b) projected end dates are of those inquiries.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9985","9985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759406","2017-09-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects to complete the roll-out of the Section 28 pilots in Kingston upon Thames, Liverpool and Leeds Crown courts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9902","9902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759407","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps he has taken to secure appropriate alternative court provision in Chichester after the closure of Chichester Magistrates Court and Combined Court.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9941","9941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759408","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost is of detaining foreign prisoners in British prisons.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9859","9859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759409","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost to the public purse is of the detention of people (a) awaiting trial for terrorist offences and (b) convicted of terrorist offences.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9806","9806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759410","2017-09-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is the Government's position that no child can consent to their own abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9796","9796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759411","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2017 to Question 4856, on rape: trials what information is collected and by which agency of his Department on the number of rape trials in which subsection 41 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999 has been used (a) with and (b) without an application pre-trial.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9829","9829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759412","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2017 to Question 4856, on rape: trials where the information on applications to use a complainant's previous sexual activity made under subsection 41 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999 is held.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9828","9828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759413","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many meetings his Department has had with representatives of the insurance industry to discuss changing the formula for calculating deductions from personal injury awards.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9849","9849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759414","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for exceptional case funding have been (a) lodged and (b) granted for clinical negligence claims involving the death of a child of where the claimant is the child in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9860","9860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759415","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many meetings his Department has had with the victims of accidents to discuss changing the formula for calculating deductions from personal injury awards.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9850","9850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759416","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times the Legal Aid Agency has had to intervene to ensure that legal aid services were provided since 2012-13.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9861","9861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759417","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many legal aid providers there were in each region of England and Wales in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9862","9862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759418","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of how many victims of serious accidents would have their income affected by proposed changes to the formula for calculating deductions from personal injury awards.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9851","9851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759419","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2017 to Question 4856, on rape: trials whether any agency of his Department records information on successful and unsuccessful applications made under subsection 41(3)(c)(i) of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9826","9826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759420","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost of food (a) per prison inmate per day and (b) all prison inmates was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 10014","10014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759421","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost of food (a) per inmate per day and (b) for all inmates in youth custody was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 10015","10015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759422","2017-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many injuries were sustained by children during restraint in each custodial institution in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 10017","10017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759423","2017-09-13","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9971","9971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759424","2017-09-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons the Government did not sent a Minister to the 9th Commonwealth Youth Ministers meeting in Uganda to prepare for hosting the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in 2018; and if the Government will commit to sending a Minister to the 10th Commonwealth Youth Ministers meeting in Jamaica in 2021.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9737","9737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759425","2017-09-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government was appointed as a member of the new Commonwealth Youth Ministerial Task Force following the 9th Commonwealth Youth Minister meeting in Uganda, as outlined in point 20 of the Final Communiqué.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9738","9738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759426","2017-09-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that young people are represented at the Commonwealth Heads of Government meeting in 2018.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9739","9739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759427","2017-09-13","Scotland Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9972","9972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759428","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9973","9973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759429","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will include, as part of the Think public information campaign on road safety, messages which highlights the risks of harm to cyclists and motorbike riders when people open car doors without looking to see who is coming up behind them.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9877","9877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759430","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on road improvements to the A1 in Scotland and the effect on that part of the road of improvements to the A1 from Newcastle to the Scottish border.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9895","9895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759431","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers the Welsh Government and Transport for Wales have in the design, content, tendering and award of the next Wales and Borders and Metro franchise.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9745","9745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759432","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether an agreement has been reached on the proposed transfer of ownership of the Valley Lines to the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9746","9746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759433","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the role is of the Office of Rail and Road in any proposed transfer of ownership of the Valley Lines to the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9747","9747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759434","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the risk associated with the proposed transfer of ownership of the Valley Lines to the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9748","9748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759435","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers his Department has in the design, content, tendering and award of the next Wales and Borders and Metro franchise.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9749","9749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759436","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to reform the driving test to highlight the risks of harm to cyclists and motorbike riders of people opening car doors without looking to see who is approaching from behind.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9754","9754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759437","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has for the future use of Class 707 trains which South Western Railway plan to stop using in 2019.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9752","9752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759438","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the shortage of qualified HGV drivers in the road haulage industry; what steps he is taking to address that shortage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9700","9700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759439","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that air passengers can effectively and easily access compensation for long flight delays under EU Regulation 261/2004.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9729","9729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759440","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce a decision on the delivery of a new train fleet for the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9733","9733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759441","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's plans are for funding of the Tyne and Wear Metro after the current funding arrangement ends in 2021.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9734","9734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759442","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fines have been (a) issued and (b) paid for breaches of cabotage and combined transport rules in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9703","9703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759443","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on their powers to take noise abatement enforcement against companies undertaking engineering work on the railways with respect to the Environmental Protection Act 1990 and section 122 of the Railways Act 1993.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9704","9704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759444","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people who hold a disabled person's freedom pass live in London; how many people who hold an older person's freedom pass live in London; and how many rail passengers there were in London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9825","9825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759445","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's paper, Rail passenger numbers and crowding statistics: 2016 report, published on 27 July 2017, what assessment his Department has made of (a) future crowding on South West Mainline into Waterloo and (b) the effect of Crossrail 2 on those figures.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9773","9773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759446","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on bringing forward a new southern rail access link to Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9794","9794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759447","2017-09-13","Wales Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9974","9974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759448","2017-09-13","Women and Equalities","2017-09-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what services the Government Equalities Office has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9966","9966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759449","2017-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the criteria for exemption from employment and support allowance reassessments for people with long-term health conditions.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9976","9976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759450","2017-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which organisations his Department consulted when drawing up the criteria for exemption from employment and support allowance reassessments for people with long-term health conditions.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9977","9977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759451","2017-09-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has plans to increase mental health training for personal independent payment and employment and support allowance assessors.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9943","9943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759452","2017-09-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9975","9975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759453","2017-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to maintain the exemptions from conditionality and sanctions accorded to people in the employment and support allowance support group.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9986","9986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759454","2017-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to respond to the responses to his Department's consultation entitled, Work, Health and Disability: Improving Lives; and whether he plans to publish a White Paper on that subject.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9987","9987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759455","2017-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of exempting people with long-term progressive health conditions who are in receipt of the higher rate care and mobility personal independence payment components, from reassessment for that payment.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9988","9988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759456","2017-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will ensure that personal independence payments claimants who suffer from a condition for which there is not yet any medication are not disadvantaged by that fact in their assessments.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9804","9804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759457","2017-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment claimants who no longer receive mobility payment are having taxis paid for under the Access to Work scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9805","9805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759458","2017-09-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will change current regulations so that employers are required to issue annual automatic pension statements.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9730","9730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759459","2017-09-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons there is an average waiting time of 34 weeks for a tribunal date in North Wales; and what the longest time is for which a person has had to wait for such a date.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9719","9719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759460","2017-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit recipients have waited over six weeks for their first payment.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9774","9774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759461","2017-09-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps are being taken to address the shortage of panel members needed for tribunals in the North Wales area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9776","9776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759462","2017-09-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the percentage change in the cost for the average domestic dual fuel bill for customers of (a) British Gas, (b) EDF, (c) Npower, (d) E.ON, (e) Scottish Power and (f) SSE since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9772","9772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759463","2017-09-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many of his Department's staff had a pay increase (a) above, (b) at and (c) less than one per cent in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9760","9760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759464","2017-09-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of Government policy on trends in the average cost of domestic dual fuel energy bills over the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9770","9770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759465","2017-09-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to provide financial help to businesses to invest in low carbon growth.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9835","9835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759466","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with representatives from the solar energy industry on the future of the Feed-in Tariff scheme.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9821","9821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759467","2017-09-14","Cabinet Office","2017-09-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9289, on iron and steel: procurement, what progress each Government department is making in delivering greater UK steel content in line with the Government's new public procurement guidelines published in April 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9980","9980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759468","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of how much ice has reduced in the Antarctic in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9992","9992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759469","2017-09-14","HM Treasury","2017-09-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the merits of introducing statutory regulation of pre-paid funeral plans.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9978","9978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759470","2017-09-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to change regulations to enable local authorities or central government to stipulate that food and drink that is procured centrally must be of local country or UK origin after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9924","9924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759471","2017-09-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to prioritise investment in offshore wind energy over nuclear energy in light of recent figures that shows that energy from offshore wind will now be cheaper.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9937","9937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759472","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, in what month in 2017 he plans to reintroduce the Renewable Heat Scheme Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9920","9920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759473","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many single applicants have received subsidies for multiple installations under the non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive scheme since that scheme's inception.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9921","9921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759474","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what procedures are in place to ensure the safe installation of smart meters in Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle constituency.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9922","9922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759475","2017-09-13","Department for International Trade","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since his Department's creation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9954","9954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759476","2017-09-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what products in the UK have protected geographical indication; and what steps he is taking to guarantee that status after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9705","9705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759477","2017-09-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to protect the status of Great Grimsby smoked haddock after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9845","9845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759478","2017-09-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if his Department will appoint a chief scientific advisor.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9857","9857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759479","2017-09-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what meetings his Department has had with (a) farming unions and (b) devolved administrations to discuss matters relating to farming since June 2016.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9923","9923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759480","2017-09-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since his Department's creation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9953","9953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759481","2017-09-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to recruit more officials to assist with the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 10011","10011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759603","2017-09-14","Attorney General","2017-09-11","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the Crown Prosecution Service has adequate resources to tackle social media hate crime.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900856","900856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760332","2017-09-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to tackle discrimination in sport.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900849","900849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760333","2017-09-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to improve broadband provision in rural areas in the next five years.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900850","900850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760334","2017-09-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Scottish Government on the roll-out of superfast broadband.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900848","900848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760335","2017-09-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the digital and tech industries.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900846","900846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758949","2017-09-12","Attorney General","2017-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, what services the Law Officers' Departments has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9673","9673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758950","2017-09-13","Cabinet Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the number of his Department's employees who have been employed other than in his Department's payroll in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9697","9697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758951","2017-09-13","Cabinet Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish the findings of his Department's economic crime review.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9641","9641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758952","2017-09-12","Cabinet Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9674","9674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758953","2017-09-12","Department for Transport","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the economic effect on people reaching their place of work of toll charges on the Merseygateway Project.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9654","9654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758954","2017-09-13","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the tax paid by non-doms in the UK in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9661","9661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758955","2017-09-13","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what annual growth rate results from (a) 0.2 per cent growth in Q1, (b) 0.6 per cent in Q2, (c) 0.6 per cent in Q3 and (d) 0.7 per cent in Q4.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9662","9662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758956","2017-09-13","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff in his Department are (a) female, (b) BAME and (c) part time; and what proportion of the staff in his Department who received an annual performance award were in each of those categories in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9664","9664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758957","2017-09-13","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6054, on financial services, if he will make an assessment of the level of lending through (a) banks and (b) peer-to-peer providers to small and medium-sized businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9635","9635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758958","2017-09-13","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6055, on crowdfunding, how much of the £120 million channelled by the British Business Bank to UK businesses through peer-to-peer platforms has been allocated to businesses which employ fewer than (a) 50 and (b) 10 people.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9636","9636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758959","2017-09-13","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6053, on crowdfunding, what estimate he has made of the volume of peer-to-peer lending which would provide competition to the marketplace.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9637","9637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758960","2017-09-13","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6052, what proportion of the £425 million Capability and Innovation Fund will be made available to (a) challenger banks and (b) other financial services providers.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9638","9638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758961","2017-09-13","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6051, what estimate he has made of the additional costs to (a) lenders and (b) business customers that would be created by setting rules on the level of business lending allowed through non-bank finance providers.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9639","9639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758962","2017-09-12","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to require insurance companies to offer terrorism insurance on all business policies.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9689","9689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758963","2017-09-12","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to introduce legislation to update the Reinsurance (Acts of Terrorism) Act 1993 to enable insurance companies to offer terrorism insurance beyond property damage to businesses.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9694","9694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758964","2017-09-12","HM Treasury","2017-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce legislation to update the Reinsurance (Acts of Terrorism) Act 1993 to enable insurance companies to pay compensation to businesses after terrorism attacks when there is no damage to property.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9695","9695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758965","2017-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of (a) building regulations concerning fire safety and (b) fire safety guidance for commercial and domestic planning applications used by fire services and local authorities' planning departments.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9696","9696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758966","2017-09-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment has been made of the fire resistance of residential tower blocks that are (a) under construction or (b) due to begin construction soon in light of the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9698","9698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758967","2017-09-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to publish new advice and regulations on the installation of mandatory fire alarms in communal areas of public housing.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9671","9671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758968","2017-09-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to require sprinklers to be installed inside all tower blocks, including in privately-owned tower blocks in (a) Wolverhampton and (b) England.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9672","9672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758969","2017-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what services his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9675","9675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758970","2017-09-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what services her Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9676","9676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758971","2017-09-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish the Museums Review.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9643","9643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758972","2017-09-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the financial effect of recent welfare reforms on veterans.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9663","9663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758973","2017-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has made an assessment of the adequacy of support available to service personnel from Greater Manchester who have left the armed forces.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9644","9644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758974","2017-09-13","Department for Education","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of regulations on sprinklers in schools.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9667","9667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758975","2017-09-13","Department for Education","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 30 hours of free childcare eligibility codes were generated before the 31 August 2017 deadline in each (a) region of England and (b) constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9642","9642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758976","2017-09-13","Department for Education","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her oral contribution of 6 September 2017, Official Report, column 166, how she plans to ensure that nursery providers offer places to meet the working patterns of parents.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9699","9699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758977","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the legal position will be of international environmental agreements ratified jointly by the EU and the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9693","9693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758978","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9677","9677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758979","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to maintain welfare standards for farm animals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9645","9645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758980","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to recognise animals as sentinent beings in legislation, as in the Lisbon Treaty, after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9690","9690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758981","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which international environmental agreements to which the UK is currently a party as a consequence of ratification by the EU he plans the UK to ratify in order to maintain the current level of environmental protection after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9691","9691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758982","2017-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9678","9678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758983","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has carried out an equality impact assessment on the NHS offering unpaid internships in psychology.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9659","9659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758984","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the mental health training that paramedics receive.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9660","9660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758985","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2017 to Question 6693, where information is collected on the meetings his Department has had with private providers of mental health care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9656","9656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758986","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners waited more than 14 days for a transfer to hospital under the Mental Health Act 1983 in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9657","9657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758987","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9680","9680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758988","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of regulations on sprinklers in hospitals.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9666","9666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758989","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the level of cost improvement expected from the current Liverpool core bundle process.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9669","9669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758990","2017-09-13","Department of Health","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what rules or guidance he provides to health commissioning organisations on staff of those organisations taking up employment with other organisations from which the commissioning organisation had commissioned products or services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9670","9670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758991","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum claims have included reference to sexuality or gender identity in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9634","9634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758992","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9681","9681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758993","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of how many non-EU international students left the UK on the basis of exit check data collected between April 2015 and April 2016.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9655","9655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758994","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether a policy decision was taken to send letters to EU citizens lawfully living in the UK asking them to leave.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9652","9652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758995","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department was officially informed of the data collected by transport operators at exit checks between April 2015 and April 2016.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9653","9653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758996","2017-09-12","Department for International Development","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9682","9682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758997","2017-09-13","Department for International Development","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to match the humantiarian assistance provided by the French Government to the people of St Barts, St Martin and Guadeloupe in providing emergency assistance and reconstruction funds to the people of the British Overseas Territory of Anguilla.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9668","9668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758998","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time between the commencement of an employment and support allowance appeal and a decision was in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) the UK in the most recent 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9646","9646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758999","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time between the commencement of a personal independence payment appeal and a decision was in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) the UK in the most recent 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9647","9647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759000","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to introduce a Prisons Bill during the current session of Parliament.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9651","9651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759001","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9683","9683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759002","2017-09-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have died by suicide in 2017 to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9658","9658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759003","2017-09-12","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9684","9684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759004","2017-09-12","Scotland Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9685","9685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759005","2017-09-12","Department for Transport","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9686","9686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759006","2017-09-12","Wales Office","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9687","9687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759007","2017-09-12","Women and Equalities","2017-09-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much her Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9679","9679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759008","2017-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9688","9688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759009","2017-09-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on care leavers.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9665","9665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759010","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate the Government has made of the number of foreign companies which use local content in their supply chain; and if he plans to incentivise such companies to use such content.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9640","9640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759011","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to ensure UK entities cannot be used as shell companies for money laundering in light of recent allegations against prominent Azerbaijanis.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9692","9692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759012","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what services his Department and former constituent departments have received from the Behavioural Insights Team since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9648","9648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759013","2017-09-12","Department for International Trade","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since his Department's creation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9650","9650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759014","2017-09-12","Department for International Trade","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many companies helped by UK Export Finance have been part of a supply chain for (a) renewables and (b) oil and gas projects in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9631","9631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759015","2017-09-12","Department for International Trade","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff recruited to UK Export Finance in the last 24 months are specialists in renewable energy projects.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9632","9632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759016","2017-09-12","Department for International Trade","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether, when assessing the environmental, social and human rights aspects of proposals supporting activities in the oil and gas sectors, UK Export Finance considers the effect of those proposals on climate change.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9633","9633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759017","2017-09-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much his Department has paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since his Department's creation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9649","9649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758597","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will list the occasions that the (a) Welsh and (b) Scottish Governments have initiated the formal dispute resolution process with the Government.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9360","9360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758598","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Minister has responsibility for the Government's cross-departmental working on child sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9386","9386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758599","2017-09-12","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse has been of the current  Boundary Review (a) up to 3 May 2017 and (b) from that date to the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9388","9388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758600","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to review UK cyber-security capabilities.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9393","9393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758601","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many registered users there are of GOV.UK Verify; and how many such users there were (a) six months and (b) one year ago.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9401","9401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758602","2017-09-12","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Cabinet Office staff do not meet the eligibility criteria for the Civil Service Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9408","9408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758603","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of steel procured by Government departments has been supplied by British companies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9402","9402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758604","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if it is still the Government's policy to proceed with the 2018 Boundary Review.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9482","9482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758605","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with officials from the Boundary Commission on the 2018 Boundary Review.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9483","9483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758606","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many expressions of interest have been received from local authorities to run ID pilots at the 2018 local elections; and with reference to paragraph 5.6 of his Department's Electoral Integrity Pilots Prospectus, what evidence his Department will accept as a demonstration of local support for such a pilot.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9523","9523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758607","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish the new anti-corruption strategy.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9544","9544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758608","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place in the Library a copy of any written advice given by his Department's Head of Propriety and Ethics to Ministers on the timing and length of campaigns for the 2017 General Election.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9545","9545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758609","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many 11 to 15-year olds have completed a CyberFirst course in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9546","9546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758610","2017-09-12","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of procurement of British steel since the Government's procurement policy note 11/6 on procuring steel in major projects was published.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9563","9563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758611","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing proposals for secure online voting for elections.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9559","9559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758612","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward proposals to allow people to register for a postal vote online.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9560","9560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758613","2017-09-12","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff including consultants have been hired across Government Departments for work on the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in April 2018; and what the total cost of those staff is to date.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9581","9581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758614","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much debt the Government owes on existing private finance initiative contracts.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9556","9556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758615","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of Welsh workers were on zero-hours contracts in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9549","9549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758616","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs jobs were based in Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9543","9543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758617","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of life science companies reach their annual and lifetime fundraising limits with the Enterprise Innovation Scheme and Venture Capital Trusts; and if he will publish a comparison with other sectors.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9488","9488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758618","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies registered their beneficial ownership information with Companies House by the 30 June 2017 deadline.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9487","9487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758619","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the recruitment industry will contribute in apprenticeship levy payments in 2017-18.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9442","9442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758620","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the recruitment industry has paid in apprenticeship levy payments to date.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9441","9441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758621","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies registered under UK Standard Industry Classification Code Section 78 pay the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9440","9440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758622","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the total amount of foreign investment to the UK from other EU member states was; and what percentage of this investment was for Wales in each year for which data are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9573","9573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758623","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans HM Revenue and Customs has to adopt GOV.UK Verify.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9363","9363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758624","2017-09-12","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure the collection of taxes that have not been paid through error by HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9405","9405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758625","2017-09-12","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the level of tax receipts from fixed-odds betting terminals in each of the next three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9374","9374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758626","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the projected spend is for each City Deal in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9345","9345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758627","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) central government and (b) local government has invested in each of the City Deals in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9346","9346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758628","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on additional funding to tackle gun crime for (a) Merseyside Police and (b) other police forces.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9333","9333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758629","2017-09-11","Church Commissioners","2017-09-07","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what assessment she has made of the effect of admission costs for cathedrals and abbeys in England on the ability of UK families to visit such places.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9310","9310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758630","2017-10-09","Church Commissioners","2017-09-07","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what events and activities the Diocese of Blackburn is undertaking to mark the Quincentenary of the nailing of Ninety-five Theses by Martin Luther on the door of All Saints' Church, Wittenberg, on 31 October 1517.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9589","9589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758631","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to UN Sustainable Development Goal 2.1 to by 2030 end hunger and ensure access by all people to safe, nutritious and sufficient food all year round, what steps his Department is taking with local government to meet that target.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9610","9610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758632","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2017 to Question 4915, whether the Government is still requesting samples of cladding material.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9597","9597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758633","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2017 to Question 4915, whether the Government sought the advice of the expert panel on fire safety before the original testing of samples of cladding material.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9598","9598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758634","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his oral contribution of 26 July 2017, Official Report, column 347, whether samples of cladding and insulation were tested at a rate of 100 a day.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9599","9599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758635","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of legislation regarding travellers' illegal encampments.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9449","9449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758636","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish his Department's response to the future funding of supported housing consultation.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9443","9443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758637","2017-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to improve broadband speeds in rural areas.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9481","9481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758638","2017-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2017 to Question 5176, whether those from voluntary sector organisations and those working at the Westway Assistance Centre who are working with children affected by the Grenfell Tower fire are required to undertake Disclosure and Barring Service checks.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9517","9517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758639","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2017 to Question 5176, what advice his Department issued to the local authority and voluntary sector organisations providing support to survivors of the Grenfell Tower fire on working with (a) vulnerable people and (b) children.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9514","9514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758640","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the letter to residents following the Grenfell Tower fire of 5 September 2017, if he will set out how the process by which former Grenfell Tower residents bid for new housing ensures that former residents do not bid against each other.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9541","9541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758641","2017-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made in trends of levels of employment for local authorities for (a) child social care, (b) adult social care, (c) refuse collection and (d) other services when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9491","9491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758642","2017-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has made to the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on the effect of an end to free movement of people on the delivery of local authority services when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9492","9492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758643","2017-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a list of his European counterparts that he has met to discuss the effect on local government of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9490","9490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758644","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2017 to Question 5177, how many case workers have been allocated to work with (a) Grenfell Tower survivors and (b) members of the local community affected by that fire.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9513","9513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758645","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2017 to Question 5175, on Grenfell Tower: fires, (a) how many staff from his Department are working to provide that support, (b) what work his Department has done to support the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea in engaging with the local community and (c) what work his Department has done to support the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea to ensure it fully meets the needs of residents and supports community organisations.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9516","9516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758646","2017-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2017 to Question 5213, on buildings: fire prevention, whether replacement of cladding with cladding of a similar appearance but of a different material composition requires planning permission.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9520","9520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758647","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount of revenue raised by public space protection orders since their inception.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9314","9314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758648","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department will refund local authorities the cost of ensuring that all existing housing stock is made safe as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9326","9326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758649","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) council and (b) social houses were built in each local authority area in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9349","9349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758650","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many homes were insulated under national and local government initiatives in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9350","9350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758651","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much each local authority spent on council tax reduction schemes in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9351","9351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758652","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of small businesses paid business rates in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9344","9344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758653","2017-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of children's librarians in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9361","9361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758654","2017-09-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will list the attendees at any roundtable events that she or Ministers in her Department have held with representatives of the creative industries.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9406","9406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758655","2017-09-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much the National Lottery received from the sale of lottery tickets in each constituency in Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9381","9381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758656","2017-09-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish details of (a) the roundtable events she or Ministers of her Department have held with representatives of the creative industries and (b) the attendees at those events.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9412","9412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758657","2017-09-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether departmental guidance on the implementation of the Digital Economy Act 2017 will make it clear that section 106 encompasses all methods of mass online harvesting of tickets.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9521","9521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758658","2017-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the proportion of UK steel which will be used to produce the five new frigates announced on 6 September 2017.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9536","9536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758659","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with organisers of the Defence and Security Equipment International on attendance at that event by Amnesty International UK officials.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9484","9484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758660","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he received from  Amnesty International UK on that organisation's attendance at the Defence and Security Equipment International.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9485","9485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758661","2017-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the missile defence capabilities of the Royal Navy in light of the recent advances in the development of hypersonic missiles by Russia.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9595","9595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758662","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many cyber-attacks on his Department were prevented during the last 12 months.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9391","9391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758663","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what cyber-security agreements have been reached with allied states in the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9395","9395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758664","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many under 18-year olds enrolled on computer or IT-based (a) training and (b) degree courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9399","9399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758665","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has her Department paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9400","9400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758666","2017-09-12","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps are being taken to ensure that teaching schools have staff who are qualified to train others to teach dyslexic pupils.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9407","9407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758667","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage more young people to train in computer-based industries.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9392","9392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758668","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the study of foreign languages in schools.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9394","9394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758669","2017-09-12","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the annual cost is of the Government's policy Staying put, arrangements for care leavers aged 18 and above to stay on with former foster carers.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9411","9411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758670","2017-09-12","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have remained in placement under the Government's policy Staying put, arrangements for care leavers aged 18 and above to stay on with former foster carers.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9410","9410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758671","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to (a) cap or (b) reduce the interest rate applied to student loans.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9342","9342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758672","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on the public purse of the write-off student loans after the 30 year term expires.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9343","9343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758673","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the process is for replacing a failing academy with a new sponsor.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9340","9340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758674","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to UN Sustainable Development Goal 2.1 to by 2030 end hunger and ensure access by all people to safe, nutritious and sufficient food all year round, what steps her Department is taking to tackle child hunger.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9611","9611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758675","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to ensure children are being educated about the environmental challenges faced by the UK and the rest of the world.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9591","9591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758676","2017-09-12","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships in Ashfield constituency are (a) above and (b) below NVQ Level 2.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9460","9460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758677","2017-09-12","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the guidance on tackling peer-to-peer abuse in Keeping children safe in education will be reviewed and updated.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9535","9535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758678","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding and resources her Department is providing to reduce the number of people not in education, employment and training in (a) Easington constituency and (b) County Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9555","9555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758679","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the value of domestic fish landings which are exported to other EU member states.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9564","9564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758680","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the completion of the coastal Blue Belt around the UK.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9548","9548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758681","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's policy is on the use of the Goodnature A24 mammal trap in England and Wales.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9524","9524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758682","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to meet the recycling targets of the EU's Circular Economy Package.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9462","9462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758683","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of household waste his Department expects England to recycle by 2030.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9450","9450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758684","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to UN Sustainable Development Goal 2.1 to by 2030 end hunger and ensure access by all people to safe, nutritious and sufficient food all year round, what steps his Department is taking to meet that target.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9613","9613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758685","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which courts will enforce environmental legislation when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9316","9316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758686","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to encourage the fitting of solar panels where appropriate to private sector new-build homes.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9317","9317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758687","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the capacity within UK universities and research institutes to continue to investigate the European geo-political area after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9312","9312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758688","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Protection of Badgers Act 1992 in each police force area in 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9337","9337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758689","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the cost of (a) administration, (b) delivery and (c) policing of badger culls in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9369","9369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758690","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) freelance and (b) temporary staff were employed by his Department in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9370","9370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758691","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of waste was recycled in each local authority area in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9352","9352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758692","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) freelance and (b) temporary staff were employed by his Department in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9371","9371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758693","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of existing environmental legislation to maintain and restore the UK's natural heritage.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9403","9403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758694","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to ensure that Government funding for the formed environment is invested to preserve the standard of water, soil and landscapes and to mitigate climate change.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9404","9404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758695","2017-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish a list of projects in Mexico that (a) have been funded by the Magna Carta Fund between 2015 and 2017 and (b) will be funded through that Fund in 2017 and 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9375","9375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758696","2017-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding from the Magna Carta Fund was spent in Mexico in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016; and what estimate he has made of the level of such funding to be spent in (i) 2017 and (ii) 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9376","9376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758697","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to support (a) British holidaymakers and (b) residents of the Overseas Territories in the Caribbean affected by Hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9320","9320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758698","2017-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the shelling of Awamiyah, Saudi Arabia; what representations he has made to the Saudi Government on that matter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9319","9319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758699","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that relations with the Republic of Ireland are not detrimentally affected by the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9594","9594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758700","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote whistleblowing in his Department and agencies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9416","9416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758701","2017-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Matthew Rycroft, the UK's Permanent Ambassador to the UN, on a new UN Security Council resolution on Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9453","9453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758702","2017-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Saudi Arabia on re-opening Sana'a Airport.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9454","9454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758703","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to promote whistleblowing in his Department and agencies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9417","9417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758704","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many referrals by Tier 1 Authorities under Regulation 23(9) of the Local Authority (Public Health, Health and Wellbeing Boards and Health Scrutiny) Regulations 2013 have been made in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9448","9448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758705","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the risk to patients caused by delays to the transfer of patient records to GPs under the primary care support services contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9461","9461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758706","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of patients' records formerly held by Henley Cross GP practice in Tudway Road, Greenwich have yet to be delivered to new GP practices since it closed in February 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9439","9439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758707","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the remuneration is of the Chair and Chief Executive of the Cheshire and Merseyside Sustainability and Transformation Partnership.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9429","9429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758708","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will set out the consultation process that a sustainability and transformation partnership is required to undertake when a decision to substantially change services is made.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9436","9436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758709","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nursing, midwifery and allied health students started their studies in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9430","9430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758710","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the performance of the primary care support services contract since it was taken over by Capita; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9437","9437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758711","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will list the Agenda for Change job grades which have been re-evaluated in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9431","9431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758712","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many sustainability and transformation partnerships have employed private sector consultants as part of the Accountable Care System process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9432","9432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758713","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been paid out in compensation by Capita for a failure to meet its obligations under the contract for primary care support services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9438","9438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758714","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide an update on negotiations between NICE and the drug manufacturer Vertex on the potential use of the drug Orkambi.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9489","9489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758715","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides for women with FGM seeking care who live in areas where there is no dedicated FGM clinic.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9476","9476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758716","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information the Government holds on recent or ongoing research on FGM clinical provision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9478","9478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758717","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to consult with (a) families, (b) carers and (c) those detained under current provision on the content of the proposed Mental Health Bill.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9502","9502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758718","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Mental Health Bill will be available for pre-legislative scrutiny.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9503","9503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758719","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the proposed Mental Health Bill will be published.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9504","9504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758720","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 August 2017 to Question 5853, if he will make an assessment of the income of NHS Property Services Ltd for the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9466","9466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758721","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2017 to Question 5742, what the total amount was of GP practice service charges that were overdue in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9467","9467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758722","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2017 to Question 5811, how many areas were subject to the capped expenditure process plan to reduce the number of endoscopies undertaken.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9468","9468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758723","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued on joint working between GP practices and hospitals which run FGM clinics.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9474","9474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758724","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the location and date of planned opening of new clinics for dealing with FGM cases.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9475","9475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758725","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number and location of clinics which are recommended for people who have undergone FGM.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9472","9472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758726","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the categories of clinic which have dealt with people who have undergone FGM.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9473","9473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758727","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will encourage medical schools to support the Royal College of Psychiatrists' #ChoosePsychiatry campaign; and what assessment he has made of the psychiatric workforce's capacity to respond to the growing demand for mental health services.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9547","9547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758728","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many neonatal units have the recommended amount of overnight parent accommodation to meet the standards outlined in the toolkit for high quality neonatal services; and what resources are provided to NHS trusts to increase the provision of overnight parent accommodation in places where that standard is not met.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9562","9562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758729","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding Durham County Council has received from the public health grant in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9554","9554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758730","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what improvements the Government has made to the provision of mental and emotional support available to children and young people suffering from cancer and their families since 2010.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9608","9608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758731","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Government has made towards meeting its commitment to recruit 5,000 additional GPs by 2020.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9605","9605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758732","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has assessed the potential merits of improvements to the mental and emotional support available to young people suffering from cancer and to their families.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9607","9607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758733","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the financial burden on families which are directly affected by cancer.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9606","9606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758734","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of the NHS accommodating patients who cannot be discharged due to the lack of disabled housing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9604","9604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758735","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding has been committed so far from the public purse to the new oral health preventative programme, Starting Well.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9601","9601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758736","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who will benefit from the new oral health programme, Starting Well.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9600","9600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758737","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NHS England's publication of 15 November 2015, Excellence in continence care, what progress his Department has made on measuring any reduction in (a) inappropriate or unnecessary catheterisation and (b) catheter associated urinary tract infections; and what statistics are collated to confirm progress that has been made.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9588","9588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758738","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NHS England's publication of 15 November 2015, Excellence in continence care, what progress his Department has made in measuring (a) any reduction in the number of prescriptions for catheters, (b) out-patient appointments, (c) surgical interventions and (d) costs relating to pads and other incontinence products; and what statistics are collated to confirm progress that has been made.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9587","9587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758739","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the importance of the data provided by the Adult Dental Health Survey to planning and commissioning oral health services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9621","9621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758740","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many dental practices will be involved in the new oral health preventive programme, Starting Well.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9622","9622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758741","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when work on the next Adult Dental Health Survey is due to commence; and what the timetable is for the publication of that survey's results.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9623","9623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758742","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what level of funding has been allocated for the delivery of the next Adult Dental Health Survey.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9624","9624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758743","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure equal access to overnight rooms or bed-space next to their child for parents saying overnight with their child in a paediatric ward and parents staying overnight with their baby in a neonatal unit.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9331","9331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758744","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of FIT testing on the capacity of the NHS to perform endoscopy procedures.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9321","9321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758745","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to assess future recruitment needs of the NHS diagnostic workforce to deliver adequate numbers of (a) endoscopists, (b) radiologists, (c) radiographers and (d) pathologists.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9322","9322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758746","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish details of all communications between his Department and the tobacco industry on the Tobacco Control Plan; and what steps he has taken to encourage tobacco companies to engage with the Government in written, as well as oral, form.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9323","9323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758747","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many abortions were carried out at (a) NHS hospitals and (b) registered clinics in Lancashire in 2016; and how many (i) male and (ii) female foetuses were aborted at each location during that year.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9329","9329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758748","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost per child is of the dental removal of one or more teeth.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9384","9384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758749","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2017 to Question 6837, in what format his Department holds information on spending on low and medium-secure inpatient mental health care since April 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9366","9366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758750","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2017 to Question 6832, and with reference to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 51972, whether the process for collection of data on the number of people who attended accident and emergency departments due to intentional self-harm has changed since the Answer of 14 November 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9365","9365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758751","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of Mental Health Investment Standards letters have been signed and reported to his Department.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9368","9368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758752","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent in real terms per head of the population on health in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9348","9348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758753","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many new hospitals were built in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9347","9347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758754","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many delayed transfers of care there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9353","9353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758755","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff have had their Agenda for Change job grade re-evaluated in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9425","9425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758756","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will set out the responsibilities of a sustainability and transformation partnership (STP) Chief Executive and STP Chair.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9433","9433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758757","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to provide a statutory basis to sustainability and transformation partnership structures.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9434","9434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758758","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were treated with a transvaginal mesh implant in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9426","9426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758759","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have suffered complications with transvaginal mesh implants in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9427","9427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758760","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many never events have occurred involving (a) audiologists, (b) cardiac physiologists, (c) gastro-intestinal physiologists, (d) neurophysiologists, (e) respiratory physiologists and (f) sleep physiologists in the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9435","9435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758761","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide a list of sustainability and transformation partnership chairs and chief executives and their remuneration.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9428","9428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758762","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many sustainability and transformation partnerships are chaired by a local government official.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9423","9423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758763","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints were made to the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency regarding transvaginal mesh implants in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9424","9424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758764","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage the provision of hoists in health centres to help transfer patients to examination beds.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9387","9387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758765","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many looked after children (a) had an initial mental health screening and (b) are awaiting further assessments or treatment in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9409","9409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758766","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) pre-school, (b) primary and (c) secondary age children have undergone the dental removal of one or more teeth in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9382","9382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758767","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was to the public purse of removing one or more teeth from children in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9383","9383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758768","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of neuromuscular care advisors for people with muscle-wasting conditions.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9390","9390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758769","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support the Government provides to people who have terminal cancer and their families.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9396","9396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758770","2017-09-12","Cabinet Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has plans to remove drugs questions on illegal drugs from the Crime Survey for England and Wales.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9378","9378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758771","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide an update on the work of the National Crime Agency to tackle drug trafficking in Venezuela.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9377","9377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758772","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff are employed in her Department to process asylum claims and clear the backlog of cases.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9325","9325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758773","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make statutory provision of appropriate adults for vulnerable adult detainees; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9364","9364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758774","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of police forces whose reserves are below the National Audit Office recommended level; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9336","9336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758775","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with Merseyside Police on the effect of (a) funding and (b) the number of police officers on tackling (i) serious and organised and (ii) gun crime across Merseyside.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9335","9335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758776","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how her Department plans to assess whether an individual applying for a spouse visa will meet the specific circumstances criteria if they (a) do not meet the minimum income requirement of £18,600 a year or (b) they have one child but earn less than £22,400.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9327","9327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758777","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the trends in the level of gun crime in (a) Merseyside and (b) England and the implications of that assessment for any reform of police funding.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9334","9334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758778","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which recommendations of the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Missing and Runaway Children and Adults report, Inquiry into the safeguarding of absent children, published in July 2017, her Department (a) has implemented, (b) is planning to implement and (c) will not be implementing.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9330","9330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758779","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of people who have been stopped and searched in (a) the area covered by West Midlands Police authority, (b) the City of Wolverhampton and (c) Wolverhampton North East constituency in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9619","9619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758780","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many suspects have been granted police bail by each police force in each month since 2015.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9620","9620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758781","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on drug rehabilitation services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9614","9614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758782","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unsuccessful bids were made for the Police Transformation Fund; and what the amount was of each unsuccessful bid to that fund.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9570","9570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758783","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many instances of knife-related crime have been recorded in (a) Wolverhampton and (b) the area covered by West Midlands Police in each month since 2015; and how many of those instances involved the use of machetes.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9519","9519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758784","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many retailers have reported suspicious transactions involving reportable poisons since the commencement of the Deregulation Act 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9561","9561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758785","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many instances of gun-related crime have been recorded in Wolverhampton in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9518","9518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758786","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there is a national or local register of organisations and people who are promoting the ending of FGM.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9479","9479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758787","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many accounts in UK banks have been frozen as a result of allegations of terrorist financing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9486","9486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758788","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what mechanisms the Government employs to liaise with external organisations in tackling FGM; who the chief points of contact are (a) nationally and (b) regionally for that liaison; and who outside Government is responsible for leading on work to end FGM.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9480","9480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758789","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what documentation is required to be held by a mother and father when travelling abroad with their child where the child has taken their father's name but the mother has retained her maiden name.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9464","9464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758790","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many visa appeals took more than six months to be decided in each month of the last two years .","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9494","9494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758791","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many visa appeals have been decided for those who have no recourse to public funds in each month of the last two years.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9493","9493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758792","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many visa appeals decided for those who have no recourse to public funds took more than six months to be decided in each month of the last two years.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9495","9495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758793","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many visa appeals have been decided in each month of the last two years.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9496","9496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758794","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to promote whistleblowing in her Department and agencies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9418","9418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758795","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to amend children's passports to include the names of both of their parents.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9458","9458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758796","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many British women have been asked by UK Border Control to prove they were related to their children when attempting to enter the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9459","9459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758797","2017-09-11","House of Commons Commission","2017-09-07","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what preparations the House authorities have made to apply big data analytics to House and hon. Member activities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9522","9522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758798","2017-09-12","Department for International Development","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the international aid budget has been spent on (a) disaster relief and (b) refugee assistance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9385","9385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758799","2017-09-12","Department for International Development","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support those affected by Hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9567","9567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758800","2017-09-12","Department for International Development","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in the Overseas Territories and other Caribbean states on the humanitarian response to Hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9568","9568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758801","2017-09-12","Department for International Development","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the US on the provision of humanitarian assistance to those territories and states affected by Hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9569","9569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758802","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to promote whistleblowing in her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9419","9419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758803","2017-09-12","Department for International Development","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to publish a breakdown of new funding for Nigeria announced in August 2017.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9584","9584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758804","2017-09-12","Department for International Development","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the cost including for staff of maintaining her Department's In the News webpage is annually.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9582","9582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758805","2017-09-12","Department for International Development","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to review her Department's financial contribution to any UN agencies.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9583","9583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758806","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps are being taken to ensure Travellers who trespass on property pay for any criminal damages and limit the expense incurred to innocent parties.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9590","9590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758807","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Wild Mammals (Protection) Act 1996 in each police force area in 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9451","9451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758808","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to promote whistleblowing in his Department and agencies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9421","9421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758809","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been prosecuted and convicted under the Psychoactive Substances Act 2016 (a) in total and (b) for offences involving nitrous oxide since the commencement of that Act.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9455","9455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758810","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) e-cigarettes and (b) tobacco products were sold in prison shops in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9456","9456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758811","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison governors have worked at two or more other prisons in the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9457","9457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758812","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Hunting Act 2004 in each police force area in 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9465","9465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758813","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness and performance of community rehabilitation companies since their inception.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9532","9532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758814","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what factors led him to conclude in July 2017 that the problems experienced as a result of the reform of the probation service were unforeseen.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9533","9533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758815","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have been sent on detached duty to fill staffing gaps in other prisons in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9372","9372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758816","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers recruited in the last 12 months have subsequently resigned from their post.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9373","9373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758817","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the Prison and Probation Ombudsman has spent on investigations into self-inflicted deaths in 2016-17.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9367","9367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758818","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will give the Parole Board the authority to decide when a hearing can be held to consider the cases of those with imprisonment for public protection sentences who are still in prison.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9379","9379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758819","2017-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason the recommendation from Abigail Rogers at the Public Protection Casework Section of the Parole Board in her letter dated 19 May 2017 that a prisoner be transferred to an open conditions prison has not yet been acted upon.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9380","9380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758820","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will instigate a coroner-led inquest into the death of Dr David Kelly in 2005.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9311","9311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758821","2017-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many prosecutions have been brought for breach of fire safety building regulations in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9318","9318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758822","2017-09-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress he and the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport are making to attract more visitors to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9341","9341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758823","2017-09-11","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to promote whistleblowing in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9422","9422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758824","2017-09-12","Prime Minister","2017-09-07","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she has had recent discussions with the Saudi Foreign Minister on ending the blockade of Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9452","9452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758825","2017-09-12","Prime Minister","2017-09-07","To ask the Prime Minister, which representatives of which companies accompanied her on her visit to Japan from 30 August to 1 September 2017.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9463","9463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758826","2017-09-11","Prime Minister","2017-09-07","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2017 to Question 4882, how many advisers in her foreign affairs team are not Foreign and Commonwealth Office staff.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9552","9552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758827","2017-09-11","Prime Minister","2017-09-07","To ask the Prime Minister, what the last occasion was that a serving Prime Minister visited Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9603","9603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758828","2017-09-11","Prime Minister","2017-09-07","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will visit Easington constituency to discuss housing issues in Horden.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9602","9602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758829","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of railway track is located in each region of England and Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9355","9355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758830","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department received from Arriva Trains Wales in rebates in each year since that franchise has been in operation.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9356","9356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758831","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many miles of railway track were electrified in each region of England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9357","9357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758832","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many miles of new railway track were laid in each region of England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9358","9358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758833","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was invested in improving railway infrastructure in each region of England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9359","9359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758834","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department has made to other EU member states on easing waiting times at their airports.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9313","9313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758835","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure the equitable distribution of rail funding.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9338","9338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758836","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to increase railway links from Huddersfield to other towns in the north of England.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9339","9339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758837","2017-09-12","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the rolling stock which will be in operation on the Midland Mainline between 2020 and 2022 when the high speed trains are out of service and the new bi-mode trains will not yet be available.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9580","9580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758838","2017-09-12","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparable assessment he has made of the performance and costs of bi-mode trains and electric rolling stock.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9585","9585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758839","2017-09-12","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the future pattern of rail services and timetabling between London and (a) Nottingham, (b) Leicester and (c) Sheffield as a result of the decision to introduce bi-mode trains on the Midland Mainline from 2022.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9586","9586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758840","2017-09-12","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost has been to the public purse of plans to electrify the Midland Mainline north of Kettering to date.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9578","9578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758841","2017-09-12","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect that the decision to cancel the electrification of the Midland Mainline will have on the economy of the East Midlands.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9579","9579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758842","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which planned rail electrification projects have been cancelled in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9530","9530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758843","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average savings in travel time were from each rail electrification project in England and Wales in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9529","9529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758844","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which projects in Wales have benefited from the coastal communities fund in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9550","9550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758845","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent meetings he has had with Cabinet colleagues on tidal lagoons.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9572","9572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758846","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of Welsh exports and imports were traded with the EU in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9571","9571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758847","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much in EU structural funds has been spent in each local authority area of Wales in each year for which data are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9531","9531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758848","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many people in work were living in poverty in Wales in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9542","9542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758849","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which railway stations in Wales are being considered for remodelling to accommodate bimodal trains.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9577","9577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758850","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much funding Wales has received from the public purse in real terms under the Barnett Formula in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9575","9575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758851","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the timescale is for the completion of rail electrification to Cardiff.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9576","9576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758852","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what percentage of foreign inward investment in Wales was from other EU member states in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9574","9574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758853","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much (a) central, (b) Welsh and (c) local government has spent on the (i) Cardiff City Deal, (ii) Swansea City Deal and (iii) North Wales growth deal to date; and what projections he has made of spending on each of those City Deals in the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9609","9609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758854","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much planned spending from EU structural funds will occur in each local authority area in Wales in each of the next six years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9596","9596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758855","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that women travelling from Northern Ireland as part of their abortion care are able to receive free access to STI testing and contraception.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9471","9471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758856","2017-09-11","Women and Equalities","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to further support women from Northern Ireland accessing abortion care in England with regard to travel and accommodation costs.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9470","9470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758857","2017-09-11","Women and Equalities","2017-09-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what changes the Government plans to the funding of the Government Equalities Office to support its work in helping women from Northern Ireland access abortion care in England.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9469","9469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758858","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the evidential basis is for the projected increase in longevity for women affected by the Pensions Acts of 1995 and 2011.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9304","9304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758859","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support the Government is offering to women affected by the Pensions Acts of 1995 and 2011 to stay in work to a later age; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9305","9305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758860","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made on reviewing disabled people's access and amending regulations where necessary to improve disabled access to licensed premises, parking and housing.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9306","9306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758861","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made on working with providers of (a) energy, (b) telecoms and (c) other essential services on reducing the extra costs that disability can incur.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9307","9307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758862","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to support one million more people with disabilities into employment over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9308","9308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758863","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made on bringing forward legislative proposals to give unemployed disabled claimants personalised and tailored employment support.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9309","9309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758864","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many visits ministers of  his Department have made to (a) food banks, (b) summer holiday lunch clubs and (c) credit unions since 1 June 2017; and if he will publish the dates and locations of those visits.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9328","9328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758865","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he or Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the (a) insurance, (b) mortgage and (c) banking industry on updating their standard terms and conditions to reflect increased life expectancy and later retirement and pension ages.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9324","9324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758866","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment the Department has made of the effect of the Walker v Innospec Limited case on pensions liabilities.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9315","9315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758867","2017-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent progress his Department has made on the implementation of the Government's Cycle to Work scheme for his Department's employees.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9389","9389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758868","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which jobcentres in Wales have closed since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9354","9354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758869","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support is currently available to children and young people diagnosed with cancer for claims for (a) disability living allowance and (b) personal independence payments.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9397","9397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758870","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure access to benefits for children and young people who have been diagnosed with cancer.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9398","9398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758872","2017-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of universal credit claimants who were paid (i) monthly and (ii) weekly prior to claiming the benefit.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9413","9413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758873","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants in Stretford and Urmston constituency have had their personal independence payments decisions overturned in their favour as a result of (a) mandatory reconsideration and (b) an appeal hearing in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9507","9507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758874","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will introduce a free telephone number for benefit claimants to contact his Department to discuss benefit inquiries and short-term benefit advance.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9515","9515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758875","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants received advance payments in each month from January 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9501","9501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758876","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of universal credit claimants have fallen into rent arrears in each month from January 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9500","9500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758877","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time for first payments to be made to new claimants of universal credit between application and receipt of payment was in each month from January 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9499","9499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758878","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of claimants have received hardship payments under universal credit in each month from January 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9498","9498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758879","2017-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of people who claim universal credit as in-work support and who are paid (i) monthly and (ii) weekly.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9414","9414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758880","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will be affected by removal of support for mortgage interest in April 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9506","9506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758881","2017-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what evidence his Department has that (a) under the full service and (b) under the live service universal credit (i) moves people into work more quickly and (ii) supports people to stay in work longer than the previous system; and if he will set out the timescale over which that evidence was collected.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9534","9534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758882","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is possible for all new claims for existing legacy benefits excluding universal credit to be processed through one single computer screen without needing to use more than one computer.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9527","9527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758883","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will list the series of trials in which his Department is testing the effectiveness of interventions to support those already in work to increase their earnings.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9526","9526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758884","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 7 September 2017 to Question 7375 and of 13 July 2017 to Question 3059, whether the installation of cladding and external wall insulation systems requires assessment under health and safety at work legislation.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9540","9540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758885","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made in reducing the time taken to process mandatory reconsiderations for personal independence payments and employment and support allowance; and at what level the target is set for the time taken to process such reconsiderations.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9525","9525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758886","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2017 to Questions 6552 and the Answers of 25 July 2017 to Questions 5366 and 5365, whether his Department has the details of the mobility requirements of all current claimants.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9551","9551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758887","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will set up a dedicated telephone line for representatives from nominated charities to call on behalf of benefits claimants.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9528","9528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758888","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what evidence he has that releasing the work capability assessment outcome report in answer to Freedom of Information request FS50645849 would damage the reputation of the Centre for Health and Disability Assessments, Maximus or Atos.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9612","9612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758889","2017-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of tax credit recipients who are (a) lone parents with dependent children, (b) married or co-habiting couples with dependent children and (c) married or co-habiting couples with no dependent children who will receive universal credit by the completion of full service roll-out.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9615","9615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758890","2017-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people receiving tax credits who will be receiving universal credit at the completion of full service roll-out.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9616","9616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758891","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government plans to take as a result of the publication of the Taylor Review of modern working practices, published on 11 July 2017.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9617","9617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758892","2017-09-12","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013 is fully and uniformly enforced.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9618","9618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758893","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 6201, if he will meet a trustee from the Mineworkers Pension Scheme to discuss the surplus-sharing arrangement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9553","9553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758894","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much has accrued to the public purse from fines and penalties from companies failing to report their Persons of Significant Control in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9557","9557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758895","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies have not met the most recent Persons of Significant Control reporting deadline.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9558","9558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758896","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to support metal-recycling companies.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9537","9537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758897","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations the Government has received from (a) employment agencies and (b) agency workers on holiday payments.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9538","9538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758898","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to raise wages for the self-employed.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9539","9539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758899","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many MWp of solar have been installed under the revised Feed-in Tariff scheme in each month since its re-launch in 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9510","9510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758900","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of job losses in the UK solar sector since April 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9511","9511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758901","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many domestic solar installations have been completed under the Feed-in Tariff scheme in 2017; and how many domestic solar installations there were in each of the preceding five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9512","9512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758902","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received from the metals industries on the effect on that sector of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9444","9444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758903","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to ensure that solar and other micro-generation technologies receive a fair price for exported electricity from March 2019.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9508","9508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758904","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made on running a consultation on amending the FIT scheme technology caps in 2017.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9509","9509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758905","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he intends to renew the Feed-in Tariff scheme after March 2019.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9505","9505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758906","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the current underspend in the revised Feed-in Tariff scheme is; and what is the total amount unused under that scheme was across all technologies in (a) August 2017, (b) May 2017, (c) February 2017 and (d) November 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9497","9497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758907","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the potential correlation between periods of high electricity usage and electrical fires in the home.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9362","9362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758908","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for publication of ACAS guidelines for employers whose employees have a baby born premature or sick; and what plans his Department has to ensure that those guidelines are (a) implemented and (b) evaluated.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9332","9332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758909","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which areas of the Japanese market are considered to be the most attractive to British exporters.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9446","9446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758910","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to improve trade relations with (a) Tunisia and (b) other Northern African countries.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9447","9447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758911","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to promote whistleblowing in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9420","9420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758912","2017-09-12","Department for International Trade","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of his senior trade negotiating team are from black and minority ethnic backgrounds.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9565","9565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758913","2017-09-12","Department for International Trade","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of his senior trade negotiating team are women.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9566","9566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758914","2017-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to establish a free trade area between the UK and Gibraltar after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9592","9592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758915","2017-09-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the customs union on trade between the UK and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9593","9593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758916","2017-09-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all EU citizens are reassured of their right to remain in the UK for two years after March 2019 if the Government's proposals are agreed to.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9445","9445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758917","2017-09-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking to promote whistleblowing in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9415","9415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758921","2017-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the tourism industry shared between the UK and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9629","9629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758922","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 13 March 2017 to Question 67199, when the results of the consultation on proposals to ban microbeads in cosmetics and personal care products will be published.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9628","9628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758923","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to encourage police forces to pursue suspects on mopeds and motorcycles who are not wearing crash helmets.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9627","9627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758924","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police community support officers have been recruited to cover Wolverhampton in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9630","9630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758925","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the National Rail projects in Wales which were (a) finished on time and on budget and (b) not finished on time and on budget in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9625","9625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758926","2017-09-11","Wales Office","2017-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much the UK received in EU Structural Funds in each year since 2000; and what proportion of that funding was allocated to Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9626","9626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758038","2017-09-11","Attorney General","2017-09-06","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Law Officers' Departments paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9180","9180"
