"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873654","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of IVF cycles in which more than 50 eggs were collected in the last five years.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134768","134768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873655","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of IVF cycles in which more than 60 eggs were collected in the last five years.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134769","134769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873656","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of IVF cycles in which more than 70 eggs were collected in the last five years.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134770","134770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873657","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of egg donor cycles in 2013 in which at least 20 eggs were collected.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134771","134771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873658","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of egg donor cycles in 2013 in which at least 20 eggs were collected.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134772","134772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873659","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of IVF cycles in 2015 in which at least 20 eggs were collected.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134773","134773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873660","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of IVF cycles in 2016 in which at least 20 eggs were collected.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134774","134774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873661","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of IVF cycles in 2017 in which at least 20 eggs were collected.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134775","134775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873662","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority places limitations on the number of times an egg donor can be stimulated with drugs to donate eggs in each year.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134776","134776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873663","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority places limitations on the number of times an egg donor can be stimulated with drugs to donate eggs in her lifetime.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134777","134777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873664","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2018 to Question 132489, on AWACS, if he will identify in the tender process the long-term (a) support and (b) maintenance costs in the value for money assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134778","134778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873665","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2018 to Question 132489, on AWACS, whether he has allocated an out of service date for the current RAF airborne early warning aircraft; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134779","134779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873666","2018-04-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with (a) pharmaceutical and (b) aerospace industry representatives in Northern Ireland on licencing in trade talks with the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134780","134780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873667","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer , what information the Government holds on the proportion of outward trade flows from UK ports which represents goods which originated from outside the UK in each of the last five years; and if he will publish that information by (a) country of origin and (b) sector.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134781","134781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873668","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the level of housing benefit (a) fraud and (b) overpayments in each region of England and Wales in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134782","134782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873669","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the UK's gross national income which has been invested in overseas aid in each of the last 10 years; and what comparative estimate her Department has made of those proportions and the proportions spent by other EU countries.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134783","134783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873670","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in Uzbekistan on freedom of religion.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134784","134784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873671","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of places in the PrEP Impact Trial are currently filled.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134785","134785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873672","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for all sites participating in the PrEP Impact Trial to be live.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134786","134786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873673","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students from each socio-economic group achieved three or more A* or A grades at A level in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134787","134787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873674","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to improve the quality of further education.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134788","134788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873675","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the take-up rate for sickle cell disease and thalassaemia screening for pregnant women in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry was in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134789","134789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873676","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on introducing a part-time season ticket for rail.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134790","134790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873677","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the take-up rate for bowel cancer home screening kits in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry was in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134791","134791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873678","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the number of shale oil wells that will be in place by (a) 2025 and (b) 2030.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134792","134792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873679","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the level of availability of treatments for patients diagnosed with Ascher's Syndrome.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134793","134793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873680","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in the Phillipines; and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134794","134794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873681","2018-04-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-28","To ask Secretary of State for Justice, how many Albanian nationals are in the prison population in England and Wales; and what proportion of the total prison population that number represents.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134795","134795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873682","2018-04-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government plans to make an economic analysis of its final deal on leaving the EU available to hon. Members before a decision on the deal is taken in Parliament; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134796","134796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873683","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the current level of employer demand for apprenticeships at (a) higher and (ii) degree level; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134797","134797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873684","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential for offshore wind to deliver significant electricity system cost reductions by 2030.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134798","134798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873685","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to enable onshore wind and solar developers to compete for low cost power contracts in areas where communities accept such developments.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134799","134799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873686","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many tier 2 visa applications for positions in Scotland were accepted, declined or deferred in each month from September 2016 to March 2018.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134800","134800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873687","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many tier 2 visa applications for positions in Wales were accepted, declined or deferred in each month from September 2016 to March 2018.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134801","134801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873688","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many tier 2 visa applications for positions in Northern Ireland were accepted, declined or deferred in each month from September 2016 to March 2018.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134802","134802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873689","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many tier 2 visa applications for positions in England were accepted, declined or deferred in each month from September 2016 to March 2018.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134803","134803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873690","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many tier 2 visa applications for positions in the NHS were accepted, declined or deferred in each month from September 2016 to March 2018.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134804","134804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873691","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of  changes in the level of violence in northern Iraq; and what recent reports he has received of deaths of civilians and security personnel caused by Islamic State in that region.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134805","134805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873692","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to counter resurgence of Islamic State in northern Iraq.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134806","134806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873693","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the estimated net cost to the public purse in England is of gun licensing and certification.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134807","134807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873694","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on ensuring that the costs to the public purse of gun licensing and certification are covered by the fees charged to the public for those licenses and certificates.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134808","134808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873695","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consultation her Department undertook on the definition of torture set out in The Detention Centre (Amendment) Rules 2018 and the Immigration Act 2016: Revised Guidance on adults at risk in immigration detention published on 21st March, S.I No. 411/2018, published on 21 March 2018.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134809","134809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873696","2018-04-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make an assessment of the extent to which the appointment of Professor Dr Martin Selmayr as Secretary General of the European Commission followed professionally approved procedures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134810","134810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873697","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 129467, if he will take steps to encourage podiatrists to seek leadership positions in foot protection services.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134811","134811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873698","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 129467, if he will mandate that the 2018 National Diabetes Footcare Audit commissioner survey includes questions on adherence to each aspect of NICE Clinical Guidance 19.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134812","134812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873699","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 129469, what assessment he has made of the level of variation in practice since the publication of the NICE guideline of August 2015,  Diabetic foot problems: prevention and management.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134813","134813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873700","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Institute for Apprenticeship's policy document of February 2018, Faster and better: Transforming the development of quality apprenticeship standards, what steps he plans to take to help prospective applicants to degree apprenticeships and their advisers understand which programmes offer a degree qualification.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134814","134814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873701","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to parish councils on compliance the General Data Protection Regulation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134815","134815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873702","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance has been provided in respect of parish meetings on compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134816","134816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873703","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England on the decision to disband its specialist team focused on combating female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134817","134817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873704","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England on how strategic planning to combat female genital mutilation will take place after the decision was taken to disband the specialist team  focused on that issue.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134818","134818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873705","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England on ensuring that there is co-ordination between local (a) NHS trusts, (b) police forces and (c) police and crime commissioners as a result of the decision to disband the specialist team in NHS England focused on such co-ordination.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134819","134819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873706","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England on ensuring NHS staff are appropriately trained in how to detect and report female genital mutilation (FGM) and support patients who have been subjected to FGM after the decision was taken to disband the specialist FGM team.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134820","134820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873707","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has received reports of disciplinary action initiated against Special Branch officers communicating with organisations or individuals that blacklisted construction workers.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134821","134821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873708","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 March 2018 to Question 133309, how much income tax was paid by people who fall under the jurisdiction of HMRC’s high net worth unit in each year between 2000 and 2009.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134822","134822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873709","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason households in the area surrounding Grenfell Tower which were made homeless by the Grenfell Tower fire are excluded from statistics on the rehousing process for survivors of that fire.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134823","134823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873710","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will ensure that all households made homeless by the Grenfell Tower fire regardless of whether they lived in that tower are offered secure tenancies when they are rehoused.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134824","134824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873711","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposal by the independent inspection report on Northamptonshire County Council to create two unitary councils in Northamptonshire on shared services between South Northamptonshire District Council and Cherwell District Council in Oxfordshire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134825","134825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873712","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Commonwealth-born citizens were detained by UK immigration services between January 2015 and January 2018.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134826","134826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873713","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2018 to Question 130922, what the funding methodology was for the allocation of rail funding to the Scottish Government for Control Period 5.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134827","134827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873714","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2018 to Question 130922, on Railways: Scotland, if he will publish the (a) criteria and (b) methodology for the Barnett Consequential element of the Control Period 6 rail funding allocation to the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134828","134828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873715","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 28 March 2018, whether the £600 million for the Dreadnought program has been allocated from the centrally held £0.8 billion contingency for nuclear projects.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134829","134829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873716","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the funding methodology is for the allocation of rail funding within England and Wales for Control Period 6.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134830","134830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873717","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the merits of the UK continuing to send representatives to sit on the Committee of the Regions.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134831","134831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873718","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of sending UK representatives to the Committee of the Regions in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134832","134832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873719","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the UK Government is taking to (a) support UN Resolution 2401 on the humanitarian crisis in Syria, and (b) collect evidence of (i) violations of international humanitarian law and (ii) crimes against humanity.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134833","134833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873720","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the political situation in Malaysia in the run-up to general elections this year.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134834","134834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873721","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect  of proposed electoral boundary changes in Malaysia on the veracity of the general election in that country.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134835","134835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873722","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his counterpart in the Malaysian Government on the potential effect of proposed legislation to criminalise fake news on freedom of speech in that country.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134836","134836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873723","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 129509, on Chiropody, what the name of the NHS Digital healthcare workforce information working group will be.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134837","134837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873724","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March to Question 129509, on Chiropody, what plans the NHS Digital healthcare workforce information working group has to consult (a) external organisations and (b) professional bodies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134838","134838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873725","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 5 March to Question 129509, on Chiropody, what the timetable is for the NHS Digital healthcare workforce information working group to report.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134839","134839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873726","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that children can access mental health care.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134840","134840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873727","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will expand the review into the educational outcomes of children in need of help or support to include the (a) employment, (b) housing and (c) health outcomes of that group of children.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134841","134841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873728","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for children's mental health services.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134842","134842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873729","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect the proposed reforms to supported housing on the financial sustainability of women’s refuges.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134843","134843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873730","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of providing funding for accredited English language teaching for all refugees.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134844","134844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873731","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government has provided for accredited English language teaching for refugees in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134845","134845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873732","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many accident and emergency visits there were for minor ailments in each clinical commissioning group in each year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134846","134846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873733","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of calls made to NHS 111 resulted in a referral to pharmacy in (a) England and (b) each clinical commissioning group in each year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134847","134847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873734","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to take steps to improve out-of-school mental health support for children and young people.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134848","134848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873735","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to establish waiting time targets for (a) elective surgery and (b) A&E waiting times.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134849","134849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873736","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the White Paper Industrial Strategy: Building a Britain fit for the future, published on 27 November 2017, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the equality of health outcomes between the north and south of England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134850","134850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873737","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the recommendation of the Centre for Mental Health's report of July 2017 entitled Against the Odds, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of implementing a Concordat for Black and Minority Ethnic Mental Health to ensure that schools prioritise young people’s mental health and well-being.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134851","134851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873738","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have support mechanisms available for young people from Black and Minority Ethnic groups that are being considered for exclusion.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134852","134852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873739","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to introduce the new route to Indefinite Leave for Remain (IDR) for self-employed Turkish business people in the UK under the European Community Association Agreement with Turkey (Ankara Agreement) Business Persons visa category; what principles her Department will apply in designing the new route to ILR; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the new route complies with the UK’s obligations under the Ankara Agreement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134853","134853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873740","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of dualling and upgrading the A1237 in York.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134854","134854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873741","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement of 28 March 2018 that Halton Hospital within Warrington and Halton Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, was unsuccessful in its bid to receive Sustainability and Transformation Partnership capital funding, whether he plans to allocate additional funding for (a) capital investment and (b) health provision to that area.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134855","134855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873742","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's decision of 28 March 2018 not fund a new Hospital at Halton though sustainability and transformation partnership capital funding on the provision of health services in Halton and Warrington NHS Trust area.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134856","134856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873743","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will make an estimate of the average (a) hourly and (b) weekly wages of (i) agency workers and (ii) directly employed staff working in comparable (A) jobs and (B) sectors.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134857","134857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873744","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of agency workers have been employed on pay between assignment contracts under regulation 10 of the Agency Worker Regulations 2010 in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134858","134858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873745","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of Regulation 10 of the Agency Worker Regulations 2010 on the pay of agency workers.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134859","134859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873746","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of  Part 5 of the Agency Workers Regulations 2010 on pay rates for agency workers.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134860","134860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873747","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the second remedial plan for Govia Thameslink Railway will be published.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134861","134861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873748","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on the application of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 to private healthcare providers in respect of information they hold on behalf of the NHS.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134862","134862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873749","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the merits of the proposed transfer of Rohingya refugees to Bhasan Char Island.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134863","134863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873750","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has made an assessment of the viability of Bhasan Char Island the relocation of Rohingya refugees.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134864","134864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873751","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has received assurances from her counterpart in the Bangladesh Government on the adequacy of food, water and other resources for Rohingya refugees relocated to Bhasan Char Island.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134865","134865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873752","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to contribute to the relocation of Rohingya refugees to Bhasan Char Island.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134866","134866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873753","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of potential changes in trading opportunities for British beet sugar after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134867","134867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873754","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he plans to take to ensure British farmers remain internationally competitive.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134868","134868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873755","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 17 of the National Security Capability Review, when his Department plans to bring forward proposals for changes to the compensation paid to (a) injured personnel and (b) families of those killed on operations.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134869","134869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873756","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to universal credit claimants who have deductions in their standard allowance in Part 4 of their monthly award letters, excluding managed payments to landlords, how many and what proportion of claimants of universal credit have been subject to a deduction in their standard allowance in each of the past twelve months.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134870","134870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873757","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to universal credit claimants who have deductions in their standard allowance in Part 4 of their monthly award letters, excluding managed payments to landlords, how many and what proportion of claimants of monthly awards for universal credit have had greater than 40 per cent of the standard allowance taken in deductions and recoveries during the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134871","134871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873758","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to universal credit claimants who have deductions in their standard allowance in Part 4 of their monthly award letters, excluding managed payments to landlords, how many and what proportion of claimants have had 40 per cent or more of their standard allowance deducted in (a) one and (b) more than one month, in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134872","134872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873759","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to universal credit claimants who have deductions in their standard allowance in Part 4 of their monthly award letters, excluding managed payments to landlords, how many and what proportion of claimants have had (a) 20 per cent and (b) more than 20 per cent of their standard allowance taken off in (i) one and (ii) more than one month in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134873","134873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873760","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit deductions for (a) rent and (b) service charges have been taken at the (i) 20 per cent higher rate, (ii) between 10 per cent and 20 per cent and (iii) the 10 per cent lower rate in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134874","134874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873762","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average rate was of deductions from universal credit for (a) rent and (b) service charges in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134876","134876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873763","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit deductions for (a) fines and (b) compensation orders are taken at (i) £108.35, (ii) a rate between 5 percent of standard allowance and £108.35 and (iii) 5 per cent of standard allowance in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134877","134877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873764","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average rate was at which deductions from universal credit were made to pay (a) fines and (b) compensation orders in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134878","134878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873765","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to universal credit claimants who have deductions in their standard allowance in Part 4 of their monthly award letters, excluding managed payments to landlords, what the average proportion of claimants’ standard allowance was in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134879","134879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873766","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to universal credit claimants who have deductions in their standard allowance in Part 4 of their monthly award letters, excluding managed payments to landlords, what the average amount taken was from a claimants standard allowance in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134880","134880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873767","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the delivery and distribution of aid, including food, to Yemen through the ports in Yemen.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134881","134881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873768","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the openness to trade in UK (a) goods and (b) services of developing countries in receipt of UK aid broken down by recipient country.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134882","134882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873769","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the trends in the (a) availability of sexual health clinics and (b) waiting times for appointments to see clinicians in those clinics.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134883","134883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873770","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has (a) made and (b) received representations from the charitable sector on the effectiveness of people-to-people or coexistence projects.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134884","134884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873771","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what consultation her Department had prior to the announcement of the People For Peaceful Change project in Israel and the occupied Palestinian territories .","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134885","134885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873773","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 20 of the Ministry for Housing, Communities and Local Government's Litter Strategy for England, published in April 2017, what definition his Department uses for household waste; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134887","134887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873774","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department work on (a) the preventing sexual violence initiative and (b) the preventing sexual violence team of experts; and of those staff, how many are deployed overseas.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134888","134888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873775","2018-04-16","Department for International Trade","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, for which periods since 2010, members of the the Gulf Cooperation Council received a green rating for each of the 22 groups of military items on the UK Strategic Export Control Lists.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134889","134889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873776","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households remain to be contacted with respect to the change in Support for Mortgage Interest.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134890","134890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873777","2018-04-16","Department for International Trade","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, by what methodology the RAG ratings used by desk officers within the Export Control Joint Unit are determined.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134891","134891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873778","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many working-age households have been contacted with respect to the change in Support for Mortgage Interest.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134892","134892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873779","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in receipt of pension credit and support for mortgage interest have applied for the replacement loan when support for mortgage interest ends in April 2018.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134893","134893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873780","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of levels of violence and displacement in Rakhine State.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134894","134894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873781","2018-04-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent estimate she has made of the number of Rohingya refugees crossing the Bangladesh-Burma border; and what assessment she has made of the capacity of refugee camps in Bangladesh to cope with the number of refugees entering that country.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134895","134895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873782","2018-04-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the Government's policy is on adapting domestic law in the case of changes to existing EU regulations that will come into force after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134896","134896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873783","2018-04-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on implementing EU regulations which have implementation acts set to be drafted after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134897","134897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873784","2018-04-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on adopting future EU regulations after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134898","134898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873785","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to review The Road Vehicles Lighting Regulations 1989,1989 No. 1796, PART III, Regulation 27; what assessment his Department has made of the effect of brighter car headlamps on other road users; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134899","134899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873786","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government in Turkey on ending the attacks on the Christian community in Syria.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134900","134900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873787","2018-04-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timescale is for the appointment of a trade union representative to the Creative Industries Council.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134901","134901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873788","2018-04-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of banning gambling adverts on television shown prior to the watershed of 9pm.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134902","134902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873789","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the use of electronic vaping devices on smoker mortality levels.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134903","134903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873790","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Government's mandate to NHS England for 2018-19, published on 20 March 2018, for reasons the elective surgery waiting time of 18 weeks and the emergency waiting time of 4 hours will not be met until 2020.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134904","134904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873791","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Government's mandate to NHS England for 2018-19, published on 20 March 2018, what plans his Department has to ensure that the elective surgery and emergency waiting times will be maintained at levels set out in previous years' mandates to NHS England.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134905","134905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873792","2018-04-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he next plans to meet the Press Recognition Panel.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134906","134906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873793","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average number of calls has been to the HMRC Childcare system hotline per day since that hotline was established; and what the average length of each call has been.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134907","134907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873794","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of people using HMRC's online service for tax-free childcare have experienced technical problems; and how many accounts remain unresolved.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134908","134908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873795","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she and her predecessors were briefed by the Metropolitan Police Commissioner on Special Branch officers communicating with organisations or individuals that blacklisted construction workers.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134909","134909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873796","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 31 of the National Security Capabilities Review, published in July 2017, which countries have taken part in International Defence Training courses; and how many nationals of those countries have taken part in each such course since 2015.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134910","134910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873797","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has held with his counterpart in Burundi on (a) human rights and (b) the rule of law in Burundi; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134911","134911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873798","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions his Department has had with (a) universities, (b) further education colleges and (c) Local Enterprise Partnerships on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund and accessing such funding after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134912","134912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873799","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions the Universities Minister has had with the Chair of the Office for Students on future representation for further education colleges and students on the Board of the Office for Students and the general governance of that Board.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134913","134913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873800","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to appoint a new permanent chief executive of the Student Loans Company.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134914","134914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873801","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to announce the funding rate for the early years level 3 apprenticeship.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134915","134915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873802","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans reduce the size of the guide for the mid-tier manual and supplements.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134916","134916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873803","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much and what proportion of the adult education budget was spent on ESOL in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134917","134917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873804","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the potential merits of putting in place a single management team to run the Halton Clinical Commissioning Group and Warrington Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134918","134918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873805","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that U.K Visas and Immigration have adequate resources to meet an increase in applications before the 2020 cut-off date for non-UK EU nationals.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134919","134919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873806","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to establish a comprehensive register of non-UK EU citizens in the UK.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134920","134920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873807","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time is for UK Visas and Immigration to process a visa application.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134921","134921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873808","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unprocessed visa applications there are and what steps she is taking to reduce that number.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134922","134922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873809","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many family reunion visa applications were processed within service standards in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134923","134923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873810","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many notifications that require no further action are sent on average to applicants for Tier 4 visas.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134924","134924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873811","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department is taking steps to simplify the process of applying for a tier 4 visa.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134925","134925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873812","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for him to appoint the chair of the Social Mobility Commission.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134926","134926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873813","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps have been taken since the first quarter of 2016 to reduce fraud in the English language testing system.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134927","134927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873814","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps have been taken to improve the speed at which outstanding asylum applications are completed.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134930","134930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873815","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Education of 13 March 2018, Official Report, Column 802, on what date in October 2018 the childcare vouchers scheme will close to new applicants.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134931","134931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873816","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what percentage of all new and outstanding asylum applications were completed in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c)2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134932","134932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873817","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers were repatriated to countries her Department considered to be unsafe at the time of their repatriation in 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134933","134933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873818","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees from Syria had their application for refugee status granted in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134934","134934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873819","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2018 to Question 132573 on Halton Clinical Commissioning Group, how many additional hours the interim Chief Officer for that Clinical Commissioning Group works each week.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134935","134935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873820","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government projects that the target of accepting 20,000 Syrian refugees will be met by 2020.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134936","134936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873821","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied child asylum seekers have been resettled in the UK since the first quarter of 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134937","134937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873822","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that all homosexual citizens in British Overseas Territories have access to the institution of marriage.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134938","134938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873823","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the sleep-in back pay liability for providers in Hampshire.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134928","134928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/874636","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the potential (a) amount in compensation payments by the Metropolitan Police to the victims of Special Branch officers who communicated with organisations and individuals that blacklisted construction workers, (b) number of recipients of such compensation and (c) amount of each individual payment; and what information her Department holds on the Metropolitan Police accounts from which similar compensation payments have been made.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135201","135201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872263","2018-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average net weekly household income was for people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East, (d) London, (e) the South East, (f) England, and (g) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134177","134177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872536","2018-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","Whether his Department plans to publish a position paper on political and diplomatic co-operation with the US after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904602","904602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872537","2018-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","What recent diplomatic steps he has taken to support a negotiated solution to the conflict in Cyprus.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904603","904603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872538","2018-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","What diplomatic steps his Department has taken to support the implementation of the Paris agreement on climate change.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904604","904604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872539","2018-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","What steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequacy of the advice available to mountaineers and explorers visiting remote areas overseas.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904605","904605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872545","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential (a) merits and (b) savings to the public purse of alternatives to the use of detention in monitoring people facing removal from the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134359","134359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872546","2018-04-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many times he has visited (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands since his appointment.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134360","134360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872547","2018-03-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what sentencing guidelines have been put in place to provide for the consideration of the specific needs of transgender people.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134361","134361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872548","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the change in the level of unemployment in (a) Coventry South constituency, (b) Coventry and (c) the West Midlands in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134362","134362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872549","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with OFGEM on Distribution Network Operator margins and profits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134363","134363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872550","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of looked after children who were reported missing from their placement by (a) placement type, (b) placement provider, (c) distance from placing authority in the last 5 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134364","134364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872551","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that colleges advertise in a way which is consistent with his Department;s most recent guidance on the early years workforce, specifically that level 3 learners no longer need GCSE passes in English and Maths in order to work in early years settings.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134365","134365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872552","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding for early years providers; what steps he plans to take as a result of those discusions; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134366","134366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872553","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities have (a) been granted permission to move (i) up to 0.5%, or (ii) in excess of 0.5% of Schools Block funding to High Needs Block funding, (b) been denied permission to move Schools Block funding to High Needs Block funding and (c) made a request to move Schools Block funding to High Needs Block funding but no decision has yet been made; and what criteria his Department uses to determine those applications.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134367","134367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872554","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Capital funding for schools, published in February 2017, what recent estimate his Department has made of the cost of returning all school buildings to satisfactory or better condition.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134368","134368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872555","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to carry out an updated property data survey.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134369","134369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872556","2018-03-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will review the value and purpose of secondary post-mortems.","Biography information for Rachel Maclean","Rachel Maclean","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134370","134370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872557","2018-03-29","Church Commissioners","2018-03-27","To ask the Honourable Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, with reference to news release Church of England’s National Investing Bodies launch policy on investing in Extractive Industries, published by the Church of England in November 2017, what steps the Church Commissioners have taken to promote ethical investment policies in respect of the extractive industries to other faiths.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134371","134371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872558","2018-04-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the number and proportion of school children in England under the age of 16 who have been to the theatre in the twelve months.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134372","134372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872559","2018-04-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of Crown Courts in England which have a copy of the Magistrates Courts' Sentencing Guidelines available in paper format.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134373","134373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872560","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with Preston City Council on external cladding on buildings in Fishwick, Town Centre and St Matthews wards in Preston.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134374","134374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872561","2018-04-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many parents wait (a) less than one month, (b) more than one month and (c) more than three months to see their children at a child contact centre.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134375","134375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872562","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask the Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to ensure (a) retailers and (b) consumers are aware of (i) the ITunes HMRC and (ii) other scams.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134376","134376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872563","2018-03-29","Women and Equalities","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department takes to ensure that those with facial disfigurements are not subject to discrimination on the basis of their appearance and emotional well-being; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134377","134377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872564","2018-03-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the extent of variations in rules and protocols surrounding second post-mortems throughout the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134378","134378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872565","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding the Government has committed to  reduce deaths associated with solvent abuse via each (a) Department, (b) Agency, (c) Local authorities, and (d) voluntary organisation?","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134379","134379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872566","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for its policies of the Office for National Statistics report into solvent abuse, published on 26 March 2018.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134380","134380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872567","2018-03-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of introducing qualified one-way costs shifting for claims against non-medical professionals in line with claims against medical professionals.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134381","134381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872568","2018-03-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits of making adjudication compulsory for claims against non-medical professionals similar to adjudication for construction disputes under the Housing Grants, Construction and Regeneration Act 1996.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134382","134382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872569","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which universities have been affected by overpayments of student loans and maintenance grants to nursing students by the Student Loans Company.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134383","134383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872570","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to reimburse people who received incorrect employment and support allowance payments.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134384","134384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872571","2018-03-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much money his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134385","134385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872572","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 86 of the Ninth Report of Session 2017-19 of the Treasury Select Committee, HC 757, whether the funding arrangements for the 2018-19 academic year take into consideration the increase in the national minimum wage and auto-enrolment into workplace pensions.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134386","134386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872573","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is to make publicly available a complete list of all unregistered publicly-held land.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134387","134387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872574","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release, New action to improve outcomes for children with additional needs, published on 16 March 2018, what the selection process was for the appointment of Edward Timpson to carry out a review into school exclusions.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134388","134388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872575","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last met  her (a) US and (b) Canadian counterparts to discuss cross-border customs checks between those two countries.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134389","134389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872576","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which countries she has visited to observe border control operations.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134390","134390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872577","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the maintenance of animal welfare standards for game birds.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134391","134391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872578","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to undertake a review of the Code of Practice for the Welfare of Gamebirds Reared for Sporting Purposes.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134392","134392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872579","2018-03-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of trends in the number of landlords using (a) licence agreements, and (b) tenancy agreements.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134393","134393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872580","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the statutory provisions for combating fraudulent activities and scams aimed at the elderly.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134394","134394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872581","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with representatives of the devolved administrations on the work of the European Reference Networks after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134395","134395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872582","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in the Rwandan Government on freedom of religion in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134396","134396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872583","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made recent representations to his counterpart in the Pakistani Government on the release of prisoners sentenced to death for blasphemy.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134397","134397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872584","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the EU Special Envoy for Freedom of Religion or Belief on his work.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134398","134398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872585","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals for the Agriculture Bill.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134399","134399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872586","2018-03-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has met with the US-Canada Regulatory Cooperation Council to discuss border templates in the past twelve months.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134400","134400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872587","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what programmes are in place to help students from disadvantaged backgrounds access PhD courses in universities.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134401","134401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872588","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland authorities on the effectiveness of schemes to encourage students from disadvantaged backgrounds to access PhD courses in universities in England.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134402","134402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872589","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passport applications the British embassy in Dublin approved in each of the last three years; and of those applications what proportion were (a) for new and (b) to renew passports.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134403","134403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872590","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has for the UK to conform to the obligations on ballast water management for the control of invasive non-native species necessary to accede to the International Convention for the Control and Management of Ships' Ballast Water and Sediments.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134404","134404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872591","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to give effect to the obligations of the International Convention for the Control and Management of Ships' Ballast Water and Sediments in UK law.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134405","134405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872592","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of introducing a VAT exemption for goods and services required for the (a) repair, (b) maintenance and (c) renovation of Grade II listed buildings used for (i) community and (ii) religious events after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134406","134406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872593","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans the Government has to ratify the International Convention for the Control and Management of Ships' Ballast Water and Sediments.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134407","134407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872594","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the publication of the review of the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134408","134408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872595","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on recommendation 32 of the NHS Cancer Strategy, Achieving World Class Outcomes, on the adoption of immunotherapy treatments.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134409","134409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872596","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what new procedures and operations for treating glaucoma are planned to become available on the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134410","134410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872597","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on implementing recommendation 32 of the NHS Cancer Strategy on the adaptation of immunotheropy treatments.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134411","134411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872598","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2017 to Question 438, on Ministry of Defence: equality, for what reasons the strategic equality objectives were not published in August 2017.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134412","134412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872599","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to Question 127841, on Army: Recruitment, if he will publish (a) a copy of the digital file or a link to each social media asset used in paid campaigns by his Department for Army recruitment advertisements and (b) each platform those assets were published on in (i) 2015-16 and (ii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134413","134413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872600","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many print adverts focused on Army recruitment were placed in regional newspapers by newspaper in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134414","134414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872601","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the external companies contracted to provide services to Army Foundation College Harrogate in each of the last three years; and what budget was allocated to each of those companies in that same period.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134415","134415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872604","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to contribute to the debate arising from the Financial Conduct Authority's discussion paper, Transforming culture in Financial Services, published on 12 March 2018.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134418","134418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872605","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132437, whether the culture of honouring people as martyrs within Palestinian society contributes to regional tensions and extremism and retards progress towards peace between Israel and the Palestinians.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134419","134419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872606","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134420","134420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872607","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much money his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134421","134421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872608","2018-03-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much money his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134422","134422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872609","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134423","134423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872610","2018-03-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much money his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134424","134424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872611","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money her Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134425","134425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872612","2018-03-29","Wales Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much money his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134426","134426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872613","2018-03-29","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much money her Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134427","134427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872614","2018-03-29","Department for International Trade","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much money his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134428","134428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872615","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of automated electronic monitoring of hand gel usage as a means of collecting more accurate data on hand hygiene compliance.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134429","134429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872616","2018-03-29","Cabinet Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women have been diagnosed with triple negative breast cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134430","134430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872617","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from Stamp Duty Land Tax on transfers involving demutualisation of an insurance company in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134431","134431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872618","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from Stamp Duty Land Tax on transfers involving Diplomatic Privileges Relief  in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134432","134432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872619","2018-03-29","Cabinet Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were diagnosed with brain tumours in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134433","134433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872620","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from Stamp Duty Land Tax on transfers involving Collective Enfranchisement by Leaseholders in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134434","134434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872621","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that sufficient funding is available to provide drugs for Alzheimer's disease to patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134435","134435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872622","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from Stamp Duty Land Tax on transfers involving compliance with planning obligations in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134436","134436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872623","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from Stamp Duty Land Tax on transfers involving right to buy transactions in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134437","134437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872624","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from Stamp Duty Land Tax on transfers involving transfers in consequence of reorganisation of parliamentary constituencies in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134438","134438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872625","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from Stamp Duty Land Tax on transfers involving alternative property finance in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134439","134439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872626","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from Stamp Duty Land Tax on transfers involving alternative finance investment bonds in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134440","134440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872627","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from corporation tax on land remediation relief in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134441","134441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872628","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief on NI benefit child dependancy additions in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134442","134442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872629","2018-04-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Defence of 20 March 2018, Official Report [HL], column 20GC, whether the Government plans to publish the National Security Capability Review at Easter 2018.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134443","134443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872630","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received reliefs with tax expenditure and structural components on exemption of British Government securities where owner not ordinarily resident in UK in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134444","134444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872631","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received reliefs with tax expenditure and structural components on marriage allowance in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134445","134445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872632","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Hunting Act 2004 in each police force area in 2017.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134446","134446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872633","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Protection of Badgers Act 1992 in each police force area in 2017.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134447","134447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872634","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Wild Mammals (Protection) Act 1996 in each police force area in 2017.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134448","134448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872635","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax age-related personal allowances in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134449","134449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872636","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133410 on Schools: Finance, what criteria his Department uses for decisions to (a) allow, (b) refuse and (c) partially allow funding transfers.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134450","134450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872637","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cattle movements in England were recorded by the British Cattle Movement Service in each year from 2008 to 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134451","134451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872638","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cattle movements in England direct to slaughter were recorded by the British Cattle Movement Service in each year from 2008 to 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134452","134452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872639","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what contribution the UK has made to the European Union's Global Satellite Navigation System to date.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134453","134453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872640","2018-03-29","House of Commons Commission","2018-03-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what plans the Commission has to improve the (a) availability and (b) speed of Wi-Fi provision on the Parliamentary estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134454","134454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872641","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of requiring claims for a male-female couple to be paid into (a) the woman's bank account and (b) a joint bank account; and what representations her Department received from (i) NGOs and (ii) other organisations on that matter.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134455","134455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872642","2018-03-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the average first year public sector set-up cost for a new resident in any part of England needing social housing and two school places for children.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134456","134456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872643","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average net weekly household income was for people in (a) Coventry South constituency, (b) the West Midlands, (c) London, (d) the South East, (e) England and (f) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134457","134457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872644","2018-04-16","Women and Equalities","2018-03-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what meetings her Department held with LGBT+ organisations in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134458","134458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872645","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the take-up rate for six week post-partum examinations for women in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry was in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134459","134459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872646","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women aged between 60 and 65 are in receipt of the state pension; the level at which that state pension is paid; and how many women aged between 60 and 65 only receive their National Insurance contributions in (a) Coventry and (b) West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134460","134460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872647","2018-03-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 131729, on Ministry of Defence; buildings, what the average annual rent charged for those properties was.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134461","134461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872648","2018-03-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 131729, on Ministry of Defence: Buildings, the location of the accommodation properties owned by his Department which were rented to non-military personnel between January 2016 and January 2017.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134462","134462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872649","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what contribution the UK has made to the Copernicus Programme to date.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134463","134463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872650","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether payments for school efficiency advisers who are already employed as school business professionals will be made to the school that employs them; and whether such advisers will be paid to advise the school that already employs those advisers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134464","134464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872651","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money the UK (a) received from EU Member States for the treatment of EU nationals in the UK on the NHS and (b) paid to EU Member States for the treatment of UK nationals in 2017.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134465","134465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872652","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money the NHS collected in charges for the non-emergency treatment of visitors to the UK in 2017.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134466","134466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872653","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to meet its target for net inward migration.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134467","134467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872654","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish her policy on migration after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134468","134468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872655","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of digital signalling systems on levels of train capacity on the rail network.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134469","134469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872656","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the locations are for his Department's piloting of digital signalling systems on the rail network.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134470","134470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872657","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average age is of public service buses in use in England.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134471","134471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872658","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) pedestrians and (b) cyclists were (i) injured and (ii) killed in accidents with buses in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134472","134472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872659","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) pedestrians and (b) cyclists were (i) injured or (ii) killed in accidents with buses in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134473","134473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872660","2018-03-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to create a Roma integration strategy for after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134474","134474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872661","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of passengers per public bus journey in England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134475","134475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872662","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to improve standards of animal welfare in transit after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134476","134476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872663","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to announce its policy on fishing for after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134477","134477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872664","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to raise awareness of the availability of access to work grants.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134478","134478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872665","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are in receipt of access to work grants by region.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134479","134479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872666","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the cap on access to work grants on progress in reducing the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134480","134480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872667","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she or her predecessors met with representatives of the SCL group or Cambridge Analytica; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134481","134481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872668","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February to Question 128018, on Clinical Priorities Advisory Group, on what date NHS England plans to announce (a) announce the results of the prioritisation process and (b) make funding available for approved medicines policies.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134482","134482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872669","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department or any of it agencies or associated public bodies has had contracts with SCL group or Cambridge Analytica; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134483","134483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872670","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what process was used to forecast budgetary need in order to determine the £25 million annual budget allocation for products undergoing review by the NHS England specialised commissioning prioritisation process.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134484","134484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872671","2018-04-16","Women and Equalities","2018-03-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she or her predecessors met with representatives of the SCL group or Cambridge Analytica.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134485","134485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872672","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the (a) annual budget, (b) total annual expenditure and (c) rationale for how budget allocations were arrived at was for products reviewed by the NHS England specialised commissioning prioritisation process for the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134486","134486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872673","2018-04-16","Women and Equalities","2018-03-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether her Department has had contracts with SCL group or Cambridge Analytica.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134487","134487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872674","2018-04-16","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether her Department or any of its agencies or associated bodies has had contracts with SCL group or Cambridge Analytica.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134488","134488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872675","2018-03-29","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2018-03-27","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2018 to Question 132978, how many of the allegations of electoral fraud concerning the 2017 General Election of which they were made aware were then passed to the relevant police force.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134489","134489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872676","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to update its 2014 Modern Slavery Strategy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134490","134490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872677","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department collects on the number of confirmed victims of trafficking who are subsequently re-trafficked once they have left the National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134491","134491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872678","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Iraqi citizens have been resettled under the (a) Vulnerable Persons Resettlement Scheme and (b) Vulnerable Children's Resettlement Scheme.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134492","134492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872679","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the provision of specialist support for victims of sexual violence resettled under the (a) Vulnerable Persons Resettlement Scheme and (b) Vulnerable Children's Resettlement Scheme.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134493","134493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872680","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Iraq and (b) the Kurdistan Regional Government on protection and support for victims of sexual violence by Daesh.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134494","134494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872681","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an estimate of the number of women and girls held in sexual slavery by Daesh; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134495","134495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872682","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of changing Support for Mortgage Interest payments to a loan for people participating in the Home Ownership for people with Long Term Disabilities (HOLD) scheme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134496","134496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872683","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to inform people participating in the Home Ownership for people with Long Term Disabilities (HOLD) scheme that Support for Mortgage Interest payments will be replaced by a loan; whether letters and phone communications from her Department relating to that change have been specifically tailored to those people; how many of those people have been contacted by her Department about that change; what responses her Department have received from those people on that change; how much notice those people have been given of that change prior to its implementation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134497","134497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872684","2018-04-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment has been made of flood risk in areas along the River Ribble and River Darwen as part of the Preston and South Ribble Flood Management Scheme; what funding has been made available to improve flood defences in affected locations in those areas; what (a) meetings have taken place and (b) correspondence has been exchanged between the Environment Agency and Lancashire County Council to facilitate that work; and when that work will be completed in each of those locations identified as at risk of flooding.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134498","134498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872685","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department spent on facilitating mandatory reconsiderations relating to (a) employment support allowance and (b) personal independence payment claims in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134499","134499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872686","2018-04-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on hearing appeals in Social Security and Child Support Tribunals relating to (a) employment support allowance and (b) personal independence payment claims in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134500","134500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872687","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the HM Courts and Tribunals Service data published by her Department on 8 March 2018 on appeals to the Social Security and Child Support Tribunal, if she will publish the data on (a) employment support allowance and (b) personal independence payment appeals as a proportion of the total number of such claims submitted in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134501","134501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872688","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding has been (a) allocated and (b) paid out through the Cheshire and Merseyside sustainability and transformation partnership to each acute trust in the Cheshire and Merseyside area in (i) 2015-2016, (ii) 2016-2017 and (iii) 2017-2018.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134502","134502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872689","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much revenue funding has been (a) allocated and (b) paid out to the 5-Boroughs Partnership NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 through the Cheshire and Merseyside sustainability and transformation partnership.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134503","134503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872690","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much of the revenue funding that was allocated to the Aintree University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-18 under the Cheshire and Merseyside sustainability and transformation plan has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134504","134504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872691","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the number of clinical commissioning groups which have a body mass index threshold that patients must meet to be eligible for (a) knee and (b) hip replacement surgery.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134505","134505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872692","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the number of clinical commissioning groups which have introduced requirements for smoking cessation for patients to be eligible for (a) knee and (b) hip replacement surgery.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134506","134506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872693","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Clinical Commissioning Groups have a pain threshold that patients must meet to be eligible for (a) knee and (b) hip replacement surgery.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134507","134507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872694","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the number of clinical commissioning groups which have designated (a) knee and (b) hip replacement surgery as a procedure of limited clinical effectiveness.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134508","134508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872695","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much revenue funding has been allocated to the Alder Hey Children’s NHS Foundation Trust in 2017-2018 through the Cheshire and Merseyside sustainability and transformation partnership.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134509","134509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872696","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure compliance with part 9(45)(3) of the National Health Service Commissioning Board and Clinical Commissioning Groups (Responsibilities and Standing Rules) Regulations 2012 by relevant bodies.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134510","134510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872697","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which clinical commissioning groups have (a) met, (b) exceeded and (c) failed to meet the requirement in part 9(45)(3) of the National Health Service Commissioning Board and Clinical Commissioning Groups (Responsibilities and Standing Rules) Regulations 2012 that at the end of each data collection period not less than 92 per cent of the persons falling within paragraph 4 have been waiting to commence treatment for less than 18 weeks in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134511","134511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872698","2018-03-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve conditions for prisoners with mental health problems in prisons in England.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134512","134512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872699","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much was spent on the treatment of mental illness in children and young people in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134513","134513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872700","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times for people requiring cataract surgery.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134514","134514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872701","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of mental health service users have co-morbid (a) alcohol, (b) drug and (c) alcohol and drug dependence.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134515","134515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872702","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to meet the psychological needs of people with (a) inflammatory bowel disease and (b) other long-term health conditions.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134516","134516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872704","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for how many days each hospital in England issued a (a) black and (b) red alert in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134517","134517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872705","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many public relations and communications staff have been hired directly by the NHS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134518","134518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872706","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the NHS budget was spent on public relations consultancy firms in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134519","134519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872707","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nurses left the NHS in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134520","134520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872708","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was for ambulances in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134521","134521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872709","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Bridgewater Community Healthcare NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134522","134522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872710","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Cheshire and Wirral Partnership NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134523","134523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872711","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Clatterbridge Cancer Centre NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134524","134524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872712","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Countess of Chester NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134525","134525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872713","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Liverpool Community Health NHS Trust  for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134526","134526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872714","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Liverpool Heart and Chest Hospital NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134527","134527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872715","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many photovoltaics installations through Green Deal plans provided by Home Energy Lifestyle Management Systems were undertaken in the Motherwell and Wishaw constituency.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134528","134528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872716","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Liverpool Women’s Hospital NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134529","134529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872717","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Mersey Care NHS Foundation Trust  for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134530","134530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872718","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the North West Ambulance Service NHS Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134531","134531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872719","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Royal Liverpool and Broadgreen University Hospitals NHS Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134532","134532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872720","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the St Helens and Knowsley Teaching Hospitals NHS Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134533","134533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872721","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Southport and Ormskirk Hospital NHS Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134534","134534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872722","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Walton Centre NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134535","134535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872723","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134536","134536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872724","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Wirral Community NHS Foundation Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134537","134537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872725","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the Warrington and Halton Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust  for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside STP process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134538","134538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872726","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2018 to Question 125210 on Incinerators: Health Hazards, whether the small area health statistics unit has submitted its papers to peer-reviewed journals.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134539","134539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872727","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment has he made of the accuracy of medical assessments for personal independence payment claimants who have autism.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134540","134540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872728","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications for new GCSE qualifications have been received by Ofqual in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134541","134541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872729","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department provides to specifically help people with autism into work.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134542","134542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872730","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how funding has been allocated by his Department for repairing potholes in York.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134543","134543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872731","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for the Armed Forces of 5 March 2018, Official Report, column 20, what estimate he has made of the cost of moving 150 personnel to act as role models on the frontline for recruiting.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134544","134544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872732","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of full-time equivalent staff employed by Halton Clinical Commissioning Group in (a) 2013, (b) 2015 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134545","134545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872733","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of vacancies there are in Halton Clinical Commisioning Group; and if he will list those vacancies by job title.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134546","134546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872734","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for the Armed Forces of 5 March 2018, Official Report, column 20, what budget will pay the cost of providing 150 personnel to act as role models on the frontline for recruiting.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134547","134547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872735","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people making a claim for employment and support allowance have waited over one year for a medical assessment in (a) Scotland and (b) Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency in the last five years.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134548","134548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872736","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 124308, on Personal Independence Payment: Mental Health, when she plans for the administrative review of the 1.6 million personal independence claims to be completed.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134549","134549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872737","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 March 2018 to Question 133913, on Personal Independence Payment: Visual Impairment, for what reason the Certificate of Visual Impairment is deemed not to provide sufficient information for a comprehensive assessment of functional visual ability.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134550","134550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872738","2018-04-16","Department for International Trade","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of the ML4 rated arms licenses issued for export to Saudi Arabia was utilised in the period (a) 1 March 2013 to 28 February 2015 and (b) and 1 March 2015 to 30 June 2017.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134551","134551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872739","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to receive the security assessment of the takeover bid for GKN by Melrose.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134552","134552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872740","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the latest date is by which he can (a) call in and (b) block the hostile takeover bid for GKN by Melrose.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134553","134553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872741","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral statement of 27 March 2018 on GKN: Proposed Takeover by Melrose, if he will take steps to ensure that the pensions commitment given to him by Melrose is legally enforceable post-offer undertaking; and what discussions he has had with Melrose on that commitment.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134554","134554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872742","2018-03-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent representations the Government has received from the F-35 Joint Program Office on the proposed takeover of GKN by Melrose.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134555","134555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872743","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the merger of Siemens and Alstom (a) on the value for money delivered to Network Rail’s signalling framework contract process and (b) the competitiveness of the wider supply side of the UK rail industry.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134556","134556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872744","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to (a) restructure (b) reorganise and (c) increase the number of staff in his Department in preparation for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134557","134557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872745","2018-03-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2018 to Question 131951, whether his Department has recently reviewed the estimate for the number of jobs that fracking could result in at peak published in the report by Ernst and Young, part-funded by his Department, entitled Getting ready for UK shale gas, published in April 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134558","134558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872746","2018-04-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a ranked list of Departments in order of the proportion of Named Day Questions which they answered on that Named Day excluding holding answers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134559","134559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872747","2018-04-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts in the UK have been visited by Ministers of his Department since the beginning of the 2018.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134560","134560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872748","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for how long the ticket hall at Harrow and Wealdstone station will be closed for repair; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134561","134561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872749","2018-03-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of new registrations with HM Land Registry were registered within the 25 day period in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134562","134562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872750","2018-04-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that perpetrators of child sexual abuse have access to rehabilitative programmes.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134563","134563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872751","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of illegal or unregistered schools identified by his Department and Ofsted have a religious basis.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134564","134564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872752","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of providing sanitary products to girls in receipt of free school meals.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134565","134565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872753","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps her Department has taken to ensure the identification of victims of human trafficking among (a) migrant and (b) asylum seeking children.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134566","134566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872754","2018-03-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that HM Land Registry completes new registrations within the 25 day turnaround period.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134567","134567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872755","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the (a) statutory powers of the police to pursue crimes involving online child abuse images and (b) the funding available to police to pursue those crimes.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134568","134568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872756","2018-03-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of changing the Ogden rate on insurance premiums paid by businesses.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134569","134569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872757","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the level of availability of specialist support for victims of sexual violence resettled under the (a) Syrian Vulnerable Persons Resettlement Scheme and (b) Vulnerable Children's Resettlement Scheme.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134570","134570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872758","2018-04-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will review the long-term effect of the Homelessness Reduction Act 2017 periodically after that Act comes into force in April 2017.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134571","134571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872759","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 March to Question 133321 on tax allowances, which tax reliefs are currently subject to a sunset clause.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134572","134572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872760","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which tax reliefs have expired as a result of a sunset clause since 2010.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134573","134573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872761","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of electric shock collars in use on dogs.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134574","134574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872762","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of medical procedures that are being provided in France due to limited hospital capacity in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134575","134575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872763","2018-03-29","Department for International Development","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of UK aid to Pakistan that has been lost to corruption in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134576","134576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872764","2018-04-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the proposed environmental mitigation measures in the application from Premier Oil to develop the Sea Lion oil field in the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134577","134577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872765","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle delays on TfL Rail services.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134578","134578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872766","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much compensation Network Rail has paid to train operating companies in (a) 2014, (b) 2015, (c) 2016 and (d) 2017; and if he will publish that same information by train operating company.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134579","134579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872767","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings his Department held with representatives of the rail industry prior to the announcement that diesel traction would be withdrawn from the rail network in 2040.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134580","134580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872768","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nursing places have been allocated for the year 2018-19.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134581","134581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872769","2018-03-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has a policy to attract the television and film industry to work in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134582","134582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872770","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what correspondence his Department had with the UK Commissioner to the EU on the appointment of Professor Dr Martin Selmayr as Secretary General of the European Commission prior to that appointment.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134583","134583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872771","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of (a) sexual assault and (b) rape were reported in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134584","134584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872772","2018-03-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure there are no derelict houses in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134585","134585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872773","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to support the removal of graffiti tagging to clean up (a) towns and (b) cities in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134586","134586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872774","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department plans to take steps to tackle housing benefit (a) fraud and (b) overpayments in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134587","134587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872775","2018-03-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if the Government will make an assessment of whether the appointment of Professor Dr Martin Selmayr as Secretary General of the European Commission was done through professional and fair recruitment and selection procedures.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134588","134588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872776","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have Crohn's disease.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134589","134589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872777","2018-03-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to commemorate the centenary of the end of the First World War.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134590","134590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872778","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of children who receive free school transport.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134591","134591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872779","2018-03-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of exiting the EU on UK citizens with properties in one of the 27 remaining EU Member States.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134592","134592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872780","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many farmers received the Single Farm Payment in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134593","134593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872781","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many recycling centres are there in (a) England and (b) Wales.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134594","134594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872782","2018-03-29","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to introduce electric-powered trains in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134595","134595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872783","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Permanent Secretary before the Committee of Public Accounts on 1 March 2017 HC 957, Q135  how many contracts of value over £100m awarded since the 2015 SDSR have taken tax revenues into account as an award criteria; and what the weighting was in each of those contracts.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134596","134596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872784","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of his Department's (a) resources and (b) expertise to administer (i) multiple and (ii) interrelated contracts in the event that the maritime support delivery framework is broken up into smaller contracts under the future maritime support strategy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134597","134597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872785","2018-04-16","Treasury","2018-03-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that the National Infrastructure Commission assesses the potential effect of proposals for infrastructure building on biodiversity.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134598","134598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872786","2018-03-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with (a) the UK’s European Commissioner and (b) the European Commissioner for Climate Action & Energy, on the Energy Package being considered in Trilogues by the European Union.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134599","134599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872787","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that any repatriation of Rohingya refugees to Myanmar includes (a) guarantees on the physical and legal safety of returnees and (b) UNHCR supervision.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134600","134600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872788","2018-03-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to support at the European Council for the Energy Union the EU-level (a) 35 per cent renewable energy and (b) 35 per cent energy efficiency target.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134601","134601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872789","2018-03-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to introduce a legal framework after the UK has left the EU that will ensure UK restructuring and insolvency practitioners will be able to practice across the EU.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134602","134602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872790","2018-03-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the most recent estimate is of the number of fracking wells that will be in place by 2025.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134603","134603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872791","2018-03-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what projection he has made of the contribution of gas fracking to the UK’s energy mix by (a) 2025 and (b) 2030.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134604","134604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872792","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people who were detained under the Mental Health Act 1983 died in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134605","134605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872793","2018-04-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many deaths in prison custody occurred in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134606","134606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872794","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.11 of the Migration Advisory Committee’s report of the 27 March 2018, EEA-workers in the UK labour market: Interim Update, what steps he plans to take to ensure that there is not a shortage of academics available to teach STEM subjects after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134607","134607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872795","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people died in (a) police custody and (b) immigration removal centres in each year since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134608","134608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872796","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.11 of the Migration Advisory Committee’s report of the 27 March 2018, EEA-workers in the UK labour market: Interim Update, what discussions he has had with the (a) Home Secretary and (b) Secretary of State for the Department for Exiting the European Union on universities being able to continue to recruit academics to teach STEM subjects after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134609","134609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872797","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 1.8 of the Migration Advisory Committee’s report of 27 March 2018, EEA-workers in the UK labour market: Interim Update, what steps he plans to take to address employers' concerns that without employing migrants, they would not be able to address the skill shortages they are currently facing.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134610","134610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872798","2018-04-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Northern Health Science Alliance on delivering a northern life sciences sector deal.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134611","134611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872799","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of predicted skills shortages in each sector as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134612","134612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872800","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving test stations have closed in each constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134613","134613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872801","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated from the public purse to the Careers and Enterprise Company for (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18 and (c) 2018-19.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134614","134614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872802","2018-04-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many railway stations (a) opened and (b) closed in each constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134615","134615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872803","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on the implementation of his Department's proposals for reform of death certification by April 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134616","134616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872804","2018-04-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish the Heritage Action Zones designated by Heritage Lottery Fund in each constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134617","134617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872805","2018-03-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the proposed timetable is for the implementation of the Northumberland Local Plan; and what funding his Department has allocated to ensure that implementation.","Biography information for Mr Ronnie Campbell","Mr Ronnie Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134618","134618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872806","2018-04-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) theatres and (b) cinemas have closed in each constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134619","134619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872807","2018-04-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many libraries have closed in each constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134620","134620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872808","2018-03-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many public swimming pools have closed in each constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134621","134621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872809","2018-03-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of providing support services to Northumberland County Council in support of the Northumberland Local Plan; and where that funding will come from.","Biography information for Mr Ronnie Campbell","Mr Ronnie Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134622","134622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872810","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many women have had to wait for longer than two weeks from their initial appointment for an abortion in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134623","134623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872811","2018-04-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the availability of appointments for abortions in NHS hospital settings for women with complex medical conditions.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134624","134624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872812","2018-03-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from Northumberland County Council on the Northumberland Local Plan.","Biography information for Mr Ronnie Campbell","Mr Ronnie Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134625","134625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872813","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will extend the two-year validity visa pilot scheme offered to Chinese nationals to Indian nationals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134626","134626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872814","2018-03-29","Cabinet Office","2018-03-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will request that the Office for National Statistics include in the faiths section of the next census a box specifically for those who are Jains to register their faith; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134627","134627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872815","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Childcare and early education funding in London Report for Greater London Authority, March 2018, published by the Mayor of London and the Family and Childcare Trust on 27 March 2018, if he will make an assessment of the implications for this policy on funding levels for 30 hours of funded childcare in London as a result of the findings in that report.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134628","134628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872816","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 6 December 2017, HCWS 317, Government asset sale and pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133614, on Student: Loans, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of plan 1 student loans held by the Government that will not be repaid.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134629","134629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872817","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the net present value of the student loan book.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134630","134630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872818","2018-04-16","Department for Education","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of childcare and early education funding on the number of (a) childminders and (b) nurseries between 31 August and 31 December 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134631","134631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872819","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on procuring Type 31e frigates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134632","134632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872820","2018-04-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on procuring fleet support ships for the Royal Fleet Auxiliary; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134633","134633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872821","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions her Department has had with (a) Ofcom and (b) the Phone-paid Services Authority on call connection service access to the helplines her Department provides; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134634","134634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872822","2018-04-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps her Department has taken to ensure that (a) the gov.uk website and (b) internet providers advertise the correct information on the cost of calls to her Department's helplines; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134635","134635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/868468","2018-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the satisfaction levels of claimants during the tribunal stage of the Personal Independence Payments claims process in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133688","133688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/871700","2018-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on continued foreign policy co-operation after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904597","904597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/871710","2018-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-26","What steps the Government is taking to help young people with disabilities into work.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904565","904565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/871711","2018-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-26","What steps her Department is taking to strengthen families.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904566","904566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/871712","2018-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-26","What steps she is taking to ensure that universal credit supports people in progressing at work and increasing their earnings.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904567","904567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872218","2018-03-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to protect the independence of regional press organisations.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134132","134132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872219","2018-03-28","Department for Transport","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department plans to take to use updated technology to reduce the evasion of tolls and penalty charge notices by foreign registered commercial vehicles; and whether he has plans to refuse entry to the UK to those who have evaded such charges.","Biography information for Andrew Lewer","Andrew Lewer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134133","134133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872220","2018-03-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to ensure that the Chief Officer of Warrington Care Commissioning Group spending 50 per cent of his time as acting head of Halton clinical commissioning group does not detrimentally affect his management of Warrington Care Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134134","134134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872221","2018-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131390, who the person was who made the decision to appoint the Chief Officer of Warrington clinical commissioning group as the acting, interim, Chief Officer of Halton clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134135","134135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872222","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps are being taken to ensure that (a) academies and (b) free schools admit a reasonable proportion of children with disabilities and special needs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134136","134136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872223","2018-03-28","Department for Education","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on (a) short-skills sectors of setting apprenticeship bands which are lower than the average costing proposals submitted and (b) the expected quality of apprenticeships delivered against the standards and on training providers of those bands being so set lower.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134137","134137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872224","2018-03-28","Home Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Flag it up campaign; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134138","134138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872225","2018-03-28","Home Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many corporate prosecutions there have been for money laundering under s327 of the Proceeds of Crime Act of 2002.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134139","134139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872226","2018-03-28","Home Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken to reduce the amount of suspicious wealth owned by people resident in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134140","134140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872227","2018-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Sino-British Joint Declaration, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the change to the national anthem law in Hong Kong on the operation of British businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134141","134141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872228","2018-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure greater protection for consumers when (a) structural and (b) other problems occur with new build homes.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134142","134142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872229","2018-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequacy of redress arrangements for consumers when (a) structural and (b) other problems occur with new build homes.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134143","134143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872230","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Ofsted plans to refer to the Gatsby Foundation’s eight benchmarks for good careers advice when inspecting schools and colleges.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134144","134144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872231","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether its is planned to measure and report on the progress of schools against the Gatsby Foundation’s eight benchmarks for good careers advice.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134145","134145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872232","2018-03-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking to negotiate a UK-EU withdrawal agreement which ensures that after the implementation period the UK does not trade control over its fisheries for preferential access to the EU internal market for UK financial services.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134146","134146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872233","2018-03-28","Treasury","2018-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the policy of the Inland Revenue on street and other similar markets not attracting VAT has changed; and whether the Government has plans for such changes.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134147","134147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872234","2018-03-28","Treasury","2018-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Upper Tax Tribunal decision that VAT (a) is due on the hire of pitches at organised events and (b) liability goes back up to four years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134148","134148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872235","2018-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the criteria used to designate housing as affordable for identifying real affordability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134149","134149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872236","2018-03-29","Home Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department's policy on the contract to print UK passports included local value for the North East.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134150","134150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872237","2018-03-29","Cabinet Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent steps he is taking to that ensure public services are protected against cyber-attacks.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134151","134151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872238","2018-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) injuries and (b) deaths caused to (i) farmed animals and (ii) wild animals by (A) plastic and (B) other forms of litter.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134152","134152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872239","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2018 to Question 132796, on Children: Day Care, if he will ensure that the Government makes available further opportunities for hon. Members to voice concerns on the planned closure of Childcare Vouchers to new applicants.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134153","134153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872240","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many support for mortgage interest claimants in Scotland have been contacted by (a) letter and (b) telephone.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134154","134154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872241","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions she has had in respect of staff at her Department's office in Kirkcaldy; and what the outcome of those discussions has been.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134155","134155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872242","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the compatibility with the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights of proposed National Security Legislation in Hong Kong; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134156","134156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872243","2018-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of doctors who have been awarded bonuses by clinical commissioning groups limiting the number of patients they refer to hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134157","134157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872244","2018-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of doctors who have been awarded bonuses by clinical commissioning groups for limiting the number of patients they refer for cancer screening; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134158","134158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872245","2018-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of the recommendation in the Brain Tumour Charity’s report entitled The Price You Pay, published in March 2018, on including brain tumours in the list of health conditions requiring additional support in the personal independence payment assessment guide.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134159","134159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872246","2018-03-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for the village of Harewood in Elmet and Rothwell constituency to be included in the roll-out of superfast broadband; and what is policy is on BT Retail advertising broadband speeds well in excess of those actually available to customers.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134160","134160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872247","2018-03-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on the revenue of the entertainment and sports industries of consumers paying higher prices for tickets purchased through secondary sites and less on further tickets and purchases at music and sports venues.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134161","134161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872248","2018-03-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the steps taken by the Advertising Standards Authority as a result of its investigation into the big four secondary ticketing websites; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134162","134162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872249","2018-03-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) frequency and (b) viability of large-scale automated ticket reselling of the (a) Digital Economy Act 2017 and (b) other recent steps the Government has taken.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134163","134163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872250","2018-03-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he consulted the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs before concluding the deal on fisheries on 19 March 2018.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134164","134164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872251","2018-03-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he consulted the Prime Minister before concluding the deal on fisheries on 19 March 2018.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134165","134165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872252","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2018 to Question 131814, on Universal Credit: Scotland, on what date his Department held early discussions with the Scottish Government on the split payment policy for universal credit; whether these discussions took the form of a meeting; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134166","134166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872253","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2018 to Question 131814, on Universal Credit: Scotland, what information the Scottish Government has provided to her Department on its split payment policy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134167","134167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872254","2018-03-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that women are able to control the way in which benefits that are paid to them as an individual are spent.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134168","134168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872255","2018-03-28","Department for Education","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that kinship carers receive adequate financial support.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134169","134169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872256","2018-03-29","Department for Education","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Government's consultation on the guidance on home education for parents and local authorities is planned to begin; how long that consultation is planned to last; and what the timetable is for the Government to respond to that consultation.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134170","134170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872257","2018-03-29","Cabinet Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the responses to his Department's consultation, A democracy that works for everyone: British citizens overseas, published on 7 October 2016.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134171","134171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872258","2018-03-29","Treasury","2018-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to recoup money from employers who have paid into disguised remuneration schemes.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134172","134172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872259","2018-03-28","Department for Education","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the long-term (a) education, (b) employment, (c) training, (d) housing and (e) health outcomes of children who are classified as in need at the age of (a) 16 and (b) 17.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134173","134173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872260","2018-03-28","Treasury","2018-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have registered trusts with the Trusts Registration Service in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134174","134174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872261","2018-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the effect of shale gas extraction on the (a) farming and (b) tourism industry.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134175","134175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872262","2018-03-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the barriers to the implementation of UN Security Council resolution 2401 since the adoption of that resolution on 5 March 2018.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134176","134176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872264","2018-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the UN Security Council to ensure that the UN peacekeeping mission to Western Sahara is given a mandate to monitor and report on human rights in Western Sahara.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134178","134178"
