"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12572","2013-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of cases brought to court on behalf of the British Transport Police in the last three years were against people with a disability.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167153","167153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12573","2013-09-03","Home Office","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications have been (a) made and (b) granted under the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 for the civil use of drones for the purposes of communication interception and covert surveillance; what assessment she has made of the extent to which drones are used in police intelligence work; what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the current regulatory framework for the civil use of drones; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167159","167159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12574","2013-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the May 2013 Resolution by the UN Commission on Crime Prevention and Criminal Justice on the categorisation of wildlife and forest crime as a serious form of organised crime, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on the utilisation of the Instrument for Stability to tackle wildlife trafficking; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167160","167160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12575","2013-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his (a) EU and (b) G8 counterparts on tackling wildlife trafficking; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167162","167162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12576","2013-09-03","Department of Health","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who requested the updated study on meningococcal vaccines referred to on page 22 of the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation's minutes from 12 June 2013; and on what basis that request was made.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167179","167179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12577","2013-09-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many fracking licence applications have been (a) received, (b) granted and (c) refused for exploratory hydraulic fracturing in (i) North West Norfolk constituency, (ii) Norfolk and (iii) the UK to date.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167185","167185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12578","2013-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the process is for dealing with Reserve Forces applications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Gray","Mr James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167197","167197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12579","2013-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions were made under the Offences Against the Person Act 1861 where a dog was used as a weapon in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167218","167218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12580","2013-09-04","Department for Education","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to appoint a new Schools Commissioner.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167457","167457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12581","2013-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 21 July 2010, Official Report, column 322W, on courts: Sunderland, what the cost was of (a) commissioning architects and (b) buying land for the redevelopment of Sunderland City Court.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167225","167225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12582","2013-09-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has conducted any research into the number of people on zero-hours contracts separately from that carried out by the Office for National Statistics; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167257","167257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12583","2013-09-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his Department's Notice to Exporters 2013-18: Important Changes to the Strategic Export Control Transparency Initiative, for what reason exporters will not be required to (a) report the rating or goods description and (b) provide control list classifications or descriptions of the items exported.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167265","167265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12584","2013-09-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on the availability of public toilets of the reduced resources made available to local authorities since May 2010; and what steps he is taking to restore public conveniences closed during this period.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167233","167233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12585","2013-09-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues in the Department of Transport about the loss of business rates to local authorities in areas where the proposed High Speed 2 route would have an adverse effect on or lead to the closure of existing businesses.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167469","167469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12586","2013-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of driving whilst disqualified had been convicted of the same offence within the previous 10 years in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167269","167269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12587","2013-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people given a custodial sentence for driving whilst disqualified had been convicted of the same offence within the previous 10 years in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167270","167270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12588","2013-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been given multiple custodial sentences for driving whilst disqualified since 2000.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167271","167271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12589","2013-09-03","Department for Education","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he expects to announce the calculation of the return funds to local authorities following the 2012-13 top-slicing for academies; and when local authorities will receive this payment.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167279","167279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12590","2013-09-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) telephone calls, (b) web chats, (c) texts and (d) e-mails from young people aged 13 to 18 years old have been handled by the National Careers Service in each month since April 2012.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167474","167474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12591","2013-09-03","Department of Health","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements he plans to put in place to ensure that new ovarian cancer patients who could benefit from treatments currently available on the Cancer Drugs Fund will be able to access appropriate treatments from 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167292","167292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12592","2013-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which senior officials of his Department are entitled to use the Government Car Service.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167295","167295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12593","2013-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he next plans to visit RAF Spadeadam.","Biography information for Guy Opperman","Guy Opperman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167478","167478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12594","2013-09-03","Department of Health","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements he plans to put in place to ensure that ovarian cancer patients currently receiving treatment through the Cancer Drugs Fund will continue to be able to access treatment from 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167291","167291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12595","2013-09-03","Home Office","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the preparedness of local authorities for implementation of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Kelly","Chris Kelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167374","167374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12596","2013-09-03","Department for Education","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Table 3 in his Department's publication, GCSE and equivalent attainment by pupil characteristics in England: 2011 to 2012, if he will further disaggregate those results by ethnicity from the broad categories of ethnicity listed at (a) local authority and (b) Government Office Region level.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167449","167449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12597","2013-09-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who will provide the apprenticeships funded by the Skills Funding Agency in 2013 in (a) Sheffield, (b) Doncaster, (c) Bansley and (d) Rotherham.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167490","167490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12598","2013-09-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the London 2012 Paralympics legacy.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167563","167563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12599","2013-09-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the average number of hours worked per week by people on zero-hours contracts.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167565","167565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12600","2013-09-03","Department of Health","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many quick service restaurant chains have endorsed public health responsibility deals; which such chains have committed to deals that deliver a healthier product to consumers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167568","167568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12601","2013-09-03","Department for International Development","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on the education of girls in Afghanistan of the decision by USAID not to fund Aid Afghanistan for Education; whether she has considered funding such activity; and what communications her Department has received from the Afghanistan Technical Vocational Institute in respect of the funding for girls' education in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167561","167561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12602","2013-09-03","Department for International Development","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the length of the average stay in a refugee camp.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167582","167582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12603","2013-09-03","Home Office","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce a departmental service level agreement covering responses by Ministers of her Department to correspondence from hon. Members.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167584","167584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12604","2013-09-03","Department for Transport","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent research he has commissioned on the role played by old tyres in public service vehicle crashes.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167577","167577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12605","2013-09-03","HM Treasury","2013-08-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the annual revenue forgone to HM Revenue and Customs as a result of the operation of the secondary ticketing market.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167591","167591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12606","2013-09-03","Home Office","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many convicted murderers have gone on to murder again following their release in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167617","167617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12607","2013-09-03","HM Treasury","2013-08-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the minimum requirements are for public access to properties to qualify for estate duty exemption.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167635","167635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12608","2013-09-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether he plans to discuss the Fifth Report from the Energy and Climate Change Committee on Energy Prices, Profits and Poverty, HC 108, with (a) the big six energy companies, (b) smaller energy suppliers and (c) Ofgem before making his response to that report.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167669","167669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12609","2013-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2013, Official Report, column 1280W, on reserve services, what changes have been made to the contract procedures followed by his Department as a result of lessons learned from the abandonment of the bidding process for the SAR-H competition in 2010; and whether he has concluded that any officials in his Department at the time have any responsibility for the improper release of information.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167651","167651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12655","2013-09-04","Department of Health","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date licences were granted for horse slaughter to the five UK abattoirs which were in possession of such licences in January 2013.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167455","167455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12656","2013-09-04","Department for International Development","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps he has taken to ensure the preservation of women's rights and young girls' access to education in Afghanistan once UK armed forces leave that country.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167421","167421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12657","2013-09-03","Department of Health","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of retailed chickens tested positive for (a) campylobacter and (b) salmonella in the most recent survey of chicken on retail sale by the Food Standards Agency.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167314","167314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12658","2013-09-03","Department of Health","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the extension of the length of animal feeding studies designed to establish genetically-modified organism toxicity or safety.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167318","167318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12659","2013-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received a cold weather payment in (a) February 2013 and (b) March 2013 in (i) the Bishopton weather station area, (ii) Scotland and (iii) the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167203","167203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12660","2013-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he had made of the reasons for the recent fall in the number of people receiving rewards for work-related injuries and diseases.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167251","167251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12661","2013-09-04","HM Treasury","2013-08-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Prime Minister's policy is on the introduction of EU regulation to collect beneficial ownership information on companies and to make such information public; and what the Prime Minister's policy is on including such requirements in the anti-money laundering directives.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167463","167463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12662","2013-09-03","HM Treasury","2013-08-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether UK civil servants working for EU institutions pay income tax at the same level as other UK citizens.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167258","167258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12663","2013-09-03","HM Treasury","2013-08-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether members of the European Parliament representing constituencies in the UK pay income tax at the same level as other UK citizens.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167259","167259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12664","2013-09-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many of the UK's arms export licences to Egypt have been revoked, suspended or reviewed since 3 July 2013; how many such licences still stand; and if he will provide a list of all military equipment sold to Egypt under a UK arms export licence since 13 February 2011, by (a) type of equipment and (b) the Egyptian body receiving it.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167274","167274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12665","2013-09-03","Department for Transport","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Department for Transport Statistics: Table NTS9904 - Average distance travelled by mode, region and area type: Great Britain, 2011-12, what estimate he has made of the number of miles per person per year in Scotland for each of the means of transport under the heading of other public transport.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167267","167267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12666","2013-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average cost to Government departments of responding to each Freedom of Information Act request.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167477","167477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12667","2013-09-03","Home Office","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to ratify the Council of Europe's Istanbul Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence against Women and Domestic Violence.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167367","167367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12668","2013-09-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to (a) reduce the number of threatening messages and harassment of women on social media platforms and (b) ensure that all platforms improve the ease of reporting such abuse; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167348","167348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12669","2013-09-03","HM Treasury","2013-08-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what sum in wage arrears was identified as a result of complaints to HM Revenue and Customs on payment of wages below the national minimum wage in (a) the UK and (b) London in each year since 1998-99.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167505","167505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12670","2013-09-03","HM Treasury","2013-08-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his Ministerial colleagues on the refurbishment of Frogmore House.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167546","167546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12671","2013-09-03","HM Treasury","2013-08-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations his Department has received on the refurbishment of Frogmore House.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167547","167547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12672","2013-09-03","Department for Education","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which visits in an official capacity (a) he and (b) his Ministerial colleagues made to a youth club before the responsibility for youth services was transferred to the Cabinet Office.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167560","167560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12673","2013-09-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with telecommunications companies on their telephone sales policies.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167592","167592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12674","2013-09-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the practice of telephone selling by telecommunications companies.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167593","167593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12675","2013-09-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the Government's policy is on requiring UK-based companies to produce publicly-available financial reports on a country-by-country basis (a) as a UK-only initiative, (b) as a result of EU requirements and (c) as part of a wider international initiative.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167652","167652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12025","2013-09-04","Cabinet Office","2013-08-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, What assessment he has made of the National Audit Office report, Charges for customer telephone lines, HC 541, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 900025","900025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/13125","2013-09-09","Northern Ireland Office","2013-08-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, What input she plans to have to the Haass talks.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 900157","900157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10065","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the Government will announce the findings of its further work to understand the implications of decentralisation of planning fees.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167065","167065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10066","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made on its commitment to consider whether the scope of fee chargeable applications should be widened to potentially include allowing local authorities to charge for services on a cost recovery basis which do not currently require a fee as set out in the Proposals for changes to planning application fees in England - Summary of responses.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167076","167076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10067","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made in respect of its work with the Local Government Association to further understand the implications of the decentralisation of planning fees across all authorities as set out in his Department's document on Proposals for changes to planning application fees in England - Summary of responses.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167077","167077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10128","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the number of staff currently working in the NHS in England who had been engaged by NHS bodies (a) through personal service companies and (b) as permanent members of staff before having their contract of employment terminated and then being re-employed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166881","166881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10129","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much of the £539.6 million announced by his Department on 27 June 2013 for the North East Local Enterprise Partnership for 2014 to 2020 will be allocated to (a) Northumberland, (b) Tyne and Wear and (c) County Durham; and if he will estimate how much funding each of these areas would have received if the EU formula for the allocation of funding had been implemented.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166882","166882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10253","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of whether an increase of 0.8 degrees celsius in average global temperatures is statistically significant.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166941","166941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10254","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received about the welfare of Christians living in rebel-held areas of Syria.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166942","166942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10255","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the costs to UK hospitals of complying with climate change legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166943","166943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10256","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the UK of complying with the Climate Change Act 2008.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166945","166945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10257","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, further to his letter to the hon. Member for Monmouth, what progress his Department has made on locating the school attended by Adil Rashid.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166926","166926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10258","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the armed forces are being required to undertake any measures to reduce carbon emissions.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166927","166927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10259","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimates his Department were given in 2008 of the expected average global temperature in 2013.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166928","166928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10260","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with members of the free Syrian Army about the welfare of Christians living in rebel-held areas of Syria.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166930","166930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10261","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether British civil servants seconded to the EU or to EU bodies pay tax at the same level as other British citizens.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166896","166896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10262","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimates his Department has been given by the Met Office of the expected average global temperature in 2018.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167028","167028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10475","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many single parents in each branch of the armed forces have been promoted in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166886","166886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10476","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the armed forces are single parents.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166887","166887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10477","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what cap he will set on the level of reservist award in non-specialist roles.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166888","166888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10782","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the public purse of reducing VAT to five per cent on all hospitality, rooms, food and alcohol.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167052","167052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10865","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Scottish congenital cardiac surgery unit will be included in the new review of congenital cardiac care.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166907","166907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10866","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the new review of congenital cardiac care will commence.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166908","166908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10867","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the new review of  congenital cardiac care will consider quality of care through the entire process of child heart surgery.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166909","166909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10868","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what role (a) patients, (b) the public and (c) other stakeholders will have in the new review of congenital cardiac care.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166910","166910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11875","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether UK work permit legislation applies to non-EEA seafarers offered work on a vessel registered under a flag of convenience working on routes between ports in the UK and Ireland.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166922","166922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11876","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the national minimum wage applies to non-EEA seafarers employed on a commercial passenger vessel working on routes between ports in the UK and Ireland.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166923","166923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11877","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions officials in his Department have had with their counterparts in Transport Scotland regarding his Department's policies on (a) procurement, (b) service levels, (c) passenger fares and (d) concessionary fare schemes in the ferries sector; and whether such meetings take place on a regular basis.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166924","166924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12030","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason agricultural reservoirs were not included within the Annual Investment Allowance scheme.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166912","166912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12031","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when each Minister in his Department has met the Chairman of the Armed Forces Parliamentary Scheme since May 2010; and what issues were discussed at each such meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166913","166913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12032","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Armed Forces Parliamentary Scheme in informing hon. and right hon. Members of both Houses of the work of Armed Forces.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166914","166914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12033","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what purpose officials based at the British High Commission in Kuala Lumpur monitored the 1993-96 Malaysian police investigation into the killings at Batang Kali, Malaya in December 1948.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166893","166893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12034","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve prisoners' awareness of hepatitis C and the testing and treatments available to prisoners.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166903","166903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12035","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the budget per pupil for each school in England before and after the introduction of the pupil premium.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166971","166971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12036","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps she is taking to ensure the measures put in place by the Health Act 2006 and Smoke-Free Regulations are being effectively enforced in shisha bars.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167005","167005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12037","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of families receiving the current childcare vouchers scheme which will not be eligible for the new tax free childcare scheme in 2015 due to their children being over the age of five.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166995","166995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12038","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Prime Minister's policy is towards the development of the social dimension of Economic and Monetary Union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Brian Binley","Mr Brian Binley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166955","166955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12039","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his latest estimate is of the number of school age pupils who have been prescribed drugs for (a) depression, (b) behaviour control and (c) mental health problems in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166988","166988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12040","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking following the murder of Drummer Lee Rigby in Woolwich on tackling far right extremism and groups such as the English Defence League.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167009","167009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12041","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will implement the enforcement restriction order, as provided for under Part 6A of the Tribunals, Courts and Enforcement Act 2007.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167038","167038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12042","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on returns to creditors across all debt resolution procedures which may occur if the simple IVA were to be introduced.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167040","167040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12043","2013-09-02","Attorney General","2013-07-18","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2013, Official Report, column 512W, on Crown Prosecution Service, what recent discussions he has had on the work of the Crown Prosecution Service.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167054","167054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12044","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent progress he has made on plans to move to a fairer schools funding formula before 2015.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167064","167064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12045","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average gross weekly earnings of full-time employed (a) men and (b) women in the UK in each year since 1997 were in cash terms.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167089","167089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12651","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) objectives, (b) project partners, (c) intended beneficiaries and (d) allocated funding from his Department is of the Security and Judicial Reform Project in Nepal; and how his Department plans to measure the impact of that project.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166894","166894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12654","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports her Department has received on the work being undertaken by the Hadassah Hospital in support of the Palestinian healthcare system; and if her Department will provide support to extend such medical programmes for the purpose of encouraging peaceful coexistence.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167061","167061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/281","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value of UK exports to Israel was in 2012.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166879","166879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/332","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value of bilateral trade between the UK and Israel was in 2012.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166880","166880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether holders of UK travel documents who are not UK citizens require a visa to visit the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166875","166875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/354","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, under what circumstances an individual who holds a permanently unspent criminal conviction is allowed to become a British citizen.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166878","166878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/356","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Article 24(2) of Directive 2004/38/EC, for what reasons EU nationals residing in the UK as jobseekers are allowed to access income-based jobseeker's allowance, housing benefit and council tax benefit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166906","166906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/358","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken in response to the recent attacks on the Hazara people in Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166931","166931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/359","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has allocated funding in its aid budget for supporting victims of terrorism in Quetta, Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166932","166932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/360","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has attached conditions to UK bilateral aid to Pakistan that would protect the human rights of (a) the Hazaras and (b) other persecuted groups in  Quetta.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166933","166933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/361","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Pakistan government regarding the terrorist group Lashkar-e-Jhangvi.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166934","166934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/362","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received concerning the murder of four Hazara traders on the Masjid Road in Quetta, Pakistan on 15 July 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166935","166935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/363","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on the recent suicide bomb attack on a mosque in Hazara Town, Quetta, Pakistan on 30 June 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166936","166936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/364","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when representatives of the Government last met leaders of the Hazara community in Quetta, Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166937","166937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/365","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the UN Rapporteur on Human Rights regarding the recent attacks on the Hazara community in Quetta, Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166938","166938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/366","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of Hazara people murdered in Quetta, Pakistan in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166939","166939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/367","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when representatives of the Government last met representatives from the Pakistan government to discuss the recent attacks on Hazara people in Quetta.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166940","166940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/368","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of hepatitis C in prisons in England.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166904","166904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/369","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department has provided for Family Information Services in each of the last four years; and what such funding it plans to provide in 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167002","167002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/370","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the role of grandparents and other extended family members in providing informal childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167003","167003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/371","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to improve public awareness about how to access funding for new business ideas.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166993","166993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/372","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to consult on the eligibility of free school meals for children whose parents will be in receipt of universal credit ahead of the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166994","166994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/373","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the health implications of smoking a shisha pipe compared to a cigarette.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167004","167004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/374","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to measure the (a) presence of and (b) risk to health from second hand smoke to underage children in shisha bars.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167006","167006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/375","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funds have been set aside by HM Revenue and Customs to begin preliminary work on the operation of the new tax free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166996","166996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/376","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what evidential basis he made the decision to set the duration of the proposed Contracts for Differences for renewable energy at 15 years; and if he will publish the analysis produced in support of this decision.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166895","166895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/377","2013-09-02","Women and Equalities","2013-07-18","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many creditors of her Department owed more than £10,000 which remained unpaid after (a) 30 days, (b) 45 days, (c) 60 days, (d) 75 days and (e) more than 90 days in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166897","166897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/378","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason NHS England stopped funding patients for gamma knife treatment at the National Hospital for Neurology and neurosurgery at University College London Hospital but will fund such treatment at private hospitals in London.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166898","166898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/379","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much is being budgeted for the design of the IT system for the tax free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166997","166997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/380","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what projections his Department has made of the cost of the overheads associated with the new tax free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166998","166998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will carry out an impact assessment of the introduction of housing costs contributions under universal credit.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166999","166999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/382","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the availability of places  for the 130,000 disadvantaged two-year-olds eligible for the free 15 hours childcare for disadvantaged two-year-olds scheme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167000","167000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government has any plans to regulate nannies and other home childcarers working outside the childcare regulatory system.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167001","167001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of whether the education provider activities of the British Council constitute unfair competition to British private-sector education providers abroad.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166953","166953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will examine where it can work with British private-sector education providers to reduce the cost to the public purse of providing services through the British Council.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166954","166954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/386","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2013, Official Report, columns 556-8W, on average earnings: Clwyd, what the average weekly gross earnings of a full-time employed (a) man and (b) woman was in each local authority area in north Wales in cash terms in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166972","166972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/387","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to license the selling of tobacco products within shisha bars.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167007","167007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what reports the Domestic Extremism Unit at the Metropolitan Police have passed to her Department in the last 24 months; and when her Department received each such report.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167010","167010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of gross domestic product the UK spends on scientific research.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167019","167019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent work her Department has commissioned on armed forces servicemen becoming involved in far right groups while they are still serving or once they have left the military.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167017","167017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there is a Government working group on armed forces servicemen or former servicemen involved in far right groups.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167018","167018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/392","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the mobility criteria for personal independence payment has been changed to 50 metres instead of 20 metres.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167022","167022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/393","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many representations he has received calling for a boycott of Israeli goods and services in the last year.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167059","167059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/394","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many representations he has received on Iran's nuclear programme in the last year.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167060","167060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/395","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of people in work that are adversely affected by the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167079","167079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/396","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the effect of the measures in the Welfare Reform Act 2012 on the economy of (a) St Helens South and Whiston constituency and (b) the North West.","Biography information for Mr Shaun Woodward","Mr Shaun Woodward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167066","167066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/397","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from microprocessor knees and do not currently have them.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167082","167082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/398","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for a (a) budgeting loan and (b) crisis loan in (i) St Helens Metropolitan Borough Council area and (ii) Knowsley Metropolitan Borough Council area were (A) made and (B) approved in each month since April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Shaun Woodward","Mr Shaun Woodward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167069","167069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/399","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that all patients who could benefit from prosthetic technology have access to it, regardless of the area in which they live.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167083","167083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/400","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding he makes available for the Clinical Reference  Group (CRG) on Disability Equipment; and in what circumstances he would consider allocating further funding to CRGs which make a particular case for specific use for that funding.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167084","167084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/401","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in St Helens South and Whiston constituency have been affected by the under-occupancy penalty; and how many such people are disabled.","Biography information for Mr Shaun Woodward","Mr Shaun Woodward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167067","167067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/402","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the average change in benefit for those in St Helens and Whiston constituency affected by the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Shaun Woodward","Mr Shaun Woodward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167068","167068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/403","2013-09-02","Attorney General","2013-07-18","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Tenth Report of the Public Accounts Committee, Session 2013-14, HC 360 on Serious Fraud Office: redundancy and severance arrangements, what assessment he has made of the unauthorised redundancy and severance payments made by the former director of the Serious Fraud Office in relation to misconduct in public office.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167085","167085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/404","2013-09-02","Attorney General","2013-07-18","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Tenth Report of the Public Accounts Committee, Session 2013-14, HC 360 on Serious Fraud Office: redundancy and severance arrangements, whether the police will be asked to investigate the unauthorised redundancy and severance payments made by the former director of the Serious Fraud Office.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167086","167086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/405","2013-09-02","Attorney General","2013-07-18","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Tenth Report of the Public Accounts Committee, Session 2013-14, HC 360 on Serious Fraud Office: redundancy and severance arrangements, what steps he is taking to recover the  unauthorised redundancy and severance payments made by the former director of the Serious Fraud Office.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167087","167087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/406","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has received the action plan from Chethams School of Music expected in May 2013; and whether he is confident that the necessary safeguarding and child protection measures are in place to protect pupils at the school.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167088","167088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/407","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage children to read more books in the summer holidays.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167062","167062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/408","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his latest assessment is of the situation in the Maldives.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167063","167063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/409","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many representations he has received in opposition to Israeli settlement activity.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167075","167075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/410","2013-09-03","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-18","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, to what use he will put the Trident Alternatives Report; for what reason the report excluded consideration of the (a) costs and (b) utility of a two-submarine Trident force; how many Civil Servant man-hours were expended upon this report; and at what attributable cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167090","167090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/411","2013-09-03","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-18","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, for what reason the Trident Alternatives Report took 30 months to prepare; for what reason it was published so near to the Summer Recess of the House; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167091","167091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/412","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Statement of 26 March 2013, Official Report, column 1473, what minimum period of time work nurse trainees will be required to complete as support workers to healthcare assistants.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167078","167078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5464","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the number of UK service personnel based in Gibraltar who have accounts with Barclays Bank.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166885","166885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5916","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent per pupil for (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in each local authority area in the West Midlands for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166921","166921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5917","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the three-month vacancy rate was for nurses in each specialist group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167029","167029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6199","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2013, Official Report, column 266W, on armed forces: sexual offences, what sanctions against a perpetrator are available to a commanding officer following the conclusion of an investigation of an offence under sections 3, 66, 67 and 71 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167030","167030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6200","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what budget is allocated for the (a) Royal Naval Reserve HMS Cambria and (b) proposed additional reserve unit in Cardiff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167058","167058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6201","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2013, Official Report, column 266W, on armed forces: sexual offences, what guidance is given to a commanding officer on the conduct of investigations of an offence under sections 3, 66, 67 and 71 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167057","167057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6202","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many sites are being considered for the proposed additional reserve unit in Cardiff; whether the site will be (a) rented and (b) purchased; and what budget has been allocated for a site to be (i) rented and (ii) purchased.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167074","167074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6525","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools and local authorities have (a) sought and (b) been granted permission to change the use of playing fields by putting school buildings on them since February 2012.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167024","167024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6526","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools and local authorities have (a) sought and (b) been granted permission to change the use of playing fields by putting classrooms on them since February 2012.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167025","167025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6855","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS Trusts had an end-of-year deficit between their income and expenditure in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13 by (i) region and (ii) multiples of £500,000; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166916","166916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6856","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of renting a three-bedroom family property in each (a) region of the UK and (b) London borough in (i) 2011-12 and (ii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166917","166917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6857","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he expects that the Minister of State for Schools will reply to the letter to him of 3 July 2013 from the hon. Member for Harrow West; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166920","166920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6858","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2013, Official Report, columns 688-90W, on crime, if she will publish the equivalent data for 2012-13.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167031","167031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6859","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2013, Official Report, column 414W, on Big Society Network, if he will publish the letter of complaint about the Big Society Network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167056","167056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7116","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current timetable is for the Essex Thameside franchise; and whether the tender process will include a commitment that all rolling stock will be of equal or better quality than at present.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166873","166873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7263","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was paid out by UK Border Agency in adverse legal fees in immigration cases related to incorrect or contested National Referral Mechanism decisions in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166925","166925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7291","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobseeker Allowance claimants were temporarily barred from claiming on a monthly basis in the last year for which figures are available by (a) local authority area and (b) constituency; and what the average length of bar was.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166899","166899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7471","2013-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convicted murders (a) are currently on a day release and (b) have been on a day release in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167032","167032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7472","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of households whose only income is out-of-work benefits with a higher household income than households with one person or more in employment.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167033","167033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7473","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of (a) the money raised for the good causes and (b) the annual percentage difference from society lotteries in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167034","167034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7474","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of the costs of recruiting society lottery players on the amount that the society lotteries give to charities.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167042","167042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7475","2013-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2013, Official Report, column 731W, on prisons: swimming pools, what consideration he has given to the removal of the swimming pools in HM Prison Holloway and HM Prison Stanford Hill.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167043","167043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7476","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2013, Official Report, column 59W, on fires: warehouses, at which warehouse each such fire took place.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167044","167044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7477","2013-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2013, Official Report, column 731W, on prisons: swimming pools, how much on average local groups are charged for the use of the swimming pools.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167045","167045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7732","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2013, Official Report, column 989W, on local government: ICT, what progress he has made on measures to allow town and parish councils to (a) make online payments and (b) send agendas electronically.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167055","167055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7733","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the outcome was of his visit to Sevenoaks Town Council on 22 June 2013 was; what assessment he has made of the calls from the National Association of Local Councils for further reform of business rates to assist town and parish councils in supporting local economic growth; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167081","167081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7788","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what regard his Department has for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office's Countries of Concern List as part of its work promoting exports and trade.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167011","167011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7789","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made regarding the attendance of foreign delegations from (a) countries of concern and (b) other countries identified by his Department  in its annual human rights report at the Defence and Security International Exhibition in London.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167012","167012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7790","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how composers and performers will be rewarded if fair compensation is recovered at the point of sale under proposals for a private copying exception.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167026","167026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7793","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in what proportion of cases during labour a 1:1 ratio of midwives to expectant mothers was achieved in each NHS maternity unit in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Charles Hendry","Charles Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167070","167070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7794","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women transferred from each NHS maternity unit to another facility during labour in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Charles Hendry","Charles Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167071","167071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7795","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many births took place in each obstetric-led NHS maternity unit in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Charles Hendry","Charles Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167072","167072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7796","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many serious incidents occurred in each NHS maternity unit in the most recent year for which figures are available; and what definition his Department uses of a serious incident.","Biography information for Charles Hendry","Charles Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167073","167073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7885","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of funding allocated under the EU's Nepal Peace Trust Fund.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166874","166874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7886","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assist with addressing the problem of impunity in Nepal.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166876","166876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7887","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Nepal about the problem of impunity and the need to ensure that those responsible for serious human rights violations in that country are held to account.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166877","166877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7888","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to (a) support human rights defenders, (b) support those working to end impunity and (c) implement the EU Guidelines on Human Rights Defenders in Nepal.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166902","166902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7889","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what field visits officials of his Department have undertaken in Nepal in the last two years with the aim of supporting human rights defenders and civil society.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166905","166905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8076","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the support provided by Jobcentre Plus to jobseekers aged over 50 with prior senior managerial experience.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166883","166883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8077","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged over 50 who have been referred to the Work Programme since June 2011 were identified as being from an ethnic minority background; and how many have secured a sustained job outcome to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166884","166884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8078","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides to Jobcentre Plus staff on assisting jobseekers aged over 50 into employment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166889","166889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8079","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged over 50 who have been referred to the Work Programme since June 2011 (a) received a sanction while on the Work Programme, (b) disputed the sanction and (c) had a sanction overturned.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166890","166890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8080","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the universal credit IT systems will take into account the planned uprating of the national minimum wage from 1 October 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167027","167027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8232","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what differences there are in the obligations placed on installers by the codes of practice for the Green Deal and the Energy Company Obligation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166992","166992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8257","2013-09-02","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-18","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which representatives of the Government attended the most recent Nobel Peace Prize Concert in Oslo.","Biography information for Mr Brian Binley","Mr Brian Binley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166973","166973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8258","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the current activities of the high level expert group on the structure of the EU banking sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Brian Binley","Mr Brian Binley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166974","166974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8259","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what ex-post levies will be raised on the financial sector in support of the EU single resolution mechanism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Brian Binley","Mr Brian Binley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166975","166975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8260","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the European Commission's proposals to establish a joint Eurozone Society Security Fund with payments linked to adherence to policy targets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Brian Binley","Mr Brian Binley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166976","166976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8261","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on participating in projected solidarity mechanisms under future Eurozone arrangements; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Brian Binley","Mr Brian Binley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166990","166990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8262","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to opt into EU contracts for competitiveness and growth.","Biography information for Mr Brian Binley","Mr Brian Binley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166991","166991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8263","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the annual costs from homicide and wounding since 2005; and how this figure for 2013 is broken down.","Biography information for Mr Brian Binley","Mr Brian Binley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167080","167080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8385","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Minister of State for Immigration dated 18 June 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Paul Mendy.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166967","166967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8386","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 31 May 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms L. Molona.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166968","166968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8387","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he intends to reply to the letter dated 30 May 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms P. Atkinson, transferred from the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166969","166969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8388","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Minister of State for Immigration dated 10 June 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Adeel Farrukh.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166970","166970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8515","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who has been contracted to provide the apprenticeships funded by the Skills Funding Agency in (a) Newark, (b) Bassetlaw, (c) Sherwood, (d) Gedling, (e) Ashfield and (f) Nottingham city.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166901","166901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8695","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many flights over the UK have been conducted under the Open Skies treaty, by nation conducting each flight, since 2002.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166929","166929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8696","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Royal Navy continues to offer a frigate or destroyer to NATO Immediate Reaction Force activation.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167047","167047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8818","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the government of Bahrain's implementation of the Bahrain Independent Commission of Inquiry's recommendations.","Biography information for Conor Burns","Conor Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167048","167048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8819","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what projects the UK is providing technical assistance to the government of Bahrain to assist that country's implementation of the Bahrain Independent Commission of Inquiry's recommendations.","Biography information for Conor Burns","Conor Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167049","167049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8820","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the government of Bahrain's (a) recent human rights reforms and (b) establishment of the National Institution for Human Rights in that country.","Biography information for Conor Burns","Conor Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167050","167050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8821","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the recent efforts made towards national conciliation and power-sharing by the government of Bahrain.","Biography information for Conor Burns","Conor Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167051","167051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8822","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Government departments and agencies have offices based in (a) Bristol, (b) Swindon and (c) Bournemouth; and how many people are employed in each such office.","Biography information for Conor Burns","Conor Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167053","167053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8846","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many small and medium-sized businesses in Haltemprice and Howden constituency were offered Enterprise Finance Guarantee loans in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167023","167023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9036","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions officials based at the British High Commission in Kuala Lumpur met Malaysian police between 1995 and 1997; and whether the police investigation into the killings at Batang Kali in December 1948 were discussed on any such occasions.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166891","166891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9037","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will respond to the postcards submitted through the British High Commission in Kuala Lumpur by Malaysians on 18 June 2013 calling on the Government to take responsibility for the killings at Batang Kali in December 1948.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166892","166892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9366","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether, as part of its consideration of a contract-based model for the administration of the Nursery Milk Scheme, his Department has assessed the likelihood that a company that wins the contract would be able to put in place an immediate supply chain.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166915","166915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9367","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the influence in decision-making of the advocate in personal independence payment benefit assessments for people with cognitive impairments who lack insight into their condition.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166918","166918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9368","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of reductions in funding for local authorities on the provision of library services in England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166919","166919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9369","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what change there was in the number of miles cycled in 2012 compared with 2011 in (a) Barnsley, (b) Barnsley Central constituency, (c) South Yorkshire, (d) England and (e) the UK; and what assessment he has made of whether any such changes resulted from changes in the number of (i) people taking up cycling and (ii) trips by existing cyclists.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167008","167008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9370","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) each of the non-departmental public bodies for which he is responsible has allocated to Barnsley Metropolitan Borough Council in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167013","167013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9371","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time to be seen by a doctor in accident and emergency for (a) walk-in patients and (b) those arriving by ambulance are (i) for each hospital in South Yorkshire and (ii) nationally.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167014","167014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9372","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) England are in council tax arrears.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167015","167015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9373","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many apprentices are currently employed by his Department; and how many such apprentices are aged (a) under 19, (b) 19 to 25, (c) 26 to 30, (d) 31 to 59 and (e) 60 years and over.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167020","167020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9374","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many apprentices are currently employed by his Department; and how many such apprentices are aged (a) under 19, (b) 19 to 25, (c) 26 to 30, (d) 31 to 59 and (e) 60 years and over.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167021","167021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9391","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to encourage all creditors to agree to the Debt Management Plan Protocol.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167037","167037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9392","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of how many informal debt management plans might be replaced by Simple IVAs.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167039","167039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9393","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he plans to introduce the simple IVA, as originally proposed by the Insolvency Service in November 2008.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167041","167041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9394","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will review creditor behaviour regulation regarding non-performing unsecured credit debtors.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167035","167035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9395","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on plans by creditors to introduce modifications to Individual Voluntary Arrangements (IVAs) that may make it difficult for an IVA to be provided to a debtor by a licensed insolvency practitioner; and whether he has any plans to bring forward further regulation in light of these plans.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167036","167036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9396","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to introduce further reform of personal insolvency procedures.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167046","167046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9690","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he had with the (a) Roman Catholic Church and (b) Church of England when deciding on a 50 per cent cap on admissions for Free Schools.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166900","166900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9700","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of suspicious marriages taking place she received under Section 24 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 167016","167016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9767","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) mutual legal assistance treaty requests and (b) mutal legal assistance treaty requests for communications data were made to the US in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166911","166911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9922","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the structural changes necessary in the schools system to drive up standards; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166981","166981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9923","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people are training to become (a) primary and (b) secondary school teachers by subject area; and how many were in such training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166961","166961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9924","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what increased resources are provided to schools due to higher staff costs in some parts of the country; what the basis is of that allocation policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166962","166962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9925","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of GCSE entries from (a) independent schools and (b) state schools scored an A* or A grade in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166963","166963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9926","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted school inspections took place in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166964","166964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9927","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools were classed as requiring significant improvement in each reporting period since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166965","166965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9928","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in English schools took school meals in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166966","166966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9929","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his latest estimate is of the (a) number and (b) proportion of (i) 16, (ii) 17 and (iii) 18 year olds who are not in education or training; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166944","166944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9930","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what change there has been in the number of teaching assistants in England since 2010; what assessment he has made of the effects of that change on levels of pupil attainment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166951","166951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9931","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants are employed in each (a) Government region and (b) local education authority.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166952","166952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9932","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the teenage pregnancy rate was in each year since 2010; and what he expects it be in 2014-15.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166946","166946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9933","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total spend by his Department was on anti-truancy programmes in each year since 2010; and what assessment of value for money has been made of such spending.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166947","166947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9934","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average time taken was to carry out an assessment for a statement of special educational needs in each year since 2010, broken down by local education authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166948","166948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9935","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve access to mental health services for children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166949","166949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9936","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been (a) in care and (b) taken into care in each year since 2010; if he will place in the Library a breakdown of the reasons why children went into care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166950","166950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9937","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of headteachers in England are within (a) one year, (b) two, (c) three, (d) five and (e) 10 years of standard pension age; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166956","166956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9938","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will estimate the annual cost of reducing class sizes at Key Stage 1 in English schools to (a) 20 or fewer and (b) 25 or fewer.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166957","166957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9939","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total capital spending on (a) primary and (b) secondary schools was in each year since 2010 in real terms; what the planned real-term figures are for each year to 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166958","166958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9940","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academies have been co-sponsored by local authorities to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166959","166959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9941","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in each local authority area have no on-site facilities for producing hot school lunches; what information his Department collects on the (i) quality, (ii) availability and (iii) take-up of school lunches; whether all English schools meet the food-based and nutrient standards for lunch and non-lunch food; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166960","166960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9942","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to attract more of the best graduates into teaching; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166982","166982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9943","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his estimate is of the real terms changes (a) in total and (b) per pupil  in his Department's budgets for (i) all spending, (ii) spending on schools and (iii) spending on schools capital projects in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166983","166983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9944","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what freedoms are available to academies that are not automatically available to local authority schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166984","166984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9945","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost has been of each new academy built since 2010; and what the estimated costs are of each academy so far approved but not completed.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166985","166985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9946","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) GCSE results and (b) truancy rates were for each academy in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166986","166986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9947","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils were (a) temporarily and (b) permanently excluded from English (i) infant schools, (ii) primary schools, (iii) secondary schools and (iv) colleges in each year since 2010, by age; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166987","166987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9948","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department gives to its officials on making references to the policies of the previous Government in the drafting of press releases, statements, explanatory memoranda and other departmental publications.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166989","166989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9949","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of schools funding is distributed without reference to pupil numbers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166977","166977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9950","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of appeals against permanent exclusion were decided in favour of parents in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166978","166978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9951","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to increase the number of schools with post-16 provision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166979","166979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9952","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) teachers, (b) pupils, (c) teaching assistants and (d) support staff there were in English (i) primary schools and (ii) secondary schools in each year since 2010, by local authority area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166980","166980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10250","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the income tax arrangements are for UK members of the European Parliament.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166844","166844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10251","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish a table showing the salaries of the chief executive of each organisation that receives more than 50 per cent of its revenue from her Department.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166845","166845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10252","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost of offshore windfarm construction to meet the UK's renewable targets for 2020.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166846","166846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10339","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of households with one or more adults in employment used (a) home collected credit, (b) payday loans and (c) all forms of high cost credit in 2012.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166758","166758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10340","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of households used credit for everyday living expenses in (a) 2008-09, (b) 2009-10 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166759","166759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10341","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average amount owed by households in relation to (a) student loans, (b) personal loans, (c) credit cards, (d) overdrafts and (e) high cost credit in (i) 2011 and (ii) 2012 was.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166760","166760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10700","2013-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether firms involved in over-charging for electronic tagging services will still be excluded from bidding for further departmental contracts.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166633","166633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10701","2013-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will undertake an urgent review of the prison management competition for the Doncaster cluster of prisons.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166634","166634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10702","2013-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reasons were for the delay in announcing the new contract for managing the Doncaster cluster of prisons; and what affect the over-charging by firms for existing departmental contracts has had on this process.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166635","166635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11474","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to Question 161181 tabled on 18 June 2013 for Answer on 20 June 2013; and what the reasons are for the time taken to answer.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166642","166642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11475","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Unum Ltd or any subsidiary companies of Unum Ltd had a role in designing the work capability assessment; what relationship there has been between his Department and Unum over the last 10 years; what payments have been made by his Department to any Unum companies in that time period; and for what reason this question originally tabled by the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion on this matter on 23 April 2013 did not receive an answer.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166645","166645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11476","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Written Statement of 16 July 2013, Official Report, columns 78-9WS, on Tree Health and Plant Biosecurity Taskforce, what (a) powers, (b) budgets and (c) staffing the Chief Plant Health Officer will be given; whether these will be on an equivalent basis to those given to the Chief Animal Health Officer;  and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166850","166850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11477","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Written Statement of 16 July 2013, Official Report, columns 78-9WS, on Tree Health and Plant Biosecurity Taskforce, what steps he has put in place to (a) avoid the introduction into the UK of the emerald ash borer and (b) reduce the threat to tree health and bio-security from the global trade in soil; what assessment he has made of whether the emerald ash borer would reproduce effectively in and kill the ash trees showing resistance to Chalara; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166851","166851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11715","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the minutes of the most recent Bus Partnership Forum.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166834","166834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11716","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with bus operating companies on audio-visual next stop and final destination announcement systems.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166835","166835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11717","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which bus operating companies he has met representatives of (a) between May 2010 and July 2012 and (b) since July 2012.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166836","166836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12028","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses have been convicted of hiring unpaid interns in (a) 2013 to date, (b) 2012, (c) 2011 and (d) 2010.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166677","166677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12029","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2013, Official Report, columns 556-8W, on average earnings: Clwyd, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the doubling of female full-time gross weekly earnings between 1997 and 2012.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166870","166870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12652","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what level of aid her Department provides to the Tibet Autonomous Region and other Tibetan regions in China; and what the main areas of focus are of such programmes.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166629","166629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12653","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to engage parliamentarians in developing policy on the Post-2015 Development Framework; and if she will ask the Prime Minister to meet parliamentarians to discuss their role in that process.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166841","166841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14426","2013-09-02","Leader of the House","2013-07-17","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Office containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166735","166735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14427","2013-09-02","Leader of the House","2013-07-17","To ask the Leader of the House, how many questions answered by his Office included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166710","166710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/150","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding was given to local community groups to promote the Prevent Strategy in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166755","166755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/151","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many local community projects received direct Government funding to implement the Prevent Strategy in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166756","166756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/208","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the level of consultancy fees commissioned by Ofwat was in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166626","166626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/219","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures are in place for patients to appeal against decisions made about their treatment by NHS England.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166627","166627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/226","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether charging for tests in Public Health England microbiology laboratories is on a per test basis.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166628","166628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/227","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with disability groups about young people's experiences regarding watching live music.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166630","166630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2013, Official Report, column 360W, on health visitors: Bury, when NHS England last sought assurance from its area team that the core national service requirement was being met in Bury.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166631","166631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/236","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166697","166697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/237","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many times the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for his Department has had meetings with Derek Webb of the Fairer Gambling Trust.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166647","166647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/238","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) teachers and (b) classroom assistants were employed in maintained schools in (i) Brigg and Goole constituency and (ii) Yorkshire and the Humber in each of the last five academic years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166649","166649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/239","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support he will provide for continuing professional development to ensure teachers are equipped to teach the curriculum following the National Curriculum Reform; when such budgetary support will be determined; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166654","166654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/240","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) NHS trusts and (b) NHS foundation trusts there are; how many NHS trusts are expected to satisfy the requirements for conversion to foundation status by 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Shaun Woodward","Mr Shaun Woodward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166660","166660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/241","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many betting shops are located in each parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166665","166665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/242","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much betting shops have paid in (a) VAT and (b) corporation tax in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166666","166666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/243","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria are used to decide on the procurement of universal sample containers for urine sample collection and transport.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166636","166636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/244","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Final Project Report: An investigation of the effect of EPC ratings on house prices, what the evidential basis is for his Department's conclusion that the cost of energy is having an affect on house prices.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166640","166640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/245","2013-09-02","House of Commons Commission","2013-07-17","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many House of Commons staff were on zero hours contracts in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166643","166643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/246","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to raise awareness amongst teachers of the changes made to the teaching of the curriculum following the National Curriculum Reform; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166656","166656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/247","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the restaurant industry that do not allow waiters to keep tips, but instead use this additional income to pay other business costs.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166672","166672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/248","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of restaurants  that do not allow waiters to keep tips, but instead use this additional income to pay other business costs.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166673","166673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/249","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many minimum wage compliance officers there are in HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166674","166674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/250","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many instances of non-compliance with minimum wage were identified in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166675","166675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/251","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to increase the number of minimum wage compliance officers.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166676","166676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/252","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have taken out a payday loan in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Renfrewshire, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166678","166678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/253","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166694","166694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/254","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2013, Official Report, column 280W, on Syria, if she will make representations to the United Nations to specifically assess the needs of (a) disabled and (b) young refugees from Syria.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166680","166680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/255","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of Syrian refugees coming into refugee camps in (a) Lebanon, (b) Jordan, (c) Iraq and (d) Turkey on the resources and needs of long-term refugees already present in these countries.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166681","166681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/256","2013-09-02","Attorney General","2013-07-17","To ask the Attorney General, how many questions answered by the Law Officers' Departments included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166695","166695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/257","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166696","166696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/258","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with employers on the minimum wage and illegal immigration.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166682","166682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/259","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of illegal immigrants in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Renfrewshire, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166683","166683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/260","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will be affected by the move to personal independence payment in Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166684","166684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/261","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date he expects universal credit to be implemented in Wales (a) as a pilot scheme and (b) in full.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166686","166686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/262","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date he expects personal independence payments  to be implemented in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166687","166687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/263","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provisions will be made for those wanting to claim universal credit through the medium of Welsh.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166688","166688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/264","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Welsh Government regarding introducing minimum unit pricing for alcohol in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166689","166689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/265","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what future sums he has earmarked for relief of hardship arising from the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166690","166690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/266","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the proportion of (a) under-16 year olds, (b) 16 to 25 year olds, (c) 25 to 40 year olds, (d) 40 to 60 year olds and (e) over 60 year olds who take part in recreational sport in (i) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (ii) Renfrewshire and (iii) Scotland.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166679","166679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/267","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has issued to local authorities in respect of the priority to be given to competing applicants for help from hardship funds allocated to relieve the effects of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166691","166691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/268","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage Commonwealth member states that criminalise consensual, private same-sex sexual conduct to repeal such legislation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Shaun Woodward","Mr Shaun Woodward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166693","166693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/269","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many questions answered by her Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166698","166698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/270","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166699","166699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/271","2013-09-02","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-17","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many questions answered by his Office included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166700","166700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/272","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166701","166701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/273","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166702","166702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/274","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166703","166703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/275","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166704","166704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/276","2013-09-02","Women and Equalities","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many questions answered by the Government Equalities Office included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166705","166705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/277","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166706","166706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/278","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many questions answered by her Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166707","166707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/279","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many questions answered by her Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166708","166708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/280","2013-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166709","166709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/282","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been paid from the public purse to WS Atkins from contracts related to High Speed 2 since May 2010; and how much remains to be paid under uncompleted contracts.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166743","166743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/283","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what current projects in all Government departments have no financial limit imposed on them by his Department.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166744","166744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/284","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what environmental evaluations of High Speed 2 have been conducted by his Department; and if he will publish all reports that have been prepared for Ministers on that matter.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166745","166745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/285","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many jobs have been created (a) directly and (b) indirectly by High Speed 2 to date; and how many such jobs will be created in (i) phase 1 and (ii) phase 2 of the project.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166747","166747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/286","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) discussions and (b) correspondence Ministers of his Department have had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on the subject of High Speed 2; and if he will publish such correspondence.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166746","166746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/287","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many of the 14 hospitals investigated as part of Sir Bruce Keogh's recent report were regulated by Monitor; and what steps the regulator took to address the problems identified in the Keogh Report at each such hospital during the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166752","166752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/288","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will consider restricting the use of the third-party certification option under the revision of Part P of the Building Regulations to those carrying out work not-for-trade for the purposes of preventing electricians from being encouraged to leave Part P competent persons schemes.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166769","166769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/289","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the audit of procurement contracts held by G4S and Serco will (a) start and (b) finish.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166753","166753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/290","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the audit of procurement contracts held by G4S and Serco will cost.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166754","166754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/291","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times she has met David Anderson QC to discuss terrorism since 1 January 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166757","166757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/292","2013-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2013, Official Report, columns 471-2W, on prisoners, how many female offenders were given immediate custodial sentences for failing to surrender to bail in (a) 2011 and (b) 2012.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166787","166787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/293","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166718","166718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/294","2013-09-02","Attorney General","2013-07-17","To ask the Attorney General, if he will make it the Law Officers' Departments' policy to ensure that all answers provided by the Law Officers' Departments containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166719","166719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/295","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166720","166720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/296","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166722","166722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/297","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make it her policy to ensure that all answers provided by her Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166723","166723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/298","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166724","166724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/299","2013-09-02","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-17","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Office containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166725","166725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/300","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166726","166726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/301","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166727","166727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/302","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166728","166728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/303","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166729","166729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/304","2013-09-02","Women and Equalities","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will make it her policy to ensure that all answers provided by the Government Equalities Office containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166730","166730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/305","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166731","166731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/306","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to ensure that all answers provided by her Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166732","166732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/307","2013-09-02","Department for International Development","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to ensure that all answers provided by her Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166733","166733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/308","2013-09-02","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166734","166734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/309","2013-09-02","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will make it her policy to ensure that all answers provided by her Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166736","166736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/310","2013-09-02","Prime Minister","2013-07-17","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by No. 10 Downing Street containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166737","166737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/311","2013-09-02","Scotland Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166738","166738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/312","2013-09-02","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many questions answered by her Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166711","166711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/313","2013-09-02","Prime Minister","2013-07-17","To ask the Prime Minister, how many questions answered by No. 10 Downing Street included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166712","166712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/314","2013-09-02","Scotland Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166713","166713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/315","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166714","166714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/316","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166715","166715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/317","2013-09-02","Wales Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166716","166716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/318","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many questions answered by his Department included fewer than four pages of statistics in the Official Report for the last month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166717","166717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/319","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166739","166739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/320","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166740","166740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/321","2013-09-02","Wales Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166741","166741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/322","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to ensure that all answers provided by his Department containing tables of statistical data which would not require more than four pages in the Official Report are published in full rather than by reference to a hyperlink.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166742","166742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/323","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding mental health services have received in (a) England, (b) the North East, (c) Tees, Esk and Wear Valley NHS Foundation Trust and (d) Durham in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166761","166761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/324","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research his Department has (a) carried out and (b) funded into non-chemical methods of pest control for oil seed rape; and if he will make any useful findings of such research available to farmers ahead of the two year suspension of some uses of neonicotinoid insecticides.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166782","166782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/325","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding her Department provides to support women amateur boxers.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166762","166762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/326","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times the COBRA Committee has convened since January 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166783","166783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/327","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve choice in the provision of services for mental health service users.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166763","166763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/328","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the commissioning of mental health services.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166764","166764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/329","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings she and her officials attended with colleagues in the Department for Communities and Local Government to review the Prevent Strategy in each year since 1 January 2011.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166784","166784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/330","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of National Security Council meetings have focused on (a) terrorism and (b) organised crime since May 2010.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166785","166785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/331","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of third party certification under the revision of Part P of the Building Regulations on the ability of non-registered electricians to perform work.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166765","166765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/333","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many stop and search actions have led to arrests under the Terrorism Act 2000 in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166795","166795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/334","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what time limits are set for decisions made by the Planning Inspectorate.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166796","166796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/335","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons brain cancer patients and patients who have benign, vascular and functional neuro disease who were treated at the National Hospital for Neurology and Neurosurgery up to 31 March 2013 are required to transfer their treatment to another hospital by NHS England.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166830","166830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/336","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs who have been elected to the boards of clinical commissioning groups hold directorships or have shares held in private healthcare companies.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166815","166815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/337","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure appropriate labelling of meat that has come from animals who have not been stunned due to ritual slaughtering.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166799","166799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/338","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the invitation to negotiate for his proposed Government Owned Contractor Operated model.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166822","166822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/339","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the UK's trade policy with respect to the EU's directive that member states should not sign deals with Israel unless a settlement exclusion clause is included.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166825","166825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/340","2013-09-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the value was of sales of National Lottery scratch cards in Northern Ireland in each year between 2009 and 2012; and what the value was of National Lottery ticket sales in Northern Ireland in each such year.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166826","166826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/341","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to the Answer to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Northfield of 12 June 2013, Official Report, column 355W, on Occupied Territories, whether UK companies operating in Israel and the Occupied Territories will be consulted during the development of a UK strategy on business and human rights.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166827","166827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/342","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to the Answer to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Northfield of 12 June 2013, Official Report, column 355W, on Occupied Territories, when his Department will publish the UK strategy on business and human rights.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166828","166828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/343","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the potential total savings to the public purse of setting a benefits cap at (a) £26,000, (b) £20,000, (c) £19,000, (d) £18,000 and (e) £17,000.","Biography information for Chris Skidmore","Chris Skidmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166847","166847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/344","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria or formula his Department used to determine the funding allocations for additional money for physical education and sport in primary schools.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166849","166849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/345","2013-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to ensure the survival of Regimental Headquarters of the Cheshire Regiment, at Chester Castle, following the amalgamation of the 22nd (Cheshire) Regiment in the Mercian Regiment.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166864","166864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/346","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of the new funding system for higher needs students on (a) a local authority's ability to commission independent specialist colleges to provide courses, (b) the teaching time a student can expect and (c) the quality of the course.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166839","166839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many answers by his Department to the last 100 Parliamentary Questions asked involving tables of statistics fewer than four pages in length were (a) printed in full and (b) provided via a link to a website.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166852","166852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/348","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officers the UK Border Agency has dedicated to organised crime.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166853","166853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he expects to announce what subjects will be included in the technical baccalaureate.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166854","166854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the role of teaching assistants.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166855","166855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/351","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many decisions relating to potential Traveller and showpeople sites have been determined by the Planning Inspectorate in 2013 to date.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166856","166856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/352","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2013, Official Report, columns 556-8W, on average earnings: Clywd, what the average weekly gross earnings of a full-time employed (a) man and (b) woman in Wales was in cash terms in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166869","166869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/355","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the First Report of the Committees on Arms Exports Control, Scrutiny of Arms Exports and Arms Control, Annex 13: Extant arms export licences to Countries of concern, Ev w170, Letter from the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills to the Chair of the Committees, dated 10 May 2013, and Ev w264, Letter from the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills to the Chair of the Committees dated 20 May 2013 on the Standard Individual Export Licence (Permanent) for equipment employing cryptography and software for equipment employing cryptography of the value £7,765,450,000 to Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories, how many companies the licence was granted to; for what reasons the value of the licence is higher than others for similar goods; and if he will provide further details on what the licence was granted for.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166871","166871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/357","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the RAC Foundation's report entitled Young Driver Safety Solutions to an Age-old Problem published in July 2013 and its conclusions on (a) a minimum learning period that contains requirements to drive in all conditions and (b) placing limitations on newly-qualified drivers.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166829","166829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5448","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent consideration he has given to the building of two new offshore patrol vessels.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166800","166800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5484","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority about fulfilling its Road Map commitment to end incitement against Israel.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166641","166641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5485","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions his Department has had with the government of Israel about Israel's high-tech sector.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166842","166842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5553","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations he has received on the dangers posed by Chinese lanterns.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166848","166848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5610","2013-09-02","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-07-17","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, on what dates (a) board members and (b) staff of the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority attended the Selsdon Park Hotel to discuss remuneration proposals for hon. Members; whether other locations were considered for the meeting; and who attended.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166768","166768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5611","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy that all new schools or major extensions should have defibrillators provided; and if he will establish a programme to provide defibrillators in all existing schools.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166766","166766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5612","2013-09-02","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-07-17","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, if he will publish a breakdown of the costs associated with the two-day gathering at the Selsdon Park Hotel to discuss remuneration proposals for hon. Members.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166767","166767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5753","2013-09-04","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what action his Department is taking to block fraudulent websites of companies that offer fast-track services for a fee to renew the European Health Card.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166786","166786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6004","2013-09-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to collect information on the number of payday loans taken out in each (a) local authority area, (b) region and (c) nation within the UK.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166632","166632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6005","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the next UK-China human rights dialogue will take place; what its agenda will be; and if he will raise concerns about the human rights of the Tibetan people at this dialogue.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166650","166650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6006","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Chinese counterparts on the whereabouts and wellbeing of the 10 Tibetans who were shot and injured whilst taking part in a peaceful community picnic to celebrate the birthday of the Tibetan spiritual leader, the Dalai Lama.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166651","166651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6007","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Chinese counterpart on that country upholding its constitutional commitments to allow freedom of assembly and religious belief; and if he will request an investigation into the actions of the security forces who opened fire on unarmed Tibetans celebrating the birthday of their spiritual leader.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166652","166652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6008","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the actions of Chinese security forces who opened fire on unarmed Tibetans in Tawu, Sichuan province.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166653","166653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6009","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passport applications were made by residents in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency in respect of people (a) under the age of 16 years and (b) over the age of 16 years in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166872","166872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6037","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Highways Agency will take action to facilitate access by mobility scooters, wheelchairs and pushchairs to the pavements at the junctions of St Leonard's Hospital with the A31 trunk road.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166667","166667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6220","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Welsh Government's decision to introduce presumed consent will result in administrative changes to the way the organ donation system operates in England.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166831","166831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6221","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects of presumed consent organ donation in Wales on (a) English prisoners in Welsh prisons, (b) individuals who normally reside in England who die in intensive care in Wales and (c) individuals who normally reside in Wales who die in intensive care in England.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166832","166832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6222","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effects on organ donation in England of the introduction of presumed consent for organ donation in Wales.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166833","166833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6223","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Welsh Assembly decision to introduce presumed consent will result in any additional costs to the UK Government.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166837","166837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6224","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Welsh Assembly decision to introduce presumed consent will require any changes to legislation by the UK Government.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166838","166838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6522","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will commission an investigation into the UK's oil price setting process.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166748","166748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6523","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent representations he has received calling for a review of the oil price setting process.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166749","166749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6524","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) US and (b) EU regulation of oil prices.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166750","166750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6853","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will assess the effectiveness of the UK Envoy for Post-Holocaust Issues; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166751","166751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6854","2013-09-02","Home Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects that a reply will be sent to the letters dated 24 April 2013 and 4 June 2013 from the hon. Member for Harrow West to the UK Border Agency regarding Mr Hiren Patel of Harrow.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166774","166774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6885","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many local authorities (a) have a contingency plan in place in the event of a rabies outbreak and (b) are currently reviewing such a plan.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166840","166840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6886","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of staff at the Highways Agency and the Vehicle and Operators Services Agency are first aid-trained.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166863","166863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6959","2013-09-02","Prime Minister","2013-07-17","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 4 March 2013, Official Report, column 847W, on Michael Dugher, on how many occasions Mr Lynton Crosby has been registered on the access control records as a visitor to Downing Street since November 2012.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166655","166655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7084","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on linking the use of funding from international finance institutions to agricultural and food producers to improve animal welfare standards.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166692","166692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7085","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what opportunities his Department provides for stakeholders to comment on proposals for new environmental land management schemes.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166788","166788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7086","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consultation his Department has undertaken with stakeholders in respect of new environmental land management schemes.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166789","166789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7087","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consideration he has given to providing funding for landowners for walking and access infrastructure under new environmental land management schemes.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166790","166790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7088","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will estimate the income generated by walking and recreation in coastal communities.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166791","166791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7089","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will estimate the income generated by the England Coast Path for coastal communities.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166792","166792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7090","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on the future implementation of the England Coast Path project.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166793","166793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7091","2013-09-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will estimate the income generated by walking and recreation by county.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166794","166794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7593","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2013, Official Report, columns 335-6W, on floods: finance, how much funding will have been paid out to each local authority between 1 January and 31 July 2013 under the Bellwin scheme as a result of flooding.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166821","166821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7594","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many breakfast clubs there are in schools by (a) region and (b) local authority.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166823","166823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7741","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in (a) Surrey and (b) England secured places at (i) their first choice and (ii) one of their top three choices of secondary school in the most recent application period.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166775","166775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7742","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what NHS spending per head of population in Surrey was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166776","166776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7743","2013-09-02","Cabinet Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many business start-ups there have been in Woking constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166777","166777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7744","2013-09-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many homes in Woking constituency have received insulation under his Department's energy efficiency programmes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166778","166778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7745","2013-09-02","Department for Education","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much schools in (a) Woking constituency, (b) Surrey and (c) England received in funding from the pupil premium in 2011-12; and how much such schools received in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166779","166779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7746","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authority properties have been purchased through the Government's right-to-buy scheme in Woking constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166780","166780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7792","2013-09-02","HM Treasury","2013-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will set out how his Department calculates the levels of settlements offered to each Equitable Life claimant.","Biography information for Charles Hendry","Charles Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166648","166648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7875","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on local assisted conception policies which restrict access to IVF treatment on the grounds that one partner has children from a previous relationship.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166661","166661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7876","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will endorse the recommendations contained within the 2013 NICE guideline on fertility which recommends that three full cycles of IVF be provided to eligible couples.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166662","166662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7877","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 1 March 2013 to the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West, Official Report, column 726W, on IVF, when Infertility Network UK's eligibility criteria commissioning tool was published; and what steps his Department has taken since then to reduce variations in access criteria across the country.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166663","166663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7878","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue guidance on whether a clinical commissioning group can be deemed to have failed in its duty to discharge its functions if it refuses to commission fertility services; and what his policy is on intervention by NHS England in such cases.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166664","166664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8072","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he next plans to visit a foodbank.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166807","166807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8073","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment  he has made of the merits of recording on a regular basis the number of foodbank vouchers issued by jobcentres; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166808","166808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8074","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to discuss with representatives of groups operating foodbanks the reasons for recent trends in the level of foodbank demand; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166809","166809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8075","2013-09-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2013, Official Report, column 660W, on universal credit, whether he expects any further jobcentres to take new claims for universal credit before April 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166806","166806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8253","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) apprentices and (b) graduate trainees are working on High Speed 2 (HS2) in (i) his Department and (ii) HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166811","166811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8254","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the role of signalling in achieving efficiencies in the rail sector.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166812","166812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8255","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the recent steps taken by Network Rail to reduce delays caused by signal failures.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166813","166813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8256","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library a copy of the (a) feasibility study and (b) any value management studies for HS2 Ltd's option 8 design for Euston Station.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166814","166814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8342","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve awareness amongst the public and healthcare professionals of the symptoms of stroke.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166646","166646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8343","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support healthier lifestyles and reduce cardiovascular and stroke risk.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166657","166657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8344","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to involve stroke patients in their care planning.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166658","166658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8345","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that stroke patients are treated in acute stroke centres that provide 24 hour care.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166659","166659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8346","2013-09-02","Department of Health","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on diagnosing and treating transient ischaemic attacks.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166824","166824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8420","2013-09-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress the Islamophobia Working Group has made; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166810","166810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8575","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the formula is to determine the funding for the British Transport Police on the East Coast Main Line; and if he will place a copy of the formula in the Library.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166797","166797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8576","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the funding agreed between the British Transport Police (BTP) and the companies operating the East Coast Main Line was for BTP staff on the franchise in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010 -11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-04.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166798","166798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8686","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the main gate decision will be taken for the Crowsnest project; and what recent estimate he has made of its total cost.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166770","166770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8687","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many flights the UK has made under the NATO Strategic Airlift Interim Solution since January 2012; what the (a) total cost and (b) cost per flight has been; and which aircraft were used.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166771","166771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8688","2013-09-02","Department for Transport","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assets he has designated for search and rescue under section 2.5 of Annex 12 of the Convention on International Civil Aviation; and where each is located.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166772","166772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8689","2013-09-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) name and (b) address is of each building owned by his Department; and what the estimated monetary value is of each such building.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166773","166773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8690","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel from 51 Squadron will be deployed to Afghanistan to support US operations using the Rivet Joint aircraft.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166801","166801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8691","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which NATO member states have sent maritime patrol aircraft to (a) RAF Lossiemouth and (b) RAF Leuchars since December 2012; which aircraft were sent; and what the purpose was of their visit.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166802","166802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8692","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what requests the UK has made to other NATO member states to provide maritime patrol aircraft to patrol UK waters in order to detect submarines since March 2010.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166803","166803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8693","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the (a) number of payments and (b) cost to the public purse of key industrial capability notices issued to BAE systems under the terms of the 2009 Terms of Business Agreement.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166804","166804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8694","2013-09-02","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions BAE systems has written to his Department to notify it of a (a) key industrial capability trigger event and (b) key industrial capability notice under the terms of the 2009 Terms of Business Agreement since June 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 166805","166805"
