"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782305","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent (a) in total, (b) on consultancy fees and (c) on reviews by the Sussex and East Surrey Sustainability and Transformation Partnership since it was sent up.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110981","110981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782306","2017-11-06","Department of Health","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the physiotherapy treatments in England carried out in the private sector.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110897","110897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782307","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time for a cognitive behaviour therapy appointment for a mental health condition is in each clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110978","110978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782308","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time taken to process GP applications to the medical performers list is; and what steps he is taking to reduce that time.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110979","110979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782309","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of redrawing the geographical scope of the Sussex and East Surrey Sustainability and Transformation Partnership.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110980","110980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782310","2017-11-06","Home Office","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list the (a) reviews and (b) reports commissioned by her Department which have yet to be published.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110846","110846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782311","2017-11-06","Home Office","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the uplift in funding for armed officers has been provided (a) centrally and (b) by police forces.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110901","110901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782312","2017-11-06","Home Office","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate the Government has made of how much it receives per year in fees from people applying to enter the country legally; and what that money is spent on.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110932","110932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782313","2017-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October to Question 10164, what the Government's position on Israel's 27th amendment to its Entry into Israel Law.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110921","110921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782314","2017-11-06","Home Office","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she will provide a substantive response to the letter dated 27 June 2017 from the hon. Member for Christchurch on the application by Mr Morley for British citizenship.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110954","110954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782315","2017-11-06","Home Office","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential costs and benefits for (a) her Department and (b) the tech sector of high tech visas.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110948","110948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782316","2017-11-06","Department for International Development","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department is making on achieving Sustainable Development Goal number five to achieve gender equality and empower all women and girls.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110942","110942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782317","2017-11-06","Department for International Development","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to report against the Sustainable Development Goals to the UN's High Level Political Forum in 2018.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110941","110941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782318","2017-11-06","Department for International Development","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109476, on Sub-Saharan Africa: poaching, how the decision to provide anti-poaching support to improve welfare is made when no official definition of welfare exists.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110963","110963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782319","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken with the Scottish Government to assess the effect on railway policing across the border between Scotland and England of the planned integration of British Transport Police in Scotland into Police Scotland.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110877","110877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782320","2017-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of trends in the number of cases involving litigants in person since the changes to legal aid provision in 2012.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110988","110988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782321","2017-11-06","Home Office","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how each department responsible for the Government's Violence Against Women and Girls Strategy are contributing to her Department's development of (a) the Domestic Violence and Abuse Bill and (b) the non-legislative package supporting the Bill.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110925","110925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782322","2017-11-06","Home Office","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what form of consultation her Department is undertaking with (a) civil society organisations and (b) academics and experts on the new definition of domestic violence and abuse to be included in the proposed new Domestic Violence and Abuse Bill.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110926","110926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782323","2017-11-06","Home Office","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will collect data on violent crimes that includes (a) the sex and age of the perpetrator and the victim, (b) the relationship between those people and (c) whether those crimes involve repeat victimisation.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110927","110927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782324","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to assist former employees of Monarch Airlines since its collapse.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110964","110964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782325","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the involvement was of Monarch Airlines crew in repatriating UK passengers after the collapse of the airline.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110965","110965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782326","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government has taken to help former Monarch Airlines employees who did not receive redundancy payments.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110966","110966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782327","2017-11-06","Department for Transport","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of relocating the Lakeside Energy from Waste plant as part of the proposed Heathrow Northwest Runway scheme.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110895","110895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782328","2017-11-06","Department of Health","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for patients referred from primary care to NHS physiotherapy services (a) in England and (b) broken down by clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110896","110896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782329","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will carry out a cost benefit analysis of the effect of High Speed 2 on Leigh.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110886","110886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782330","2017-11-06","Women and Equalities","2017-11-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government has taken to raise awareness among employers of (a) the health and safety implications and (b) their duty under equalities legislation of requiring women to wear unsuitable footwear at work.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110934","110934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782331","2017-11-06","Women and Equalities","2017-11-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that women are aware that they cannot be compelled to wear unsuitable footwear or clothing at work.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110936","110936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782332","2017-11-06","Women and Equalities","2017-11-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the law in offering protection to women who are compelled to wear unsuitable footwear at work.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110935","110935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782333","2017-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will release data to (a) local authorities and (b) housing associations on the claimants who have migrated from legacy benefits to universal credit on a daily basis.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110900","110900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782334","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to promote the extension of apprenticeships to women in their sixties.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110977","110977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782335","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships have been taken up by women born in the 1950s after they reached the age of 60.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110976","110976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782336","2017-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former claimants of disability living allowance in Hull West and Hessle constituency were (a) unsuccessful in their claim for personal independence payment and (b) have appealed their unsuccessful decision to change to personal independence payment in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110845","110845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782337","2017-11-06","HM Treasury","2017-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 April 2017 to Question 70847, whether his Department has made an interim assessment of the effects of the freeze on child benefit and child tax credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110949","110949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782338","2017-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of the new approach for determining local housing need in the Department for Communities and Local Government's consultation published on 14 September 2017, on the ability of the North East to meet the jobs targets laid out in the Strategic Economic Plans for (a) the North East Local Enterprise Partnership and (b) the Tees Valley Combined Authority.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110946","110946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782339","2017-11-06","HM Treasury","2017-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations the Government is making to ensure that European Investment Bank funds are made available as soon as possible to be disbursed to businesses in the North East through the North East Fund.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110943","110943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782340","2017-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what non-electricity generating uses his Department plans for indigenous coal in the UK's industrial strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110881","110881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782341","2017-11-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on not reaching a deal with the EU on exiting the EU on the UK economy.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110920","110920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782381","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the potential merits of extending the Financial Conduct Authority's Financial Services Compensation Scheme to cover debt management.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901632","901632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781235","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has to extend the voting rights of UK citizens who are resident overseas in UK elections and referendums.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110469","110469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781236","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to guarantee votes for life in UK elections and referendums for all UK citizens living abroad.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110470","110470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781237","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of changing the electoral system for local government elections in England to the single transferrable vote system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110486","110486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781238","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of placing questions in 2021 census on (a) military service and (b) membership of the Armed Forces community.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110487","110487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781239","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans his Department has to consult the public on the merits of alternative methods to the first past the post system for voting in general elections.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110500","110500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781240","2017-11-03","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of removing unpatched, unsupported or out of date software and hardware from government departments and agencies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110491","110491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781241","2017-11-03","HM Treasury","2017-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timetable is to bring forward legislative proposals to abolish Class 2 National Insurance contributions for the self-employed.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110493","110493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781242","2017-11-02","HM Treasury","2017-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings his Department has held with the Financial Conduct Authority to discuss the retirement income market since April 2015.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110542","110542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781243","2017-11-02","HM Treasury","2017-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax revenue has been generated for the public purse from pension withdrawals in each financial year since April 2015.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110543","110543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781244","2017-11-02","HM Treasury","2017-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had in the last 12 months with the ATM Industry Association in Europe on interchange fees.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110582","110582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781245","2017-11-02","HM Treasury","2017-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the need for additional Revenue and Customs officials in Northern Ireland as a result of the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110573","110573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781246","2017-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had in the last 12 months with the ATM Industry Association in Europe on interchange fees.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110583","110583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781247","2017-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new starter homes have been built in Southampton since 2015.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110544","110544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781248","2017-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of help to rent projects in enabling homeless people to gain access to accommodation in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110498","110498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781249","2017-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of help to rent projects de-risking the private rented sector for homeless households.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110466","110466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781250","2017-11-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information her Department holds on the extent of the gender pay gap for staff at Tech City and Tech North.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110507","110507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781251","2017-11-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the amount spent by gamblers on fixed-odds betting terminals in Enfield North constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110518","110518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781252","2017-11-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many projects made bids for funding from the Tampon Tax Fund; how many of those bids were unsuccessful; and which projects were unsuccessful.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110540","110540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781253","2017-11-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2017 to Question 105258, on football: commercial agents, if she will make it her policy that any proposals from the Football Association on the future regulation of football agents are discussed with her Department.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110523","110523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781254","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what research his Department has commissioned into the prevention of non-freezing cold injury.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110515","110515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781255","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Marines personnel are employed in the (a) armoured support, (b) armourer, (c) assault engineer, (d) clerk, (e) combat intelligence, (f) driver, (g) drill instructor, (h) general duties, (i) heavy weapons (air defence), (j) heavy weapons (anti-tank), (k) heavy weapons (mortars), (l) landing craft, (m) metalsmith, (n) mountain leader, (o) physical training instructor, (p) platoon weapons (sniper), (q) platoon weapons (machine gunner), (r) Royal Marines aircrewman, (s) Royal Marines communications technician, (t) Royal Marines information systems (RMIS, (u) Royal Marines medical assistant (RMMA), (v) Royal Marines Police, (w) signaller, (x) special forces communicator (SFC), (y) stores accountant, (z) telecommunications technician, (aa) vehicle mechanic (ab) artificer telecommunications, (ac) artificer vehicles, (ad) foreman of signals and (ae) yeoman of signals specialist roles.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110519","110519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781256","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and which of his Department's contracts since the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Revenue of value equal to or greater than £1 billion have been placed taking into account National Security Objective 3.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110520","110520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781257","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and which of his Department's contracts since the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Revenue of value equal to or greater than £100 million have been placed taking into account National Security Objective 3.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110521","110521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781258","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and which of his Department's contracts since the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Revenue of value equal to or greater than £10 million have been placed taking into account National Security Objective 3.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110522","110522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781259","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what weight he attached to the marking criteria for National Security Objective 3 in developing each of his Department's contracts whose value is £1 billion or above for which that objective was taken into account.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110526","110526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781260","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what weight he attached to the marking criteria for National Security Objective 3 in developing each of his Department's contracts whose value is £10 million or above for which that objective was taken into account.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110527","110527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781261","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what weight he attached to the marking criteria for National Security Objective 3 in developing each of his Department's contracts whose value is £100 million or above for which that objective was taken into account.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110528","110528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781262","2017-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which units from HM Armed Forces will be participating in cold weather training in Norway in 2018; and how many such personnel will take part from each unit.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110567","110567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781263","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times officials of his Department have received hospitality from Babcock International in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110529","110529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781264","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has received from Babcock International on the National Shipbuilding Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110530","110530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781265","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contracts are currently in place between his Department and Babcock International.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110531","110531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781266","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) senior civil servants of his Department and (b) former officers in the Armed Forces have taken up employment with Babcock International in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110532","110532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781267","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many events organised on behalf of his Department have received sponsorship from Babcock International in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110533","110533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781268","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with Babcock International on the provision of information requested by the Single Source Regulations Office.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110534","110534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781269","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which operations are personnel from the Royal Marines currently deployed.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110535","110535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781270","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which operations personnel from the Royal Marines have been deployed in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110536","110536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781271","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings have taken place between (a) Ministers and civil servants of his Department and (b) members of the Armed Forces with Babcock International in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110510","110510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781272","2017-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which units from HM Armed Forces will be participating in Exercise Trident Juncture 2018; and how many such personnel will take part from each unit.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110568","110568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781273","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance his Department offers to corporate signatories of the Armed Forces Covenant to support the Armed Forces community.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110549","110549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781274","2017-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimated cost is for support and maintenance for each RAF and Royal Navy F-35 aircraft once those aircraft reach initial operational capability with each of those branches of the armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110561","110561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781275","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made in Northern Ireland on the implementation of the Military Covenant; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110569","110569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781276","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the expenditure was on the (a) Saudi Arabian National Guard Communications Project and (b) Ministry of Defence Saudi Armed Forces Project in the 2016-17 financial year; and what the budget is for each of those projects for the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110485","110485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781277","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) of his Department's civilian staff based in the UK, (b) UK military personnel based in the UK, (c) of his Department's civilian staff based in Saudi Arabia and (d) UK military personnel based in Saudi Arabia were employed by the (i) Saudi Arabian National Guard Communications Project and (ii) Ministry of Defence Saudi Armed Forces Project respectively on 1 April 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110471","110471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781278","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage collaboration between adult education colleges and businesses requiring language skills to assist English for Speakers of Other Languages learners into employment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110478","110478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781279","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with (a) awarding organisations and (b) English for Speakers of Other Languages (ESOL) providers on modernising the ESOL qualifications and curriculum framework.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110479","110479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781280","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to require all state-funded schools to work with local authorities in developing a language needs assessment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110480","110480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781281","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve collaboration between English for Speakers of Other Languages (ESOL) providers and local authorities to (a) identify and (b) meet the need for ESOL provision in each such authority area.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110481","110481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781282","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of children of service personnel receiving education in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in Oxford West and Abingdon constituency.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110482","110482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781283","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the pupil-teacher ratio was in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in Oxford West and Abingdon constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110483","110483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781284","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to allow children living in the UK who were adopted in a foreign country to be eligible for Pupil Premium Plus.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110484","110484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781285","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish its response to the Home Office public consultation, Reporting and acting on child abuse and neglect; and if she will pay particular regard to mandatory reporting and acting on child sexual abuse and neglect in that response.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110566","110566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781286","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 107980, on children: day care, how many of the valid 30 hours codes have been generated by successful applications in each local authority area.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110559","110559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781287","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department offers to (a) primary and (b) secondary schools to ensure that they understand the difference between type 1 and type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110580","110580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781288","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make British sign language available as a GCSE.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110558","110558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781289","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships have been offered at Level 5 and above to people aged under 25 in each local authority area of the West Midlands in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110551","110551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781290","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that schools in England are (a) aware of and (b) comply with the statutory guidance Supporting pupils with medical conditions at school.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110581","110581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781291","2017-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to establish a body to replicate the work of the EU's Scientific Committee on Consumer Safety in providing scientific analysis of cosmetic products that enter the market in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110472","110472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781292","2017-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that cosmetic products that have been tested on animals do not enter the UK market in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110473","110473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781293","2017-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on the regulation of cosmetic products that have been tested on animals in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110474","110474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781294","2017-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the European Food Safety Authority on the effect of neonicotinoid pesticides on other pesticides; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110475","110475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781295","2017-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward proposals to allow the Natural Capital Committee to set legally binding targets on air and water quality.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110476","110476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781296","2017-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on British food exports of defaulting to WTO tariffs.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110477","110477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781297","2017-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the environmental effect of fracking.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110508","110508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781298","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Nepal since the commencement of its mandate as a UN Human Rights Council member on upholding fundamental freedoms and human rights in that country.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110503","110503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781299","2017-11-03","Department for International Development","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the Government's priorities are for the Fourth Global Conference on the Sustained Eradication of Child Labour in Buenos Aires, 14 to 16 November 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110497","110497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781300","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Bahrain on the trial and sentencing of Mansoor Hassan, Sayed Nizar Alwadei and Mahmood Marzooq.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110556","110556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781301","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the time it will take to restore basic infrastructure in the British Virgin Islands.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110550","110550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781302","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via A&E with a primary diagnosis of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in each of the financial years from 2010-11 to 2016-17.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110547","110547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781303","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted to hospital via A&E with a primary diagnosis of pneumonia in each of the financial years from 2010-11 to 2016-17.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110548","110548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781304","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) highest, (b) lowest and (c) average cost of implementing CareCERT alerts for each NHS trust in England.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110560","110560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781305","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that health care professionals report cases of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110525","110525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781306","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency departments with a primary diagnosis of dislocation, fracture, joint injury or amputation in each month since 2010-11.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110554","110554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781307","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to (a) alleviate the work pressures on mental health staff working in the NHS and (b) ensure that such workers receive effective support and care in the event of mental health illness.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110511","110511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781308","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the effect on plans for accountable care organisations in Manchester of NHS VAT arrangements agreed with HM Revenue and Customs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110509","110509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781309","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which categories of claimants of universal credit are entitled to claim help with healthcare travel costs; and whether he plans to change that entitlement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110496","110496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781310","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the average cost to the NHS of an emergency admission for pneumonia.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110537","110537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781311","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the average cost to the NHS of an emergency admission for chronic obstructive pulmonary disease.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110538","110538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781312","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that sugary snacks are no longer on offer in vending machines in NHS Trust hospitals.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110539","110539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781313","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons ibrutinib is not prescribed on the NHS as a treatment for chronic lymphocytic leukaemia.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110489","110489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781314","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of removing unpatched, unsupported or out of date software and hardware.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110492","110492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781315","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each NHS trust has spent on rental payments for mobile CT scanners in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110464","110464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781316","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on rental payments for mobile CT scanners in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110465","110465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781317","2017-11-03","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the twelfth report of the Science and Technology Select Committee of 2016-17, Science in emergencies: chemical, biological, radiological or nuclear incidents, published on 5 April 2017, HC 163.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110490","110490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781318","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to change the (a) design, (b) colour and (c) wording of the new UK passport after the UK leaves the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110499","110499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781319","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will make an assessment of the adequacy of police patrol coverage across geographical force areas.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110501","110501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781320","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of instances of metal theft from commercial premises since 2010; and what steps her Department is taking to tackle metal theft from commercial premises.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110502","110502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781321","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the National Referral Mechanism in respect of child victims of trafficking; and whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of providing additional funding to local authorities to enable them to provide specialist support for child victims of trafficking.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110512","110512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781322","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to ensure that all asylum seekers are guaranteed the right to work in the UK.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110524","110524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781323","2017-11-03","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will grant the same additional support for English language learning recently made available for refugees resettled to the UK under the Vulnerable Persons Resettlement Scheme and Vulnerable Children's Resettlement Scheme to all refugees.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110565","110565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781324","2017-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil proceedings related to housing funded by legal aid were brought in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110562","110562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781325","2017-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on legal help and legal representation for (a) under 18 and (b) 18 to 24 year olds in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110563","110563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781326","2017-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many legal aid-funded cases were started in each local authority area in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110564","110564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781327","2017-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is his policy to maintain current reciprocal arrangements between the UK and the EU in respect of family law cases after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110557","110557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781328","2017-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what categories of claimants of universal credit are entitled to claim (a) help with prison visiting costs, (b) legal aid and (c) remission from court fees; and whether he plans to change those entitlements.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110504","110504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781329","2017-11-02","Leader of the House","2017-10-31","To ask the Leader of the House, if she will bring forward proposals to provide more parliamentary time per session for consideration of Private Members' Bills.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110516","110516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781330","2017-11-02","Leader of the House","2017-10-31","To ask the Leader of the House, whether the Government plans to seek Select Committee scrutiny for any draft Bills during the 2017 Parliament.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110517","110517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781331","2017-11-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 23 October 2017, on the European Council, Official Report, column 35, what assessment he has made of which technological devices for monitoring the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland would be excluded in the event that there is no physical infrastructure at that border after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110570","110570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781332","2017-11-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will visit the Storehouse North Down food bank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110571","110571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781333","2017-11-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the effect on public appointments in Northern Ireland of not having a First Minister and Deputy First Minister acting jointly to make such appointments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110572","110572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781334","2017-11-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans he has to visit border communities in Northern Ireland to discuss the effect of the UK leaving the EU on those communities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110574","110574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781335","2017-11-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of jobs in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110575","110575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781336","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Office for Rail and Road's regulation of Network Rail; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110467","110467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781337","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Transport Focus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110468","110468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781338","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when HS2 construction plans and timetables for the Chilterns will be published.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110585","110585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781339","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 108458, on motor vehicle: registration, whether the number of statutory off road notifications vehicles has increased in the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110555","110555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781340","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Transport for Greater Manchester on rail and High Speed 2 connectivity in Leigh.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110552","110552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781341","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the (a) number of rail bridge strikes, (b) cost to his Department of those strikes and (c) amount recovered from insurers of vehicles involved in such strikes in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110495","110495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781342","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many job vacancies there were at HS2 Ltd on 1 November 2017; and what the titles of those jobs were.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110586","110586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781343","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost to the public purse was of processing an individual employment and support allowance claim in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110545","110545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781344","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of employment and support allowance claims were refused by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110546","110546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781345","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of people receiving benefits due to expending their personal pension in the most recent period for which information is available.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110541","110541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781346","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which categories of claimants of universal credit are entitled to claim (a) cold weather payments, (b) funeral payments and (c) the Sure Start maternity grant; and whether he plans to change those entitlements.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110505","110505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781347","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, from what date payments from his Department will no longer be paid into Post Office card accounts.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110506","110506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781348","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to publish an annual report on the disability employment gap as part of the national employment statistics.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110494","110494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781349","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to incentivise employers to contribute towards the cost of English for Speakers of Other Languages classes for their employees.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110488","110488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781350","2017-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had in the last 12 months with the ATM Industry Association in Europe on interchange fees.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110579","110579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781351","2017-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 108862, on energy: housing, when he plans to (a) review the best support for home energy efficiency beyond 2022, (b) consult on raising EPC standards and (c) publish recommendations made by the Green Finance Taskforce.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110513","110513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781352","2017-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 108836, on carbon emissions, whether the proposals set out in the Clean Growth Strategy will enable the UK to meet the target set in the fifth carbon budget.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110514","110514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781353","2017-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the equity of the fiscal regime for rooftop solar power compared with those for other energy generation technologies.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110587","110587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781354","2017-11-02","Department for International Trade","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the cost to the public purse was of establishing the trade remedies framework between January and August 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110584","110584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781355","2017-11-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate his Department has made of the number of small businesses in Leigh that could be significantly impacted financially by the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110553","110553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781358","2017-11-03","Attorney General","2017-10-31","To ask the Attorney General, how the Government complies with Article 16 of the International Law Commission's Articles on the Responsibility of States for Internationally Unlawful Acts, with specific reference to the sharing of intelligence to identify targets with our coalition partners.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110693","110693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781359","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109496, how many of those journeys to Brussels used first class travel; and what the total amount spent was on such visits to Brussels.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110655","110655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781360","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether there is a right to appeal against use of the Radcliffe exclusion rule.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110704","110704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781361","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Radcliffe exclusion rule recommended by the Radcliffe Committee of Enquiry into Civil Service Security Procedure remains in force; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110705","110705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781362","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what records his Department holds on the use of the Radcliffe exclusion rule recommended by the Radcliffe Committee of Enquiry into Civil Service Security Procedure.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110706","110706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781363","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of savings to the public purse as a result of moving Department's back office servers and ERP systems into shared service centres in each of the last three years; and to which Department's budgets those savings have been accrued.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110707","110707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781364","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the relevant sections of ministerial or civil service guidance on the Radcliffe exclusion rule.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110708","110708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781365","2017-11-03","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what childcare facilities his Department makes available for staff; how much his Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those childcare facilities in the last year; and how many staff members use those childcare facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110611","110611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781366","2017-11-03","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8518, on civil servants: training, what the average cost of providing that training was to each public sector worker.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110628","110628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781367","2017-11-03","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of electors who were eligible to vote in the 2017 General Election but who did not register to do so.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110636","110636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781368","2017-11-03","Cabinet Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8518, on civil servants: training, how many people from sectors other than the public sector have received such training; and what the average cost of providing that training was to each of those people.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110629","110629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781369","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government has taken to assess the (a) cost and (b) economic productivity to the public purse of (i) alcohol misuse, (ii) obesity and (iii) viral hepatitis.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110669","110669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781370","2017-11-02","HM Treasury","2017-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce a higher rate of tax for high-strength white ciders.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110594","110594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781371","2017-11-02","HM Treasury","2017-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the change in the level of tax revenues since scrapping the Alcohol Duty Escalator.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110668","110668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781372","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will make it her policy to support the provision of birth registration in children's centres and family hubs.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110657","110657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781373","2017-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2017 to Question 109354, on Grenfell Tower: fire, what the specific fault with the fridge freezer was that caused the fire.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110635","110635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781374","2017-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what childcare facilities his Department makes available for staff; how much his Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those childcare facilities in the last year; and how many staff members use those childcare facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110612","110612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781375","2017-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department actively encourages registered providers or local councils to pursue or support mergers between social housing providers.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110651","110651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781376","2017-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of mergers between registered providers of social housing.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110652","110652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781377","2017-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the Government's policy is on the invitation from the Local Government Association to participate in cross-party talks on the future of adult social care.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110646","110646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781378","2017-11-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what childcare facilities her Department makes available for staff; how much her Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those childcare facilities in the last year; and how many staff members use those childcare facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110614","110614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781379","2017-11-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the number of jobs in the technology, culture and heritage sectors that will be (a) created and (b) lost in the event that if the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU result in no deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110617","110617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781380","2017-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of armed forces veterans who are homeless in Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110625","110625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781381","2017-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the reported use of civilians, including women and children as human shields by ISIS combatants in Syria; and whether this falls within acceptable collateral damage.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110698","110698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781382","2017-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which countries will support the maintenance of Royal Navy and RAF F-35 aircraft once those aircraft reach initial operating capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110637","110637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781383","2017-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what childcare facilities his Department makes available for staff; how much his Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those childcare facilities in the last year; and how many staff members use those childcare facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110613","110613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781384","2017-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department of the findings of the United States Government Accountability Office report to Congressional Committees published in October 2017, on F-35 aircraft sustainment.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110647","110647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781385","2017-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the ISC report on lethal drone strikes in Syria published in April 2017, what steps the Government is taking to better scrutinise and assess collateral damage arising from UK or joint operations drone strikes.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110648","110648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781386","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on the number of armed forces veterans receiving inpatient and outpatient mental healthcare in Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110597","110597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781387","2017-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential benefit to the armed forces of offering applicants a mental health check prior to joining.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110697","110697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781388","2017-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has received assurances from the F-35 Joint Programme Office that the findings of the United States Government Accountability Office Report to Congressional Committees of October 2017 on F-35 aircraft sustainment will be addressed.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110691","110691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781389","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of nurseries in York have signed up to the provisions of 30 hours of free childcare.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110592","110592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781390","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the merits of allowing parents to take children out of school and on educational visits during term-time.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110643","110643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781391","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the German model for varying  school term dates by region.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110644","110644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781392","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many fines have been issued to parents for non-attendance at school by a child in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110649","110649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781393","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the level of benefit received by local communities from monies given by her Department to Wakefield City Academy Trust as part of the Northern Powerhouse programme in 2015.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110686","110686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781394","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the level of benefit received by students at schools served by Wakefield City Academy Trust from the funding given to that Trust by her Department as part of the Northern Powerhouse programme in 2015.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110687","110687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781395","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship starts there were in (a) May, (b) June and (c) July 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110645","110645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781396","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the remit of the Office for Students will include anti-discrimination on campus.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110676","110676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781397","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of each day of school missed on a pupil's attainment record.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110642","110642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781398","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Minister for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation last met with (a) Universities UK, (b) University and College Union, (c) the Sutton Trust and (d) Unison.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110699","110699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781399","2017-11-03","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's press release of 31 October 2017, when she plans to release further details of the review of higher-level technical education.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110700","110700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781400","2017-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the level of recycling rates in each London Borough.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110601","110601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781401","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of Cameroon on restoring internet access in the south of that country.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110604","110604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781402","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of Sudan on the decree requiring Christian schools in Khartoum to remain open on a Sunday.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110684","110684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781403","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of freedom of religion or belief in Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110683","110683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781404","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of Sudan on the arrests of religious leaders in Khartoum in August 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110685","110685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781405","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of minimum unit pricing for alcohol.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110656","110656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781406","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to expand the number of health visitors and school nurses.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110679","110679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781407","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to improve the detection of hepatitis B and C.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110658","110658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781408","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to raise awareness of myalgic encephalomyelitis among (a) healthcare professionals and (b) the general public.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110590","110590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781409","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to mark International Awareness Day for Chronic Immunological and Neurological Diseases on 12 May 2018.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110595","110595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781410","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of armed forces veterans in inpatient and outpatient mental healthcare in England.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110596","110596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781411","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what percentage of pharmacies that applied for the Pharmacy Access Scheme payment were deemed eligible for that payment.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110672","110672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781412","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote a cross-cutting and comprehensive approach to tackling mental health problems among young people.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110598","110598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781413","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many additional pharmacies who applied for the Pharmacy Access Scheme payment were deemed eligible for that payment.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110673","110673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781414","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2017 to Question 106946, how much from the public purse was spent on post-transplant stem cell treatment by (a) NHS England and (b) clinical commissioning groups in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110607","110607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781415","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital trusts in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland and (d) Scotland have recorded budget deficits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110650","110650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781416","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of people who have de-transitioned in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110608","110608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781417","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the proposals contained in the NHS England consultation entitled, Items which should not be routinely prescribed in primary care: A Consultation on guidance of CCGs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of those proposals on patients with (a) inflammatory bowel disease and (b) a long-term condition.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110618","110618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781418","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the proposals contained in the NHS England consultation entitled, Items which should not be routinely prescribed in primary care: A Consultation on guidance of CCGs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of those proposals on (a) the management of urgent care services and (b) the number of hospital admissions.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110619","110619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781419","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the proposals contained in the NHS England consultation entitled, Items which should not be routinely prescribed in primary care: A Consultation on guidance of CCGs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of those proposals on access to medications for (a) children, (b) older people and (c) other vulnerable people.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110620","110620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781420","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the proposals contained in the NHS England consultation entitled, Items which should not be routinely prescribed in primary care: A Consultation on guidance of CCGs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of those proposals on patients with a long-term condition who have already purchased a prescription prepayment certificate.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110621","110621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781421","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the proposals contained in the NHS England consultation entitled, Items which should not be routinely prescribed in primary care: A Consultation on guidance of CCGs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of those proposals on the medicine-taking behaviour of patients who rely on regular and multiple medications to prevent symptoms of long-term conditions.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110622","110622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781422","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures he plans to put in place to ensure standards of health visiting are maintained when responsibility for such visitors is transferred from the NHS to local authorities.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110678","110678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781423","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to use health visitors to reduce health inequalities by (a) increasing the amount and time duration of breast feeding and (b) extending early educational intervention.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110677","110677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781424","2017-11-03","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients aged (a) under one, (b) between one and four, (c) between five and nine, (d) between 10 and 14, (e) between 15 and 19 and (f) between 20 and 24 were admitted to hospital through accident and emergency departments with a diagnosis of bronchiolitis in each month in the last six financial years.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110641","110641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781425","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109414, on police: finance, for what reason the publicised lists do not include unsuccessful bids.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110609","110609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781426","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of additional UK Border Agency officials that will be needed in Northern Ireland as a result of the UK leaving the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110578","110578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781427","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to promote and enhance community policing.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110605","110605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781428","2017-11-03","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2017 to Question 105855, what information her Department holds on the number of people who have registered complaints for the loss of documents by UK Visas and Immigration in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110694","110694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781429","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will ensure that all 280 remaining places allocated for unaccompanied child refugees under section 67 of the 2016 Immigration Act will be filled.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110671","110671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781430","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to take account of (a) the views of advocacy organisations and (b) regional trends in Northern Ireland for the draft Domestic Violence and Abuse Bill.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110681","110681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781431","2017-11-02","Department for International Development","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what humanitarian and medical aid is being sent to southern Cameroon.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110603","110603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781432","2017-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the need for changes in the family courts system to address the issue of parental alienation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110599","110599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781433","2017-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost of training and maintaining Tornado teams has been for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110632","110632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781434","2017-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions Tornado teams have been deployed to prisons since September 2016.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110633","110633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781435","2017-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he is aware of the work being done by the charity Care after Combat to reduce reoffending among armed forces veterans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110702","110702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781436","2017-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of armed forces veterans in prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110627","110627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781437","2017-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of armed forces veterans under the supervision of Probation Service in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110696","110696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781438","2017-11-02","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans he has to visit Bombardier in Belfast; if he will make an assessment of the implications of the recent deal between Bombardier and Airbus in the United States on future job prospects for people in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110576","110576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781439","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what change there has been in the number of (a) untaxed vehicles, (b) uninsured vehicles and (c) vehicles without an MOT in the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110600","110600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781440","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2017 to Question 108734, if he will publish his Department's analysis of the environmental benefits of the electrification of the Midland Mainline.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110602","110602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781441","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 108866, on aviation, how many meetings negotiating teams in his Department have had with (a) legal advisers, (b) CAA and (c) industry experts to discuss bilateral aviation negotiations in advance of negotiations with the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110701","110701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781442","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 108695, on transport: iron and steel, when his Department plans to make that assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110623","110623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781443","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2017 to Question 108870, on Kobe Steel Europe, when his Department plans to make that assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110624","110624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781444","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff at HS2 Ltd have (a) resigned (b) been made redundant and (c) been employed on (i) a fixed-term contract, (ii) a full-time basis and (iii) secondment in the most recent 12 month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110634","110634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781445","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the tolls on the New Mersey Gateway bridge are clearly signposted for motorists crossing that bridge.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110638","110638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781446","2017-11-03","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of people who have been fined for failure to pay the toll on the New Mersey Gateway bridge since it opened; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110639","110639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781447","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the eligibility criteria will be for the planned £300 million infrastructure funding to be connected to northern towns and cities with High Speed 2.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110675","110675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781448","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 108459, on motor vehicles: registration, what redress there is for local residents who live on a public road on which a SORN vehicle is not removed after 72 hours.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110589","110589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781449","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the cost of a direct rail line between Leigh and High Speed 2.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110682","110682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781450","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that rail and station operators meet their obligations as set out by their disabled people's protection policy.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110591","110591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781451","2017-11-02","Department for Transport","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that blind and partially-sighted passengers can access rail services.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110593","110593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781452","2017-11-03","Wales Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he is taking to ensure that Welsh interests are protected in future international trade negotiations.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110615","110615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781453","2017-11-03","Wales Office","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether the Wales Office plans to make discrete assessments on the effects of future potential free trade deals on the economy in Wales.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110616","110616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781454","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions his Department has been taken to an employment tribunal for maternity discrimination in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110703","110703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781455","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of armed forces veterans in receipt of disability and work-related benefits.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110626","110626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781456","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2017 to Question 69473, on children: poverty, what the factors of disadvantage are that will be taken into consideration by local government.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110630","110630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781457","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 30 March 2017 to Question 69357, on children: poverty, how he plans to tackle the root causes of poverty and disadvantage.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110631","110631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781458","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the progress of the roll-out of universal credit in Northern Ireland in the absence of a functioning Northern Ireland Assembly and responsible ministers to oversee that roll-out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110577","110577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781459","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications of universal credit being paid into one person's account when the claim is in the name of a couple; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110606","110606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781460","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that children's benefits change in line with the cost of living.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110653","110653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781461","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to reduce the number of children living in poverty over the 2017 Parliament.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110654","110654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781462","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to review the local housing allowance rate to ensure it is accurately aligned with the rental market.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110664","110664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781463","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimates his Department has made of the number of disabled people who will apply for universal credit in the next phase of roll-out.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110667","110667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781464","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will include data on the number of disabled people receiving universal credit in its monthly publication of universal credit statistics.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110665","110665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781465","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to record the number of people who apply for and receive universal credit.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110666","110666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781466","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108977, what research his Department has conducted on the effect of bank branch closures on those people it has written to about receiving their state pension or benefits payments into a bank, building society or credit union account.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110689","110689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781467","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108977, what estimate his Department has made of the numbers of people claiming state pension who cannot access a bank branch.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110688","110688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781468","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to reform the work capability assessment.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110670","110670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781469","2017-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have personal independence payment claims initially refused are successful at appeal.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110680","110680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781470","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria must be met to deem a medical assessment unfit for purpose during a personal independence payment dispute process; and whether it is his Department's policy that a medical assessment can be used to form a judgement if the (a) claimant has requested a mandatory reconsideration and (b) medical assessment is being disputed by the claimant on the grounds of additional medical evidence.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110692","110692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781471","2017-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108977, on post office card accounts, what estimate his Department has made of the numbers of people so written to who have been affected by bank branch closures.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110690","110690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781472","2017-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2017 to Questions 109428, 109477, 109380, 109381, 109382, 109383, 109426 and 109427, on Cost of Energy Independent Review, whether officials of his Department drafted the document Professor Helm-declaration of interest published on 6 August 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110695","110695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781473","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Government has made on improving the transparency and affordability of publicly funded medical research.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110659","110659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781474","2017-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what childcare facilities his Department makes available for staff; how much his Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those childcare facilities in the last year; and how many staff members use those childcare facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110610","110610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781475","2017-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on solar power; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110588","110588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781476","2017-11-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to Annex A of the Secretary of State's letter of 30 October 2017 to the Chair of the Lords Sub-Committee on EU External Affairs, for what reason his Department has not included the charity sector in its list of sectors to help structure analytical work on EU exit.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110640","110640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781477","2017-11-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the future of projects funded by the European Social Fund for which that funding is due to end in March 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110661","110661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781478","2017-11-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Work and Pensions on the future of projects funded by the European Structural and Investment Funds for which that funding is due to end in March 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110660","110660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781479","2017-11-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Communities and Local Government on the future of projects funded by European Structural and Investment Funds for which that funding is due to end in March 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110663","110663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781480","2017-11-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the future of projects funded by the European Structural and Investment Funds for which that funding is due to end in March 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110662","110662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/781481","2017-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the commitment in the White Paper entitled, the United Kingdom's exit from. and new partnership with, the European Union to fully fund all European structural and investment funds projects signed, or with funding agreements that were in place before the Autumn Statement 2016, what estimate he has made of the value of contracts supported by European structural and investment funds for the financial year ending March (a) 2018, (b) 2019 and (c) 2020.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110674","110674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784367","2017-11-06","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of homophobic, biphobic and transphobic bullying in schools.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901617","901617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784368","2017-11-06","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of teacher recruitment and retention.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901618","901618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784369","2017-11-06","Department for Education","2017-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications of the new National Funding Formula for areas experiencing rapid housing growth.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901621","901621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780371","2017-11-01","Attorney General","2017-10-30","To ask the Attorney General, if he will extend the range of offences for which an unduly lenient sentence may be referred to the Court of Appeal to include stalking, under section 4(1)(a) of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997, and coercive control, under section 76 of the Serious Crime Act 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110251","110251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780372","2017-11-01","Cabinet Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what products have been sold through Common Technology Services; to which Departments those products have been sold; and what the value is of each such product.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110275","110275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780373","2017-11-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the cost to the public purse has been of the analyses undertaken to assess the potential effect on different sectors of the UK economy in the event that no deal is reached in negotiations for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110256","110256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780374","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the Association of Electoral Administrators' recommendation that the collection of voters' email addresses should no longer be optional when registering to vote.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110231","110231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780375","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of setting up an online service for voters to check whether they are already registered to vote for the purposes of reducing the number of duplicate applications.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110232","110232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780376","2017-11-01","Cabinet Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) financial, (b) organisational and (c) other support the Government has given to which think-tanks in the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110162","110162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780377","2017-11-02","Cabinet Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much of the £450 million awarded to the Government Digital Service in 2015 has been spent to date; and on what such funds have been spent.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110290","110290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780378","2017-11-01","Cabinet Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Departments outsource their finance, HR and payroll services to Shared Services Connected Ltd.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110312","110312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780379","2017-11-01","Cabinet Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many days work were lost to industrial action taken by employees of the Government and its agencies in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110431","110431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780380","2017-11-01","Cabinet Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2017 to Question 9559, on electronic voting, whether he will trial electronic voting for parish or town council elections.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110446","110446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780381","2017-11-01","Cabinet Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2017 to Question 9559, on electronic voting, whether he plans to trial postal votes only for parish or town council elections.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110447","110447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780382","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are employed to investigate tax evasion in the HM Revenue and Customs (a) affluent unit and (b) high net worth unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110432","110432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780383","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Exchequer Secretary of 24 October 2017, Official Report, column 148, what the evidential basis is that Government transport investment is equal across the different regions in England; and if he will publish per capita transport investment for each region in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110454","110454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780384","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions officials of his Department have had with trade union representatives on the proposed transfer of 2,700 HM Revenue and Customs posts from East Kilbride to Glasgow.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110349","110349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780385","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what financial impact assessment the Government has made relating to the transfer of HM Revenue and Customs posts from East Kilbride to Glasgow.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110350","110350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780386","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions officials in his Department have had with (a) the Scottish Government and (b) South Lanarkshire Council on the proposed transfer of HM Revenue and Customs posts from East Kilbride to Glasgow.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110351","110351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780387","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has considered the use of stamp duty relief to encourage homeowners to downsize.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110354","110354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780388","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on (a) reducing fuel duty and (b) other fiscal methods for reducing the cost of fuel for motorists; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110363","110363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780389","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the 3.9 per cent increase in spirits duty in March 2017 on spirits revenue to the Exchequer in the first quarter of 2017-18.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110365","110365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780390","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many needs-enhanced enquiries were made to HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110424","110424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780391","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Scotch Whisky Association on tax on whisky.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110441","110441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780392","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much excise duty was collected on Scotch whisky in the past five financial years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110442","110442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780393","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of any increase in excise duty collected from the sale of Scotch whisky in the current financial year.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110443","110443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780394","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which tickets relating to which journeys set out in the transparency release, entitled HMT ministers' meetings, hospitality, gifts and overseas travel: 1 April to 30 June 2017, published on 13 October 2017, were (a) first, (b) business, (c) economy and (d) any other class.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110168","110168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780395","2017-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how income inequality has changed by percentile since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110198","110198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780396","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with representatives from the banking and finance sector about the potential effect of no deal with the EU on the banking and finance sector after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110235","110235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780397","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he is taking to support the Scotch whisky industry in the UK market.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110266","110266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780398","2017-11-02","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Sefton Central of 26 October 2017, Official Report, column 469, if he will instigate a judge-led inquiry into RBS's treatment of SMEs.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110240","110240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780399","2017-11-02","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to allow equity release for terminally ill people with mortgages whatever the age of that person.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110283","110283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780400","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of whether the UK leaving the EU without a deal will have an effect on the level of available public finance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110254","110254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780401","2017-11-01","HM Treasury","2017-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of whether the UK leaving the EU without a deal will have an effect on income tax rates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110255","110255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780402","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support 16 to 21-year olds leaving social care but not eligible to claim housing benefit.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110247","110247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780403","2017-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to announce which local authority areas will be piloted for 100 per cent business rates retention; what representations he has received from councils in West Sussex on that pilot scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110238","110238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780404","2017-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans for the Transition Grant to be allocated as part of the 2018-19 local government finance settlement.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110234","110234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780405","2017-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to make a decision on the compulsory purchase orders required for the delivery of the new housing and retail facilities planned for the Brent Cross and Cricklewood development.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110229","110229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780406","2017-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the consultation on Fixing Our Broken Housing Market, published in February 2017, what progress has been made in reviewing home energy efficiency standards; and what plans there are for new standards to (a) require all homes to have an energy performance certificate, (b) improve energy efficiency standards for private rented homes and (c) ensure that all new homes from 2020 are low emission homes.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110194","110194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780407","2017-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which tickets relating to which journeys set out in the transparency release, entitled DCLG ministerial travel, April to June 2017, published on 13 October 2017, were (a) first, (b) business, (c) economy and (d) any other class.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110169","110169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780408","2017-11-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if the Government will publish the recommendations made by the Park Homes Working Group set up in 2015.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110161","110161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780409","2017-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of resources available to local authorities to fulfil the additional duties placed on them under the Homelessness Reduction Act 2017.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110376","110376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780410","2017-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place a copy of any government impact assessment on the effect of leaving the EU on the construction sector in the Library.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110397","110397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780411","2017-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 750, on building regulations: fires, when the Government plans to publish the outcome of the review of fire safety guidance as a result of the fire at Lakanal House in 2013.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110353","110353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780412","2017-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 750, on building regulations: fires, what the evidential basis is for progress having been made on the review of fire safety guidance since the fire at Lakanal House in 2013.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110371","110371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780413","2017-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for bids for the next round of the coastal communities fund.","Biography information for Peter Heaton-Jones","Peter Heaton-Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110357","110357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780414","2017-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding he plans to provide to local authorities for the installation of sprinklers in tower blocks.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110358","110358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780415","2017-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the proportion of temporary accommodation declared unfit for human habitation; and what estimate he has made of the number of children living in such temporary accommodation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110370","110370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780416","2017-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to devolve powers to Cheshire and Warrington.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110295","110295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780417","2017-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications to become a Unitary Authority are currently pending.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110453","110453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780418","2017-11-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many times the Minister for Sport has met representatives from Kick It Out since her appointment (a) in total and (b) in each year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110380","110380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780419","2017-11-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the date was of the last occasion on which the Minister for Sport met with a representative of the Professional Footballers Association.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110383","110383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780420","2017-11-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many times the Minister for Sport has met representatives of the Professional Footballers Association since her appointment (a) in total and (b) in each year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110382","110382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780421","2017-11-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when was the last occasion on which the Minister for Sport met a representative from Kick It Out.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110381","110381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780422","2017-11-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to restrict access to online porn for those aged under 18.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110410","110410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780423","2017-11-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential effect on cultural development in the UK of the withdrawal of the US Administration from participation in UNESCO; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110179","110179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780424","2017-11-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the decision to award the Life charity monies from the Tampon Tax Fund was made (a) before or (b) after the grant agreement with that charity was signed.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110223","110223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780425","2017-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the NAO Report, Improving value for money in non-competitive procurement of defence equipment, published on 25 October 2017, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Single Source Contract Regulations under the Defence Reform Act 2014.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110246","110246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780426","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the future is of HMS Ocean and HMS Bulwark; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Drax","Richard Drax","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110276","110276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780427","2017-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on redundancy payments to civilian employees in each of the past three years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110195","110195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780428","2017-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will break his Department's link with the Single Source Regulations Office and make it an independent body.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110196","110196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780429","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK Officer Cadets completed their Commissioning Course at Royal Military Academy Sandhurst in each course since the start of 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110416","110416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780430","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many training places were taken up in the September 2017 Commissioning Course at Royal Military Academy Sandhurst.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110415","110415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780431","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the assessed Army intake requirement for Officers in each of the Commissioning Course periods for the last three years at Royal Military Academy Sandhurst.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110417","110417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780432","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the total number of (a) available regular training places and (b) places that have been filled at (i) ITC Catterick, (ii) ATC Pirbright, (iii) ATC Winchester, (iv) ATC Harrogate and (v) Royal Military Academy Sandhurst in each of the last six months, broken down by course.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110418","110418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780433","2017-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support is available to educate Ministry of Defence service personnel on alcohol and drug consumption; and what support is provided to personnel who are addicted to alcohol or drugs.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110304","110304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780434","2017-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what alcohol and drug testing is currently carried out on military personnel on active service.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110303","110303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780435","2017-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the annual savings to the public purse for MOD civilian employees who have (a) accepted redundancy and (b) left the service but whose jobs will not be replaced in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110369","110369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780436","2017-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will introduce new veterans support services staffed and run by former service personnel.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110333","110333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780437","2017-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will name one of the new Royal Navy Frigates, HMS Seaham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110334","110334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780438","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will review guidelines on the recruitment and training of naval officers in light of positive drug tests aboard HMS Vigilant.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110460","110460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780440","2017-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what anti-submarine warfare capability he plans to include on the Type 31e General Purpose Frigate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110430","110430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780441","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to deal with reports of HMS Vigilant crew members testing positive for class A drugs.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110458","110458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780442","2017-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps were taken on on-duty consumption of alcohol by naval officers following the fatal shooting of a crew member aboard HMS Astute in 2011.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110459","110459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780443","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost per digital transaction of applications for full-time study support in October 2018.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110348","110348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780444","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109339, on children: day care, what the timetable is for publication of the independent evaluation.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110302","110302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780445","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many sibling groups have been adopted in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110270","110270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780446","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many registered foster carers there have been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110271","110271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780447","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have been approved as adopters in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110272","110272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780448","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been placed for adoption in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110268","110268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780449","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many adoptions have broken down in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110269","110269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780450","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish all correspondence on the 30 hours free childcare policy which she has had with Suffolk Country Council in the last six months.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110318","110318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780451","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which pupils whose parents claim universal credit count towards a school's pupil premium; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110321","110321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780452","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which categories claimants of universal credit are entitled to claim free school meals for their children; and whether she plans to review that entitlement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110323","110323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780453","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what the £530,000 from her Department given to Wakefield City Academy Trust as part of the Northern Powerhouse project in 2015 has been spent.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110398","110398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780454","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109339, on children: day care, what the timetable is for publication of the independent evaluation.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110384","110384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780455","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109407, on children: day care, which local authorities received funding; and how many projects were awarded that funding.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110361","110361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780456","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which tickets relating to which journeys set out in her Department's transparency release entitled Ministers' Quarterly Returns Apr to June 2017, were (a) first, (b) business, (c) economy or (d) any other class.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110172","110172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780458","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's guidance, entitled Supporting pupils at school with medical conditions, published in December 2015, if she will make an assessment of the proportion of schools with published policies for supporting pupils with medical conditions.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110185","110185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780459","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's guidance, entitled Supporting pupils at school with medical conditions, published in December 2015, if she will make an assessment of the extent and effectiveness of partnership working in support of pupils with medical conditions between school staff, healthcare and social care professionals, local authorities and parents and pupils.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110186","110186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780460","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to section 100 of the Children and Families Act 2014, if she will bring forward a plan of action to raise awareness within (a) schools, (b) school governance bodies and (c) school inspectorates on the statutory requirement for schools to make arrangements for children with medical conditions.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110177","110177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780461","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to section 100 of the Children and Families Act 2014, how her Department monitors the implementation of the statutory duty on appropriate school authorities to make arrangements for pupils with medical conditions; and what records her Department holds on interventions to enforce that section by her Department or any other public body.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110178","110178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780462","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assistance is available for children with dyslexia and learning difficulties to support them during key stage 2 assessment.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110200","110200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780463","2017-11-01","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Home Secretary on ensuring that DBS checks for volunteers and governors who volunteer at multiple schools remain valid across all schools.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110273","110273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780464","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of (a) government and (b) other schemes in recruiting science teachers in secondary schools.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110214","110214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780465","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been madeon targeting young people from disadvantaged backgrounds to further their education in the last 10 years .","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110242","110242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780466","2017-11-02","Department for Education","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's guidance, entitled Supporting pupils at school with medical conditions, published in December 2015, what the scope and timetable for the planned review of that guidance will be.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110230","110230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780467","2017-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate his Department has made of the (a) value, (b) amount and (c) proportion of food grown on farms in the UK which is rejected for sale because it does not meet buyer specifications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110221","110221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780468","2017-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that food which is rejected for sale on account of specifications not being met is not wasted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110222","110222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780469","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on (a) the number and (b) which slaughterhouses do not have comprehensive CCTV installed on their premises.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110364","110364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780470","2017-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on ice reduction in the Antarctic in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110401","110401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780471","2017-11-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the Government's progress on helping to prevent fly-tipping on commercial premises.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110338","110338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780472","2017-11-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Environment Agency's licensing, monitoring and enforcement of the law on the dumping of waste materials.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110339","110339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780473","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he or officials from his Department have made to the Government of Cameroon on recent alleged massacres in southern Cameroon.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110340","110340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780474","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the Government of Cameroon and representatives of the Anglophone community in that country to negotiate in peace talks to put an end to recent alleged massacres in southern Cameroon.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110341","110341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780475","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the potential merits of a UN-mandated global arms embargo against Burma.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110301","110301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780476","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Turkey on human rights in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110406","110406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780477","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Sudan on the humanitarian and military situation in South Sudan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110402","110402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780478","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Malaysia on the introduction of public caning in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110400","110400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780479","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Kazakhstan counterpart on the treatment of the Protestant Source of Life and New Life Churches; and what steps he is taking to promote religious freedoms in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110387","110387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780480","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with to his Nigerian counterpart on the role of the International Centre of Interfaith, Peace and Harmony in promoting an end to religious violence in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110388","110388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780481","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Turkish counterpart on the treatment of Pastor Andrew Brunson in respect of religious minorities and fair and equitable access to justice for those minorities in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110389","110389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780482","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with governments of the British Overseas Territories on the treatment of LGBT people.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110374","110374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780483","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the treatment of LGBT people in the British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110375","110375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780484","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will make representations to the UN's Security Council on introducing a resolution that calls for an end to the military campaign and violence in Rakhine State and demands (a) immediate and unimpeded access for international humanitarian organisations to populations in need in Rakhine State, (b) immediate and unhindered access for international monitors and journalists to Rakhine State, (c) access by the UN mandated fact-finding mission to Myanmar to carry out its work unhindered, by providing visas to the members of the mission and full access for the mission to meet civilian and military officials and (d) the Myanmar authorities return all Rohingya refugees and displaced people to their homes and places of origin in Myanmar safely, voluntarily and with dignity.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110372","110372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780485","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the comment by the Joint Minister of State for International Development and the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, the hon. Member for Penrith and The Border, that in almost every case the only way to deal with British citizens who have been fighting in Iraq is to kill them was a statement of Government policy.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110297","110297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780486","2017-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Tanzania about reports that pregnant teenage women in that country will be allowed to study in state schools both during and after pregnancy.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110298","110298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780487","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the creation of a humanitarian corridor to allow aid agencies and NGOs access to people in need in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110449","110449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780488","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the shortages of medical supplies, food and water in Yemen on the humanitarian situation in Yemen; and what support he plans to provide to authorities in Yemen to mitigate ill effects of those shortages.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110448","110448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780489","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Gulf State counterparts on the effect of UK arms sales to Saudi Arabia on the ongoing humanitarian crisis in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110450","110450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780490","2017-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received from civil society groups on the effects of UK arms sales to Saudi Arabia on the ongoing humanitarian crisis in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110451","110451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780491","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency departments in each month of the last six financial years with (a) asthma, (b) bronchitis and (c) bronchiolitis were aged (i) under one, (ii) one to four, (iii) five to nine, (iv) 10 to 14, (v) 15 to 19 and (vi) 20 to 24.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110457","110457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780492","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to recognised local authority mental health services as a key service alongside the NHS and to ensure that the statutory functions of local authority mental health services are adequately funded.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110445","110445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780493","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve the sharing of medical records between medical institutions and trusts for mental health service users.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110444","110444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780494","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his Department's policy that rules on pharmacy supervision should be changed to all non-pharmacists to supervise the sale and supply of prescription medicines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110277","110277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780495","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) there are sufficient psychiatric beds to meet demand and (b) out-of-area placements are avoided.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110274","110274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780496","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Yellow Cards submitted to the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency on the HPV vaccination have been classified as serious in the last three years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110248","110248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780497","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential merits of introducing a cap on care costs for older people.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110249","110249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780498","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what timeline he plans to consult on and publish a Green Paper on adult social care.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110250","110250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780499","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what penalties are imposed on NHS hospitals which fail to follow his Department's guidance on charging staff, patients and visitors to park their vehicles in NHS car parks.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110284","110284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780500","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress is being made on the inquiry into the Primodos hormone-based pregnancy test; and when he plans to publish the report.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110285","110285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780501","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the Welsh Government's decision to introduce minimum unit pricing for alcohol.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110265","110265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780502","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how often the Pharmacy Rebalancing Board has met; and whether the minutes of those meetings are publicly available.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110278","110278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780503","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has received policy recommendations from the Pharmacy Rebalancing Board on pharmacy supervision; and what the timetable is for the receipt of further such recommendations.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110279","110279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780504","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential patient safety implications of allowing non-pharmacists to supervise the sale and supply of prescription medicines.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110280","110280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780505","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding the Government has allocated for the Female Genital Mutilation Prevention Programme.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110215","110215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780506","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to implement the Female Genital Mutilation Risk Indication System.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110216","110216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780507","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS 111 calls in each (a) region of England and (b) clinical commissioning group area were triaged to the ambulance service in the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110226","110226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780508","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GPs who will work in the NHS in each year until 2022.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110243","110243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780509","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the trends in the level of obesity in children in the last 10 years; and how those trends compare with data from other countries.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110245","110245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780510","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NHS England's publications Biological Medicines Commissioning Framework published on 12 September 2017 and What is a Biosimilar Medicine published on 24 September 2015, what steps he has taken to ensure that patients in England will have the right to an informed discussion and consultation with their clinician before a decision is made to switch them from their existing biologic treatment to a biosimilar treatment.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110267","110267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780511","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which tickets for journeys he took which are set out  out in the transparency release, entitled Ministerial gifts, hospitality, travel and external meetings: April to June 2017, published on 13 October 2017, were (a) first, (b) business, (c) economy or (d) any other class.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110174","110174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780512","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings of the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists report, Maternal mental health - Women's voices, published in February 2017, that states that only seven per cent of women with pregnancy-related mental health challenges, such as post-natal depression, will receive the specialist care they need.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110199","110199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780513","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what average waiting time after referral was for treatment of mental health challenges experienced in pregnancy and the first postnatal year in (a) York Central constituency, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber Region and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110203","110203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780514","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many beds there were in specialist mother and baby mental health units in (a) York Central constituency, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber Region and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110204","110204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780515","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women with a maternal mental health condition have been transferred out-of-area for specialist treatment (a) nationally, (b) from York to Leeds and (c) from York to elsewhere in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110205","110205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780516","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to raise awareness of mental health challenges experienced in pregnancy and the first postnatal year.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110206","110206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780517","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to improve bereavement care following miscarriage or stillbirth.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110207","110207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780518","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NHS England has to (a) engage with patient groups to explain biosimilar medicines and (b) discuss how such medicines can be integrated into patient care in a safe and sustainable way.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110182","110182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780519","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Yellow Cards submitted to the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency for the HPV vaccination were classified as serious; and how many of those cases were reviewed to establish whether the patient had returned to full health in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110360","110360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780520","2017-11-07","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will reinstate vaccinations against meningococcal serogroup c for infants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110385","110385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780521","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence evaluation of the Duchenne muscular dystrophy treatment Exondys 51.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110412","110412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780522","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to ensure that NHS England and Sarepta Therapeutics conduct pricing negotiations at an early stage in the evaluation of Exondys 51.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110413","110413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780523","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the capacity of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence Highly Specialised Technologies Programme to evaluate new treatments for rare conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110414","110414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780524","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects blood tests for pancreatitis to be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110399","110399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780525","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people infected by blood transfusions have contracted (a) hepatitis and (b) HIV in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110408","110408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780526","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people with HIV in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110409","110409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780527","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in China on exchange of information on drugs and medicine between the UK and China.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110403","110403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780528","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects Aithon DS1517499 to be available for prostate cancer treatment on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110404","110404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780529","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the transanal submucosal resection technique to be available for bowel treatment on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110405","110405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780530","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an estimate of the cost of a national roll-out of street triage services in mental health and policing.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110289","110289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780531","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NHS England publication, GE3 Hospital Medicines Optimisation and the Biological Medicines Commissioning Framework on 12 September 2017, what criteria his Department has set to determine the best value biologic.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110253","110253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780532","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of the nine street triage pilots on mental health and policing which it commissioned.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110288","110288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780533","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how many and which NHS hospitals have failed to follow its guidance on charging staff, patients and visitors to park their vehicles in NHS car parks.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110292","110292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780534","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which categories of claimants of universal credit are entitled to claim free prescriptions; and whether he has plans to review that entitlement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110322","110322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780535","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's guidance to NHS hospitals is on charging staff, patients and visitors to park their vehicles in NHS car parks.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110291","110291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780536","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure the prescription exemption checking service distinguishes between people intentionally defrauding the NHS and cases where a prepayment prescription certificate expires; and whether fines should be imposed in both circumstances.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110326","110326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780537","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of prescriptions which are scrutinised by the prescription exemption checking service annually.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110327","110327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780538","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount that has recovered by the prescription exemption checking service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110328","110328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780539","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish a new alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110329","110329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780540","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse is of the prescription exemption checking service.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110330","110330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780541","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of breaches of guidance of mixed-sex sleeping arrangements that occurred at the Royal Bolton Hospital in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110366","110366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780542","2017-11-02","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which categories of claimants of universal credit are entitled to claim free dental treatment; and whether he has plans to review that entitlement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110320","110320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780543","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which patient groups were consulted in the development of the Biological Medicines Commissioning Framework, published on 12 September 2017.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110368","110368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780544","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost per digital transaction of prescription prepayment certificates in October 2018.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110347","110347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780545","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the effect that private sector usage of NHS premises and facilities has had on NHS waiting times in the last three years.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110355","110355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780546","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the roles and responsibilities of his Department's Pharmacy Rebalancing Board are.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110356","110356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780547","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential cost to the public purse of universal free prescriptions in NHS England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110331","110331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780548","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of minor ailment clinics in reducing demand for GP services.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110332","110332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780549","2017-11-01","Department of Health","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients with an eating disorder were treated at a specialist inpatient eating disorder clinic out of area in each year from 2011 to 2016; and for how many days on average did each such patient receive such treatment.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110352","110352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780550","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has put in place to ensure that groups run by people supporting extremist views are excluded from working with public sector institutions covered by the Prevent strategy, including the police.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110367","110367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780551","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109740, on Cybercrime: surveys, how much has been paid from the public purse to IPSOS Mori for running the National Crime Security Tracker survey.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110342","110342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780552","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2017 to Question 109366, on asylum: applications, what number of decision makers constitute the level that allows her Department to progress cases in line with service standards.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110343","110343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780553","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her oral contribution to the Home Affairs Committee, on 17 October 2017, which police leaders have confirmed to her that they have sufficient resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110335","110335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780554","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits  of using an exclusion order on Mr Tapan Ghosh, prior to his arrival to the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110313","110313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780555","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Extremism Analysis Unit conducted research into the views of Mr Tapan Ghosh prior to his arrival to the UK in October 2017.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110314","110314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780556","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to conclude her consideration of the Independent Police Complaints Commission's draft statutory guidance on best evidence in cases involving death and serious injury.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110310","110310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780557","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for publication of her Department's response to the consultation on the Investigatory Powers Act Codes of Practice; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110324","110324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780558","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the introduction of stalking protection orders in 2018 on the number of police investigations of alleged cases of stalking.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110307","110307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780559","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Compass contracts for housing asylum seekers.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110300","110300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780560","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to introduce bereavement counselling for families where there has been a death in police custody in cases where families are not entitled to support from the National Homicide Service.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110294","110294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780561","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been victims of identity theft in each of the past five years; and what steps she is taking to reduce the prevalence of identity theft.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110407","110407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780562","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many failed asylum seekers have been deported on non-civilian aircraft in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110436","110436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780563","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of deporting a failed asylum seeker on a non-civilian chartered flight in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110437","110437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780564","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle online jihadi terrorist propaganda as a means of radicalisation.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110378","110378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780565","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 2 December 2016 to Question 54519, what the timetable is for the publication of the Government's review of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110362","110362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780566","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether test purchase operations have been conducted to monitor the compliance of (a) online and (b) offline retailers with the provisions of the Poisons Act 1972; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110184","110184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780567","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations her Department has received from (a) police forces, (b) their associated governance and advisory bodies, (c) housing and homelessness non-governmental organisations and (d) policing unions on the extent and effect on policing of homeless people coming or being directed to police stations in search of shelter.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110180","110180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780568","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff hours her Department spent confirming whether employees have the right to work in the UK in response to queries from or on behalf of (a) employers and (b) employees in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110181","110181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780569","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on programmes similar to Operation Constrain in other countries; what discussions she has had with her counterparts in other countries on managing the return of Daesh fighters to their countries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110210","110210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780570","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether people returning from Syria and Iraq who fall within the scope of Operation Constrain are permitted to return to the communities in the UK which they left to travel to the Middle East.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110211","110211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780571","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the budget is for Operation Constrain.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110212","110212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780572","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the threshold of evidence is for prosecutions against returning Daesh fighters under Operation Constrain; and whether that threshold has been changed in anticipation of an expected increase in the number of such people returning to the UK.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110213","110213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780573","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which tickets relating to which journeys set out in the transparency release, entitled Ministerial overseas travel, April to June 2017, published on 13 October 2017, were (a) first, (b) business, (c) economy and (d) any other class.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110171","110171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780574","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of her Department's resources for UK Visas and Immigration when UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110160","110160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780575","2017-11-06","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the policing budget was spent on (a) cyber-crime and (b) counter-terrorism in (i) the UK and (ii) Nottinghamshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110233","110233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780576","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what restrictions Operation Constrain places on (a) the communication with each other, (b) travel around the UK and to other countries, (c) activities conducted online and (d) other forms of interaction with previous networks within the UK of returning Daesh fighters.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110228","110228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780577","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that unaccompanied child asylum seekers in France eligible to care in the UK under the (a) Dubs Amendment and (b) Dublin III Regulations are aware of their rights.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110237","110237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780578","2017-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government has taken to create a national process to co-ordinate the collection and dissemination of all forced marriage protection orders and female genital mutilation protection orders.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110218","110218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780579","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's advertisement for a Lead Commissioner for Counter Extremism, published on 17 September 2017, who the 90 civil society groups are which are cited as having been funded; which regions each of those groups operate in; how much each such group was funded for; and what type of extremism each such group tackles.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110286","110286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780580","2017-11-02","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's advertisement for a Lead Commissioner for Counter Extremism, published on 17 September 2017, when disaggregated hate crime data by victim religion will be published.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110287","110287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780581","2017-11-03","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department will publish its response to the firearms licensing fees public consultation.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110299","110299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780582","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that the accommodation provided under the Compass contracts are fit for human habitation.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110456","110456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780583","2017-11-01","Home Office","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to assist Prevent in its duty to inhibit public sector engagement with extremist groups.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110455","110455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780584","2017-11-02","Department for International Development","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps the Government has taken to support meeting the specific targets on (a) violence against women and girls, (b) female genital mutilation and (c) child and early forced marriage within the United Nations Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110217","110217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780585","2017-11-02","Department for International Development","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department is spending on dialogue-based peace building work in South Sudan in 2017-18; and what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of such work to date.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110225","110225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/780586","2017-11-02","Department for International Development","2017-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that humanitarian aid can reach civilians in (a) East Ghouta and (b) other besieged areas inside Syria.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110227","110227"
