"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43824","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what categories of personal information are contained on each relevant database managed by his Department and its executive agencies; on what date each category of information was first collected; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192728","192728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43825","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many breaches of security have been reported at (a) HM Courts Service, (b) the Land Registry, (c) the National Offender Management Service, (d) the National Archives, (e) the Office of the Public Guardian and (f) the Tribunals Service in each year since May 2010; and what procedures each agency follows when a breach of security involves the disclosure of personal data.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192730","192730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43826","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff of each (a) prison and (b) young offender institutions in the North East were made redundant in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192684","192684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43827","2014-04-02","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which (a) prisons and (b) young offender institutions in the North East have had members of staff take detached duty since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192683","192683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43828","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects to launch the consultation on the creation of a status of guardian of the affairs of a missing person.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192669","192669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43829","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much Essex Probation (a) budgeted for and (b) spent on security in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192561","192561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43830","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what complaints against Essex Probation were upheld in each month since November 2013; what (a) response was made and (b) steps were taken by Essex Probation in each such case; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192559","192559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43831","2014-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions there have been under the Computer Misuse Act 1990 in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192534","192534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43832","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to announce the membership of the board to succeed Essex Probation Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192560","192560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43833","2014-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2014, Official Report, column 209W, on the Computer Misuse Act 1990, how his Department measures compliance with the Government's cyber security strategy when rehabilitating and managing offenders convicted under the Computer Misuse Act 1990; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192506","192506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43834","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which towns in England and Wales have more than one court in the same building.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192528","192528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43835","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department plans to pay each member of Essex Probation Trust Board in each of the next six months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192621","192621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43836","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he plans to take to increase the cost-effectiveness of Essex Probation in the next 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192563","192563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43837","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of the public have attended each meeting of the Essex Probation Trust in each month since November 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192584","192584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43838","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made in the winding up of Essex Probation Trust; how much he plans to pay members of the Essex Probation Board in redundancy payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192585","192585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43839","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what mandatory training is given to prison officers to help them identify prisoners susceptible to being radicalised.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192529","192529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43840","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners in each adult and youth prison in England and Wales identified as Muslim on 1 January of each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192530","192530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43841","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners in each adult and youth prison in England and Wales were identified as (a) a radicalised Muslim or (b) at risk of being radicalised in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192531","192531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43842","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a record of Essex Probation's government procurement card transactions indicating the (a) date, (b) merchant and (c) amount of each such transaction since November 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192583","192583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43843","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress Essex Probation Trust has made since November 2013 on the integrated Offender Management project; how much has been spent by Essex Probation Trust on that project to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192582","192582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43844","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of (a) the lifespan and (b) health outcomes of prisoners and young offenders.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192613","192613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43845","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times the Chief Executive of Essex Probation has met hon. Members since November 2013; when and for what purpose each such meeting took place; where each such meeting took place; what the duration of each such meeting was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192581","192581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43846","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners of each (a) ethnicity, (b) country of origin and (c) gender are held in the UK.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192615","192615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43847","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners in the (a) whole secure estate, (b) adult male secure estate, (c) adult female secure estate, (d) youth male secure estate and (e) youth female secure estate identified as Muslim on 1 January in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192526","192526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43848","2014-03-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2014, Official Report, column 1830W, on terrorism, if she will amend her Answer to take account of the testimony given by Dr Richard Haass to the US Congressional Sub-committee of Foreign Relations on 12 March 2014 on the extent of her knowledge of on-the-runs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192745","192745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43849","2014-03-26","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the comments made on 11 March 2014 by Dr Richard Haass to the US Congressional Sub-committee of Foreign Relations on the likelihood of violence returning to daily life in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192702","192702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43850","2014-03-24","Scotland Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the extent of the use of zero-hours contracts in Scotland; and in which areas of employment such use is most prevalent.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192674","192674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43851","2014-03-24","Scotland Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make an assessment of the financial benefits of Scotland remaining part of the UK.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192675","192675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43852","2014-03-24","Scotland Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of Scottish independence on industry in Scotland.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192673","192673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43853","2014-03-24","Scotland Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his policy is on the cost of decommissioning the nuclear power stations at Torness and Hunterston if Scotland votes for independence.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192544","192544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43854","2014-03-24","Scotland Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his policy is on the cost of decommissioning and clean up of the site at Dounreay if Scotland votes for independence.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192545","192545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43855","2014-03-24","Scotland Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his policy is on the cost of the decommissioning and safe dismantling of the remains of the nuclear powered submarines anchored at Rosyth if Scotland votes for independence.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192546","192546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43856","2014-03-24","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to ensure provision of adequate rolling stock to serve the Hull-Manchester train route from April 2015.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192519","192519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43857","2014-03-24","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy that the new Transpennine Express franchise due to begin in 2015 maintains hourly direct services between Hull and Manchester.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192520","192520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43858","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the level of cross-subsidy between fare paying passengers and those using the Concessionary Travel Scheme (a) generally and (b) in rural areas.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192473","192473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43860","2014-03-24","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the joint investment between his Department and First Great Western to fund additional standard class capacity and a refresh of first class is provided by his Department.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192533","192533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43861","2014-03-24","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2014, Official Report, column 456W, on motorways: repairs and maintenance, what the reasons are for the discrepancy between the figures of eight deaths in the preceding three years and 1,747 injuries in the preceding 12 months of people repairing motorways stated by the Highways Agency in a press release dated 21 October 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192569","192569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43862","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans the Government has to improve the rail infrastructure on the North Kent rail line.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192670","192670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43863","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of implementing the recommendations in the Civil Aviation Authority's safety review of helicopter operations in the offshore oil and gas industry on the annual number of passenger-carrying helicopter flights in that industry.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192716","192716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43864","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 May 2013, Official Report, column 335W, on the Merchant Shipping (Diving Safety) Regulations 2002, whether it is still his policy to pursue revocation of the regulations.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192714","192714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43865","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current level of (a) use and (b) availability is amongst offshore helicopter passengers in the oil and gas industry of emergency breathing systems that meet Category A of the Civil Aviation Authority's relevant technical specifications.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192715","192715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43866","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 May 2013, Official Report, column 335W, on the Merchant Shipping (Diving Safety) Regulations 2002, what discussions (a) Ministers in his Department and (b) officials from the Maritime and Coastguard Agency have held with the Health and Safety Executive regarding the implications for diver safety or revoking the regulations; and what the outcomes were of those discussions.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192713","192713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43867","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department used in the decision to include the Garden Bridge in the Government's National Infrastructure Plan.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192746","192746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43868","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of an extension to Crewe of the first phase of High Speed 2 on the (a) route through Lichfield constituency and (b) need for an additional railway line north of the City of Lichfield connecting the end of Phase one to the West Coast mainline.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192537","192537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43869","2014-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken from an application for reconsideration of an employment and support allowance decision to a decision being made on the case was in each month since October 2013.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192738","192738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43870","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the criteria are for self-employed people to be eligible for contributions-based jobseekers' allowance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192697","192697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43871","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to take steps to ensure that employers with employees who earn less than £10,000 per year will be legally obliged to provide those employees with an auto-enrolment pension scheme.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192722","192722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43872","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of work capability assessments appeals that were found in favour of the claimant heard by January 2014, were awarded zero points at the initial decision; and what proportion of such decisions were awarded to (a) the WRAG and (b) the Support Group.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192577","192577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43873","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department issues on (a) the amount of class 1 National Insurance contributions an individual must have made and (b) for how long such contributions must be paid in order to be eligible for contribution-based jobseekers' allowance; and how his Department makes such guidance available to the public.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192696","192696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43874","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which organisations for deaf people his Department consulted before the Access to Work guidance on support workers was amended.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192591","192591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43875","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the maximum grants for funding support workers under the Access to Work scheme were determined.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192589","192589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43876","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent meetings he has had with representatives of the deaf community.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192590","192590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43877","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was paid in disability living allowance and personal independence payments to recipients in (a) Scotland and (b) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192484","192484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43878","2014-03-20","Cabinet Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people and what proportion of the working age population have been in receipt of jobseeker's allowance for over (a) two and (b) five years in (i) Scotland and (ii) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192483","192483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43879","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department provides to assist deaf people in seeking employment.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192486","192486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43880","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was paid in jobseeker's allowance to recipients in (a) Scotland and (b) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192485","192485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43881","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make the mobility component of the disability living allowance available to children with life-limiting conditions under the age of three who are technology or ventilator dependent.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192518","192518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43882","2014-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of disability living allowance claims took longer than 40 days to process in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192527","192527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43883","2014-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he has received and approved any apprenticeship standards and assessment approaches as outlined in the timetable in the October 2013 report The Future of Apprenticeships in England: Guidance for Trailblazers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192741","192741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43884","2014-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the annual usage figures are for the National Apprenticeship Service online search function.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192742","192742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43885","2014-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many employers have accessed the National Apprenticeship Service online; and how many such employers have entered into contracts with training providers following use of the National Apprenticeship Service.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192743","192743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43886","2014-03-20","HM Treasury","2014-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the possibility of reducing VAT on local procurement; and whether he has any plans to propose such a reduction.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192657","192657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43887","2014-03-25","HM Treasury","2014-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the tourism industry in (a) Northern Ireland, (b) Scotland and (c) England and Wales of the decision by the government of Ireland to retain a reduced rate of VAT on tourism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192754","192754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43889","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how long the UK plans to host Syrian refugees who come as part of the resettlement deal; and whether such refugees will be issued with a visa for a specified time period.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192656","192656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43890","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned or undertaken on links between mental health conditions and Type 1 and Type 2 diabetes. [R]","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192599","192599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43891","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many diabetes-related limb amputations took place in the NHS in each year since 2008; what assessment he has made of the proportion of those amputations which may have been preventable; and if he will make a statement. [R]","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192601","192601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43892","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if Public Health England will develop a template national service specification for the delivery of NHS health check services.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192603","192603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43893","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of geographical variations in the rate of limb amputations among people with diabetes; what steps he has taken to reduce such variations; and if he will make a statement. [R]","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192602","192602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43894","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment Public Health England has made of and what evidence that body has collected on the effectiveness of the NHS health check programme in helping to diagnose diabetes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192604","192604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43895","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans Public Health England has to increase the number of people diagnosed with diabetes through the NHS health check programme.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192605","192605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43896","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department (a) has taken and (b) plans to take in the next 12 months to increase the number of mental health specialists in the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192663","192663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43897","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received from experts in diabetes on the NHS health check programme in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192606","192606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43898","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Public Health England is taking to encourage investment by local authorities in services which will help prevent the onset of diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192607","192607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43899","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department (a) has taken and (b) plans to take in the next 12 months to improve detection of mental health illnesses in people under 24 years of age; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192664","192664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43900","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how Academic Health Science Networks improve the care of people with diabetes. [R]","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192608","192608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43901","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to collect accurate figures on the costs of treating diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192609","192609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43902","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the proportion of people younger than 65 years old with mental health problems who receive adequate care; what steps he plans to take in each of the next 12 months to ensure that such people receive adequate care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192665","192665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43903","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of the March 2012 letter from Simon Reeve in his Department to the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence concerning the appraisal of the treatment abiraterone for prostate cancer.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192610","192610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43904","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of links between eating disorders and diabetes; what steps NHS England is taking to ensure that eating disorder services provide support to people (a) diagnosed with and (b) at risk of developing diabetes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192600","192600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43905","2014-03-24","Home Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to regularly review directions given under section 94 of the Telecommunications Act 1984.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192753","192753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43906","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the outcome of the recent Illegal Wildlife Trade conference and the resulting London Declaration; and what steps she plans to take to ensure that animal welfare is a key element of her Department's response to that declaration.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192662","192662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43907","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answers of 5 February 2014, Official Report, column 293W and 28 February 2014, Official Report, column 548W, on prisoners: foreign nationals, which three countries have the next largest number of foreign nationals in UK prisons; and what steps he is taking to return those offenders to secure detention in their own countries.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192744","192744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43908","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what agreement his Department has reached with the Welsh Government regarding the funding of electrification of the Great Western Line to Swansea and the Valleys lines.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192659","192659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43909","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to develop the North Wales line from Crewe to Holyhead in conjunction with the building of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192660","192660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43910","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of whether the London to Holyhead line will become a local stopping service following the building of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192661","192661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43911","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the London to Holyhead railway service will remain an express service after the creation of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192658","192658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43912","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consideration he has given to exempting motorists from being prosecuted for traffic light offences if they have committed the offence while making way for an emergency vehicle.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192542","192542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43913","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicle crossings of the Thames were made through the Rotherhithe and Blackwall tunnels in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192748","192748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43914","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission a study of the case for a new cycle and pedestrian crossing of the Thames east of Tower Bridge.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192749","192749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43915","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many journeys through the Rotherhithe tunnel were made by bicycle in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192750","192750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43916","2014-03-24","Department for Transport","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of new buses in the UK outside London are fitted with audio visual announcements.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192752","192752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43917","2014-03-20","Wales Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of pupils at each (a) primary and (b) secondary school in Islwyn constituency is eligible for free school meals.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192747","192747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43918","2014-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the processing time target is for personal independence payment (PIP) claims; and what proportion of such claims took longer than this target time to process since the introduction of PIPs.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192751","192751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43919","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the advantages to deaf people of funding a team of interpreters through the Access to Work scheme rather than being assigned a single interpreter by their employer.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192543","192543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44020","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure more employers offer apprenticeships to 16 to 18 year-olds.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903193","903193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44353","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that children and adoptive parents receive support beyond the initial stages of the adoption process.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903202","903202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44357","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to reform faith-based admissions to free schools.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903211","903211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45149","2014-03-26","Wales Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the number of workers in Wales employed on zero-hours contracts; and what assessment he has made of trends in that number since 2010.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903230","903230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45150","2014-03-26","Wales Office","2014-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the future performance of the manufacturing sector in Wales.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903228","903228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43330","2014-03-19","Attorney General","2014-03-17","To ask the Attorney General, what the total cost to his Department has been of challenging the decision of the Information Commissioner on the publication of letters from HRH the Prince of Wales.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192074","192074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43331","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in Harlow constituency were enrolled in adult skills training in each of the last 10 years; and what estimate he has made of the number of adults in (a) Harlow constituency, (b) Essex and (c) East Anglia who were unable to (i) read and (ii) write in that time period.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192245","192245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43332","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency, (b) Yorkshire and Humber and (c) England received Enterprise Finance Guarantee loans between (i) May 2011 and May 2012 and (ii) May 2012 and May 2013; and what the total value of such loans guaranteed was.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192281","192281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43333","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses were registered in Brigg and Goole constituency in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192282","192282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43334","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the approved cables initiative; and whether he has considered bringing forward legislative proposals to ensure that only cables compliant with British, European or International standards which carry a third-party certificate are sold in the UK.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192388","192388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43335","2014-03-19","Cabinet Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of children being cared for by a single parent in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192279","192279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43336","2014-03-19","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-17","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 510W, on Electoral Register: young people, what steps his Department has taken to circulate the Rock Enrol! resources to (a) hon. Members, (b) members of the European Parliament, (c) members of the Scottish Parliament, members of the Legislative Assembly and Assembly members, (d) local councillors, (e) schools, colleges and universities and (f) local education authorities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192328","192328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43337","2014-03-19","Cabinet Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change there has been in median gross weekly earnings for (a) men and (b) women in Vale of Clwyd constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192077","192077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43338","2014-03-19","Cabinet Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of jobseekers over the age of (a) 50 and (b) 60 years in Vale of Clwyd constituency.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192078","192078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43339","2014-03-19","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-17","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 28 Janaury 2014, Official Report, column 510W, on the electoral register, what estimate his Department has made of the number of young people registered through Bite the Ballot; what the average cost to the public purse was of each registration through Bite the Ballot; and what the average cost to the public purse has been of each registration arising from the registration campaigns of (a) the Electoral Commission and (b) his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192310","192310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43340","2014-03-20","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effects on revenues of (a) changes in the top rate of tax and (b) a reduction in the top rate from 45p to (i) 44p, (ii) 43p, (iii) 42p, (iv) 41p and (v) 40p.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192296","192296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43341","2014-03-20","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of multi-ticketing on the revenue accruing to the Exchequer from air passenger duty in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192302","192302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43342","2014-03-20","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the change in employment levels of (a) a freeze in fuel duty and (b) a reduction in fuel duty by 3 pence or more in the final year of this Parliament.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192288","192288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43343","2014-03-20","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he next plans to meet members of FairFuelUK to discuss (a) a freeze in fuel duty and (b) a reduction in fuel duty by 3 pence or more.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192289","192289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43344","2014-03-20","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the economic effect of (a) a rise in fuel duty, (b) freezing fuel duty, (c) cutting fuel duty by 3 pence or more in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192285","192285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43345","2014-03-20","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) evaluated on the (i) economic effects and (ii) effects on the average motorist of (A) a freeze in fuel duty and (B) a reduction in fuel duty by 3 pence or more.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192286","192286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43346","2014-03-20","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to commit to a real terms cut in fuel duty in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192287","192287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43347","2014-03-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many affordable houses were built in Harlow in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192244","192244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43348","2014-03-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals resulted in local authority decisions being overturned by the planning inspector in South Staffordshire in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192251","192251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43349","2014-03-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) managerial and (b) clerical local authority staff in Enfield were paid more than (i) £42,000, (ii) £69,000 and (iii) £100,000 in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192257","192257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43350","2014-03-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what consultation he has had with volunteers on parish councils and other local authorities on proposals to allow local authority public meetings to be filmed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192276","192276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43351","2014-03-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the National Housing Advice Service will continue to deliver the Homelessness Gold Standard in 2014-15.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192075","192075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43352","2014-03-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations he has received on filming of local authority public meetings by the media and members of the public; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192330","192330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43353","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of all new housing in each local authority area since March 2010 was classed as (a) social and (b) affordable.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192103","192103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43354","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of housing starts in each English local authority area since March 2010 were classed as (a) social and (b) affordable.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192101","192101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43355","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many houses have been started in each English local authority area since March 2010; and what proportion of existing housing stock these represented.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192102","192102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43356","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of domestic fires in the private rented sector in England that have occurred as a result of (a) smoking and (b) electrical fires since 2010.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192094","192094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43357","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what monitoring mechanisms his Department uses to inform policy making and priority setting to reduce inequalities for ethnic communities not recognised on the national census.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192347","192347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43358","2014-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to her Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 148W, on the National Museum of Computing, what response she has had to her letter; and what progress the Arts Council has made in mediation of the disagreement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192292","192292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43359","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many firms with contracts with his Department employ cyber reservists.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192340","192340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43360","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the physical fitness criteria are for recruitment to the cyber reserve force.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192334","192334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43361","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to help schools that are unable to deliver free infant school meals in September 2014 because of a lack of capital funding.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192335","192335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43362","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what education funding per pupil was in (a) Staffordshire and (b) Brent in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192300","192300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43363","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the implementation of The School Information (England) (Amendment) Regulations 2012. [R]","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192341","192341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43364","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve the education of children on the autistic spectrum.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192331","192331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43365","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy trusts account returns remain outstanding.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192304","192304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43366","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy trusts did not submit their account returns on time in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192305","192305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43367","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils in (a) Chelmsford constituency and (b) Essex continued into (i) further education, (ii) higher education (iii) apprenticeships in each the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192350","192350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43368","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of state-funded schools that have opened since September 2011 have changed their headteacher since opening.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192322","192322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43369","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of academy trusts did not submit their account returns on time (a) in the current year, (b) in 2013, (c) in 2012 and (d) in 2011.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192306","192306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43370","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start centres have reduced the services they offer since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192307","192307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43371","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of maintained schools have changed their headteacher since September 2011.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192308","192308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43372","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of free schools have changed their headteacher since opening.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192321","192321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43373","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department gives to teachers and teaching support staff on supporting children with type one diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192297","192297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43374","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training schemes his Department has in place to enable teachers to support children who have type one diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192298","192298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43375","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of maintained schools that have opened since September 2011 have changed their headteacher since that date.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192313","192313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43376","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the education funding per pupil is in (a) Staffordshire and (b) Brent for 2014-15.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192248","192248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43377","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of state-funded schools have changed their head teacher since September 2011.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192316","192316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43378","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in Brigg and Goole constituency participate in the Schools Direct Programme.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192277","192277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43379","2014-03-24","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of teachers teaching in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Essex and (d) Chelmsford constituency undertook specialist training on educational provision for children and young people on the autism spectrum in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192349","192349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43380","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start centres have fewer staff now than in May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192314","192314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43381","2014-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will set up an independent committee to the review the effect of the pilot badger culls on bovine TB ahead of any wider roll-out of the cull.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192315","192315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43382","2014-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the objectives were of his visit to the Mondelez factory on 13 March 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192312","192312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43383","2014-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 552W, on forests, what records (a) his Department and (b) the Environment Agency keeps of the projects it has funded and the performance of each against its objectives.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192327","192327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43384","2014-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, columns 552-3W, on forests: finance, in which parliamentary constituencies the unsuccessful grant applications were located.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192311","192311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43385","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many reports of mis-cutting before each method of religiously exempted non-stunning he has received in each year since 2004, broken down by type of animal.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192079","192079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43386","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many reports of mis-stunning before slaughter for each method of stunning he has received in each year since 2004, broken down by type of animal.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192080","192080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43387","2014-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the UK has made to Israel about the recent settler land encroachment in the West Bank villages of Salfeet, Isaka, Broqeen, Yasouf and Hares.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192100","192100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43388","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Venezuela on freedom of press and speech and the detention of political opponents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192259","192259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43389","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on political unrest in Venezuela; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192260","192260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43390","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of conditions in Camp Liberty in Iraq; and what estimate he has made of the amount of food and medicine received at that site in the last three months.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192261","192261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43391","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the government of Iraq on the welfare of residents in Camp Liberty.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192262","192262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43392","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) male and (b) female postgraduate students in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192263","192263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43393","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of undergraduate students in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192264","192264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43394","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding Wolverhampton City Primary Care Trust received in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192268","192268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43395","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding South Staffordshire Primary Care Trust received in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192269","192269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43396","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence is reviewing the availability of eculizumab for the treatment of atypical haemolytic uraemic syndrome.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192272","192272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43397","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with (a) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and (b) NHS England on the availability of funding for treatments for atypical haemolytic uraemic syndrome since 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192271","192271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43398","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that patient data does not leave GP surgeries under care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192283","192283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43399","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many reported incidents of self-harm there were by people under the age of 18 years in South Staffordshire in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192270","192270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43400","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) most recently reported and (b) planned deficit is in NHS England's specialised services commissioning budget.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192274","192274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43401","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people (a) living with atypical haemolytic uraemic syndrome (aHUS) and (b) who are diagnosed each year with aHUS.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192275","192275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43402","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether commercial re-use licences for hospital episode statistics and other medical information gathered from NHS patients remain in operation.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192291","192291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43403","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve health outcomes for people on the autistic spectrum.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192240","192240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43404","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) clinical, (b) management and (c) clerical NHS staff in Essex were paid more than (i) £50,000, (ii) £65,738 and (iii) £100,000 in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192242","192242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43405","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the efficacy and quality of care of patients with cancer in (a) Harlow constituency, (b) Essex, (c) the East of England and (d) England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192247","192247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43406","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) clinical, (b) managerial and (c) clerical NHS staff in (i) Enfield, (ii) London and (iii) Barnet and Chase Farm Hospital Trust were paid more than (A) £42,000, (B) £69,000 and (C) £100,000 in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192258","192258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43407","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding Lewisham Primary Care Trust received in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192252","192252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43408","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding the Heart of Birmingham Primary Care Trust received in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192253","192253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43409","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding Sandwell Primary Care Trust received in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192254","192254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43410","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding Dudley Primary Care Trust received in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192255","192255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43411","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what planned items of expenditure against NHS England's specialised services commissioning budget in 2013-14 have been (a) cancelled and (b) delayed in the 2013-14 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192273","192273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43412","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children of (a) pre-school, (b) primary school and (c) secondary school age were diagnosed with type one diabetes in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192295","192295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43413","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children have presented at accident and emergency departments direct from school requiring treatment for type one diabetes-related problems in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192299","192299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43414","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on implementing the recommendations of the Marmot Review on health inequalities in England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192105","192105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43415","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of multidrug-resistant TB were recorded in each region in the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192067","192067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43416","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were treated with the gamma knife at University College London hospitals between 1 April 2008 and 1 April 2013; from which NHS trusts they were referred; and how payment was made for their treatment.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192332","192332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43417","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his Answer of 13 March 2014, Official Report, column 355W, on medical records: databases, whether Atos has bid for the care.data extraction contract.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192336","192336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43418","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued on outstanding cases of maladministration surrounding the care of sufferers of myalgic encephalomyelitis, fibromyalgia and dysphagia.","Biography information for Mr Jeremy Browne","Mr Jeremy Browne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192072","192072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43419","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that people with (a) myalgic encephalomyelitis, (b) fibromyalgia and (c) dysphagia receive the treatment they need and help with the cost of treatment.","Biography information for Mr Jeremy Browne","Mr Jeremy Browne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192071","192071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43420","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the National Midwifery Council on its membership costs and their impact on recruitment and retention in the profession.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192073","192073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43421","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to find new treatments to tackle multidrug-resistant TB; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192066","192066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43422","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the recommendations of the Marmot Review on health inequalities in England are being implemented across all relevant government departments.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192106","192106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43423","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission a national survey of investment in mental health services in 2013-14.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192108","192108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43424","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the risk of female genital mutilation is assessed under immigration rules for applicants for asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192329","192329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43425","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2014, Official Report, column 182W, on Daniel Morgan, from which (a) individuals and (b) organisations documents have been received; what protocols with relevant organisations are required; and if she will place in the Library a copy of all (i) minutes and (ii) documents from the meetings of the Independent Panel held to date.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192069","192069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43426","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2014, Official Report, column 325W, on the Child Exploitation and Online Protection Centre, how many NCA employees who work in Child Exploitation and Online Protection Command have arrest powers.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192070","192070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43427","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrians have relocated under the vulnerable person relocation scheme since 29 January 2014.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192325","192325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43428","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what rules govern the conduct of former immigration officials in respect of dealings with those still employed by the Immigration Service.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192294","192294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43429","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are allocated to each room in immigration detention centres.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192293","192293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43430","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the nationality and gender was of each suspected victim of trafficking referred to the Trafficking Victim Support Scheme operated by the Salvation Army in January 2014; in which (a) region, (b) county, (c) metropolitan district, (d) district council area, (e) city and (f) parliamentary constituency each of the suspected victims was found; which agency referred each person to that Scheme; in which town the shelter to which such people were placed for the statutory period was; what continued contact is had with each such victim after they have exited the shelter to avoid re-trafficking; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192320","192320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43431","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) managerial, (b) clerical and (c) operational Metropolitan Police staff in Enfield were paid more than (i) £42,000, (ii) £69,000 and (iii) £100,000 in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192256","192256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43432","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of crime in South Staffordshire in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192250","192250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43433","2014-03-20","Department for International Development","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with international non-governmental organisations about the language difficulties of Syrian refugee children in schools in (a) Lebanon and (b) Jordan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192091","192091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43434","2014-03-20","Department for International Development","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Lebanese government on the provision of work permits to Syrian refugees in Lebanon.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192090","192090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43435","2014-03-20","Department for International Development","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with international non-governmental organisations about the provision of work permits to Syrian refugees in (a) Lebanon and (b) Jordan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192092","192092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43436","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what sentence was received by each employee of the Prison Service found guilty in 2013 of criminal activity in the workplace.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192343","192343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43437","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison staff were dismissed in 2013 for conducting inappropriate relationships with prisoners.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192342","192342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43438","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance he has issued to coroners in England and Wales on the storage and retention of files over 30 years old.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192068","192068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43439","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in each police force area have been caught speeding and received points on their driving licence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192301","192301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43440","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was recovered from (a) convicted offenders and (b) prisoners on remand following damage caused by them to prison service property in the last full financial year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192318","192318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43441","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many parents represented themselves at court in child proceedings in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192290","192290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43442","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on TV licensing training for magistrates in (a) 2008, (b) 2009, (c) 2010, (d) 2011 and (e) 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192326","192326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43443","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were fined for not holding a television licence in each local authority in North Wales in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192104","192104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43444","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time between judgement and sentencing in criminal trials in England was in the latest period for which figures are available; and what assessment he has made of the trends in the time taken.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192266","192266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43445","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was of damage to prison service property caused by (a) convicted offenders and (b) prisoners on remand in the last full financial year for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192319","192319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43446","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times a non-molestation order was breached on average before the perpetrator was jailed in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192243","192243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43447","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which towns in England and Wales have only a (a) magistrates court, (b) crown court and (c) county court.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192346","192346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43448","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made on each of the recommendations in Lord Justice Keith's Report into the death of Zahid Mubarek in YOI Feltham in 2000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192345","192345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43449","2014-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which towns in England and Wales have more than one court housed in separate buildings; and which type of court in each case.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192344","192344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43450","2014-03-20","Prime Minister","2014-03-17","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the appointment of the hon. Member for Wealden as (a) a consultant to Vitol Group and (b) a senior adviser to Atlantic Supergrid Corporation Ltd were considered by the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments; and whether any conditions were imposed by the Advisory Committee on either such appointment.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192093","192093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43451","2014-03-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 19W, on the electoral register, what measures the Electoral Commission agreed following its meetings with the Department for Work and Pensions, Cabinet Office and other departments on co-operation in electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192076","192076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43452","2014-03-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, columns 20-1W, on electoral registration, which local authorities and electoral registration officers the Electoral Commission has identified as pursuing best practice in electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192338","192338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43453","2014-03-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, columns 20-1W, on electoral registration, which electoral registration officers and local authorities had the biggest improvement in registering attainers between 2008 and 2013.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192337","192337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43454","2014-03-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 22 Janaury 2013, Official Report, columns 131-3W, on the electoral register, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the reasons for the increase from 8 to 58 in the number of electoral registration officers who failed performance standard 3 between 2010 and 2011.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192309","192309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43455","2014-03-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 20W, on the electoral register, if the Electoral Commission will make a copy of its evaluation of the effectiveness of electoral registration grants available online; and if he will inform the Political and Constitutional Reform Committee once this action is complete.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192249","192249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43456","2014-03-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 19W, on the electoral register, with which civic society organisations the Electoral Commission is proactively seeking partnerships for the purpose of increasing electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192241","192241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43457","2014-03-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to his Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 22W, on the Electoral Register, whether the Electoral Commission plans to consider initiating voter national registration days or weeks for UK citizens.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192317","192317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43458","2014-03-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2014, Official Report, columns 18-19W, on the electoral register, in which month of 2014 the statistics on data matching on electoral registration between the Office of National Statistics, Northern Ireland Statistics and Research Agency and the National Records of Scotland will be published.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192265","192265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43459","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to respond to the High Speed 2 Environmental Statement consultation.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192284","192284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43460","2014-03-24","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average change in rail fares was between Chelmsford and London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192303","192303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43461","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the punctuality levels of train services between Harlow Town train station and London Liverpool Street station have been over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192246","192246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43462","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with companies within the supply chain for railways on the wheel sets and other spare parts for trains.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192339","192339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43463","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has any plans to reduce the number of trains per hour on the East Coast Main Line from London to Newcastle following the opening of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192389","192389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43464","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that Kettering station has a half-hourly service northwards on the Midland Mainline restored to it when the East Midlands Train franchise is renegotiated.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192107","192107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43465","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2014, Official Report, column 280W, on the work capability assessment, how many and  what proportion of those who have undertaken a work capability test in each nation and region of the UK have been declared fit for work.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192323","192323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43466","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 638W, on work capability assessment, if he will make it his policy to collect this data.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192324","192324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43467","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit sanctions were issued in South Staffordshire constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192333","192333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43468","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in South Staffordshire constituency under the age of 25 years old were in receipt of housing benefit in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192267","192267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43469","2014-03-19","Cabinet Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Brigg and Goole constituency no longer claim unemployment benefit as a result of gaining employment in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192280","192280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43470","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many businesses in (a) the UK and (b) Brigg and Goole constituency have taken part in wage incentive schemes since the introduction of the Youth Contract.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192278","192278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43471","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with local authorities on promoting the Green Investment Bank's new green loan scheme.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192370","192370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43472","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to (a) increase social mobility and (b) prevent unpaid internships; and what sanctions are in place for employers who breach minimum wage legislation.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192371","192371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43473","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Green Investment Bank on the uptake of the new green loan scheme by local authorities.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192369","192369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43474","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Deprtment has issued to retailers on the Sale of Goods Act 1979 as amended by the Sale and Supply of Goods to Consumers Regulations 2002 in respect of decisions on offering a full or partial refund after six months for a faulty good.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192378","192378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43475","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effects on the universal postal service of TNT extending end-to-end services.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192383","192383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43476","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the extent to which the general public value the universal postal service.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192384","192384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43477","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the extent to which small businesses are reliant on the universal postal service.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192387","192387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43478","2014-03-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will hold discussions with the Northern Ireland Enterprise Minister on potential economic effects of private sector investment into the Northern Ireland economy by companies located in the South East of England.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192364","192364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43479","2014-03-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the value of bilateral trade between the UK and Ukraine in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192366","192366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43480","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192437","192437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43481","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many times he met representatives of Young Enterprise in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192354","192354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43482","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to ensure the availability of direct business experience for young people at school and university.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192355","192355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43483","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps UK Trade & Investment has taken to increase the number of businesses exporting to the Commonwealth; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192356","192356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43484","2014-03-19","Cabinet Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192438","192438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43485","2014-03-19","Cabinet Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much sugar was purchased for No. 10 Downing Street in 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192416","192416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43486","2014-03-19","Cabinet Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Pendle constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West who have jobs which primarily require working (i) during the day and (ii) at night.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192413","192413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43487","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many rentcharge payers his Department has arranged to receive rentcharge redemption in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and Humber and (c) Brigg and Goole constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192396","192396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43488","2014-03-19","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff had been employed on fixed-term contracts by HM Revenue and Customs for two years or more (a) in Edinburgh and (b) the rest of the UK at the most recent date for which figures are available; and how many such staff will be made redundant in each case by 31 March 2014.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192381","192381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43489","2014-03-20","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to promote greater (a) knowledge of and (b) investment in ISAs and pensions among women.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192363","192363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43490","2014-03-19","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192453","192453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43491","2014-03-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192439","192439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43492","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of people who have sought to access the home ownership for people with long-term disabilities scheme as owner-occupiers in housing need, have been unable to complete the process of moving to a new property due to the delays and logistical challenges of selling their property as part of accessing the scheme since the inception of the scheme.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192420","192420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43493","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has any plans to amend the operation or rules of the home ownership for people with long-term disabilities scheme to make it more responsive to the delays and logistical challenges of selling property as part of the scheme for the purposes of ensuring those who access the scheme as owner-occupiers in housing need are not disadvantaged.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192402","192402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43494","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average cost to the owner of a domestic dwelling of damage caused by fire in a property that (a) has and (b) does not have a smoke alarm.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192096","192096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43495","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of (a) privately rented, (b) social and (c) owner-occupied homes in England with at least one working smoke alarm in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192095","192095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43496","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average cost to (a) the fire and rescue service, (b) the ambulance service and (c) the police service of responding to a fire incident in a domestic dwelling (i) with and (ii) without a smoke alarm.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192098","192098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43497","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the effect on the likelihood of (a) death and (b) non-fatal injury as a result of fire in a domestic dwelling of being without a smoke alarm.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192097","192097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43498","2014-03-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage local authorities to switch to low-energy street lighting.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192392","192392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43499","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on housing benefit for tenants in (a) council property, (b) housing association and registered social landlord property and (c) private sector housing in (i) Yorkshire and Humber and (ii) Brigg and Goole constituency in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192397","192397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43500","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of people who have been provided with assistance through the home ownership for people with long-term disabilities scheme have been owner-occupiers in housing need rather than first-time buyers to date.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192419","192419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43501","2014-03-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications have been made in (a) Lancashire and (b) Pendle constituency to list (i) facilities and (ii) buildings as assets of community value; and how many such applications were approved.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192433","192433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43502","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of planning applications to build on sites in (a) Yorkshire and Humber and (b) Brigg and Goole constituency involved building on designated green belt land in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192395","192395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43503","2014-03-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much arts funding (a) in total and (b) per head of population was allocated in (i) Lancashire and (ii) Pendle constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192432","192432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43504","2014-03-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of people in (a) the North West, (b) Lancashire and (c) Pendle constituency who suffer from a gambling addiction.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192374","192374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43505","2014-03-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much was raised from the payment of licence fees to the BBC in the last year for which figures are available; and how much additional funding her Department provided to the BBC in that year.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192372","192372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43506","2014-03-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) her Department and (b) her Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192440","192440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43507","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192441","192441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43508","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings he has had with industry on UK cyber hygiene policy in the last three years.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192082","192082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43509","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many NATO or EU cyber exercises are planned in 2014; and what the UK's involvement will be in each such exercise.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192083","192083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43510","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many cyber reservists have been recruited to the Joint Cyber Reserve Force to date; and when he expects to meet his recruitment target.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192357","192357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43511","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many cyber incidents were recorded by firms with contracts with his Department in 2013.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192358","192358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43512","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the NATO Co-operative Cyber Defence Centre of Excellence.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192359","192359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43513","2014-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 818W, on Burma, what the name and rank is of the Burmese Army officer visiting the UK for training; and when that officer will be visiting the UK.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192456","192456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43514","2014-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Commodore at Faslane Naval Base was alerted that collant radioactivity had been detected in the prototype reactor at NRTE Dounreay.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192099","192099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43515","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what additional surveillance capability the Watchkeeper system will provide over the Hermes 450 UAV following the commencement of army trials.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192368","192368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43516","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of staff in Defence Equipment and Support who will see their terms and conditions change as a result of introducing the private sector into the procurement process.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192373","192373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43517","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the longevity of fuel rods used in the Vanguard and Astute class submaries under normal patrol conditions since the leakage incident at Dounreay.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192376","192376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43518","2014-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers have been made compulsorily redundant since May 2010; and what proportion of those soldiers were within one year of receiving a pension.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192382","192382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43519","2014-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people left the armed forces in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192398","192398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43520","2014-03-19","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-17","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 510W, on the electoral register: young people, what estimate he has made of the number of young people who have been added to the electoral register as a result of Rock Enrol!","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192086","192086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43521","2014-03-19","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-17","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2014, Official Report, column 570W, on the electoral register: young people, how many times the student forum has met since its creation; and what the main outcomes of the forum have been in the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192084","192084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43522","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were put up for adoption by Norfolk County Council social services against the wishes of their birth family in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192352","192352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43523","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) converter academies and (b) maintained schools achieved a higher percentage of students achieving five GCSE A* to C grades including English and mathematics than the previous year in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192423","192423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43524","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) converter academies and (b) maintained schools achieved a higher percentage of students achieving five GCSE A* to C grades than the previous year in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192425","192425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43525","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) converter academies and (b) maintained schools achieved a lower percentage of students achieving five GCSE A* to C grades including English and mathematics than the previous year in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192424","192424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43526","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to expand the languages curriculum to encompass Urdu.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192434","192434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43527","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress he has made on encouraging computer science and programming in UK schools.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192351","192351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43528","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192442","192442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43529","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) converter academies and (b) maintained schools achieved a lower percentage of students achieving five GCSE A* to C grades than the previous year in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192426","192426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43530","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications to foster or adopt were made by relatives of the child's parents in (a) North West Norfolk constituency, (b) Norfolk and (c) the UK in each of the last 10 years; and how many such applications were successful in each area and in each year.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192353","192353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43531","2014-03-20","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and Humber continued into (i) further education, (ii) higher education and (iii) apprenticeships in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192394","192394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43532","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Pendle constituency and (b) Lancashire were eligible for but did not claim free school meals in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192429","192429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43533","2014-03-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) energy companies obligation, (b) affordable warmth and (c) green deal grants were allocated in the BB postcode area in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192430","192430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43534","2014-03-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have been removed from fuel poverty as a result of the energy companies obligation in (a) Lancashire and (b) Pendle constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192431","192431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43535","2014-03-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192443","192443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43536","2014-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192444","192444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43537","2014-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 552W, on forests, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness in reducing flood risk of (a) the Slowing the flow project in North Yorkshire and the (b) Forestry Commission projects in the catchments of the (i) River Parrett in Somerset and (ii) River Irthing in Northumberland.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192087","192087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43538","2014-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 552W, on forests, if he will make it his policy to record these projects centrally.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192088","192088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43539","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to tackle the production of counterfeit alcohol that contains dangerous substances such as methanol or isopropanol.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192410","192410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43540","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) discuss with the Moroccan Ambassador to the UK and (b) instruct the British Ambassador in Rabat to investigate reports of injuries by the Moroccan police to Sultana Khaya, President of Saharawi Observatory for the protection of Natural Resources in Bojador when she was demonstrating against the use of Saharawi natural resources in Bojador, Western Sahara.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192386","192386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43541","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192445","192445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43542","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many vehicles are owned or leased by the British High Commission in Nairobi; and what the make of each such vehicle is.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192414","192414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43543","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who authorised the continuing payment of the salary of the National Director for Human Resources, Jo-Anne Wass of NHS England during her secondment to the University of Leeds.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192421","192421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43544","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192446","192446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43545","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding (a) local authorities and (b) the Food Standards Agency had to carry out food sampling analyses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192407","192407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43546","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken through the Change4Life initiative to change long-term consumer food habits.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192408","192408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43547","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the risk to public health of the sale of counterfeit alcohol that contains substances such as methanol or isopropanol.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192411","192411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43548","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the promotion by Public Health England of ready meals, tinned vegetables and soft drinks as part of the Smart Swaps campaign and Change4Life initiative; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192412","192412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43549","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2014, Official Report, column 950W, on food: testing, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the decline in the number of food sampling tests being carried out over the last five years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192409","192409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43550","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on extending patient choice of provider of mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192362","192362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43551","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish data on mental health spending in 2012-13.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192361","192361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43552","2014-03-20","Department of Health","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many healthcare professionals in the NHS are not regulated by statutory regulation.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192348","192348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43553","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of illegal taking of game have been recorded in (a) the North West and (b) Lancashire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192391","192391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43554","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of domestic violence were recorded in each local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192377","192377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43555","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current status is of the Border Systems Programme (BSP); what the timescale is for tendering and choosing suppliers; and when the BSP is expected to be developed and rolled out.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192403","192403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43556","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on levels of organised crime in Northern Ireland of extending the operations of the National Crime Agency in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192367","192367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43557","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many criminal offences by foreign-born nationals were recorded in Pendle constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192375","192375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43558","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many penalties for infringement of advanced stop lines were issued to (a) motorists and (b) cyclists in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192428","192428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43559","2014-03-20","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last visited national security establishments and personnel in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192365","192365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43560","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) her Department and (b) her Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192447","192447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43561","2014-03-19","Home Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa centres have been contracted to be delivered by teleperformance in Africa; how many such centres are operational; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192415","192415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43562","2014-03-20","House of Commons Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many passes for entry into the Commons estate (a) are in issue and (b) were lost in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192418","192418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43563","2014-03-20","Department for International Development","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding the Government provides in Burma for programmes supporting the eradication of drug production.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192417","192417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43564","2014-03-19","Department for International Development","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) her Department and (b) her Department's non-departmental public body in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192448","192448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43565","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192449","192449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43566","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff of his Department and its agencies have been made redundant and subsequently re-employed by his Department and its agencies on (a) permanent and (b) fixed-term contract basis since May 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192089","192089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43568","2014-03-19","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate she has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) her Department and (b) her Department's non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192450","192450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43569","2014-03-19","Scotland Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in his Department in (a) 2010, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192451","192451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43570","2014-03-19","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 20W on the electoral register, whether measurements of the effectiveness of electoral registration officers' implementation of Electoral Commission advice on increasing the number of attainers registered includes changes in the number of attainers registered.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192081","192081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43571","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192452","192452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43572","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the report of the Commission on Devolution in Wales published on 3 March 2014, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Wales on the potential implications for (a) rail services in Chester and (b) Chester railway station of the recommendation in that report to devolve the Wales and Borders rail franchise to the National Assembly for Wales.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192435","192435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43573","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, column 386W, on bus services: finance, if he will provide a breakdown of (a) funding previously paid to bus operators for running services under tender to local authorities, (b) funding previously paid to local authorities for running community transport services in-house, (c) bus service operators' grant funding and top-up payments for those authorities which have been designated as Better Bus Areas for (i) each of the last three years and (ii) the next two years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192399","192399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43574","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 525W, on cycling: safety, if he will publish a breakdown of the source of cycling funding by (a) central Government, (b) local authority and (c) the private sector for the period 2005 to 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192400","192400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43575","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for how many days the (a) Colne to Blackpool South and (b) Skipton to Leeds lines were closed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192427","192427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43576","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of High Speed 2 on the frequency of trains on the East Coast Main Line from London to Newcastle.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192390","192390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43577","2014-03-19","Wales Office","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in his Department in (a) 2010, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192454","192454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43578","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace nurseries available to staff in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies in (i) 2010, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192455","192455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43579","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 638W, on the work capability assessment, if he will make it his policy to collect such information in future.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192085","192085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43580","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was paid in service charges to housing associations for adaptations to accommodation for disabled tenants in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192422","192422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43581","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how disputed child tax credits claims will be managed under the universal credit system.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192385","192385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43582","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what consultation his Department has had with groups representing separated parents on steps to ensure universal credit makes shared parenting a financially viable option for parents who do not have family-based financial arrangements in place.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192380","192380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43583","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Universal Jobmatch employer accounts have been found to be in breach of its rules since the service started.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192404","192404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43584","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent assessment is of the (a) effectiveness and (b) value for money of Universal Jobmatch.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192406","192406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43585","2014-03-19","HM Treasury","2014-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to address financial inequalities faced by parents with shared custody of their child where state benefits are paid to only one parent.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192379","192379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43586","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the extent of (a) fraud, (b) duplication of job entries and (c) entries for non-existent jobs in the Universal Jobmatch website.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192405","192405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43587","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many entries there are on the Universal Jobmatch database; and what his estimate is of the number of vacancies such entries represent.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192401","192401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43588","2014-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2014, Official Report, column 316W, on children: maintenance, in how many cases within the Child Support Agency collection service, excluding those with a deduction from earnings order, the Agency was notified of a missed child maintenance payment in the quarter up to and including December 2013; and in what proportion of such cases the non-resident parent was contacted by the Agency within 72 hours.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192436","192436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43589","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and Humber are (i) entitled to and (ii) receiving council tax relief.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192393","192393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43859","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to repair potholes.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903166","903166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43888","2014-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903154","903154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44202","2014-03-20","House of Commons Commission","2014-03-17","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps he is taking to improve the support available to hon. Members.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903162","903162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44203","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that High Speed 2 represents value for money.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903177","903177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44204","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to improve existing railway stations and build new ones.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903176","903176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44205","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve the rail network infrastructure.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903178","903178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44206","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to support rural bus services.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903179","903179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44207","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent flooding on the rail and road network.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903181","903181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44208","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the overall condition of road markings on roads and motorways.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903182","903182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43218","2014-03-19","Attorney General","2014-03-14","To ask the Attorney General, how many times the Attorney General has appointed an amicus curiae in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192195","192195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43219","2014-03-19","Attorney General","2014-03-14","To ask the Attorney General, how much has been spent by the Attorney General's Office on appointing amici curiae in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192196","192196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43220","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with the e-cigarette industry ways of ensuring better consumer safety through the testing of e-cigarette liquids.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192212","192212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43221","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the supply chain of those e-cigarettes which are regulated as consumer products is being adequately monitored.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192213","192213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43222","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of end-to-end competition in the postal sector on postal workers' pay and terms and conditions of employment.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192236","192236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43223","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on the sustainability of the universal postal service of the plans of other postal operators to extend end-to-end postal services.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192238","192238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43224","2014-03-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of other postal operators extending end-to-end services on postal services in rural areas.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192237","192237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43225","2014-03-18","HM Treasury","2014-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reduce VAT on repairs for those affected by flooding.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192189","192189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43226","2014-03-18","HM Treasury","2014-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Industrial and Provident Societies have been registered with the Financial Services Authority or Financial Conduct Authority in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192198","192198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43227","2014-03-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the three commissions provided by Hymans Robertson LLP, Squire Sanders (UK) LLP and CEM Benchmarking on the Local Government Pensions Scheme.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192185","192185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43228","2014-03-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the consultation on the Local Government Pension Scheme launched in May 2013.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192186","192186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43229","2014-03-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people were employed at Northamptonshire Fire and Rescue in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192230","192230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43230","2014-03-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will estimate the cost of recent flooding to the leisure parks, piers and attractions sector.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192206","192206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43231","2014-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance has been provided by the (a) Royal Navy and (b) Royal Air Force in the search for Malaysia Airlines flight MH370.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192199","192199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43232","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of state-funded primary schools have acquired academy status in each local authority.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192209","192209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43233","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of transporting children from secure children's homes in London and the South East to elsewhere in the UK.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192205","192205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43234","2014-03-19","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) converter academies and (b) maintained schools received a (i) higher and (ii) lower Ofsted inspection result than they had received in their previous inspections in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12 and (C) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192215","192215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43235","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of academy trusts have applied to open a free school.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192221","192221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43236","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, column 816W, on community schools, how many maintained schools his Department believes to be underperforming.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192222","192222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43237","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has carried out any form of assessment of the number of state-funded schools where religious items or articles of clothing form part of the school's (a) pupil and (b) staff uniform policy.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192224","192224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43238","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many representations he has received from local authorities indicating that the local authority does not require a proposed free school; and whether this has led to any proposed free school applications being withdrawn.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192225","192225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43239","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of free schools approved to date are faith schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192226","192226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43240","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of faith free schools opened to date have met the 50 per cent target of children and young people attending the school who do not belong to that faith.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192227","192227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43241","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what contact his Department has had with the largest 10 academy chains to confirm whether they plan to make an application for a free school in the next (a) year, (b) two years and (c) three years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192223","192223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43242","2014-03-18","HM Treasury","2014-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will put a mechanism in place to waive landfill tax for the disposal of sandbags by local authorities.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192187","192187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43243","2014-03-18","HM Treasury","2014-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the financial effect on local authorities of landfill tax payable for the disposal of sandbags since the recent floods.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192188","192188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43244","2014-03-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what flood prevention measures have been undertaken in (a) Corby and East Northamptonshire and (b) Northamptonshire in the last four years; and how many staff of (i) his Department and (ii) the Environment Agency have been employed on those matters.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192231","192231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43245","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publicly acknowledge and condemn supporting roles played by the Burmese state in the institutionalisation of persecution and violence against the Rohingya communities in Burma. [R]","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192232","192232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43246","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on an independent investigation into human rights abuses in Burma. [R]","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192201","192201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43247","2014-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Oral Answer from the Deputy Prime Minister of 12 March 2014, Official Report, column 316, what Korean language service the BBC World Service previously offered; for how long it had made such transmissions; what the cost of that service was; and what savings were made when that service was discontinued.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192233","192233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43248","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether Burma's state institutions have the capacity and capability to conduct an independent and transparent investigation into the persecution of, and violence against, minorities in Burma. [R]","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192204","192204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43249","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Burmese counterpart on ensuring that the upcoming census will not further endanger the Rohingya communities and any other minority groups in Burma. [R]","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192202","192202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43250","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Burma. [R]","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192203","192203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43251","2014-03-24","Department of Health","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what standards of data collection are required of clinical commissioning groups with respect to abortion services delivered in the independent sector.","Biography information for Sir Julian Brazier","Mr Julian Brazier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192219","192219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43252","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of psychological support available to people with cystic fibrosis after lung transplantation.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192192","192192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43253","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the current arrangements for donor lung allocation for people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192193","192193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43254","2014-03-19","Department of Health","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the report by the Cystic Fibrosis Trust entitled Hope for more: Improving access to lung transplantation and care for people with cystic fibrosis; what estimate his Department has made of the donor lung utilisation rate for transplantation; and what measures his Department has identified as having the greatest potential to increase that rate.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192234","192234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43255","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients who reside in Wales have been admitted to English hospitals for (a) cardio-vascular surgery and (b) maternity services in each of the last five years for which are figures are available.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192228","192228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43256","2014-03-18","Home Office","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take to ensure that police forces create wildlife crime officer posts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192200","192200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43257","2014-03-19","Department for International Development","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure a gender goal is included in the post-2015 framework in the post-Millennium Development Goals agenda.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192218","192218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43258","2014-03-19","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her objectives are for the UN Commission on the Status of Women.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192216","192216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43259","2014-03-19","Department for International Development","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to support women's social and political participation in fragile states at the UN Commission on the Status of Women.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192217","192217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43260","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of barristers terminating their contractual involvement in cases there have been since the introduction of changes to very high cost case fees in December 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192214","192214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43261","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many closed visits there were in English jails in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192194","192194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43262","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the (a) capacity and (b) population of each (a) secure training centre, (b) young offender institution and (c) secure children's home on 1 March (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192197","192197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43263","2014-03-18","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-14","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Blaenau Gwent County Borough Council.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192220","192220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43264","2014-03-18","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-14","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many postal votes there were as a proportion of those issued in the top 100 constituencies in turnout ranked order at the 2010 General Election.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192239","192239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43265","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) his counterpart in the Scottish Government, (b) the freight and haulage industry and (c) the European Commission on payment of the HGV user levy should Scotland vote to leave the UK in September 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192235","192235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43266","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on the Jobcentre estate in 2012-13.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192190","192190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43267","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the differential payment regime in the Work Programme in reducing creaming and parking.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192191","192191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43268","2014-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much in discretionary housing payments has been allocated in Corby and East Northamptonshire constituency for those affected by the under-occupancy penalty in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192229","192229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43269","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were entitled to income-related jobseeker's allowance (JSA), but not to contributory JSA, when they first claimed ceased claiming that benefit within (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five and (f) six months of making their initial claim in each of the last two years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192211","192211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43270","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were entitled to contributory jobseeker's allowance when they first claimed ceased claiming that benefit within (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five and (f) six months of making their initial claim in each of the last two years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192210","192210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43271","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that any foreign company found to have abandoned its pension responsibilities to UK pension holders can be made to refund that pension deficit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192208","192208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43272","2014-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether members of the Carrington Wire Pension Fund are able to access the Pension Protection Fund.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192207","192207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42967","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that registered intellectual property is used productively; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191962","191962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42968","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the UK economy of patent trolls and patent assertion entities.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191963","191963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42969","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects the chief executive of the Offshore Wind Investment Organisation to be appointed.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192004","192004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42970","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, what the date and location of each Share Fair event that has taken place to date were; and how many companies attended each such event.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192015","192015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42971","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made in providing an assessment of future markets for individual elements of an offshore wind farm.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192016","192016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42972","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made on the engagement plan for the communication of benefits of offshore renewable energy across Europe and globally through Norstec and promotion of local benefits through the Cities for Offshore Renewable Engineering.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192017","192017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42973","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, how much of the £19.9 million from the Regional Growth Fund to deliver the MAS Offshore Wind Supply Chain has been used to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192018","192018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42974","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, how many finance guarantees for offshore wind supply chain infrastructure projects have been granted through the UK Guarantees Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192024","192024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42975","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, what (a) activity and (b) investment has been made in the offshore wind industry through the new Business Bank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192025","192025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42976","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy (OWIS), what progress he has made on ensuring the Offshore Wind Investment Organisation is operational; if he will list activities of the organisation since its launch in the OWIS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192019","192019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42977","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, how many new apprenticeships have been created as part of the Wind Turbine Engineering Apprenticeship Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192026","192026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42978","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made on a supply chain analysis in the offshore wind industry.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192020","192020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42979","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, which higher education and professional institutions are including more offshore wind specific content in engineering courses.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192027","192027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42980","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, what export opportunities have (a) been identified and (b) materialised into export sales for UK-based companies operating in the offshore wind industry through the high value opportunities programme.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192021","192021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42981","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made on expanding the scope of the Offshore Wind Manufacturing Funding scheme for England.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192022","192022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42982","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Offshore Wind Industrial Strategy, what projects in offshore wind have received investment from the Green Investment Bank; and what the value of that investment is for each such project.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192023","192023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42983","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-13","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether his Department's funding of £3.6 million to improve electoral registration will be given to local authorities which have not used local government databases to improve electoral registration in the individual electoral registration dry run.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192118","192118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42984","2014-03-18","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-13","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent voter confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Darlington constituency and (b) the Borough of Darlington.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192146","192146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42985","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the size of the electorate was (a) the year before and (b) two years after the coming into force of the Representation of the People (England and Wales) Regulations 2001.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192116","192116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42986","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-13","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what measures are in place to monitor the effectiveness of the funding to improve electoral registration engagement; and when he plans to report to Parliament on the effectiveness of this initiative.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192117","192117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42987","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the level of personal debt was in (a) the UK, (b) Stockport Metropolitan Borough, (c) Tameside Metropolitan Borough and (d) Denton and Reddish constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192135","192135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42988","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-13","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if his Department's funding to improve registration will be given to local authorities that are spending (a) more than and (b) less than the average on voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192179","192179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42989","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average earnings of full-time employees in Denton and Reddish constituency were in April (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192138","192138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42990","2014-03-18","Cabinet Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged (a) 25 years and over and (b) 16 to 24 years old have been unemployed for more than a year in Brigg and Goole constituency since 2008.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191915","191915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42991","2014-03-18","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many fines have been issued to employers in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber for non-payment of the national minimum wage in each year since 2010; and what the total value of such fines was in each such area.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191917","191917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42992","2014-03-18","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings his Department has had with (a) pub companies, (b) the British Beer and Pub Association, (c) members of the British Beer and Pub Association, (d) Independent Family Brewers of Britain and (e) members of Independent Family Brewers of Britain.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192124","192124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42993","2014-03-18","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount which will be raised for charities through the Gift Aid Small Charitable Donations Scheme, by 31 March 2014.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192060","192060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42994","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the amount which will be raised for charities via the Gift Aid Small Charitable Donations Scheme, compared to the estimate provided when the Bill was passed.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192064","192064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42995","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding has been raised for charities through the Gift Aid Small Charitable Donations Scheme in each month since it commenced in April 2013.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192065","192065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42996","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent consideration he has given to enabling the Gift Aid Small Charitable Donations scheme to benefit from contactless and cashless payments.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192061","192061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42997","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of guidance in relation to the Gift Aid Small Charitable Donations Scheme; and whether he plans to amend that guidance.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192062","192062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42998","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with charities regarding the Gift Aid Small Charitable Donations Scheme.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192063","192063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42999","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the remarks made by the President of German regulator Bafin on 17 January 2014 on manipulation of currency rates and prices, if he will direct the Financial Conduct Authority to investigate currency and precious metals markets.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192001","192001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43000","2014-03-17","Church Commissioners","2014-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what consideration the Church Commissioners gave to the historical or other interest of the residence at the Bishop's Palace at Wells before planning alternative accommodation for the bishop in accordance with section 4 of the Episcopal Endowments and Stipends Measure 1943.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191893","191893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43001","2014-03-17","Church Commissioners","2014-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, if he will publish a complete list of the grounds considered valid for the purposes of an objection to the exchange of the house of residence of the Bishop of Bath and Wells by the Bishop's Council and Standing Committee.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191894","191894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43002","2014-03-17","Church Commissioners","2014-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what recent discussions the leaders of the Anglican church have had with the Archbishop of Uganda regarding lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender rights.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191905","191905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43003","2014-03-17","Church Commissioners","2014-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what recent discussions the leaders of the Anglican church have had with the Archbishop of Nigeria regarding lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender rights.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191906","191906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43004","2014-03-17","Church Commissioners","2014-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what assessment the Church Commissioners have made of recent trends in the proportion of Church of England congregations that are (a) from black and Asian minority ethnic groups, (b) women, (c) disabled people and (d) from low-income groups.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191902","191902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43005","2014-03-17","Church Commissioners","2014-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, how many clergy of the Church of England were from black and minority ethnic backgrounds in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191908","191908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43006","2014-03-17","Church Commissioners","2014-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, if he will publish a list of all (a) UK and (b) overseas equities held by the Commissioners' investment fund in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191909","191909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43007","2014-03-17","Church Commissioners","2014-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, if he will publish a breakdown of funds that the Church Commissioners have made available for dioceses based in Nigeria in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191903","191903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43008","2014-03-17","Church Commissioners","2014-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what funds in each category of expenditure the Church Commissioners have made available for dioceses based in Uganda in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191904","191904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43009","2014-03-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many onshore wind farm applications and how much onshore wind capacity have been recovered by the Secretary of State in each month in 2013; and how many such applications and capacity had previously received consent from the Planning Inspectorate.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191952","191952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43010","2014-03-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities in England and Wales use higher-rate telephone numbers for public enquiries.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191953","191953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43011","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received on permitting motorists to stop for up to 15 minutes on double yellow lines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191958","191958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43012","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library a copy of each non-confidential individual response to the consultation on local government pension funds.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191959","191959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43013","2014-03-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities have been affected by the recent flooding and have applied to his Department for funding under the Bellwin scheme.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191972","191972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43014","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish data for his Department's spending over £250 for December 2013.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191934","191934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43015","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications to dispose of statutory allotments have been (a) submitted, (b) approved and (c) rejected in each local authority area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191956","191956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43016","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the Queen Elizabeth II Conference Centre has billed the Government for use of the centre and associated facilities in the last financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191957","191957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43017","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what help he gives to community groups to finalise their neighbourhood plans and to protect them from legal appeal by developers where there is no local plan yet in place for their area.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192049","192049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43018","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce a national register of landlords; and what steps his Department is taking to make it easier for local authorities to introduce a licensing scheme for landlords.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192129","192129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43019","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that the minutes of the board meetings of (a) external organisations, (b) trusts and (c) other arm's length companies operating public services on behalf of local authorities are made available for public scrutiny.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192136","192136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43020","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on the introduction of an elected mayor for the Greater Manchester combined authority.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192134","192134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43021","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful planning appeals have been made against (i) Stockport Metropolitan Borough Council and (ii) Tameside Metropolitan Borough Council in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192143","192143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43022","2014-03-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much Sport England funding has been allocated to local authorities (a) in and (b) not in the core city group in the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192010","192010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43023","2014-03-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what type of wreath or floral tribute the Government will use in official ceremonies to commemorate the outbreak of the First World War.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191895","191895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43025","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will abandon the use of live pigs in military battlefield exercises; whether he has had discussions with his counterpart in Germany, Italy, the Netherlands and Poland to learn from their use of mannequins as a replacement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191896","191896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43026","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Minister or official, at what level within his Department, decided to advise the (a) Scottish Environmental Protection Agency and (b) Office for Nucelar Regulation that information relating to the January 2012 incident at the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment had national security implications and should be treated on a need-to-know basis.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192000","192000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43027","2014-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of 2014DIN01-023, Engagement with suppliers, contractors and former bidders following termination of the Material Strategy GO-CO procurement.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192013","192013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43028","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost under each category of expenditure was at the Army Personnel Centre at Kentigern House in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192045","192045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43029","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which radionuclides were emitted from the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment at Dounreay following the January 2012 incident; and in what quantities.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192046","192046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43030","2014-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings (a) civil servants, (b) consultants and (c) Ministers of his Department have had on the Logistical Commodities Services Transformation Programme with (i) Telford and Wrekin Council and (ii) Cherwell District Council.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192055","192055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43031","2014-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the overall consultancy budget is for the delivery of the Logistical Commodities Services Transformation Programme; and how much of that budget has been spent to date.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192056","192056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43032","2014-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) civil servants and (b) consultants are working on an in-house solution for the Logistical Commodities Services Transformation Programme; and where they are located.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192057","192057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43033","2014-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) civil servants and (b) consultants are working on the Logistical Commodities Services Transformation Programme.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192058","192058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43034","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost in each category of expenditure was of (a) RAF Leuchars, (b) HMNB Clyde, (c) RM Condor, (d) Headquarters 2nd Division, (e) Headquarters 51 Brigade, (f) Redford Barracks, (g) Dreghorn Barracks, (h) RAF Kinloss, (i) Fort George Barracks, (j) Glencorse Barracks, (k) Defence Munitions Centre Crombie, (l) Defence Munitions Centre Beith, (m) Defence Munitions Centre Glen Douglas, (n) HMS Gannet, (o) RNAD Coulport, (p) MOD Hebrides Ranges, (q) British Underwater Testing and Evaluation Centre, (r) Loch Ewe fuel depot, (s) Garelochead Defence training centre and oil fuel depot, (t) HMS Caledonia, (u) Rosyth Defence Estate and (v) West Freugh training ranges area in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192115","192115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43035","2014-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for (a) each stage and (b) the final completion of the Logistical Commodities Services Transformation Programme.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192059","192059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43036","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-13","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will introduce legislative proposals to provide that the heirs of people who disclaim hereditary peerages cannot claim any hereditary right to membership of the House of Lords; and if he will publish details of how many people entitled to hereditary peerages have renounced their titles where their oldest eligible son has subsequently claimed the title on their death.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191910","191910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43037","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's policy is on the use of adrenaline shots in schools to treat children having an anaphylactic shock.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191916","191916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43038","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on students' personal information being (a) sold to the private sector for means of advertising and (b) used to improve electoral registration of students.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191923","191923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43039","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department gives to local authorities on the use of virtual headteachers for children in care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191933","191933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43040","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many virtual headteachers there were (a) in total and (b) in each local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191950","191950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43041","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to grant virtual headteachers statutory powers to intervene when a young person is facing exclusion from school.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191951","191951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43042","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department allocated for virtual headteachers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191954","191954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43043","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the relative educational outcomes in Hull and Surrey local authority areas; and what assessment he has made of how the extra funding for schools announced on 13 March 2014 will address such differences.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191973","191973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43044","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which contractors were awarded the contract by the National College for Teaching and Leadership for professional skills tests for initial teacher training entrants.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192144","192144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43045","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations he has received on the professional skills test for initial teacher training entrants.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192145","192145"
