"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710660","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of the 2 March 2017 to Question 65538, on personal independence payment, what the criteria is for a lack of mental capacity or insight for assessing a person with a brain tumour as eligible for additional support when assessing a personal independence payment claim.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67547","67547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710661","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the daily living activity 2 of the personal independence payment assessment, how many people with epilepsy have scored points on descriptors c, d, e or f for (a) new claims and (b) disability living allowance reassessments in (i) each year before November 2016 and (ii) the period since November 2016.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67504","67504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710662","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the future of the state pensions top-up scheme for which European Economic Area citizens are currently eligible.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67514","67514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710663","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to improve the personal independence payment assessment process for people with epilepsy.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67502","67502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710664","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67472","67472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710665","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government offers any provision of female sanitary products for women who consider themselves unable to afford such products.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67492","67492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710666","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67455","67455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710667","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many prosecutions have been carried out of company directors continuing to trade when insolvent in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67505","67505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710668","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what analysis his Department has conducted of the future capacity of the Post Office, to meet its commitment, that 95 per cent of the total rural population is within three miles of a post office outlet.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67521","67521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710669","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2017 to Question 66290, on employment: disadvantaged, what proportion of funding from the Government's £12 billion Local Growth Fund has been allocated to Easington constituency to date.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67544","67544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710670","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Questions 66289 and 66310, on manufacturing industries: Durham, how much of the £379.6 million has been invested in (a) Peterlee and (b) Easington constituency to date.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67545","67545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710671","2017-03-15","Department for International Trade","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of current trends in (a) exports and (b) imports.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67556","67556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710672","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many meetings at which Government Ministers and officials of his Department have been present have taken place with representatives or employees from (a) Macquarie Group and (b) the Australian Embassy to the UK since January 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67698","67698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710673","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the Government's response to the consultation on moving the operations of the HM Land Registry to the private sector.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67681","67681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710674","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will meet tobacconists and small independent retailers who have been affected by violence, abuse and vandalism from those who refuse to show identification and proof of age when wishing to purchase tobacco and alcohol.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67664","67664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710675","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the £3.8 billion of public funding committed to the UK Green Investment Bank since its establishment in 2012, plus any profits made by the Government on its sale, will be reinvested in the UK low-carbon economy on completion of the sale of that bank.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67661","67661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710676","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's response to the Waterson review, published on 13 March 2017, how he plans to make funds available to National Trading Standards to enforce legislation relevant to secondary ticketing websites.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67627","67627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710677","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much the Government and the UK Green Investment Bank have spent on external consultants and advisers to date in relation to the privatisation of that bank.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67585","67585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710678","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make financial support available to provide incentives for businesses to relocate and operate from designated business parks in Peterlee and Seaham where there is significant under-occupancy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67596","67596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710679","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Transport on the potential merits of improving rail infrastructure on the Durham heritage coast in order to promote employment opportunities and inward investment in East Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67598","67598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710680","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to support British oil and gas companies in securing production rights in Iraq.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67618","67618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710681","2017-03-15","Department for International Trade","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how his Department assessed the levels of commitment to the best possible outcome for the UK following its departure from the EU displayed by teams bidding to deliver Market Access Discovery and Trade Remedies Discovery services.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67570","67570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710682","2017-03-15","Department for International Trade","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the level of business interest in the great.gov.uk digital platform.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67571","67571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710683","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Written Statement of 5 December 2016, HCWS 316, on UK commitments at the World Trade organisation, whether the draft schedules that will be prepared will replicate the EU25, EU27 or EU28 schedules.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67537","67537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710684","2017-03-15","Department for International Trade","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67466","67466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710685","2017-03-15","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67461","67461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710686","2017-03-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans the Government has to ensure that the views of (a) the new West Midlands combined authority and (b) other such combined authorities are represented during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67624","67624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710687","2017-03-15","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he last discussed cross-border issues resulting from the UK leaving the EU with representatives from the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67590","67590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710821","2017-03-16","Attorney General","2017-03-13","To ask the Attorney General, what the Government's policy is on which factors to take into account when deciding whether responding to an imminent threat is permitted under international law.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909275","909275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710953","2017-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the centenary of the First World War is commemorated in local communities.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909298","909298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711646","2017-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with the Scottish Government on celebrating the bicentenary of the architect Alexander Thomson.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909292","909292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709946","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average salary of full-time equivalent employees was in Coventry South constituency in April of each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67420","67420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709947","2017-03-14","Cabinet Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to give those with no fixed address access to online voter registration.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67426","67426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709948","2017-03-14","Cabinet Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to increase voter engagement and participation among those least likely to vote including (a) homeless and b) young people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67427","67427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709949","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 65105, what estimate he has made of the amount spent by his Department in each of the last 10 years on staff undertaking media relations and communications roles.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67442","67442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709950","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are registered as Class 4 national insurance contribution payers by (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) region.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67417","67417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709951","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will encourage local authorities to use the funds for discretionary relief on business rates to help music venues.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67413","67413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709952","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people will pay more in national insurance contributions (NICs) as a result of changes to rates for Class 2 and Class 4 NICs due to be implemented in April 2018 by (a) region and (b) constituency.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67418","67418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709953","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when consultation to determine eligibility for the £1,000 business rate discount for public houses announced in paragraph 4.5 of the Spring Budget 2017 will conclude.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67410","67410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709954","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether music venues will be eligible for the £1,000 business rate discount for public houses announced in paragraph 4.5 of the Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67411","67411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709955","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department is providing to music venues whose business rates are increasing from 1 April 2017.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67412","67412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709956","2017-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the breadth of sources of music broadcast by the BBC.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67383","67383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709957","2017-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will seek to exempt EU-related fisheries law from being incorporated into UK law as part of the Great Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67416","67416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709958","2017-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, in how many years since 2010 (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands have been in breach of EU air pollution levels.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67404","67404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709959","2017-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Sri Lankan Government on the (a) rights of Sri Lankan Christians to practise their faith and (b) attack on a prayer centre in Paharaiya in North West Sri Lanka on 5 January 2017.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67389","67389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709960","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the representations he has received from the Israeli Government on the threatened demolition of Khan al-Ahmar.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67392","67392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709961","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he raised the threatened demolition of the village of Khan al-Ahmar with the Israeli Government during his recent visit to that country.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67393","67393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709962","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on supporting clinicians on the export for use in other countries of clinical and management procedures that have been developed in the NHS.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67384","67384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709963","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to use the research base for clinical and management procedure that have been exported by groups of NHS clinicians for use in other countries to inform best practice within the NHS.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67385","67385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709964","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which sustainability and transformation plans (STP) will receive funding as part of the allocation announced in paragraph 6.1 of the Spring Budget 2017; and how much funding each STP will receive.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67387","67387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709965","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many sustainability and transformation plan areas will receive the funding announced in paragraph 6.1 of the Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67388","67388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709966","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to reduce the screening age for bowel cancer to 50-years old.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67382","67382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709967","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18 to 21 year olds claim the housing costs element of universal credit in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67419","67419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709968","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of public sector pay restraints on levels of expenditure by the NHS on agency staff in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67421","67421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709969","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many places there were in registered care homes in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67422","67422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709970","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2017 to Question 63752, on heart diseases: medical treatments, which body will conduct the national cardiac review; and how many staff at that body will be assigned to it.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67405","67405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709971","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2017 to Question 63752, on heart diseases: medical treatments, when he expects the national cardiac review to begin.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67406","67406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709972","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2017 to Question 63752, on heart diseases: medical treatments, when consultation on the national cardiac review will begin; and how long he expects it to last.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67407","67407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709973","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department provides guidance to the Department for Communities and Local Government on the potential health effects of mobile telephone masts.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67443","67443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709974","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of radiation levels from mobile telephone masts and the effect of those masts on health.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67444","67444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709975","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how decisions on the Commissioning through Evaluation process will be communicated to (a) patients, (b) hospital trusts and clinical commissioning groups and (c) the life sciences sector.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67424","67424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709976","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of ending access to procedures which are in the analysis phase of the current Commissioning through Evaluation process on (a) retention of skills among and (b) retraining costs of surgeons.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67428","67428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709977","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects patients to be able to receive the treatments currently in the analysis phase of the current Commissioning through Evaluation process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67429","67429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709978","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that rehabilitation wards for stroke patients receive adequate funding.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67400","67400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709979","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has commissioned research into whether the Dubs scheme for unaccompanied child refugees encouraged people trafficking.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67425","67425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709980","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 65370, on asylum: advisory services, what qualifications are needed, other than registration with the General Medical Council, to be an Asylum Support Medical Advisor; how many such advisors were registered with the General Medical Council in 2016; and whether her Department has any contracts with companies to provide such advisors.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67399","67399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709981","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, at what stage during an arrest and subsequent policy custody stay police officers should review (a) the Police National Computer and (b) other information sources for previous convictions.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67414","67414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709982","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 65370, on asylum: advisory services, what procedures govern (a) whether caseworkers should refer medical evidence to an Asylum Support Medical Advisor and (b) how that caseworker assesses the advice provided by that advisor.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67398","67398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709983","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidelines are given to police officers on giving consideration to the existence of one or more past offences by a suspect when taking a decision on granting bail.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67415","67415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709984","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she will consider reclassifying nitrous oxide as a controlled substance.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67409","67409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709985","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many customs officers have been in post in each year since 2007; and how many customs officers were in post on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67386","67386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709986","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether attacks on police dogs will no longer be classed as damage to property and be treated as an aggravated attack on a sentient being; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67394","67394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709987","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who passed through the National Referral Mechanism as victims of modern slavery or of human trafficking with positive conclusive grounds status were granted discretionary leave to remain in the UK for the periods (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 1 April to 31 December 2016 on the basis of (i) their personal circumstances or (ii) pursuing compensation.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67395","67395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709988","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who passed through the National Referral Mechanism as victims of modern slavery or of human trafficking with positive conclusive grounds status were granted discretionary leave to remain in the UK for the periods (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 1 April to 31 December 2016 on the basis of (i) their personal circumstances, (ii) pursuing compensation or (iii) cooperating with the police in their enquiries; and how many of those people had discretionary leave granted, respectively, for (A) under 12 and (B) between 12 and 30 months.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67396","67396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709989","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2017 to Question 66201, on immigration: EEA nationals, whether confirmation of this status will be needed once the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67397","67397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709990","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of deaths attributable to the inhalation of nitrous oxide.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67408","67408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709991","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Partnership Principles, what discussions her Department has had with the Palestinian Authority on the endorsement by the District Governor of Ramallah, Laila Ghannam, of the decision of the Palestinian Liberation Organization Supreme Council for Youth and Sports to name a youth camp after Dalal Mughrabi.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67423","67423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709992","2017-03-14","Department for International Development","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of heart disease rates on (a) life expectancy and (b) economic growth in developing countries.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67401","67401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709993","2017-03-14","Department for International Development","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve the availability of genetic testing for heart disease in developing countries.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67402","67402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709994","2017-03-14","Department for International Development","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help prevent deaths from heart disease in developing countries.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67403","67403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709995","2017-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has raised the increase in the cost of work permits for foreign workers in South Sudan with the South Sudanese Government.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67436","67436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709996","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether there are vacancies for Anglican chaplains in prisons in (a) London, (b) Surrey and (c) Kent.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67441","67441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709997","2017-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners serving sentences for imprisonment for public protection whose tariffs have expired (a) did not complete and (b) were waiting for places on offending behaviour courses in each year since 2010; and what those courses are.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67433","67433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709998","2017-03-14","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the Northern Ireland economy of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67391","67391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709999","2017-03-14","Department for Transport","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with drone manufacturers on the use of mapping services for geo-fencing.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67390","67390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710000","2017-03-14","Department for International Trade","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the (a) value and (b) proportion of exports of goods and services in the clean energy and renewable sector for (i) solar, (ii) wind, (iii) tidal, (iv) hydroelectric and (v) nuclear energy in each quarter of financial years (A) 2015-16 and (B) 2016-17.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67435","67435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710001","2017-03-15","Department for International Trade","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department's Trade Policy Group have experience of working on the UN sustainable development goals.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67437","67437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710002","2017-03-14","Department for International Trade","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department's Trade Policy Group have experience of working in the agricultural industry.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67430","67430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710003","2017-03-14","Department for International Trade","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the (a) value and (b) proportion of exports in the manufacturing sector for (i) automotive, (ii) aerospace and (iii) defence products in each quarter of financial years (A) 2015-16 and (B) 2016-17.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67434","67434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710004","2017-03-14","Department for International Trade","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department's Trade Policy Group have experience of working in the environmental goods and services sector.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67431","67431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710005","2017-03-15","Department for International Trade","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department's Trade Policy Group have experience of working on human rights issues.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67438","67438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710006","2017-03-14","Department for International Trade","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department's Trade Policy Group have experience of working on fisheries policy.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67432","67432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710008","2017-03-15","Department for International Trade","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department's Trade Policy Group have experience of working on labour rights.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67439","67439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710009","2017-03-15","Department for International Trade","2017-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department's Trade Policy Group have experience of working on environmental protection.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67440","67440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709615","2017-03-13","Cabinet Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed in the manufacturing sector in (a) Lancashire, (b) the North West and (c) England at the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67232","67232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709616","2017-03-13","Cabinet Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average salary of full-time equivalent employees was in Pendle constituency for April of each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67231","67231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709617","2017-03-13","Cabinet Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the level of foreign direct investment in the UK from Pakistani investors in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67230","67230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709618","2017-03-13","Cabinet Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff in his Department have been seconded from (i) businesses and (ii) charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67308","67308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709619","2017-03-13","Cabinet Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) businesses and (ii) registered charities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67317","67317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709620","2017-03-13","Cabinet Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answers of 2 March 2017 to Questions 65453, 65456 and 65480, what criteria the Government uses to determine which factors to test for their effects on voter turn out.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67334","67334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709621","2017-03-14","Cabinet Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of deaths associated with respiratory conditions in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67368","67368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709622","2017-03-14","Cabinet Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to answer Question 62917 tabled on 2 February 2017 by the hon. Member for West Bromwich East.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67375","67375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709623","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) businesses and (ii) registered charities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67322","67322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709624","2017-03-14","HM Treasury","2017-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) self-employed people in Scotland, (b) Scotland's economy and (c) the UK's economy of the measures announced in Spring Budget 2017 to increase Class 4 national insurance contributions to 10 per cent from April 2018 and 11 per cent from April 2019.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67376","67376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709625","2017-03-14","HM Treasury","2017-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims for child tax credit, made by couples not married or in a civil partnership, were cancelled due to the death of a partner in the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67358","67358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709626","2017-03-14","HM Treasury","2017-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people paying Class 4 National Insurance Contributions in (a) Aberdeen South and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67366","67366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709627","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff in his Department have been seconded from (i) businesses and (ii) charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67315","67315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709628","2017-03-14","HM Treasury","2017-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect on Scotland's economy of referendum on Scottish independence.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67297","67297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709629","2017-03-14","HM Treasury","2017-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) living standards and (b) household incomes in Scotland of the revised inflation forecasts in the Office for Budget Responsibility's Economic and Fiscal Outlook published alongside Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67301","67301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709630","2017-03-14","HM Treasury","2017-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has received representations on the creation of a children's funeral fund.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67250","67250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709631","2017-03-14","HM Treasury","2017-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average change will be in national insurance contributions for self-employed people in (a) St Helens North, (b) North West and (c) the UK will be after the new rate announced in the Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67251","67251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709632","2017-03-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of houses which have planning permission that are not built within (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four and (e) five years.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67215","67215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709633","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) businesses and (ii) registered charities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67318","67318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709634","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff in his Department have been seconded from (i) businesses and (ii) charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67309","67309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709635","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to consult with the social care sector before publishing the social care green paper as announced in paragraph 5.6 of Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67257","67257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709636","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of ending the automatic entitlement to housing benefit for 18 to 21 year olds on the effectiveness of the measures in clauses 4 and 5 of the Homelessness Reduction Bill.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67345","67345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709637","2017-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether Ofcom will continue to be a member of the Body of European Regulators for Electronic Communications after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67240","67240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709638","2017-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans for the UK to adopt the new European Electronic Communications Code after it is finalised in 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67262","67262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709639","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to require operators of social media platforms to report communications sent via their service which could reasonably be interpreted as containing content which would constitute an offence under section 1 of the Malicious Communications Act 1988 or section 127 of the Communications Act 2003 to a relevant police force.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67255","67255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709640","2017-03-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff in her Department have been seconded from (i) businesses and (ii) charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67310","67310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709641","2017-03-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department have had with (i) businesses and (ii) registered charities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67319","67319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709642","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to require operators of social media platforms to report communications sent via their service which are either indecent images or videos of children or messages which would lead to the sexual grooming of a child to a relevant police force.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67216","67216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709643","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to require operators of social media platforms to report communications sent via their service which could reasonably be interpreted as containing content which pertains to an imminent threat to the national security of the UK to the Metropolitan Police Counter Terrorism Command.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67217","67217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709644","2017-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she will publish the criteria used to determine whether a complaint received by her Department regarding library services is considered a formal complaint.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67236","67236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709646","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) serving personnel and (b) dependents will be based at Catterick in each year between 2017 and 2020.","Biography information for Rishi Sunak","Rishi Sunak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67223","67223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709647","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64194, if he will consult the Defence Select Committee on the terms of reference for the Army's Junior Entry review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67222","67222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709648","2017-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has made any payment to (a) Nassir Abd Al Zahra Al Zayi Al-Tamini, (b) Hussein Ali Kazhin Zabayain Al-Maliki, (c) A'la or Dhia Jabbar Al-Khazhair/Okthair, (d) Muhammad Hatu Karim Al-Garizi, (e) Musa Isma'il Al-Fartusi and (f) Nabil Al-Mawzani.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67238","67238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709649","2017-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what alternative anti-submarine warfare solutions for the P-8 Poseidon his Department has explored with (a) UK and (b) international suppliers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67302","67302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709650","2017-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to pay the US Department of Defence to test and evaluate UK-specific equipment for installation on the P-8 Poseidon.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67303","67303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709651","2017-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to engineer flexibility into UK P-8 Poseidon aircraft concerning the incorporation of non-standard equipment at a later date.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67304","67304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709652","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 64012, how many UK personnel are assigned to US Africa Command; at what bases they are stationed; and what roles they undertake.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67275","67275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709653","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66440, how many of those service personnel are involved in operations in Yemen.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67271","67271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709654","2017-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the revision of accommodation at the MOD Hebrides Range, West Camp, and the implications for staff at that faculty.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67365","67365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709655","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to Answer of 3 July 2014 to Question 202477, whether all deployments of US military personnel from (a) RAF Menwith Hill, (b) RAF Croughton and (c) RAF Molesworth are carried out with the full knowledge and consent of the Government.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67332","67332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709656","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria were used to determine who was invited to the unveiling of the Iraq and Afghanistan Memorial on 9 March 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67325","67325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709657","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) date and (b) location is of the small and medium-sized enterprise defence equipment event in Bridgend constituency; whether the hon. Member for Bridgend will be invited to that event; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67330","67330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709658","2017-03-14","Department for Education","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been (a) put on a child protection plan and (b) put back on a child protection plan within two years of coming off such a plan in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67371","67371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709659","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 64751, what the estimated value is of all land acquired to free schools.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67270","67270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709660","2017-03-14","Department for Education","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the illustrative funding allocations for 2016-17, published alongside the Stage 2 consultation on the schools national funding formula, December 2016, which local authorities were allocated funding in respect of the mobility factor; and how much such funding was allocated to each local authority.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67259","67259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709661","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure schools have policies in place to look after children with medical conditions.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67293","67293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709662","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will make an assessment of the effect on educational (a) provision and (b) outcomes of the physical condition of the 1960s Second Consortium of Local Authorities schools in (i) Hampshire and (ii) North East Hampshire.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67214","67214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709663","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to encourage people from Black and minority ethnic backgrounds to undertake apprenticeships.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67229","67229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709664","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to increase flood prevention in Earby.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67228","67228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709665","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Chief Scientific Adviser plans to publish the report, From Waste to Resource Productivity.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67234","67234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709666","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent on administering badger control measures in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67288","67288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709667","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the relative effectiveness of cage trapping and controlled shooting in controlling badger populations.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67289","67289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709668","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the levels of bovine TB in areas which are (a) under and (b) not under badger control measures.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67290","67290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709669","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the total value of cattle slaughtered due to the detection of bovine TB within the herd in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67291","67291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709670","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the largest single herds slaughtered due to the detection of bovine TB in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67292","67292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709671","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff in his Department have been seconded from (i) businesses and (ii) charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67312","67312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709672","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) businesses and (ii) registered charities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67320","67320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709673","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether non-participation in the March 2017 UN Conference to Negotiate a Ban on Nuclear Weapons is compliant with the UK's obligations under the Non-Proliferation Treaty.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67267","67267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709674","2017-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in the Republic of Colombia; and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67249","67249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709675","2017-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority on alleged payments to convicted terrorists.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67242","67242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709676","2017-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Middle East Peace Process of the alleged practice by the Palestinian Authority of paying salaries to convicted terrorists.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67243","67243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709677","2017-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the US Administration on the effect on UK security of leaks from US intelligence agencies.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67364","67364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709678","2017-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to support the eradication of female genital mutilation in the Gambia since the election of President Adama Barrow.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67370","67370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709679","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to fulfil its UN Human Rights Council election pledge to protect and promote freedom of religion or belief.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67342","67342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709680","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria were used to determine the first sustainable and transformation plan areas to receive Government funding.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67323","67323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709681","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the dental contract prototype on (a) patient oral health and (b) dentists' salaries and benefits.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67341","67341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709682","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 26 of Budget 2017, how the £130 million in additional capital to sustainable and transformation plans (STPs) was calculated; and what proportion of the total capital requirement of STPs that represents.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67324","67324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709683","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of sickness absence in ambulance staff resulting from injuries sustained from physical violence at work from patients and members of the public.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67359","67359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709684","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons his Department does not routinely publish details of NHS funding for dental services.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67340","67340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709685","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66737, on surrogate motherhood and lone parents, when he plans to launch a consultation on legislative proposals to give single parents with children born through surrogacy the same rights as couples.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67333","67333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709686","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2016 to Question 47007, on dental services, which 79 high street practices are continuing to test the prevention-based clinical pathway.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67343","67343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709687","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of eating disorder (a) beds and (b) services are delivered by the private sector.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67347","67347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709688","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, against what criteria the evidence and learning group will assess the success of the dental contract reform prototype scheme.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67337","67337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709689","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of providing dental services in West Yorkshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67338","67338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709690","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on replacing current NHS dental contracts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67339","67339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709691","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people with learning disabilities as of 9 March 2017 who remained in long-stay hospitals for over 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67346","67346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709692","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the level of bullying and harassment between employees in the NHS.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67360","67360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709693","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that British citizens who have made plans to retire in the EU after the UK has left the EU will have access to healthcare.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67326","67326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709694","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NHS Staff Survey results for 2016, published on 7 March 2017, what assessment his Department has made of the monetary value of discretionary effort provided by NHS staff.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67361","67361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709695","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the average weekly nutritional intake of households in (a) AB, (b) C1, (c) C2, (d) D and (e) E NRS social gradings.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67331","67331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709696","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what investigations are being carried out by the South East Coast Ambulance Service (SECAMB) on the use of approved drugs and medical equipment from East European countries; and how many members of staff of SECAMB are (a) on garden leave, (b) suspended, (c) being investigated and (d) have left employment in the last year as a result of allegations of misconduct or professional incompetence.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67373","67373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709697","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Marginal Rate Emergency Tariff (MRET) fund reinvestment in reducing emergency admissions for specialist services pathways such as neuromuscular services; and whether MRET funding is the responsibility of clinical commissioning groups or NHS England.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67211","67211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709698","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people commenced treatment for hepatitis C in the first six months of financial year 2016-17 in each operational delivery network area.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67244","67244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709699","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which sustainability and transformation plans have identified (a) hepatitis C or (b) HIV as a priority.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67245","67245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709700","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the NHS will develop a common care pathway for the treatment of different types of hepatitis C and HIV.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67246","67246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709701","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has provided to operational delivery networks for the creation of outreach services in hepatitis C since 2015.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67247","67247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709702","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 66177, on dementia, whether he plans to make an assessment of the adequacy of treatment provision for people diagnosed with early onset dementia.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67248","67248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709703","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many places there were in registered care homes in Leeds in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67219","67219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709704","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with which EEA countries the UK has bilateral reciprocal healthcare arrangements.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67221","67221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709705","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has reviewed whether Freedom of Information legislation should apply to GP Federation Organisations awarded taxpayer funded contracts.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67235","67235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709706","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS staff are encouraged to report errors and near misses.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67277","67277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709707","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place the highest priority on provision of treatment for lung disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67279","67279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709708","2017-03-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 5.5 of Spring Budget 2017, what estimate his Department has made of how much of the £2 billion of social care funding will be allocated to (a) St Helens and (b) Merseyside.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67258","67258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709709","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many delayed transfers of care were notified by (a) Lancashire Care Foundation Trust and (b) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals Trust for the monthly situation report in each month in 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67260","67260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709710","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to reduce mortality rates among patients with lung disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67276","67276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709711","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 65063, on care homes: standards, if he will provide equivalent data from 2004-05 to 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67256","67256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709712","2017-03-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 5.5 of Spring Budget 2017, what criteria his Department plans to use to determine the allocation to local authorities of the £2 billion of social care funding.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67264","67264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709713","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to enable the General Medical Council to display credentials in cosmetic surgery on its medical register of doctors.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67241","67241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709714","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question HL2227, how his Department monitors clinical commissioning groups on waiting times for cataracts surgery.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67261","67261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709715","2017-03-14","Department for Education","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost of the Immigration Skills Charge to the NHS in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20 and (d) 2020-21.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67299","67299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709716","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of sustainable and transformation plans that will not receive additional funding as part of the allocation announced in Budget 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67287","67287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709717","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for carrying out post-mortems for (a) children and (b) adults was in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67295","67295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709718","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to increase the number of pathologists available to conduct post-mortem examinations for coroners.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67296","67296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709719","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many sustainability and transformation plan areas have submitted a credible implementation plan.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67286","67286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709720","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of pathologists.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67294","67294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709721","2017-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many adult and juvenile repeat offenders in London who have not received a non-custodial sentence since Section 28 of the Criminal Justice and Courts Act 2015 came into effect have had (a) more than one previous knife conviction and (b) a previous conviction for a violent offence in addition to their previous knife crime conviction.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67298","67298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709722","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on social media platforms which operate in the UK but are based in the US reporting communications sent via their service which might pertain to an imminent threat to national security of the UK to the FBI rather than to a UK security agency.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67220","67220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709723","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Dewsbury of 10 February 2017 on child refugees.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67224","67224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709724","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people working in the UK health and social care system are doing so on a Tier 2 visa.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67252","67252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709725","2017-03-14","Department for Education","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether any exemptions from the Immigration Skills Charge will be available to (a) NHS and (b) other public sector employers.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67253","67253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709726","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people resident in Pakistan applied for (a) visitor visas and (b) permanent settlement in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67227","67227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709727","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 65319, on HM Passport Office, what the scope is of the review referred to; and when she plans for that review to be completed.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67213","67213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709728","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on the fact that books denying the Holocaust are available to buy on Amazon UK.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67208","67208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709729","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contact she has had with Amazon to discuss the fact that books denying the Holocaust are available to buy on Amazon UK.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67209","67209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709730","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to prevent the sale of books denying the Holocaust on Amazon UK.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67210","67210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709731","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the Government's response to the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67380","67380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709732","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many domestic violence protection notices have been issued by each police force in each year since March 2014.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67328","67328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709733","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to report on the review into the protection of firearms officers on operational duties announced by the previous Prime Minister.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67363","67363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709734","2017-03-14","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on trends in the level of doorstep crime in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67378","67378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709735","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans are in place to provide urgent humanitarian assistance to Palestinians who will be made homeless by demolitions in the near future.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67285","67285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709736","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department have had with (i) businesses and (ii) registered charities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67321","67321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709737","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff in her Department have been seconded from (i) businesses and (ii) charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67313","67313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709738","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding has been provided to Inter Mediate for work related to Burma in each financial year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67269","67269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709739","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what financial support her Department is providing to civil society organisations in the Lake Chad region.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67272","67272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709740","2017-03-13","Cabinet Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the level of electoral fraud; and if he will undertake a review of legislation with a view to restricting on-demand postal and proxy votes.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67268","67268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709741","2017-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of bodies were released by coroners within the Chief Coroner's target of three days in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67281","67281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709742","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff are available in Wales for the community supervision of people sentenced to less than 12 months; and what assessment she has made of the adequacy of provision of buildings and educational opportunities for those people.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67266","67266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709743","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders supervised by (a) the National Probation Service and (b) the Community Rehabilitation Company in Wales were taken back to prison having missed appointments in (i) 2014, (ii) 2015 and (iii) 2016.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67265","67265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709744","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of Operation Pallial's investigation into Peter Steen, Dafydd Vevar, Alan Challenor, Keith Evans, Kelvin Horrobin, Denis Jones and Aideen Jones, formally residential care staff of Bryn Alyn Community; and what further costs have been incurred by the (a) Police, (b) Crown Prosecution Service and (c) courts in relation to that investigation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67284","67284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709745","2017-03-14","Department of Health","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to introduce screening for brain injury as part of the admission procedure for all adult and juvenile prisoners in England and Wales.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67350","67350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709746","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to review the capability of (a) HM Prison Service and (b) contracted-out prisons to respond to incidents of concerted indiscipline.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67335","67335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709747","2017-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) community sentences and (b) suspended prison sentences included a Mental Health Treatment Requirement in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67348","67348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709748","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions in the last year private prisons have required the support of HM Prison Service to deal with concerted indiscipline.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67336","67336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709749","2017-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she will make it her policy to include training to support people with a brain injury within the basic training for all prison officers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67349","67349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709750","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many domestic violence protection orders have been made by the courts in each year since those orders March 2014.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67327","67327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709751","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will increase the fee paid to pathologists who conduct post-mortem examinations for coroners.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67379","67379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709752","2017-03-13","Leader of the House","2017-03-09","To ask the Leader of the House, when he plans to publish the Short money funding allocation to Opposition political parties for the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67233","67233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709753","2017-03-14","Scotland Office","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many meetings he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer and officials from HM Treasury to discuss the Ayrshire Growth Deal.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67218","67218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709754","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency on issuing a further recall for Vauxhall Zafira cars following reports that some vehicles that have already had both recalls are still having problems with burning and melting to the heater systems.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67225","67225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709755","2017-03-14","Department for Transport","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 4.22 of Spring Budget 2017, how much of the £690 million fund to erase road congestion will be allocated to (a) St Helens and (b) the North West.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67263","67263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709756","2017-03-14","Department for Transport","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason Network Rail did not complete a high level review of First Hull Trains' proposal to electrify the Hull-to-Selby line; when the decision not to complete a high level review was made; and whether that decision was made by (a) his Department and (b) Network Rail.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67369","67369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709757","2017-03-14","Department for Transport","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been budgeted for upgrades to stretches of the A27 at (a) Arundel, (b) Worthing/Lancing and (c) Lewes/Polegate.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67362","67362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709758","2017-03-14","Women and Equalities","2017-03-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the Appeal Court ruling in the case of Steinfeld and Keidan on opposite sex civil partnerships; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67372","67372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709759","2017-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18 to 21 year olds claim housing benefit in (a) the North East of England, (b) Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland, (c) Middlesbrough and (d) Redcar and Cleveland.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67374","67374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709760","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the significant findings were of equalities impact assessment on the removal of housing benefit for 18 to 21 year olds.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67329","67329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709761","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18 to 21 year olds claimed housing benefit in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Newport West constituency in each of the last seven financial years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67381","67381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709762","2017-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans for the proposed Green Paper on employer debt legislation associated with Section 75 of the 1995 Pensions Act to be published.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67356","67356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709763","2017-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which charities and voluntary sector organisations were consulted on proposed changes to the Widowed Parents' Allowance; and what the results of that consultation were.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67355","67355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709764","2017-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18 to 21 year olds claim the housing costs element of universal credit in (a) the North East of England, (b) Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland constituency, (c) Middlesbrough and (d) Redcar and Cleveland.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67377","67377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709765","2017-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken as a result of the Speaker's statement of 6 March 2017, Official Report, column 622, on his Department's new policy on accessing information about constituents' universal credit claims; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67354","67354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709766","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential effect of the UK's decision to leave the EU on the level of funding available for businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67212","67212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709767","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will list the revisions he has made to the timetable for publication of the emissions reduction plan.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67226","67226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709768","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of excluding onshore wind from the Government's future Contract for Difference procurement strategy on electricity bills.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67239","67239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709769","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his departmental resource DEL in Table 1.6 of Spring Budget 2017, which funds are classed as unallocated in financial years (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67254","67254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709770","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the implications for competition in the motor industry of potential restrictions on access to data collected by automobiles for (a) car manufacturers and (b) independent repair providers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67278","67278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709771","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff in his Department have been seconded from (i) businesses and (ii) charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67307","67307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709772","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) businesses and (ii) registered charities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67316","67316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709773","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to combat aggressive methods of door to door selling of items worth less than £42.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67300","67300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709774","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential to increase exports of electricity through new and existing interconnectors.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67351","67351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709775","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will provide an update on the Government's timetable for the publication of the techno-economic assessment of small modular reactors.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67344","67344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709776","2017-03-14","Department for International Trade","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment the Government has made of the implications of different legal frameworks in the devolved administrations for any new trade agreements after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67367","67367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709777","2017-03-13","Department for International Trade","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff in his Department have been seconded from (i) businesses and (ii) charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67314","67314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709778","2017-03-13","Department for International Trade","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) businesses and (ii) registered charities since his Department was established.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67306","67306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709779","2017-03-14","Department for International Trade","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will publish the section of his Department's People Survey for 2016 that covers UK Trade and Investment.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67237","67237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709780","2017-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff in his Department have been seconded from (i) businesses and (ii) charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67311","67311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709781","2017-03-14","Department for International Trade","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues on the balance to be obtained between providing inward investment to the UK and the needs of home-grown businesses.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67280","67280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709782","2017-03-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with (a) registered charities and (b) businesses the on drafting of the White Paper, The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67282","67282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709783","2017-03-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with the Office for Civil Society on the drafting of the White Paper, entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67283","67283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709784","2017-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) businesses and (ii) registered charities since his Department was established.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67305","67305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709785","2017-03-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to meet registered charities ahead of negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67274","67274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709786","2017-03-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with registered charities on the future of the charity sector in England and Wales after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67273","67273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709787","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the import of natural gas from the European Single Market.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67352","67352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709788","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on electricity prices of the (a) UK leaving the EU and (b) developing Energy Union.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67353","67353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709789","2017-03-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61497, if he will publish the estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of pursuing the appeal to the Supreme Court in the case of R Miller and Dos Santos v the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67357","67357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709263","2017-03-13","Attorney General","2017-03-08","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 64992, on Attorney General: procurement, how many civil servants of the Law Officers' Departments have contract management responsibility for external providers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66990","66990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709264","2017-03-13","Attorney General","2017-03-08","To ask the Attorney General, if he will make representations to the Serious Fraud Office to open an inquiry into any activity of Lloyds Bank Consumer Debt Recovery and Alder King.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67052","67052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709265","2017-03-13","Cabinet Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what formal guidance civil servants involved in the government procurement process receive on the implications of the Public Services (Social Value Act) 2012 for such procurement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67070","67070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709266","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consultation he plans to carry out on potential future regional investment funds to replace European Structural and Investments funds, once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67089","67089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709267","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to revisit the case for adopting public country-by-country reporting in the UK unilaterally, if a multilateral agreement is not forthcoming.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67093","67093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709268","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to reduce VAT on flight training and general aviation-related mechanical or engineering education programmes.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67039","67039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709270","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the finding of the British Vehicle Rental and Leasing Association report on the economic impact of changes to the vehicle excise duty, published in February 2017, that those changes will result in rental companies purchasing 24,800 fewer vehicles in 2017 compared with 2016.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67055","67055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709271","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his proposals on Making Tax Digital, published in December 2015, for what reasons the threshold of an income of £10,000 was agreed; and what assessment he has made of the effect of that threshold on self-employed entertainment sector workers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67049","67049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709272","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the Government's policy is on exempting (a) state, (b) free and (c) private schools from the planned increase in business rates due in April 2017.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67051","67051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709273","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, at how many meetings with Finance Ministers from (a) EU and (b) non-EU countries he has discussed public country-by-country reporting.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67027","67027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709274","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects to reach a multilateral agreement under which the UK may adopt public country-by-country reporting.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67028","67028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709275","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has considered setting a special rate of insurance premium tax for charitable organisations.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67024","67024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709276","2017-03-13","Cabinet Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department provides to people taking up public appointments against the use of aggressive tax avoidance schemes.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67012","67012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709278","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions the Financial Secretary to the Treasury has had on tobacco related taxation with representatives of (a) the All Party Parliamentary Group on Smoking and Health and (b) Action on Smoking and Health.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67103","67103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709280","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the private finance industry on how to increase the number of financial advisers qualified to advise on equity release.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67118","67118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709281","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what amounts were paid in probate fees in each of the two years ending May 2015 and 2016; and what amounts she estimates will be paid in probate fees in each of the two years following May 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67142","67142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709282","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on sixth form colleges of being ineligible for VAT registration.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67105","67105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709283","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what sanctions he plans to levy against Concentrix for its failure to meet the 15 and 40 day deadline for dealing with complaints.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67144","67144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709284","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the review of the principle of equal treatment between men and women in accessing insurance services.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67145","67145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709285","2017-03-13","Church Commissioners","2017-03-08","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what progress has been made on addressing the financial difficulties at Peterborough Cathedral; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67095","67095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709286","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64314, on NHS: finance, if he will give NHS bodies priority to transitional relief funds.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67120","67120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709287","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 March 2017 to Question 64310, on non-domestic rates, whether local authorities will have to apply for transitional relief.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67132","67132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709288","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64310, on non-domestic rates, what proportion of the transitional relief will be allocated to (a) the West Midlands and (b) Birmingham.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67133","67133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709289","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.17 of the Spring Budget 2017, if he will take steps to ensure that public houses in receipt of the proposed business rate discount do not face significant additional charges in 2018-19.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67135","67135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709290","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64309, if he  will grant public bodies the same discounted rates as charities.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67155","67155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709291","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications to open new general aviation airfields have been received by UK planning authorities in the last five years.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67007","67007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709292","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy and effectiveness of legislation related to compensation for people whose vehicles are damaged by unreported potholes.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67020","67020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709293","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the use by local authorities of central government grants to tackle potholes.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67021","67021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709294","2017-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on the ownership of data by consumers with respect to the control of that data by those consumers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67203","67203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709295","2017-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to retain the regulation of transparency of workplace data collection contained in the General Data Protection Regulation after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67204","67204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709296","2017-03-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether a television licence is required solely to view live streaming video of Parliamentary proceedings or recordings of such proceedings on www.parliamentlive.tv.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67100","67100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709297","2017-03-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times the Digital Infrastructure and Inclusion Implementation Taskforce has met in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67101","67101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709298","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK will continue to contribute to Common Security and Defence Policy operations after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67112","67112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709299","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK's exit from the EU on the status of Cypriot nationals who are resident in the UK Sovereign Base Areas on Cyprus.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67108","67108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709300","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of monitoring and reporting on the human rights situation  and developments in Yemen by the UN Office of the High Commissioner for Human Rights.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67109","67109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709302","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer to Question 62599, on Ministry of Defence: staff, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the potential merits of armed forces medical personnel assisting the NHS at peak demand periods.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67088","67088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709303","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK will be represented at the proposed 2017 UN Conference to negotiate a global ban on nuclear weapons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67117","67117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709304","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Iraq Historic Allegations Team will prosecute current and former members of the armed forces under the legal system in the constituent part of the UK in which they currently reside.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67009","67009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709305","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Chinese DF-21D missile.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66993","66993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709306","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64194, which subject matter experts in defence and government departments will be invited to contribute to the Army's Junior Entry Review; how other stakeholders and interested parties can contribute to that review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67005","67005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709308","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the current or former members of the armed forces resident in Scotland who are being investigated by the Iraq Historic Allegations Team in respect of alleged criminal actions have access to legal advice and support.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67010","67010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709309","2017-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of trends in the representation of (a) women and (b) people from BAME backgrounds in the armed forces in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67068","67068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709311","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the preparedness of schools for the new numerical GCSE grading system.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67073","67073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709312","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 63407, for what reasons her Department does not provide financial information to the public on the estimated cost of a school closure as part of the consultation process.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67084","67084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709314","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 65006, on student: loans, if she will publish details of the in-depth market testing exercise the Government conducted.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67085","67085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709315","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which (a) free schools and (b) university technical colleges have closed since 2010; what the cost to the public purse was of each of those closures; and what each of those sites had been used for since each such closure.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67037","67037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709316","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much the Government spent on the 15 hours (a) funded childcare offer for three and four year olds and (b) offer for disadvantaged two year olds in 2015-16 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67044","67044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709317","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many undergraduate students have studied for their degree at a university in an EU country other than the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67029","67029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709319","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has assessed the potential merits of introducing a helpline for children within the social care system to call or text in emergency situations.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66982","66982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709320","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a method of anonymous feedback for children who have been through the social care system on the failings and successes of that system.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66983","66983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709321","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2017 to Question 63742, on grammar schools, what proportion of the applications for expansion projects through the annual Condition Improvement Fund were from multi and single academy trusts which includes a selective school.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67131","67131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709322","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the extent to which bovine TB is spread by dogs.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67006","67006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709323","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department is on target to meet its commitment to plant 11 million trees by 2020; and how many trees have been planted to date.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67022","67022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709325","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that 11 million trees are planted by 2020.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67023","67023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709326","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits of tax incentives and more stringent air quality and other legislation to reduce the number of diesel vehicles on the roads.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67058","67058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709327","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of allocating departmental funding to support the development of technology to filter toxic particles from vehicle exhausts at source to reduce air pollution.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67059","67059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709328","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits introducing legislative proposals on the use of signage and fines in areas of high pollution to encourage drivers to switch off their engines while stationary.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67060","67060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709329","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to reduce emissions in London.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67057","67057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709330","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the formal responsibilities of his Department's Special Envoy for Gender Equality are; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67061","67061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709331","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what financial resources have been allocated to support the work of his = Department's Special Envoy for Gender Equality in (a) this financial year and (b) the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67062","67062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709332","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many full-time equivalent members of staff in his Department report directly to his Department's Special Envoy for Gender Equality; and whether he plans to increase that number.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67063","67063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709333","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent legislation passed by the Knesset on the ability of (a) UK parliamentarians and (b) other UK citizens to participate in fact-finding visits to Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67071","67071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709334","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of Israel to ensure that UK parliamentarians and other UK citizens are granted entry to Israel and through Israel to the Occupied Palestinian Territories for fact-finding purposes.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67072","67072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709335","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in Ghana; and what was discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67067","67067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709336","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what review process was undertaken to establish that Turkey should not be designated as one of the 30 Human Rights Priority Countries.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67114","67114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709337","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the UN Verification and Inspection Mechanism in Yemen.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67115","67115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709338","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to send a UK representative to the March 2017 UN Conference to negotiate a ban on nuclear weapons.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67116","67116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709339","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who will be responsible for the Empowerment Fund in his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67104","67104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709340","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of public sector pay restraints on levels of expenditure by the NHS on agency staff.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67123","67123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709341","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Migration Advisory Committee's recommendation that nurses remain on the shortage occupation list, what assessment he has made of the effect of pay restraints on long-term retention and recruitment rates for NHS nurses.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67121","67121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709342","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the potential merits of removing pay restraints for Agenda for Change staff as a result of recent inflation forecasts from the National Institute of Economic and Social Research.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67122","67122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709343","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the UN Committee on the Rights of the Child on its 2016 recommendation on implementing the International Code of Marketing of Breastmilk Substitutes.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67139","67139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709344","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of heart failure to (a) the NHS and (b) Ealing Clinical Commissioning Group in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67163","67163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709345","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to support the NHS to mitigate the financial cost of the immigration skills charge for financial year 2017-18.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67154","67154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709346","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the consultation on regulation of Physician Associates.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67164","67164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709347","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date his Department expects Bridgewater Community Healthcare NHS Foundation Trust to publish its full business case in relation to the Liverpool community health service contract.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67136","67136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709348","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria Bridgewater Community Healthcare NHS Foundation Trust will have to meet to be able to access an increased Sustainability and Transformation Fund allocation.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67137","67137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709349","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64314, on NHS: finance, if the Government will make it its policy to give NHS bodies priority access to transitional relief funds.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67134","67134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709350","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64314, on NHS: finance, if he will make an assessment of (a) the total annual cost of proposed business rates changes to the NHS and (b) the potential effect of those costs on the delivery of patient services.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67130","67130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709352","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the (a) clinical and (b) cost effectiveness of the provision of bariatric surgery alongside other preventative public health measures in reducing cases of type two diabetes.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67004","67004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709354","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many brain injuries around birth there were in (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013, (d) 2014 and (e) 2015.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67002","67002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709355","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the powers of clinical commissioning groups to make them more accountable to the public.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66999","66999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709356","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government is able to allocate Competition and Markets Authority fines collected from pharmaceutical manufacturers Pfizer and distributor Flynn Pharma for the purposes of research and treatment for epilepsy patients.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66984","66984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709357","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what duty is on local authorities to ensure that home care agencies provide mandatory bowel and bladder training for carers.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66985","66985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709358","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the study published by Oxford Academic on 17 February 2017 on inappropriate checks undertaken by online pharmacies, if he will discuss with the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency means to prevent the online sale of antibiotics and other medicines without appropriate checks.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66981","66981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709359","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2016 to Question 53151, if the Government will ensure that the Sentinel Stroke National Audit Programme begins to collect data on patient experience and outcomes.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66988","66988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709360","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff at NHS Property Services Ltd are employed in a facilities management role.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66995","66995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709361","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to establish a clinical audit database for cosmetic surgery as recommended by Professor Sir Bruce Keogh's Review of the regulation of cosmetic interventions, published in April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66996","66996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709362","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average turnaround time is for applications to the National Dental Performers List since that service has been taken over by Capita.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67038","67038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709363","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of additional GPs that will be required in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67065","67065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709364","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2017 to Question 62903, what the timescale is for publishing the review of the nutrient profile model; and what the reasons are for the time taken to publish that review.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67086","67086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709365","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 63405, how many children were seen by an NHS dentist in the latest 12-month period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67082","67082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709366","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many investigations relating to employee relations, such as disciplinary grievance and dignity at work cases, have taken place relating to Bridgewater Community Healthcare NHS Foundation Trust in each of the last three calendar years; and how many of those investigations resulted in (a) sanctions being given and (b) employees being dismissed by that Trust.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67078","67078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709367","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) number and (b) availability of dedicated maternity bereavement rooms and facilities across the NHS.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67079","67079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709368","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 63405, how many adults were seen by an NHS dentist in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67081","67081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709369","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of midwives to be recruited in (a) the London Borough of Newham, (b) Greater London and (c) the UK up to 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67045","67045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709370","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS and its agencies spent on mental health services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67046","67046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709371","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 66178, what budget has been allocated to Individual Funding Requests in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67053","67053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709372","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to expand health services in North East Bedfordshire to meet growing demand as a result of additional houses being built.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67056","67056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709373","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what service standard his Department has set Capita for the average turnaround time for applications to the National Dental Performers List; and what penalties are in place in the event that those standards are not achieved.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67033","67033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709374","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what statistics (a) his Department, (b) NHS trusts and (c) clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) hold on referrals to treatment by (i) NHS trusts and (ii) CCGs.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67042","67042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709375","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department monitors compliance with government targets on waiting times for treatment.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67043","67043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709376","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) restraint, (b) confiscation, (c) civil recovery and (d) property freezing orders the National Crime Agency has in place in relation to assets belonging to politically exposed persons from Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67047","67047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709377","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the value is of assets under restraint of assets related to politically exposed persons in Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67048","67048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709378","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional support her Department provides for people who are deaf and hard of hearing during asylum processes.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67025","67025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709379","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional support her Department provides for people who are deaf and hard of hearing during visa application processes.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67026","67026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709380","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 6 March 2017, Official Report, column 561 on immigration: indefinite detention, on what date her Department plans to publish its plan for the future of the immigration detention estate.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67080","67080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709381","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the value is of assets confiscated by the Government belonging to politically exposed persons from Nigeria since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67000","67000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709382","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total value is of recovered assets belonging to politically exposed persons from Nigeria through civil recovery orders by the National Crime Agency since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67001","67001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709383","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase the number of prosecutions related to female genital mutilation in (a) Peterborough, (b) Cambridgeshire and (c) England; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67094","67094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709384","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals from which countries are appealing against removal proceedings in  (a) the UK, (b) Southend and (c) Rochford and Southend East constituency.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67150","67150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709385","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals her Department has started removal proceedings against in (a) the UK, (b) Southend and (c) Rochford and Southend East constituency.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67147","67147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709386","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people her Department has deported from (a) the UK, (b) Southend and (c) Rochford and Southend East constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67148","67148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709387","2017-03-13","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 66044, whether her Department holds details of which countries the 40 young people that left care, were referred to in the Department for Education's statistical release entitled Children looked after in England including adoption: 2015 to 2016, published on 28 February 2017, were deported to.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67099","67099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709388","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has for the reallocation of the UK's current contribution to EU development funds after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67102","67102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709389","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, by what date she expects that all projects funded through the (a) Prosperity Fund and (b) Conflict Security and Stabilisation Fund will be listed on her Department's Development project tracker.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67107","67107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709390","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, to clarify how UK aid supports the Palestinian Authority's centralised education service.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67153","67153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709391","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2017 to Question 64094, if she will publish her Department's review of UK future trade policy.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67083","67083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709392","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to countries in the Lake Chad region to (a) increase the transparency of and (b) reduce corruption in government.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67034","67034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709393","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the root causes of the humanitarian crisis in the Lake Chad region.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67035","67035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709394","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to increase the Government's donor contributions to the Lake Chad region to match or exceed those made by other governments at the Oslo donor conference.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67036","67036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709395","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the mental health needs of children fleeing conflict in (a) Syria, (b) Iraq, (c) Afghanistan and (d) Eritrea.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67054","67054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709396","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders received a fixed-term recall in the last year for which information is available; and what the (a) violence against the person and (b) other offence category was relating to each of those recalls.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67013","67013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709397","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders received more than one fixed-term recall in the latest year for which information is available; and what the (a) violence against the person and (b) other offence category was relating to each of those recalls.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67014","67014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709398","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of recalls to prison were fixed-term in each of the last two years for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67015","67015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709399","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders received a fixed-term recall for (a) breaching the terms of their licence, (b) committing a further offence, (c) a combination of breaching their licence and reoffending and (d) any other reason in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67016","67016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709400","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many previous convictions each offender had who received more than one fixed-term recall in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67017","67017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709401","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made on tackling the abuse of personal injury whiplash claims relating to incidents involving motor vehicles.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67096","67096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709402","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of fraudulent whiplash claims.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67077","67077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709403","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to review the level of compliance with prison service instructions on prisoner escort.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67066","67066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709404","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of guidelines for tougher sentences for knife crimes on the numbers of people imprisoned for such crimes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67064","67064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709405","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will meet the (a) Law Society and (b) Solicitors Regulation Authority to discuss trends in the number of whiplash claims.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66986","66986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709406","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons she is proposing a negative discount rate for personal injury claims calculations; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67138","67138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709407","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to answer Questions (a) 55553 on prison sentences: Lancashire, tabled on 30 November 2016, (b) 62826 on Members: correspondence, tabled on 21 February 2017 and (c) 64827 on electronic tagging, tabled on 21 February 2017 by the hon. Member for Preston; and whether she plans to respond to the letter on Questions 55553 and 64827 sent by email and post by the hon. Member for Preston on 3 March 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67141","67141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709408","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national offenders by country were (a) imprisoned, (b) released from prison and (c) deported in each of the last five years.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67149","67149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709409","2017-03-13","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the role of the British-Irish Council is until the Northern Ireland Executive is restored.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67146","67146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709410","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will (a) set out the data sources, supporting information and the assumptions used and (b) estimate traffic volumes per (i) day and (ii) peak hour for (A) Option A14 and (B) Option C of the Lower Thames Crossing Option on (1) the existing Dartford Crossing, (2) a new Option A14 crossing, (3) a new Option C crossing, (4) the A282 between junction 30 and junction 2 of the M25, (5) the A2 between the M25 and the A227, (6) the A2 between the A227 and the M2, (7) the A227 between the A2 and the A20, (8) the A228 between the M2 and M20 and (9) the A229 between the M2 and the M20.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67152","67152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709411","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many properties situated less than 120 metres away from the proposed line of route for phase 2b of High Speed 2 will not be eligible for compensation because they fail to meet the criterion that at least 25 per cent of the land must be within the designated Rural Support Zone.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67106","67106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709412","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 65327, how much accrued to the public purse in charges for those speed awareness courses under the National Driver Offender Retraining Scheme in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67143","67143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709413","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will respond to the Rees Jeffreys Road Fund report, entitled A Major Road Network for England, published in October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66980","66980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709414","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess the potential effect of the Peugeot-Citroen deal to buy Vauxhall-Opel on the (a) availability and (b) level of compensation for customers affected by Vauxhall car fires.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66997","66997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709415","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that Abellio Greater Anglia meets its franchise commitments related to performance; and if he will make it his policy to use his enforcement powers as the franchising authority in the event that those commitments are not met.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66994","66994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709416","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the costs and benefits of the UK remaining a member of the European Aviation Safety Agency after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67008","67008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709417","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place the cost-benefit analysis of Option A14 of the Lower Thames Crossing in the Library; and what the data sources and supporting information were for that analysis.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67074","67074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709418","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding the Government plans to provide to Shropshire Council for developing a business case on the North West Relief Road.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67087","67087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709419","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make a revised estimate of traffic volume forecasts for 2025 and 2041 as published in tables 4.3 and 4.4 of volume 5 of the Lower Thames Crossing Pre-Consultation Scheme Assessment Report, published in January 2016, using information from traffic surveys undertaken since that report was published, including information from ANPR cameras and traffic counters.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67097","67097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709420","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on improving of the reliability and availability of wifi and mobile connectivity on trains between (a) Penzance and London and (b) Taunton and Bristol.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67011","67011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709421","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2016 to Question 54114, how many times per month traffic is stopped at the Dartford River Crossing to allow hazardous and oversized vehicles to use the tunnels for each month since November 2016; what the average duration of each such stoppage has been; and when the future work referred to in his Answer will be undertaken to model the potential reduction in the number of escorted vehicles per day.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67032","67032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709422","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the introduction of alternative penalties to fines for drivers using mobile telephones.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67050","67050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709423","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66433, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of employment and support allowance work-related activity group claimants who will only be entitled to a reduced rate who will fall below the poverty line as a result of changes in support for that group.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67041","67041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709424","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the additional processing and administration costs related to the implementation of the proposed new housing benefit rules for 18 to 21 year olds.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67018","67018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709425","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households with claimants aged 18 to 21 were in receipt of housing benefit in (a) 2010-11 and (b) the most recent period for which figures are available; and, of those households, how many received income derived from benefits only in each of those periods.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67019","67019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709426","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much top-up funding will be provided to each local authority following the introduction of the Local Housing Allowance cap.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67090","67090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709427","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect that a Local Housing Allowance cap will have on other services provided by local authorities.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67092","67092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709428","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of implementing the Local Housing Allowance cap.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67091","67091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709429","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times his Department has written to claimants of contribution-based employment and support allowance requesting details of bank and savings accounts held in each of the last 12 months; and for what reasons that information was requested.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67069","67069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709430","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what methodology his Department used to estimate how many new claimants will be exempt from the proposed new housing benefit policy for 18 to 21 year olds.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67003","67003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709431","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Clause 4, Part 2 of the Social Security (Personal Independence Payment) Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66991","66991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709432","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18 to 21 year olds jointly claimed jobseekers support allowance and housing benefit in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency in each financial year from 2010-11 to date.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67128","67128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709433","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was of housing benefit expenditure on 18 to 21 year olds for (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency in each financial year from 2010-11 to date.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67125","67125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709434","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18 to 21 year olds jointly claimed employment and support allowance and housing benefit in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency in each financial year from 2010-11 to date.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67126","67126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709435","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households claimed housing benefit in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency in each financial year from 2010-11 to date.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67127","67127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709436","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Welfare Delivery of 7 March 2017, Official Report, column 684, on housing benefits, 18 to 21 year olds, how much of the projected savings of £105 million will accrue to the public purse in each region and constituent part of the UK by year.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67124","67124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709437","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what account the Green Deal Oversight and Registration Body took of the prior business history of company directors before accrediting Green Deal installers.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67140","67140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709438","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many wind turbines were installed in the (a) Irish Sea, (b) North Sea and (c) English Channel in each year between 2006-07 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67119","67119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709439","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) directly employed and (b) contractor employees there were in the offshore wind industry in each year between 2006-07 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67098","67098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709440","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many firms have been removed from the approved list of Green Deal installers in each calendar year of the scheme to date.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67151","67151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709441","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to respond to the letter of 24 January 2017 from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West on trades unions' political funds, reference ZA6413.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67129","67129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709442","2017-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to improve public trust in the private sector management of consumer data.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67205","67205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709443","2017-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on the ownership of employee data in the workplace.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67206","67206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709444","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support small and medium-sized enterprises in accessing extended credit terms.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66992","66992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709445","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to bring into force the provisions of the Easter Act 1928 to fix the date of Easter from 2018 onwards.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66998","66998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709446","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what responsibility his Department takes for malpractice by accredited Green Deal installers.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67075","67075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709447","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what criteria were used to draw up the list of approved installers under the   Green Deal Home Improvement Fund.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67076","67076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709448","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether capacity market auctions take into account future growth projections for electric vehicles.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67030","67030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709449","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has undertaken to ensure the capacity of the electricity grid to respond to current and future demand for electric vehicles.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67031","67031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709450","2017-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps he has taken to address the national skills gap in the construction industry.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67040","67040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709451","2017-03-13","Department for International Trade","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether, in his official capacity, he has met Mr Adam Werritty abroad in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66989","66989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709452","2017-03-13","Department for International Trade","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the turnover rate for UK Trade and Investment local-hire staff in overseas postings has been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66987","66987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709453","2017-03-13","Department for International Trade","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what information he holds on annual receipts and revenue flows accruing to the regimes in Libya from oil exports in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67113","67113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709454","2017-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on maintaining automatic annual increases in the state pensions of UK residents living in other EU countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67111","67111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709455","2017-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether negotiations to secure the rights of EU citizens resident in the UK after the UK leaves the EU will also include securing the rights of EEA citizens who reside in the UK.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67110","67110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709456","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a plan to stop the use of tax havens including containing steps to help UK-linked tax havens transition towards other types of economies and steps to deter UK companies from using tax havens.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67167","67167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709457","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when and how the Government plans to use its powers to introduce public country-by-country reporting on tax havens; and what steps the Government is taking to obtain support from other countries for multilateral action.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67161","67161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709458","2017-03-13","HM Treasury","2017-03-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy not to plan any reductions in the rate of corporation tax further to those he has already announced.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67162","67162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709459","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that UK Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies introduce public registers of beneficial ownership; and whether he will set a timetable for their introduction.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67174","67174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709460","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 65551, where in the Office for National Statistics Civil Service employment statistics it states what proportion of senior civil servants in his Department are (a) men, (b) women, (c) disabled and (d) from black, Asian and minority ethnic backgrounds.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67168","67168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709461","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how he plans for the discretionary business rate relief announced in paragraph 3.16 of the Spring Budget 2017 to be distributed to local authorities.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67188","67188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709462","2017-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how he plans for the additional money proposed for adult social care in paragraph 5.5 of the Spring Budget 2017 to be distributed to local authorities.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67189","67189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709463","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of pensioners receiving local housing allowance live in the (a) private rented sector and (b) social rented sector.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67194","67194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709464","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on administering the Phonics Screening Check since it was launched in 2012; and under what headings in each year.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67183","67183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709465","2017-03-13","Department for Education","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department and the Standards and Testing Agency have spent on administering standard attainment tests over each of the last five financial years; and under what headings in each year.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67181","67181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709466","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that zoos across the UK have sufficient levels of animal welfare.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67169","67169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709467","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to improve animal welfare in abattoirs.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67171","67171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709468","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to reduce marine pollution caused by shipping in UK waters.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67172","67172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709469","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to reduce roadside pollution.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67173","67173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709470","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of microplastics entering the marine environment on (a) wild and (b) non-wild animal welfare.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67200","67200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709471","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to reduce waste and litter entering the marine environment across the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67196","67196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709472","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 65236, what plans her department has to prevent the remaining 99.99 per cent to 95.9 per cent of microplastics from entering the marine environment.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67199","67199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709473","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to help bring the former Gambian president, Yahya Jammeh, to trial at the International Criminal Court for human rights abuses.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67202","67202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709474","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support the work of the UN Secretary-General's Coordinator for improving the UN's response to sexual exploitation and abuse.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67182","67182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709475","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in other EU member states and representatives of global institutions on assistance for the new Gambian administration.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67184","67184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709476","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) military and (b) civilian UK personnel are currently deployed on UN (i) peacekeeping operations and (ii) special political missions; and on which operations such personnel are deployed.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67177","67177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709477","2017-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many and what proportion of (a) military and (b) civilian UK personnel are currently deployed on UN (i) peacekeeping operations and (ii) special political missions are women.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67178","67178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709478","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department and the NHS are taking to support uptake and implementation of the NICE Quality Standard on acute heart failure.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67165","67165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709479","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that adequate services are available for patients in areas where there is a high prevalence of heart failure.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67166","67166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709480","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 64306, if he  will provide data from each bi-annual publication of the GP Patient Survey Dental Statistics since 2010 for the statistics listed under the main results section of the data published on 7 July 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67156","67156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709481","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the 90 per cent fill rate for GP positions in England in 2016 as set out in Health Education England's General Practice ST1 recruitment figures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67157","67157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709482","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase recruitment of GPs.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67158","67158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709483","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there will be in GP education budgets in each Health Education England region between 2016-17 and 2017-18.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67159","67159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709484","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the implications of microplastics entering the marine environment for human health.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67201","67201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709485","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries working in the NHS as cardiologists; what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of such cardiologists; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on NHS productivity of that change in the number of cardiologists.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67190","67190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709486","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries working in the NHS as surgeons; what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of such surgeons; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on NHS productivity of that change in the number of surgeons.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67191","67191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709487","2017-03-13","Department of Health","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2017 to Question 66473, on mental health services: mothers, how much of the £290 million pledged he plans to spend in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67192","67192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709488","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals serving prison sentences have been deported from prisons in (a) the UK, (b) Southend and (c) Rochford and Southend East constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67207","67207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709489","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on whether the description by the newspaper Al-Hayat Al-Jadida and official Palestinian Authority television of the perpetrator of a terrorist attack as a martyr who died for Allah constitutes a breach of her Department's Partnership Principles by the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67175","67175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709490","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on whether the screening of a Palestinian television children's programme that included a poem inciting violence against Israel constitutes a breach of her Department's Partnership Principles by the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67176","67176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709491","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on whether the decision of the Palestinian Authority Ministry of Education to name a school after Salah Khalaf constitutes a breach of her Department's Partnership Principles by the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67179","67179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709492","2017-03-13","Department for International Development","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether UK direct or multilateral aid to the Palestinian Authority provides any financial or in-kind support to schools named after terrorists.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67180","67180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709493","2017-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2017 to Question 61344 on prisons: electronic equipment, what information her Department holds on the number of (a) game consoles and (b) televisions in prisons.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67198","67198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709494","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the Accessibility Action Plan since the Progress Update of January 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67187","67187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709495","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Middlesborough South and East Cleveland of 7 February 2017 to Question 62858 on bus services: visual impairment, when his Department plans to launch its consultation on the Accessibility Action Plan.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67195","67195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709496","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether provisions in the Vehicle Technology and Aviation Bill to create an offence of shining or directing a laser at a vehicle will also cover maritime vessels.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67160","67160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709497","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department supports projects to enable better access to taxi and private-hire vehicles for guide-dog owners.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67186","67186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709498","2017-03-13","Department for Transport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the potential annual percentage increase of rail fares in the next five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67170","67170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709499","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the difference in levels of income between employment and support allowance (ESA) claimants who are entitled to the former work-related activity group rate and new ESA claimants who will receive a reduced rate.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67185","67185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709500","2017-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of extending the local housing allowance from pensioners in the private rented sector to those in the social rented sector.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67193","67193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709501","2017-03-13","Department for International Trade","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he last met his counterpart in South Africa to discuss bilateral trade between the UK and South Africa.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67197","67197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/709645","2017-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to prepare for the potential effect of the use of artificial intelligence on the workplace.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909231","909231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710742","2017-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Government's industrial strategy on Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909238","909238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/708831","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 66174, what information her Department holds on the number of individual payments which were not paid within the Basic Payment Scheme payment window since January 2016.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66880","66880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/708832","2017-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the effect of recent fluctuations in the level of the pound on the payments to UK claimants under the CAP Basic Payment Scheme in each month since June 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66882","66882"
