"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444954","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to keep children safe on the internet at school and at home; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22598","22598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444955","2016-01-19","Department for Education","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many responses her Department has received (a) through its online response form and (b) by email to its Out-of-school education settings: registration and inspection consultation.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22620","22620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444956","2016-01-19","Department for Education","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new entrants there were for religious education initial teacher training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22699","22699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444957","2016-01-19","Department for Education","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the target was for new entrants on to Religious Education initial teacher training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22692","22692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444958","2016-01-19","Women and Equalities","2016-01-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how the PSHE Association guidance on body image is distributed to teachers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22693","22693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444959","2016-01-19","Department for Education","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure schools in deprived areas have adequate money in their budgets to take children on school trips connected to the curriculum.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22694","22694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444960","2016-01-19","Women and Equalities","2016-01-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Oral Answer to the hon. Member for Litchfield of 14 January 2016, how the media-smart literacy resources regarding body image are distributed to parents.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22702","22702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444961","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she last met the Home Secretary to discuss support for unaccompanied asylum seeking children and trafficked children; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22649","22649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444962","2016-01-19","Department for Education","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people achieved qualified teacher status in religious studies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22704","22704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444963","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve personal social health and economic education in schools.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22652","22652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444964","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy that personal social health, economic and education be compulsory in all schools.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22653","22653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444965","2016-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of (a) known available oil and gas reserves and (b) reserves estimated to be found as a result of fracking she plans to be left unexploited.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22698","22698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444966","2016-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much the Government plans to spend from the public purse on supporting or enabling exploratory and productive fracking in the UK.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22696","22696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444967","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many defibrillators are provided in each building her Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22556","22556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444968","2016-01-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what expenditure has been allocated to the Civil Nuclear Constabulary in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18, (d) 2018-19 and (e) 2019-20.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22582","22582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444969","2016-01-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many police officers of the Civil Nuclear Constabulary she estimates will be deployed in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18, (d) 2018-19 and (e) 2019-20.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22583","22583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444970","2016-01-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what cross-departmental structures her Department has established with the Department for Communities and Local Government and the Department for Transport since May 2015 to ensure progress on meeting the EU target of 15 per cent of energy from renewable sources by 2020.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22532","22532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444971","2016-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the 28 measures identified on pages four to six of her Department's publication, Report of the Habitats and Wild Birds Directives Implementation Review, published in March 2012, what steps she has taken to implement each of those measures.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22533","22533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444972","2016-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Written Statement of 12 January 2016, HCWS 462, on December Environment Council, what steps she plans to take to improve the implementation of EU Nature Directives.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22534","22534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444973","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many defibrillators are provided in each building her Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22557","22557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444974","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to ensure that flood maps clearly show landfill sites to aid in the assessment of risk to public health in the event of flooding.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22684","22684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444975","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will take steps to educate local flood resilience groups on the dangers of toxins in flood water.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22677","22677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444976","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will review the National Adaption Plan in order to reflect the risk to public health from toxins in flood water.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22678","22678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444977","2016-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on how many occasions the Thames Barrier has been used in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22666","22666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444978","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will work with insurers to ensure an accurate risk assessment is carried out on the threat to public health posed by toxins in flood water.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22654","22654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444979","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Forestry Commission England has spent on replanting in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22651","22651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444980","2016-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on research taking place to find alternatives to neonicotinoid pesticides.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22673","22673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444981","2016-01-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20502, if she will make it her policy to update the Veterinary Medicine Regulations and the Summary of Product Characteristics of antibiotic products in order to end the preventative administration of antibiotics where no disease has been diagnosed in any of the animals in the group being to treated.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22669","22669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444982","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of (a) the potential economic merits of water attenuation and retention by sustainable drainage systems and (b) the capital and maintenance costs of sustainable drainage systems.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22648","22648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444983","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to increase tree-planting as a method of flood prevention.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22587","22587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444984","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many hectares of trees have been (a) felled and (b) replanted on Forestry Commission land in England in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22588","22588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444985","2016-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Mauritanian government of the death sentence imposed for apostasy on Mohamed Mkhaitir in that country.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22606","22606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444986","2016-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the evidence his Department holds or is otherwise aware of on the existence of slavery in Mauritania.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22607","22607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444987","2016-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Mauritania on the imprisonment of Biram Dah Abeid in that country.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22608","22608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444988","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 20989, what information his Department holds on how many cases of murder of (a) human rights defenders, (b) trades unionists and (c) political activists there have been in the last three years in Colombia for which someone has been brought to trial.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22599","22599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444989","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 20989, whether he has made representations to the government of Colombia on the practice of locating military bases in rural villages in Colombia.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22600","22600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444990","2016-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether there will be discussion of long-term support for the countries bordering Syria at the Syria Donors Conference 2016.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22670","22670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444991","2016-01-19","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which countries were invited to the Syria Donors Conference; and which of those countries she expects to attend.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22671","22671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444992","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will hold discussions with the UN on the alleged misappropriation of reconstruction building materials to Hamas in Gaza.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22633","22633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444993","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the Middle East peace process of recent attacks against Israeli citizens.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22634","22634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444994","2016-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Palestinian Authority on recent comments related to  the practice of honouring terrorists by Rami Hamdallah.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22638","22638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444995","2016-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with his Colombian counterpart (a) the deteriorating health of many former combatant prisoners, (b) the reported human rights violations of prisoners, (c) the reported arbitrary transfers of prisoners and (d) the reported isolation of prisoners in that country which have taken place since its government's pledges of November 2015 made following the prisoners' hunger strike there.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22703","22703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444996","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he expects the report on progress on recommendations regarding child detention in Palestine by the delegation of lawyers visiting Palestine in February 2016 to be published.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22681","22681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444997","2016-01-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2016 to Question 21764, whether the government of Saudi Arabia (a) responded formally, (b) responded informally or (c) did not respond when the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State and the UK Ambassador raised the UK's concerns about the recent mass executions; on what date the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State and the Ambassador raised those concerns; and whether the exchange referred to in that Answer took place by telephone, in person, or in writing.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22661","22661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444998","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to Israel of the implications of its obligations under the Geneva Convention for the practice of forcible transportation of child prisoners from Palestine to Israeli jails.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22683","22683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444999","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of (a) the extent of differential treatment of Palestinian and Israeli child detainees by Israel and (b) whether that differential is consistent with Israelis international human rights obligations.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22682","22682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445000","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many defibrillators are provided in each building his Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22558","22558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445001","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support Indonesia in dealing with the terrorist bombings in Jakarta in January 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22521","22521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445002","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Indonesian counterpart on the (a) ISIL attacks in Jakarta in January 2016 and (b) implications of those attacks for the Government's foreign policy.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22522","22522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445003","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on potential links between the terrorist attacks in Jakarta, Indonesia, and Diyarbakir, Turkey, in January 2015.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22523","22523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445004","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2016 to Question 21111, if he will make an assessment of the effect of delays in the publication of the hepatitis C framework on (a) all people and (b) members of the South Asian population in England with hepatitis C.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22520","22520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445005","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 11 January 2016, whether Northern Ireland will receive additional funding for mental health care as a result of the Barnett consequentials of the changes to funding set out in that announcement.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22543","22543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445006","2016-01-20","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve prevention and diagnosis of (a) skin cancer and (b) melanoma.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22540","22540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445007","2016-01-20","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve GP education on skin cancer and dermatology.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22541","22541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445008","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Barnett consequentials are for Scotland of the additional £1.5 billion allocated to the Better Care Fund in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22529","22529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445009","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the funding criteria will be for the social investment outcomes fund; and whether NHS providers of alcohol and drug addiction services will be able to apply for that funding.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22530","22530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445010","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many defibrillators are provided in each building his Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22560","22560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445011","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2016 to Question 20580, how long he expects the analysis phase of NHS England's Commissioning through Evaluation programme to last.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22679","22679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445012","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2016 to Question 20580, if his Department will ask NHS England to allow patient access to technologies assessed through NHS England's Commissioning through Evaluation programme during the analysis phase on the same basis as during the first stage of the programme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22685","22685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445013","2016-01-19","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2016 to Question 21919, whether the £290 million announced for perinatal mental health, funded from the Department's overall Spending Review Settlement, is in addition to the £600 million announced in the 2015 Autumn Statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22697","22697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445014","2016-01-19","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2016 to Question 21922, how much of the £75 million allocated to CCGs to improve local services in 2015-16 has been spent.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22701","22701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445015","2016-01-19","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2016 to Question 21922, which organisations other than CCGs have been allocated funding from the £173 million that has been allocated; and how much of that amount he estimates will be spent in 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22700","22700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445016","2016-01-19","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on research being undertaken to assist those severely affected by chronic obstructive pulmonary disease.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22695","22695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445017","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the back-to-work support which is available for people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22626","22626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445018","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doses of pandemic H1N1 vaccine were administered in the UK in the 2010-11 influenza season.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22629","22629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445019","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS advised GPs to administer the pandemic influenza vaccine during the 2010-11 winter due to shortages of supply of seasonal influenza vaccine.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22630","22630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445020","2016-01-19","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) junior doctors and (b) consultants were employed by the NHS in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22674","22674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445021","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department has made available for back-to-work support for people with mental health problems in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22636","22636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445022","2016-01-19","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2016 to Question 21066, if she will provide matching data for each other region of the UK.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22667","22667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445023","2016-01-19","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2016 to 21399, what assessment she has made of whether the French government is meeting its EU and international obligations in respect of registration of non-EU citizens in France who are in need of international protection.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22595","22595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445024","2016-01-19","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2016 to 21399, what steps she has taken related to migrants in France who wish to seek international protection in the UK and not in France.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22594","22594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445025","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 28 October 2015 on the dispersal of refugees.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22609","22609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445026","2016-01-21","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support the mental welfare of officers in the Greater Manchester Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22622","22622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445027","2016-01-21","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support the mental welfare of officers in the Greater Manchester Police Service.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22623","22623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445028","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people in the UK on a tier 2 visa who will not have their visa renewed when new rules requiring them to be paid at least £35,000 per annum or the going rate in the relevant UK Border Agency Code of Practice, whichever is higher.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22686","22686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445029","2016-01-19","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of crowd control guidelines issued to local police forces for large sporting events; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22676","22676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445030","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to support unaccompanied trafficked and asylum seeking children; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22650","22650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445031","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many defibrillators are provided in each building her Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22561","22561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445032","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to offer a discounted rate for dependents who apply for a Certificate of Entitlement for Right of Abode in the UK.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22519","22519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445033","2016-01-19","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how aid disbursed by her Department's Palestinian Programme tackles anti-Israeli incitement.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22535","22535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445034","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many defibrillators are provided in each building her Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22562","22562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445035","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the Government's priorities are for the Syria Donor Conference in February 2016.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22687","22687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445036","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to encourage donors to increase access to accredited quality education for Syrian refugee children in host countries in the region.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22688","22688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445037","2016-01-19","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps UK is taking to support the education of Syrian refugees in (a) Lebanon, (b) Jordan, (c) Iraq and (d) Turkey.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22690","22690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445038","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that vulnerable Syrian refugees in Lebanon and Jordan have access to basic services such as health and education.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22642","22642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445039","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures the Government has put in place to ensure that the resettlement programme in Lebanon and Jordan is able to identify the most vulnerable people.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22643","22643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445040","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure children receive education and protection in conflict zones.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22632","22632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445041","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what proportion the UK contributed to the EU humanitarian and development budget in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22627","22627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445042","2016-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2015 to Question 12035, what teaching agency G4S contacted; and what level of security clearance that member of staff was required to hold in order to enter the facility concerned.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22640","22640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445043","2016-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Ministers in his Department have visited G4S Medway in the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22665","22665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445044","2016-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much companies contracted by his Department to operate (a) detention centres, (b) prisons, (c) young offender institutions and (d) secure training centres have paid in fines in each of the last five years; and what the reason was for each such fine imposed.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22663","22663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445045","2016-01-19","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times G4S has been in breach of its contract at Medway STC since it was awarded that contract; for what reasons each such breach occurred; and what fines were incurred by G4S for each of these breaches.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22664","22664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445046","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many defibrillators are provided in each building his Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22563","22563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445047","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of violence in prisons.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22544","22544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445048","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions there have been for motor insurance fraud in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22525","22525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445049","2016-01-18","Leader of the House","2016-01-14","To ask the Leader of the House, how many defibrillators are provided in each building his Office manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22564","22564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445050","2016-01-18","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many defibrillators are provided in each building her Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22565","22565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445051","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many defibrillators are provided in 10 Downing Street.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22566","22566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445052","2016-01-18","Scotland Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many defibrillators are provided in each building his Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22567","22567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445053","2016-01-19","Scotland Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his oral contribution of 6 January 2016, Official Report, column 275, what the source is of the figures which he quoted on application rates for higher education.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22597","22597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445054","2016-01-19","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Southeastern trains and Network Rail have contingency plans in the event of a rail line being closed due to unforeseen circumstances in order to (a) minimise disruption to other rail lines, (b) provide extra capacity on adjacent lines to get passengers as close as possible to their usual destinations and (c) ensure that up-to-the-minute information is provided to passengers regarding alternative routes and replacement services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22575","22575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445055","2016-01-19","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects repairs to the Bexleyheath line to be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22576","22576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445056","2016-01-19","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether railway verges are surveyed to identify locations where there is a danger that landslides may occur; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22577","22577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445057","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what work his Department has undertaken on helping develop a common reporting standard and collection method for incidents of disruptive passengers on flights departing from or arriving in the UK.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22610","22610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445058","2016-01-19","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the maximum number is of (a) trains and (b) international trains which are able to stop at Stratford International station in each hour.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22617","22617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445059","2016-01-19","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applications for the High Speed 2 (a) need to sell scheme and (b) exceptional hardship scheme have been received from constituents in Chesham and Amersham constituency; how many of those applications have been completed with the property now in the ownership of the Government or HS2 Ltd; how many of those properties in the ownership of the Government or HS2 Ltd have been (i) sold, (ii) rented and (iii) remain vacant; for how many of those applications that have been accepted the price has not been agreed; how many of those applications are awaiting a decision on whether they will be accepted; how many of those applications have been rejected; and of those rejected how many times each such application has been rejected and for what reasons.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22639","22639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445060","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current waiting time is for a PCV driving examination at Watnall test centre; what steps his Department is taking to reduce that waiting time; and when he expects that waiting time to be reduced.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22628","22628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445061","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the use of sealed tamper-proof bags for duty-free purchases to discourage consumption of alcohol in airports or onboard aircraft in order to reduce disruptive behaviour on flights.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22614","22614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445062","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to review the licensing arrangements for airside bars and restaurants in airports.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22615","22615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445063","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many defibrillators are provided in each building his Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22568","22568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445064","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of UK railway stations have steps but no lift access.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22546","22546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445065","2016-01-19","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains were reported as delayed due to winter sunlight since 4 January 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22573","22573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445066","2016-01-19","Department for Transport","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what explanation he has received for the cause of recent landslides on the Bexleyheath rail line; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22574","22574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445067","2016-01-18","Wales Office","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many defibrillators are provided in each building his Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22570","22570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445068","2016-01-18","Women and Equalities","2016-01-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many defibrillators are provided in each building the Government Equalities Office manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22559","22559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445069","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of Jobcentre Plus operating a smaller client facing office within Liscard Town Centre.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22548","22548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445070","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff who work at Wallasey Jobcentre Plus in Liscard live within two miles of that office; and how many of those staff will be (a) made redundant and (b) transferred as a result of the closure of that office.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22547","22547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445071","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many defibrillators are provided in each building his Department manages.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22571","22571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445072","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what projects his Department plans to fund through the £40 million allocated to the Health and Work Innovation Fund.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22584","22584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445073","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funding his Department has allocated for the expansion of the Fit for Work service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22585","22585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445074","2016-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the savings accrued by the closure of the Wallasey Jobcentre Plus in Liscard.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22579","22579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445075","2016-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who his Department consulted prior to 18 September 2015 on the proposed closure of Wallasey Jobcentre Plus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22580","22580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445076","2016-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Answer of 9 September 2015 to Question 9059, which other key stakeholders have been consulted on co-locating with Wallasey Jobcentre Plus; and when he plans to publish the outcomes, responses and findings of those consultations.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22581","22581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445077","2016-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 11 January 2015 to Questions 21337 and 21336, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the vast majority of existing universal credit claimants will see no change in entitlement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22516","22516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445078","2016-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many potential overlapping payments between those processed through the universal credit live service and those processed for housing benefit have been identified in the East London Jobcentre Plus district since 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22641","22641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445079","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment claimants were asked to attend reassessments earlier than the date originally given in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22645","22645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445080","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what circumstances claimants of personal independence payment may be asked to attend reassessments at an earlier date than initially expected.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22646","22646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445081","2016-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of women born in the 1950s who have been affected by the changes to pension terms made in 1995 and 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22675","22675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445082","2016-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the final version of the Evaluation of Removal of the Spare Room Subsidy was agreed within his Department.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22618","22618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445083","2016-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were paid their Christmas bonus on their benefits in the first week of December 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22619","22619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445084","2016-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what advice his Department gives to universal credit applicants on their eligibility for council tax reduction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22616","22616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445085","2016-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many claims for statutory shared parental pay have been linked to adoption leave since 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22621","22621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445086","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will publish an impact assessment in respect of the Universal Credit (Work Allowance) Amendment Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22612","22612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445087","2016-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total number of claims for statutory shared parental pay has been since 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22624","22624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445088","2016-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average number of weeks is for which statutory shared parental pay has been claimed since 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22625","22625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445089","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what specialist support will be available for disabled people under the new Work and Health Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22586","22586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445090","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to reimburse claimants who use the Wallasey Jobcentre Plus in Liscard for the additional cost of travel to an alternative site when that office closes.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22590","22590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444523","2016-01-18","Attorney General","2016-01-13","To ask the Attorney General, if he will review Norman James' case as raised in the letter from the hon. Member for Torfaen of 15 June 2015 to take account of recent developments in that case.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22400","22400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444524","2016-01-18","Attorney General","2016-01-13","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to his contribution of 16 September 2015, Official Report, columns 384-5WH, on Alan Richards and Kashif Shabir: SFO, what the threshold is for an investigation by the Serious Fraud Office.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22432","22432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444525","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to promote local high street retail businesses.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22502","22502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444526","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparative assessment he has made of the relative economic case for expansion of Gatwick and Heathrow Airports.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22309","22309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444527","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 20474, what proportion of businesses which have been in receipt of funding from the apprenticeship programme for the creation of apprenticeships in the retail and commercial enterprise sector subject area (a) pay at least the living wage to employees under contract and (b) have paid at least the living wage to such employees since the beginning of the apprenticeship programme in 2010.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22349","22349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444528","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 20474, how many apprenticeships created in the retail and commercial enterprise sector subject area have led to full-time, permanent employment with that employer following the completion of the apprenticeship.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22350","22350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444529","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 19955, whether the figures relating to (a) cases and (b) breaches in the tables are a measurement of the number of (i) employment agencies or (ii) agency workers.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22241","22241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444530","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answers of 12 January 2016 to Questions 19955 and 19954, (a) how much funding was allocated to and (b) how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22253","22253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444531","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the amount of private sector investment in research and development in each of the last three years; and what assessment he has made of trends in the level of such investment.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22286","22286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444532","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of changing Innovate UK funding from grants to loans.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22285","22285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444533","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department is providing universities to increase collaboration with Chinese research institutions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22272","22272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444534","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 20474, how his Department works with businesses in the (a) construction, planning and the built environment sector subject area and (b) engineering and manufacturing technologies sector subject area to create more apprenticeships.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22278","22278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444535","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 20474, which businesses have been in receipt of funding from the apprenticeship programme for the creation of apprenticeships in the retail and commercial enterprise sector subject area.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22280","22280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444536","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 20474, whether any businesses in receipt of funding from the apprenticeship programme for the creation of apprenticeships in the retail and commercial enterprise sector subject area have employed staff using zero-hours contracts in the last two years.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22281","22281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444537","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 20474, whether any businesses in receipt of funding from the apprenticeship programme for the creation of apprenticeships in the retail and commercial enterprise sector subject area have participated in the Government's work experience programme for those on jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22282","22282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444538","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 20474, how much funding has been allocated to apprenticeships in the retail and commercial enterprise sector subject area since 2010.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22279","22279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444539","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department has had with (a) the devolved administrations, (b) civic society and (c) industry on the privatisation of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22433","22433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444540","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of late payment of claims by insurance companies on SMEs.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22457","22457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444541","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of Government departments which failed to pay outstanding debts to SMEs within the 60 day maximum period set out in the Prompt Payment Code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22458","22458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444542","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what impact assessment the Government has undertaken on its decision to privatise the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22471","22471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444543","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason Cabinet Office spend over £25,000 has not been updated beyond December 2014.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22470","22470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444544","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions he has met with National Archive officials to discuss the release of Cabinet Office papers for the 1986 to 1988 period.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22436","22436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444545","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual salary is of the (a) Crown Steward and Bailiff of the Chiltern Hundreds and (b) Crown Steward and Bailiff of the Manor of Northstead.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22439","22439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444546","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on public sector and charitable provision of consumer debt advice services.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22431","22431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444547","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to encourage people to submit their tax returns before the January deadline.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22505","22505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444548","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the commercial provision of consumer debt advice services.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22374","22374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444549","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications for consumer credit licences for debt advice and debt adjusting on a commercial basis have been made in the last 12 months; and how many such applications have been (a) granted, (b) rejected, (c) withdrawn and (d) await a decision.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22375","22375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444550","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what targets his Department has for the granting, rejection and withdrawal of consumer credit licences for debt advice and debt adjusting on a commercial basis.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22376","22376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444551","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of HM Revenue and Customs office closures on the local economy in East Kilbride in 2025-26.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22370","22370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444552","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for the UK of any introduction of a financial transaction tax under the EU enhanced co-operation procedure.","Biography information for Richard Drax","Richard Drax","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22411","22411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444553","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs received in wine duty between April and December (a) 2015 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22413","22413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444554","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will support the UK's wine and spirit industry with further duty cuts in 2016.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22414","22414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444555","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what (a) discussions he has had with the Cooperative Bank and (b) what representations he has received on its decision to close bank accounts belonging to groups campaigning on matters relating to Israel and Palestine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22403","22403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444556","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications not to pay tax on income from rental properties due to the owner's overseas status were received in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2011-12 and (e) 2010-11.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22359","22359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444557","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Burnley receive working tax credit.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22336","22336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444558","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Burnley receive child tax credit.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22337","22337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444559","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of (a) the number of websites using  the HM Revenue and Customs logo without permission and (b) how many people have paid to use them; and what steps he is taking to identify and proceed against such websites.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22353","22353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444560","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he has made on analysis of responses to the pension transfers and early exit charges consultation, launched by his Department in July 2015; and when he plans to publish the response to the consultation.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22385","22385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444561","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the target of 20,000 resettled Syrian refugees is met by the end of this Parliament.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22422","22422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444562","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's press release of 1 July 2015, on tax-free childcare, how he plans to roll-out the delivery of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22423","22423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444563","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of total household debt in the UK in the final quarter of 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22290","22290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444564","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who do not qualify to be auto-enrolled into a pension because their qualifying earnings are achieved by income from more than one job.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22296","22296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444565","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on increasing the annual limit for ISA contributions.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22297","22297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444566","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people currently hold ISAs worth more than £1 million.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22314","22314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444567","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of income accruing to the Exchequer annually if ISA returns became taxable on pots greater than (a) £250,000, (b) £500,000 and (c) £1 million.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22315","22315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444568","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the value and proportion of tax relief provided on ISA investments across the income distribution.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22316","22316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444569","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of introducing flat rate tax relief on pensions contributions.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22274","22274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444570","2016-01-19","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people had supporting documents confirming identity and finances lost by the Tax Credit Office in each month in 2015; and how much was paid in compensation to people affected by such a loss.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22263","22263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444571","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much accrued to the public purse through VAT on domestic fuel in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22489","22489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444572","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the benefits of retaining the existing HM Revenue and Customs' operation in Middlesbrough.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22481","22481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444573","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Preston dated 7 October 2015 on rents for supported housing schemes run by housing associations and local authorities.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22257","22257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444574","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to improve the time to respond to correspondence from hon. Members and Peers since the tabling of the statement on 3 June 2015, Handling Members' Correspondence in 2014, HCWS11.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22258","22258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444575","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many letters his Department received from hon. Members and Peers in each month in 2015; and how many such letters received a substantive response within 10 working days.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22259","22259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444576","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on the devolution of European Regional Development Fund funding to local authorities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22311","22311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444577","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of his Department's budget has been allocated to addressing overcrowding in housing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22229","22229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444578","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of what the proportion of London residential property is owned by foreign nationals of which countries.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22358","22358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444579","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received on local authority non-compliance with statutory requirements in relation to (a) education, health and care plans and (b) the Local Offer; what mechanism is in place to ensure that local authorities comply with such statutory requirements; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure such compliance.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22367","22367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444580","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support property level flood resilience measures.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22409","22409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444581","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many £500 grants were provided to help households affected by flooding in each local authority in the Greater Manchester area between 1 December 2015 and 13 January 2016; and how much funding has been received by each of those councils to provide such grants up to 13 January 2016.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22410","22410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444582","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of Greater Manchester City Deal procurement contracts have been given to SMEs in the Greater Manchester area.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22426","22426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444583","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish the recommendations of the Gambling Commission in response to his Department's call for evidence on the National Lottery and raising funds for good causes, launched in December 2014.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22437","22437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444584","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he intends to publish the responses to his Department's call for evidence on the National Lottery and raising funds for good causes, launched in December 2014.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22438","22438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444585","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of how many museums and galleries charged for entry in (a) 2005 and (b) 2010; and what estimate his Department has made of how many museums and galleries plan to introduce such charges in 2016.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22226","22226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444586","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent on museums and galleries in (a) 2005, (b) 2010 and (c) 2014-15; and what estimate he has made of such spending in (i) 2015-16 and (ii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22254","22254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444587","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the need for a new concert hall in London.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22255","22255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444588","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many museums and galleries have closed in each region and nation of the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22256","22256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444589","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) homes and (b) businesses he expects to receive a rural satellite broadband voucher in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22493","22493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444590","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) homes and (b) businesses have (i) received and (ii) redeemed rural satellite broadband vouchers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22494","22494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444591","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of the planned budget for the rural satellite broadband voucher scheme has been spent.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22495","22495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444592","2016-01-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 21036, what funding was allocated by Sport England in each parliamentary constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22475","22475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444593","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has commenced a programme of testing shipborne rolling vertical landing of the F35B Lightning II.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22463","22463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444594","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many take-off tests for the F35B Lightning II have been completed using the Queen Elizabeth-class simulating ski ramp at US NAS Patuxent River.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22464","22464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444595","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women were recruited to the Royal Navy in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22450","22450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444596","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 21436, whether the UK will reconsider humanitarian assistance by air to Madaya in Syria if the Assad regime resumes its blockade; and if the Government will monitor the situation in order to take action if land access is blocked again.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22482","22482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444597","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the 2010 contract for £15 million with BAE Systems for the replacement of propulsion systems in the eight Hunt-class mine countermeasures vessels is still to be completed by October 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22479","22479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444598","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Hunter Class mine countermeasures vessels have completed their re-engineering; when he expects all eight to be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22480","22480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444599","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 21502, airstrikes in Syria, whether the robust process referred to includes an assessment of the number of civilian workers likely to be deployed in such installations and the potential number of casualties and other collateral damage from such airstrikes.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22496","22496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444600","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost was to the public purse of hosting Crown Prince Salman bin Hamad Isa Al Khalifa and a Bahraini delegation aboard HMS Defender at the event to mark the 200th anniversary of UK-Bahrain relations.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22497","22497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444601","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to ensure that checks on the complement and manning limit of reservist regiments are performed regularly and on time.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22242","22242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444602","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will increase investment in research on rehabilitation, health and social care models that can improve quality of life for ill Gulf War veterans and their families; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22264","22264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444603","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the Army Reserve in made up by Northern Irish soldiers.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22265","22265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444604","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21330, what estimate his Department has made of its spend on mental health specialists in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22312","22312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444605","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to Question 21228, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Letter of Request sent to the Defense Security Cooperation Agency.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22304","22304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444606","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on compiling a definitive central list of all service personnel who lost their lives on operations in Northern Ireland between 1969 and 2007.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22291","22291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444607","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what change there has been in the number of personnel in the Maritime Reserves Units in Northern Ireland in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22293","22293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444608","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what military assets his Department has decommissioned in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22273","22273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444609","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to (a) invest in research on rehabilitation, health and social care models to improve the quality of life for ill Gulf War veterans and (b) communicate the results of US research on those issues to Gulf War veterans living in the UK.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22430","22430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444610","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to commemorate the 25th anniversary of the start of combat operations in the First Gulf War.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22429","22429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444611","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of his Department's planned £8.4 million expenditure on armed forces veterans' mental health services will be spent in Scotland in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18, (d) 2018-19 and (e) 2019-20; and in which areas of mental health services that funding will be spent in each of those years.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22371","22371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444612","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 18551, for what reason his Department no longer holds records on trainee attendance and courses held; and what assessment he has made of the compliance of the disposal of those records with the policy and procedures set out in the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 20817.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22401","22401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444613","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will request the Senior Information Officer at (a) MOD Grantown-on-Spey, (b) MOD Llanrwst, (c) MOD Fairbourne and (d) MOD Crickhowell to provide a list of what records are held at that location of numbers of attendees on training courses, costs maintenance improvement and development costs, building of storage facilities and travel and accommodation costs for years prior to 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22402","22402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444614","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency plans the Government has in place should Rolls Royce be unable to complete the Nuclear Reactor Component of the Successor Programme on schedule.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22344","22344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444615","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 21502, on Syria: military intervention, what the evidential basis is for the statement that there have been no reports of civilian casualties as a result of RAF airstrikes in Iraq or Syria.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22321","22321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444616","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools teach sex education and consent in PSHE lessons.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22356","22356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444617","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with her Northern Ireland counterpart about the provision of England-based teaching jobs for unemployed teachers in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22361","22361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444618","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 11 January 2016 on parenting classes, (a) how many hours of such classes will be provided to parents and (b) whether there will be a cost to parents participating in such classes.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22306","22306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444619","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children of parents with mental illnesses there are in (a) pre-primary, (b) primary and (c) secondary schools in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22307","22307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444620","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many requests her Department has received under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 for documents relating to the opening of (a) academies and (b) free schools; and how many of those requests it responded to within the 20 working day time limit.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22320","22320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444621","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on lawyers in cases relating to the release of departmental documents under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22300","22300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444622","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will commission research on the (a) reasons for and (b) effects of the different thresholds for investigations to be initiated under section 17 and section 47 of the Children Act 1989.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22295","22295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444623","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of her Department's performance in adhering to the statutory time limit for responding to Freedom of Information requests.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22313","22313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444624","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which children's services departments have been visited by the Chief Social Worker for Children since her appointment.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22492","22492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444625","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to respond to the recommendations in the Social Mobility and Child Poverty Commission's 2015 State of the Nation Annual Report.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22484","22484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444626","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many requests under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 that were initially refused by her Department were subsequently granted in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22486","22486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444627","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that new gas-fired power stations are built in the UK.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22452","22452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444628","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on classification of capacity payments as an environmental levy.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22453","22453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444629","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will publish the methodologies and assumptions behind the projected overspend of levy control framework spending through to 2020.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22454","22454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444630","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what level of financial return the Government expects from diesel generators who will benefit from payments through the capacity market.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22447","22447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444631","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which local authorities have sought access to funds raised through the Energy Company Obligation and other green and social levies on energy bills.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22455","22455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444632","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to phase out the use of coal-fired power stations by 2025.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22283","22283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444633","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the removal of eligibility for Renewables Obligations Certificates for onshore wind on businesses which are considering developing wind farms.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22287","22287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444634","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer submitted to Question 21401, what new or changed policies her Department has implemented as a result of the evidence submitted.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22396","22396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444635","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how her Department plans to ensure that residents of park homes have access to smart meters; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22397","22397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444636","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 21401, what her Department's policy is on energy issues affecting park homes.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22398","22398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444637","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with the European Commission on the future of the White Rose Carbon Capture and Storage project.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22360","22360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444638","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2015 to Question 9021 and with reference to the Oxford Research Group, Remote Control project report: Hostile drones, published 11 January 2015, if the Office for Nuclear Regulation will review security at nuclear power stations.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22365","22365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444639","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 205 to Question 19617, what level of detail would not risk potential disclosure of confidential information consequent upon the listing of overspend against original estimates within the levy control framework arising from each of (a) performance of offshore wind, (b) levels between strike price and reference price and (v) variations in allocations of feed-in tariff payments for solar PV installations.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22354","22354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444640","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on implementing the conclusions of the COP21 climate conference in Paris.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22501","22501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444641","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce food waste.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22338","22338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444642","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage the grocery code adjudicator to investigate milk prices paid by Meadow Foods.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22364","22364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444643","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) financial and (b) other support her Department is providing to businesses which have been affected by floods to help them make resilient repairs to their properties.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22363","22363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444644","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to increase quota levels for the under-10 metres fishing fleet.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22347","22347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444645","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effects of the ban on fishing for bass on the North Devon fishing industry.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22346","22346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444646","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the value of the agricultural and horticultural industries to West Lancashire; and how many people were employed directly and through the supply chain in that industry in that area.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22227","22227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444647","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has estimated the cost to the agricultural and horticultural industry in West Lancashire of flooding in December 2015.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22228","22228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444648","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to incentivise small-scale on-farm anaerobic digestion systems.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22235","22235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444649","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she expects the two emergency authorisations covering the use of two neonicotinoid pesticides on a small proportion of the UK oilseed rape crop to expire; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22301","22301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444650","2016-01-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate her Department has made of the square mileage of the UK which has (a) permanent wind farms installed, (b) has been granted planning permission for wind farm installation and (c) is being considered for wind farm installation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22303","22303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444651","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the (a) economic contribution of pollinator activity across the UK and (b) potential last economic value if pollinator populations continue to decline at present rates; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22302","22302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444652","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2015 to Question 14627, what estimate her Department has made of the total funding available to the Waste and Resources Action Programme in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22277","22277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444653","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the online sale of puppies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22460","22460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444654","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the number and countries of origin were of dogs imported into the UK for (a) non-commercial reasons under PETS and (b) commercial reasons.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22443","22443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444655","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which local authorities received funding from her Department's air quality grant scheme in each year of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22435","22435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444656","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the conclusions of the United States Environmental Protection Agency's assessment of the neoniocotinoid imidacloprid, published on 6 January 2016.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22444","22444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444657","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the existing Vineyard Register is maintained in accordance with EU regulations.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22490","22490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444658","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish the diary of engagements of the Chief Social Worker for Children since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22491","22491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444659","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Colombian government in the last three months on the security situation for human rights defenders in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22449","22449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444660","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he and the Secretary of State for Defence met in a 2 plus 2 bilateral meeting with their Russian counterparts.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22465","22465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444661","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on Hamas' rearmament in Gaza; and if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on the Middle East Peace Process of that rearmament.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22456","22456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444662","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Ministerial Correction of 11 January 2016 on Saudi Arabia, what work has taken place under the memorandum of understanding since it came into force.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22252","22252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444663","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Iranian government on the effect on regional relations of the international competition for cartoons and caricatures on the Holocaust organised by the House of Cartoons, under the auspices of the municipality of Tehran.","Biography information for Lord Pickles","Sir Eric Pickles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22289","22289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444664","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) take steps to ensure that Saudi Arabia works for an immediate ceasefire in Yemen and (b) support the establishment of an international, independent, impartial mechanism to investigate alleged violations of international humanitarian law and human rights law by all parties in that conflict.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22276","22276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444665","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that UK-made arms are not being used to commit human rights abuses in Yemen.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22275","22275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444666","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the conduct of the first round of the general elections in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22288","22288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444667","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what statistical information his Department holds on the age, gender, ethnic group and religious identification of people in Bahrain.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22225","22225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444668","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the glorification by the Fatah movement of terrorists who have murdered Israelis.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22372","22372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444669","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority on reports of senior official Jibril Rajoub praising terror attacks against Israelis.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22373","22373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444670","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to disrupt and prevent the sale of antiquities by Daesh to finance their terrorist activities.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22391","22391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444671","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is providing to the Kurdish Peshmerga in their efforts against Daesh.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22392","22392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444672","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what planning for post-conflict stabilisation and reconstruction in Syria the Government has undertaken.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22393","22393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444673","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent bilateral discussions he has had with members of the International Syria Support Group on achieving a ceasefire in Syria.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22394","22394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444674","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of what the primary sources of finance for Daesh are; and what steps the Government is taking to disrupt those sources.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22395","22395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444675","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the US administration on the effect on UK citizens seeking to enter the US of recent changes to the US visa waiver programme affecting people who have previously visited Iran, Iraq, Syria or Sudan or hold dual citizenship of those countries.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22317","22317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444676","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Chinese authorities on the reported arrest of Pu Zhiqiang.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22504","22504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444677","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to publish written guidlines for British drone strikes.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22419","22419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444678","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his Answer of 18 December 2015 to Question 19717, which were the 28 communities in Syria supported by the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22368","22368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444679","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of reports by independent monitoring groups of civilians casualties caused by British air strikes in Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22420","22420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444680","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to help people with cancer who are also suffering from depression.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22503","22503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444681","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of mixed race stem cell donors; what discussions he has had with the Anthony Nolan Trust and others on diversifying stem cell registries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22442","22442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444682","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will bring forward proposals to require all owners and managers of care homes to give a copy of the Public Interest Disclosure Act 2013 to care workers on appointment.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22440","22440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444683","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on the creation of a new role for a part-time neuromuscular psychologist at the Colman Centre in Norwich.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22441","22441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444684","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to protect community pharmacies in areas of social deprivation.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22428","22428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444685","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recent Aviation Environment Federation report, Aircraft Noise and Public Health: The Evidence is Loud and Clear, published in January 2016.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22310","22310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444686","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of finance options available to doctors to cover their training costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22318","22318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444687","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department (a) identified and (b) supported  children of parents with mental illness.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22308","22308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444688","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to deal with antimicrobial resistance to antibiotics.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22362","22362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444689","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on regional variations on the availability of treatment for arthritis.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22345","22345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444690","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to substitute the prescribing of high volume branded medicine with generic equivalents.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22339","22339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444691","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential annual savings to the NHS through greater generic substitution compared to using their reference originator products; and what assessment he has made of the obstacles to implementing such a policy for (a) inhalers and biologics and (b) after complex products.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22340","22340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444692","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency about the requirement for some generic medicines to be given a brand name for clinical reasons; and what steps he is taking to ensure patients receive the brand name medicine specified.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22341","22341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444693","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS England received in charges for prescriptions of inhalers for people with asthma in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22390","22390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444694","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission an inquiry into contaminated blood in England and Wales.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22352","22352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444695","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to include generic medicines which are required to have a brand name by the MHRA and are already subject to market competition alongside originator medicines in the Statutory Scheme of Control the Prices of Branded Health Service Medicines.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22342","22342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444696","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of removing generic medicines required to have a brand name by the MHRA from the Statutory Scheme of Control the Prices of Branded Health Service Medicines.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22343","22343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444697","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask NHS England to publish a case study of the revised Cancer Drugs Fund (CDF) patient journey and give examples for how people are initiated onto CDF-approved treatments now and how people will be treated under the proposed new CDF scheme.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22269","22269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444698","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and which health (a) trusts and (b) services (i) Jane Cummings, (ii) Dame Barbara Hakin, (iii) Paul Baumann, (iv) Karen Wheeler and (v) Ian Dodge have visited in each year since their appointments to the board of NHS England; and on what dates each such visit was held.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22305","22305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444699","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 10658, if he will ensure that the national improvement framework for hepatitis C services contain guidance on the alignment of screening programmes for hepatitis C, HIV, tuberculosis and other blood-borne viruses or associated conditions.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22247","22247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444700","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions the his Department, NHS England and NICE have had on the effect of proposed Cancer Drugs Fund (CDF) changes on patients prescribed current CDF treatments who will not receive interim funding under that proposed new scheme.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22270","22270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444701","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the amount it will spend on (a) television, (b) print, (c) online and (d) billing advertising in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22271","22271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444702","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22268","22268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444703","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will add pulmonary arterial hypertension to the conditions which are exempt from prescription charges.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22445","22445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444704","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19788, in how many cases liability has been established for people infected by contaminated blood.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22461","22461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444705","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the effect of individual funding requests for palivizumab on premature babies at risk of severe complications from respiratory syncytial virus.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22462","22462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444706","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 1.86 of the Autumn Statement 2014, how much of the planned annual £30 million additional budget for services for young people with eating disorders has been spent; and for what purposes that budget has been spent.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22488","22488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444707","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of GP surgeries offer extended opening hours.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22478","22478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444708","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2015 to Question 18753, whether the assessment of the FRANK website was based solely on preventing drug use.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22485","22485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444709","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the guidance on how to make a request for revocation of a deportation order will be republished; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22459","22459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444710","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 6 January 2016 to Questions 21298 and 21317 on detention: centres, if she will take steps to collect the information referred to and to publish it on a regular basis.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22260","22260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444711","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost was to the public purse of immigration holding and removal centres in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22261","22261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444712","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average cost was to the public purse of the (a) detention and (b) deportation of each illegal immigrant in each constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22262","22262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444713","2016-01-18","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment her Department has made of the terrorist threat from dissident Irish Republicans to the UK mainland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22292","22292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444714","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) arrests and (b) convictions for laundering money there were from which countries in each year between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22357","22357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444715","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to prevent laundered money entering the London housing market.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22355","22355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444716","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 24 December 2015 to Questions 19956 and 19957, how many migrants granted leave to remain in the UK did not have No Recourse to public funds conditions imposed on them because of exceptional circumstances in (a) 2008, (b) 2009 and (c) 2010.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22366","22366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444717","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to renew concessions to the immigration rules for Syrian nationals lawfully in the UK beyond 28 February 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22386","22386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444718","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make representations to the French government on ensuring that NGOs and volunteers are allowed continual access to the Dunkirk refugee camp for the provision of aid and other humanitarian assistance.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22387","22387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444719","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make representations to the French government to ensure that the removal of 2,000 refugees from the Calais refugee camp into government-built shelters is co-ordinated with NGOs and volunteers; and that those refugees are (a) well-informed, (b) safely moved, (c) able to retain their possessions and (d) have their human rights respected.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22388","22388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444720","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make representations to the French government to ensure that the three-day eviction notice give to refugees at Calais refugee camp is extended.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22389","22389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444721","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the target of 20,000 resettled Syrian refugees is met by the end of this Parliament.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22421","22421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444722","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the hate mail and verbal attacks on people who are overweight.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22506","22506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444723","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many domestic workers were deported in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22507","22507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444724","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many domestic workers from overseas successfully applied for leave to remain in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22508","22508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444725","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support global efforts against schistosomiasis.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22509","22509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444726","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support global efforts against  neglected tropical diseases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22510","22510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444727","2016-01-18","Department for International Development","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation on eradication of polio.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22250","22250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444728","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of (a) the National Tactical Response Group and (b) Tornado Teams have been injured during a callout in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22284","22284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444729","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which community rehabilitation companies have been placed on a formal remedial plan under their contract in each year since 2010; and what the outcome of those plans was in each case.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22251","22251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444730","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding was allocated to the (a) gold command and (b) Tornado Team in (i) 2010, (ii) 2014 and (iii) 2015; and what he expects such budgets to be in 2016.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22299","22299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444731","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the insurance industry provided to his Department an estimate of by how much motor insurance premiums would reduce before they took effect as a consequence of the changes introduced by the Jackson reforms of the civil justice system and the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22233","22233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444732","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to implement the Low Commission's recommendation that legislative proposals should be brought forward to (a) make the Access to Justice Foundation the recipient of unclaimed damages in collective actions and (b) introduce a compulsory Interest on Lawyer Trust Accounts scheme for firms with profits above an agreed threshold with the proceeds of that scheme being paid to the Access to Justice Foundation.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22234","22234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444733","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2015 to Question 19715, what proportion of defendants in criminal cases (a) plead guilty before trial and (b) plead not guilty before trial.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22406","22406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444734","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will use his powers under clause 2, section 10 of the Criminal Justice and Public Order Act 1994 to appoint a crown servant to act as governor of the Medway Secure Training Centre.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22404","22404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444735","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions, in which prisons and for what incidents the (a) Tornado Team called into prisons, (b) Gold Command was opened and (c) National Tactical Response Group was called in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22415","22415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444736","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals were heard by the First-Tier Tribunal (Special Educational Needs and Disability) in each year since 2009-10; how many such appeals found in favour of the appellant; and how many such cases concerned local authority non-compliance with their statutory obligations in relation to (a) education, health and care plans and (b) Local Offers.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22369","22369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444737","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times has a prison governor (a) resigned, (b) been sacked and (c) left their position for any other reason in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22319","22319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444738","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2015 to Question 19715, what proportion of defendants in criminal cases in the Crown Court who plead guilty did so before their trial began in each year between 2009 and 2013.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22407","22407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444739","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to answer Question 15306, tabled on 6 November 2015, on his Department's public expenditure.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22483","22483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444740","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of business lost to the Northern Ireland economy from the maintained level of air passenger duty.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22412","22412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444741","2016-01-18","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent progress her Department has made on cross-border policing arrangements.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22446","22446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444742","2016-01-18","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department is taking to help review and improve sea defences in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22239","22239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444743","2016-01-18","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Home Secretary on the oral and written evidence provided by the Government to the Joint Committee on the Draft Investigatory Powers Bill.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22243","22243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444744","2016-01-18","Scotland Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 18729 and the oral contribution of the Financial Secretary to the Treasury of 6 January 2016, Official Report, columns 274-5, whether he has discussed the introduction of the new Work and Health Programme in Scotland with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22245","22245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444745","2016-01-18","Scotland Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what representations he has received on the Scottish Government's proposals to absorb the British Transport Police into Police Scotland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22416","22416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444746","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps Network Rail is taking to ensure co-ordination between its regional units for the purpose of redirecting traffic affected by the closure of the West Coast Main Line north of Carlisle.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22418","22418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444747","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the gauge clearance is of routes used to divert freight services disrupted by the temporary closure of the West Coast Main Line north of Carlisle.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22405","22405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444748","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department collects statistics for the purposes of monitoring on the types of tickets purchased by bus passengers.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22417","22417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444749","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the conclusions of the Aviation Environment Federation report, Aircraft Noise and Public Health, published on 12 January 2016, The Evidence is Loud and Clear.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22408","22408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444750","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the potential safety implications of the mandatory introduction of dashboard cameras in (a) cars, (b) vans and (c) heavy goods vehicles.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22499","22499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444751","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to improve the safety of hoverboards.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22500","22500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444752","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of its methods of alleviating road congestion on motorways after an incident; and what plans his Department has to improve those methods.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22427","22427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444753","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the briefing by the National Audits Office entitled Delivering major projects in government, published on 6 January 2016, what plans his Department has to increase the amount of data it publishes on major projects.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22399","22399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444754","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what requests for information his Department made regarding the cutting to 15 minutes the length of delay after which compensation for train passengers will kick in.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22351","22351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444755","2016-01-20","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that the manufacturers of electric and hybrid cars which utilise charging points adopt a common charging connection for all such vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22425","22425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444756","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 2.1 of the briefing by the National Audit Office entitled Delivering major projects in government, published on 6 January 2016, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of its monitoring the benefits of (a) ongoing and (b) complete infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22240","22240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444757","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on rail freight movements of the re-opening of the Carno station in Powys.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22236","22236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444758","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what analysis his Department has undertaken of the effect of a new rail freight depot near Northampton on the local economy.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22237","22237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444759","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the briefing by the National Audit Office, entitled Delivering major projects in government, published on 6 January 2016, what steps his Department is taking to (a) correct inconsistent reporting of costs referred to in that briefing and (b) ensure more accurate reporting of costs on major projects.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22238","22238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444760","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish advice received by his Department from Highways England on the sites considered for providing off-road lorry parking to address Operation Stack on the M20 in Kent; and what the reasons were for rejecting sites not included in the current consultation.","Biography information for Damian Collins","Damian Collins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22244","22244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444761","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the new migrant camp being built in Dunkirk does not have a negative effect on UK-bound lorries.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22248","22248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444762","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many motorhome owners from continental Europe visited England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22267","22267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444763","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2015 to Question 13946, whether his Department has received the findings of the London and South Coast Rail Corridor Study; and what the timeframe is for publication of that study's findings and his Department's response to it.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22232","22232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444764","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many motorhome-friendly parking sites there are in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Lancashire.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22266","22266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444765","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2016 to Question 20831, when the DVLA plans to roll out the piloted scheme against non-payment of vehicle excise duty.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22298","22298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444766","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20337, what steps he plans to take to improve the service offered by the DVLA to people resident in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22294","22294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444767","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the introduction of mandatory defibrillators on aircraft.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22498","22498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444768","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the vulnerability to flooding of (a) rail and (b) road networks; and what steps his Department is taking to protect such infrastructure from the risk of floods.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22469","22469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444769","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's (a) budget and (b) spend for maritime surveillance was in each of the last five years; and what the (i) names and (ii) lengths of contract are of companies engaged in UK maritime security.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22466","22466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444770","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Delivering major projects in Government, published on 6 January 2016, what steps his Department is taking to ensure all infrastructure projects are delivered on time and on budget.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22467","22467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444771","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Delivering major projects in Government, published on 6 January 2016, what steps his Department is taking to increase transparency of costs, times and benefits of infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22468","22468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444772","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the use of laser pen technology in proximity to aircraft and airports.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22448","22448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444773","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department plans to take in 2016 to ensure that young people under 16 understand road safety issues from the perspectives of pedestrians, cyclists and car users.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22451","22451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444775","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on the continuation of payments for legacy benefits to claimants being transferred to universal credit until a first universal credit payment is received.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22230","22230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444776","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were eligible to receive a Christmas bonus on their benefits had not received it on 24 December 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22231","22231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444777","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of staff working in his Department are employees on fixed-term contracts.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22249","22249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444778","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the statement in his Department's press release of 1 November 2011, entitled Iain Duncan Smith sets out next steps for moving claimants onto universal credit, on what dates since 1 November 2011 his Department has calculated the proportion of new technology required to deliver universal credit which is complete; and what that proportion was on each of those dates.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22246","22246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444779","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many lone parent households that are in receipt of housing benefit will be affected by changes to universal credit work allowances in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22323","22323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444780","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work coaches are employed by job centres in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22322","22322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444781","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value is of the personal independence payment assessment contract with ATOS; what the main key performance indicators (KPIs) are under that contract; and what the (a) financial and (b) other penalties are for failure to meet KPIs.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22348","22348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444782","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to enable applicants who have suffered from a stroke, heart attack or any other major health scare to access a work capability assessment of medical assessment within a 90 minute journey.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22424","22424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444783","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many lone parent households not in receipt of housing benefit will be affected by changes to universal credit work allowances in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22332","22332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444784","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Burnley receive housing benefit.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22333","22333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444785","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Burnley receive income support.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22334","22334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444786","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Burnley receive income-based jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22335","22335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444787","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many people will receive a lower pension credit entitlement as a result of the rise of the single saving credit threshold by 5.8 per cent and of the couples' threshold by 5.5 per cent.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22382","22382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444788","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the results were of temperature tests to determine eligibility to receive winter fuel allowance of people living abroad in 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22383","22383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444789","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many temperature tests there were to determine eligibility to receive winter fuel allowance of people living abroad in 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22384","22384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444790","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training jobcentre work coaches receive.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22329","22329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444791","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what personal budgeting advice, and in what format, is provided to recipients of universal credit.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22328","22328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444792","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department is taking steps to implement International Labour Convention No.189 on Domestic Workers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22511","22511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444793","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants who are considered by his Department to have a limited capability to work are in receipt of universal credit in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22331","22331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444794","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit switch centres there are in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22330","22330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444795","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many computers each jobcentre in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West has available for recipients of universal credit to access benefits online.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22326","22326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444796","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provision there is for ICT training for recipients of universal credit.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22327","22327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444797","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants considered by his Department to have a limited capability to work live in Burnley.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22324","22324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444798","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Burnley are in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22325","22325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444799","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many parents have been exempted from fees and charges for the 2012 child maintenance scheme.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22381","22381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444800","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many parents have moved to direct pay since the introduction of the 2012 child maintenance scheme.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22378","22378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444801","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to increase collection charges for the 2012 child maintenance scheme for the (a) parent with care and (b) non-resident parent.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22379","22379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444802","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to increase application charges to join the 2012 child maintenance scheme.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22380","22380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444803","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's legal costs were in Ashley Hurley, Mary Jarrett and Lee Palmer v Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, CO/2717/2014 and CO/3220/2014.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22377","22377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444804","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people no longer receive the disability premium following their transfer from receipt of disability living allowance to personal independence payments.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22434","22434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444805","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether universal credit applicants who are housing association tenants are informed upon application of the need for a letter from their landlord in order to receive housing cost assistance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22473","22473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444806","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2016 to Question 21590, how many universal credit claimants his Department expects to notify.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22474","22474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444807","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the estimated cost is of payments of universal credit to (a) people already in receipt of universal credit on 1 April 2016 and (b) other claimants in 2016-17.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22476","22476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444808","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were moved from receipt of employment and support allowance to jobseeker's allowance because they did not meet the new points standard in each quarter of 2015.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22472","22472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444809","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the spending reduction in 2016-17 that will result from (a) the changes in universal credit work allowances and (b) other changes in universal credit taking effect in April 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22477","22477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444810","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the number of people in work who will be in receipt of universal credit in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22487","22487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444915","2016-01-19","Cabinet Office","2016-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that government procurement helps to increase tax receipts.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903123","903123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445662","2016-01-19","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taken to widen access to basic bank accounts.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903117","903117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445663","2016-01-19","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the Financial Conduct Authority's decision to end its review into HSBC.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903115","903115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445664","2016-01-19","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take fiscal steps to support exports by SMEs.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903114","903114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445665","2016-01-19","HM Treasury","2016-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to widen access to financial advice.","Biography information for James Berry","James Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903119","903119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444100","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions for human trafficking resulted in a conviction between 1 August 2015 and 1 January 2016; and how many orders made for victim compensation as a result of such convictions resulted in payments (a) by convicted traffickers and (b) at a cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22061","22061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444101","2016-01-14","Attorney General","2016-01-12","To ask the Attorney General, whether he has had discussions with his Northern Ireland counterparts on the recent case of Pastor James McConnell.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22123","22123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444102","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which 10 companies owed the greatest amount of late payment debt to SMEs in each six-month period of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22124","22124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444103","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many SMEs have been declared bankrupt as a result of late payments in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22125","22125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444104","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost to the UK economy of late payments to SMEs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22126","22126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444105","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much on average was owed in late payment debt to SMEs in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22130","22130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444106","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the total number of FTE positions supported by funding from Research Councils UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22091","22091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444107","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to prevent the exploitation of consumers by salesmen of stair lifts and other aids to the elderly and disabled.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22189","22189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444108","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many employees were on zero-hours contracts in each financial quarter since May 2010 in each (a) constituency and (b) region.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22223","22223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444109","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) private sector companies, (b) public sector bodies went beyond the maximum 60-day period to repay debt covered by the Late Payment Directive in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22183","22183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444110","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether there have been any changes to the Government's policy on arms export licences since the Written Ministerial Statement of 25 March 2014, 9WS.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22028","22028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444111","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to assist students with minimising the accrual of credit card debt.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22020","22020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444112","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to facilitate a process of credit card transfers for people in debt.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22021","22021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444113","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with credit card companies on supporting people on low incomes with credit card debts.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22022","22022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444114","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 25 March 2014, 9WS, whether it is still the Government's policy not to grant an arms license if there is a clear risk that the items might be used in the commission of a serious violation of international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22036","22036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444115","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the five most common causes of death of children were in (a) England and Wales and (b) each London borough in (i) 2014, (ii) 2010, (iii) 2005 and (iv) 2000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22050","22050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444116","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which (a) government ministers and (b) civil servants have failed to apply to the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments before their appointment to posts outside Government in the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22194","22194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444117","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) men and (b) women took their own life in each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22217","22217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444118","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what forecast he has made of the change in population in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Yorkshire and the Humber up to 2030.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22170","22170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444119","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the change in the proportion of the working age population employed by the public sector in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Yorkshire and the Humber since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22171","22171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444120","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what advice his Department issued to Baron Barker of Battle about his appointment to the British Photovoltaic Association.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22073","22073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444121","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent communications his Department has had with the National Archives on the release of Cabinet papers dated between 1986 and 1988.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22110","22110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444122","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which contracts with his Department G4S are currently bidding for.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22109","22109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444123","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged 65 and over have continued to work in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22155","22155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444124","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who his Ministerial private office informed of his plans to visit Cardiff on 7 January 2016; by what method they so informed those people and on what date those communications took place.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22150","22150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444125","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much is outstanding of the loan to the Irish Republic given in 2010; how much of that loan has been paid back; and what estimate he has made of when the balance of that loan will be repaid in full.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22152","22152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444126","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the annual cost to the financial services sector of compliance with money laundering regulations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22146","22146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444127","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to improve access to finance for SMEs.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22104","22104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444128","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the ease by which UK SMEs can access the export market.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22105","22105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444129","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid to the Landfill Communities Fund by third party groups in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22097","22097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444130","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what timescales the Tax Credit Office in Preston has in place to respond to representations made by hon. Members by (a) telephone, (b) email and (c) letter; and how this Office performed against these timescales in the last reporting year.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22122","22122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444131","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from the Living Wage Foundation in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22092","22092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444132","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made on reducing levels of tax avoidance by large corporations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22221","22221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444133","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how much will accrue to the Exchequer as a result of the Carbon Price Support legislation in each year until 2020.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22145","22145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444134","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the letter of the Financial Secretary to the Treasury on making tax digital, dated 11 January 2016, for what reasons the increased revenue from a more accurate digital tax return system has been estimated at £600 million per annum given that the current tax gap due to errors made by small businesses has been estimated in that letter at £6.5 billion.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22224","22224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444135","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the future funding of illegal money lending teams.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22213","22213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444136","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of companies issued fines for underpayment of the minimum wage in each of the last five years; what the total value of such fines issued is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22207","22207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444137","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to introduce a one-month time limit on engagements for (a) small business and (b) other limited company contractors before they are treated as employees for tax purposes.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22025","22025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444138","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the Exchequer received in spirit duty between April and December (a) 2015 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22044","22044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444139","2016-01-14","Church Commissioners","2016-01-12","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what grants the Church Commissioners have given to churches in (a) Devon and (b) Cornwall from the Roof Repair Fund in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22084","22084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444140","2016-01-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to update planning guidance on using money from Section 106 agreements to fund flood prevention projects.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22138","22138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444141","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will increase the licensing enforcement powers available to local authorities to ensure that pubs do not act as clubs without permission.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22191","22191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444142","2016-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many family-friendly tenancies have been taken up in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22177","22177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444143","2016-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications to buy privately-owned land for residential development were made in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22178","22178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444144","2016-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications to buy publicly owned land for residential development were made in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22176","22176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444145","2016-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been built in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22168","22168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444146","2016-01-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to regulate advertising by payday loan companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22019","22019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444147","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the accessibility of mobile broadband services and wifi on public transport was (a) on the last date for which figures are available and (b) in 2010.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22153","22153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444148","2016-01-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what change there has been in the number of black and white television licences held in Northern Ireland between 1 January 2012 and 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22131","22131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444149","2016-01-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what was the number of households with black and white television licences per thousand households in (a) the UK as a whole and (b) in Northern Ireland in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22132","22132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444150","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) total research and development spend by his Department in each of the last five years and (b) forecast research and development spend by his Department in the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22119","22119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444151","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of the establishment of the HMS Juffair naval base on the UK's ability to react to humanitarian crises in the Gulf.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22077","22077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444152","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian casualties have been recorded in Syria as a result of RAF military intervention since 2 December 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22197","22197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444153","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian casualties have been recorded in Iraq as a result of RAF military intervention since 2 December 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22196","22196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444154","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's defence strategy is towards Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22190","22190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444155","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has received from civilian business jet wage of RAF Northolt in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22032","22032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444156","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he next plans to review the limit on the number of civilian flights allowed from RAF Northolt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22033","22033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444157","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with Flybe about its proposal to use RAF Northolt for domestic flights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22034","22034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444158","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian business jet movements there were at RAF Northolt in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22035","22035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444159","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to minimise the time taken for military aircraft parts to be delivered to his Department's bases in Cyprus.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22016","22016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444160","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the security situation in the Sinai and its impact on the military capability of Hamas in the Gaza Strip.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22053","22053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444161","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers of the Lancashire Regiment were deployed in tackling recent flooding; how many reserve soldiers of that Regiment were involved; how long that deployment lasted; and what assessment he has made of the effect of those soldiers' contribution to the wider recovery and rescue operation.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22078","22078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444162","2016-01-14","Department for Education","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children there were of each age in each care setting in the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22069","22069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444163","2016-01-14","Department for Education","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase retention levels of science teachers in funded secondary schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22089","22089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444164","2016-01-14","Department for Education","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the conclusions of the Social Market Foundation report, published in January 2016, Educational Inequalities in England and Wales.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22192","22192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444165","2016-01-14","Department for Education","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the amount of funding for each (a) primary age and (b) secondary age pupil in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Yorkshire and the Humber in (i) 2016-17, (ii) 2017-18 and (iii) 2018-19.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22165","22165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444166","2016-01-14","Department for Education","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on her Department's review of Special Guardian Orders.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22095","22095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444167","2016-01-14","Department for Education","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the number of apprenticeships for people aged 16 to 19 years old.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22090","22090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444168","2016-01-18","Department for Education","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of vacancies of mathematics teachers in funded secondary schools in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22118","22118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444169","2016-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with the big six energy companies on the introduction of half-hourly settlements before the national smart meter rollout.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22096","22096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444170","2016-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect on private sectors investment in carbon capture and storage (CCS) of the Government's decision to end the CCS fund.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22098","22098"
