"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077335","2019-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) charitable organisations will be paid for resettlement support services they have provided under contract to Working Links (b) those services are able to continue.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225430","225430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077336","2019-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people living in Ashfield constituency receive carer's allowance; and what estimate her Department has made of the number of people in Ashfield constituency who undertake caring responsibilities without receiving that allowance.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225473","225473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077337","2019-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to ban the importation of hunting trophies.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225553","225553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077338","2019-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 February to Question 221633 on Jobcentres: Computers, how many JobPoints/JobKiosks were available for public use in each of the regions of England in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225426","225426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077339","2019-02-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a UK Steel Charter to increase transparency of steel procurement in the UK.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225457","225457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077340","2019-02-28","Department for Education","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England that were (i) eligible and (ii) not eligible for free school meals attended a primary school rated as (A) good and (B) outstanding in the academic year ending August 2018.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225474","225474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077341","2019-02-28","Department for Education","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England who were (i) eligible and (ii) not eligible for free school meals attended a secondary school rated (A) good and (B) outstanding in the academic year ending August 2018.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225475","225475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077342","2019-02-28","Home Office","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK citizens have had their citizenship revoked by the Government since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225490","225490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077343","2019-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled, PR19 initial assessment of plans: South East Water company, published by Ofwat in January 2019, how much of the £306.2 million of funding for South and South Eastern water companies will be allocated to new reservoir infrastructure.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225620","225620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077344","2019-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled, PR19 initial assessment of plans: South East Water company, published by Ofwat in January 2019, what steps he is taking to ensure adequate public scrutiny of the options for strategic water resources developed by South and South Eastern water companies.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225621","225621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077345","2019-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled, PR19 initial assessment of plans: South East Water company, published by Ofwat in January 2019, how programmes will be funded by the allocation of £306.2 million; and what the timeframe is for the allocation of that funding.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225622","225622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077346","2019-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the tendering process was in relation to the allocation of £306.2 million to water companies to develop strategic water resources options for the South and South East of England.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225623","225623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077347","2019-02-28","Department for Education","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer on 19 February to Question 221613 on Children in Care: Ethnic Groups, whether the figures provided include children in care under Section 20 Voluntary Arrangements.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225441","225441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077348","2019-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Disabled People, Health and Work on 25 February 2019, Official Report, from which areas of departmental work the 1,200 staff assigned to correct employment and support allowance underpayments are being transferred.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225476","225476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077349","2019-02-27","Treasury","2019-02-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the banking sector on facilitating electronic cashless payments on mobile devices.","Biography information for Matt Warman","Matt Warman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225523","225523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077350","2019-02-27","Treasury","2019-02-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Royal Bank of Scotland on removing barriers for customers using electronic cashless payment methods on mobile phones.","Biography information for Matt Warman","Matt Warman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225524","225524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077351","2019-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress on UN Human Rights Commission resolution L30/1 on promoting reconciliation, accountability and human rights in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225440","225440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077352","2019-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Air Force personnel are on secondment to (a) BAE Systems and (b) EADS in (i) Saudi Arabia and (ii) the UAE; and what the roles of those seconded personnel are.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225606","225606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077353","2019-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the number of successful applications to Access to Work was in each local authority area in Wales in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225458","225458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077354","2019-02-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the post-sport employment rates of people who have participated in elite athlete programmes funded by UK Sport.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225538","225538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077355","2019-02-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of deaths of homeless people in local authorities in England since 2013.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225539","225539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077356","2019-02-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to reduce obesity in England.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225540","225540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077357","2019-02-28","Cabinet Office","2019-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the recommendations of the Reducing Regulation Committee are; and what steps the Government is taking to implement those recommendations.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225370","225370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077358","2019-02-27","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of dwellings in towers with the same cladding material as Grenfell Tower in England.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225541","225541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077359","2019-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the global network of operational and logistic support bases for the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) Royal Air Force for the purpose of delivering international security.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225371","225371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077360","2019-02-28","Department for Education","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his oral contribution of 25 February 2019, Official Report, how much funding in addition to that £6 million will be available to schools to enable them to (a) deliver high-quality (i) relationships and sex education and (ii) relationships education and (b) (i) train teachers and (ii) equip them with effective resources.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225564","225564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077361","2019-02-28","Department for Education","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how he plans to ensure that (a) Ofsted inspectors (i) know what good quality relationships and sex education and relationships education is, (ii) are trained in that education and (iii) are able to maintain school accountability and (b) Ofsted inspection processes are transparent.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225565","225565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077362","2019-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps is he taking to support SMEs in the Defence supply chain to develop innovative technologies.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225591","225591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077363","2019-02-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish the minutes of his meeting of the week commencing 18 February with Mark Zuckerburg.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225431","225431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077364","2019-02-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he discussed Facebook’s role in UK elections in his meeting of the week commencing 18 February with Mark Zuckerburg.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225432","225432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077365","2019-02-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to assess the merits of Facebook’s business practices towards other developers as part of the Government review of the UK’s competition powers in April 2019.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225433","225433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077366","2019-02-28","Department for Transport","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on local authorities charging freedom pass holders to cover the administration costs of that scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225369","225369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077367","2019-02-28","Department for Education","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of two-year-olds eligible for 15 hours of funded early education attend a maintained nursery school.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225517","225517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077368","2019-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituents have been identified as having been underpaid when migrated from incapacity benefits to employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225562","225562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077369","2019-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituents identified as having been underpaid when migrated from incapacity benefits to employment and support allowance have died before receiving backdated payments.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225563","225563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077370","2019-02-28","Department for International Trade","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 213459 on Department for International Trade: Internet, what proportion of spending on the Local to Global podcast was allocated to its (a) production and (b) promotion.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225624","225624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077371","2019-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on the new £70 million flood defences scheme.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225422","225422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077372","2019-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of Djibouti on fundamental freedoms including religious expression in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225423","225423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077373","2019-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions has he had with his Middle Eastern counterparts on the role of Hezbollah in the Government of Lebanon.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225424","225424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077374","2019-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on a potential boycott of the  Eurovision song contest in that country; and what advice his Department provides to UK citizens planning to attend that event.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225425","225425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077375","2019-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions British embassy staff in Beirut have met representatives of Hezbollah in the last two years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225375","225375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077376","2019-02-28","Department for Education","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to tackle (a) increased levels of stress among education professionals and (b) the effect of that stress on the recruitment and retention of teachers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225484","225484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077377","2019-02-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what contingency plans his Department has in place to ensure that reciprocal healthcare arrangements stay in place for UK citizens living in European countries following the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without an agreement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225485","225485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077378","2019-02-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to ensure retired UK citizen living in other EU Member States will have access to healthcare in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225486","225486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077379","2019-02-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to tackle the shortage of psychiatric beds in hospitals.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225487","225487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1077380","2019-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to put in place a protocol to ensure that there is no contact between British embassy staff in Beirut and Hezbollah Ministers in the Government of Lebanon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225376","225376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064889","2019-02-26","Department for International Development","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of whether Official Development Assistance spending is meeting targets set by the UK aid strategy.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224809","224809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064890","2019-02-26","Northern Ireland Office","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the effect on rights under the Good Friday Agreement of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224810","224810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064891","2019-02-26","Department for Education","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans the Department have to replace the sixth form places lost as a result of the closure of Bradfield School Sixth Form in Sheffield Hallam.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224828","224828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064892","2019-02-26","Department for Education","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the National Funding Formula on (a) the number of school places, (b) spending per pupil, (c) school spending reserves  and (d) sustainability of school funding in Sheffield Hallam constituency.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224829","224829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064893","2019-02-26","Department for Education","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has plans to increase the level infrastructure spending on schools in Sheffield Hallam constituency.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224830","224830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064894","2019-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants have repaid benefit overpayments at 40 per cent from their standard allowance in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224831","224831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064895","2019-02-27","Department for Transport","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has held with representatives of Fusion on the protection of wildlife on the 200 acres near Steeple Claydon due for clearance for High Speed Two.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224792","224792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064896","2019-02-27","Department for Transport","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taken to ensure the protection of (a) birds during the breeding season and (b) other wildlife at the protected nature reserve at Calvert Jubilee Buckinghamshire during ground clearance activities by HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224793","224793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064897","2019-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the ban on gestation crates for pigs will remain in force in the event of a future UK-US trade agreement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224795","224795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064898","2019-02-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many tests for sexually transmitted infections have been paid for by the public purse in each year for which information is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224804","224804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064899","2019-02-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the number of tests for sexually transmitted infections administered over the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224805","224805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064900","2019-02-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received in the last 12 months on the closure of physical clinics providing testing for sexually transmitted infections; what plans he has to encourage the use of online and postal testing services for sexually-transmitted infections; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224806","224806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064901","2019-02-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with multinational healthcare corporations since June 2016, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224807","224807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064902","2019-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to mark the 75th anniversary of the D-Day landings this year.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224816","224816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064903","2019-02-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to mark the 75th anniversary of the D-Day landings this year.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224817","224817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064904","2019-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding the Government plans to allocate to the Daks Over Normandy event taking place to commemorate the 75th anniversary of the D-Day landings.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224818","224818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064905","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequacy of (a) treatment and (b) support for people with with tuberculosis.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224822","224822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064906","2019-02-27","Department for Transport","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse was of the visit by (a)  Stephen Clark, sponsor, High Speed Rail Group HS2 phase 2b  (b) Andrew Rees, Head of Economic and Commercial Analysis  HS2 Ltd and (c) Bernadette Hurd, Benefits Strategy and Capability Manager HS2 Ltd to the recent High Speed Rail event in Budapest.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224794","224794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064907","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the public purse was of the NHS treating preventable alcohol-related injuries in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224801","224801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064908","2019-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts as a result of not meeting the criteria in that document in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224823","224823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064909","2019-02-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts as a result of not meeting the criteria in that document in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224824","224824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064910","2019-02-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the guidance entitled Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts as a result of not meeting the criteria in that document in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224825","224825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064911","2019-02-27","Department for International Trade","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts due to not meeting the criteria in his Department's Procurement Policy Note 03/14 in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224826","224826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064912","2019-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts due to not meeting the criteria in her Department's Procurement Policy Note 03/14 in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224827","224827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064913","2019-02-26","Department for Transport","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the addition of a third runway at Heathrow Airport on noise pollution levels in the Woking constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224803","224803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064914","2019-02-27","Department for Transport","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to address the anomaly whereby using an electric bicycle requires a motorcycle licence and needs to be registered with the Driver Vehicle Licensing Agency NI.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224808","224808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064915","2019-02-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to undertake a consultation on the transposition of the Posting of Workers Directive (96/71/EC) into domestic law.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224802","224802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064916","2019-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote open access to waterways for canoeists.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224812","224812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064917","2019-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department holds information on war service gratuity payments that were made at the end of the First and Second World Wars to service personnel drawn from the British dominions and colonies.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224796","224796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064918","2019-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department holds information on war service gratuity payments made at the end of the First and Second World Wars to service personnel drawn from the British dominions and colonies.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224797","224797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064919","2019-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department holds information on the (a) number and (b) identities of veterans of the Caribbean regiment who served alongside the British armed forces in the Second World War and are still alive.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224798","224798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064920","2019-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department holds information on the (a) number and (b) identities of veterans of the British Indian Army who served alongside the British armed forces in the Second World War and are still alive.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224799","224799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064921","2019-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department holds information on the (a) number and (b) identities of veterans of the East Africa Force who served alongside the British armed forces in the Second World War and are still alive.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224800","224800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064922","2019-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that Afghan Interpreters are eligible for help from UK service charities.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224813","224813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064923","2019-02-26","Department for Transport","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the current Crossrail engineers and construction teams were under contract to transfer to work on HS2 after the planned opening of Crossrail in December 2018; and how many of those contracts resulted in penalty, retainer or other payments or fees to be made to either those individuals or the companies they work for since December 2018.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224819","224819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064924","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to increase the number of places on the PrEP Impact Trial in (a) England and (b) Brentford and Isleworth constituency.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224811","224811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064925","2019-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people identifying as having a primary condition of epilepsy have been awarded personal independence payment (a) after mandatory reconsideration of their initial assessment and (b) at a tribunal in Scotland in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224814","224814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064926","2019-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of (a) all new claimants of personal independence payment and (b) new claimants of that payment identifying as having a primary condition of epilepsy did not receive an award during their initial assessment but received an award at (i) mandatory reconsideration and (ii) tribunal in Scotland in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224815","224815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064927","2019-02-27","Department for Transport","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential for delays to services departing the Eurostar terminal at London St Pancras station in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224820","224820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064928","2019-02-27","Home Office","2019-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to prevent delays at passport control at the Eurostar terminal at London St Pancras station in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224821","224821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064657","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle domestic abuse.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909406","909406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064670","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on the treatment of Uighur Muslims in China.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224366","224366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064671","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of enforcement of laws on animal cruelty.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224329","224329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064672","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS news story entitled Machine that keeps livers 'alive' may boost transplant rates, published in April 2018, whether the NHS has any plans to commission further research on such liver storage facilities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224330","224330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064673","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department provides funding to programmes that aim to support children from broken families.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224331","224331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064674","2019-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to reduce the proportion of army personnel that cannot be sent overseas due to medical reasons.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224332","224332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064675","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what housing support his Department provides to people over 55.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224333","224333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064676","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the NHS has commissioned research on potential links between infertility and endometrium.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224334","224334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064677","2019-02-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons the cap on energy bills from 1 January 2019 was revised upwards; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the new cap will not change at six weekly intervals.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224365","224365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064678","2019-02-26","Treasury","2019-02-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the (a) focused assets covered under the Asset Protection Agency and (b) focused assets underwritten by the Asset Protection Agency that were transferred to West Register between 2009 and 2012.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224359","224359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064679","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the market-led proposals on rail received by his Department since the July 2018 deadline and state which of these were (a) accepted and (b) rejected.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224349","224349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064680","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that ractopamine-fed pork is not permitted in the UK under the terms of a future UK-US trade agreement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224294","224294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064681","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the UK will continue to test pork for the parasitic worm trichinae under the terms of a future UK-US trade agreement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224295","224295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064682","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the oral contribution of 5 February 2019 of the Under-Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, Official Report column 289, how that 4 per cent figure relating  to deprivation was calculated.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224297","224297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064683","2019-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to tackle the comparatively high rates of unemployment among adults from (a) Black and (b) Pakistani and Bangladeshi ethnic groups in each (i) region and (ii) nation of the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224336","224336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064684","2019-02-26","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle the disparity in attainment between white British pupils of key stage 4 age who (a) are and (b) are not eligible for free school meals.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224337","224337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064685","2019-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made in implementing the Secure STAIRS framework at HM Young Offenders Institute Feltham; and what assessment he has made on the potential effect of that framework on the levels of (a) violence and (b) disruptive behaviour at that institution.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224338","224338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064686","2019-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young people are subject to a Youth Rehabilitation Order in (a) the Feltham and Heston constituency and (b) England and Wales.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224339","224339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064687","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK citizens have had that citizenship deprived under section 40 of the British Nationality Act 1981 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224350","224350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064688","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what considerations satisfied him that depriving Shamima Begum of her British citizenship was conducive to the public good.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224351","224351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064689","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people resident in the UK are currently under consideration for the deprivation of their British citizenship under the British Nationality Act 1981.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224352","224352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064690","2019-02-26","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to complete his review of the treatment of people accused by ETS of cheating in English language tests.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224291","224291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064691","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, what the timeframe is for the introduction of lung health checks in Southampton Care Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224354","224354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064692","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been deprived of British citizenship; how many of those people held dual-citizenship; and whether that dual citizenship was (a) current and (b) subject to a re-application since 2014.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224296","224296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064693","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with EU representatives on labelling requirements for UK food companies in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224357","224357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064694","2019-02-25","Department for International Trade","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent estimate he has made of the level of tariffs that could be applied by both the UK and EU to food exports in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224358","224358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064695","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2019 to Question 217589 on Buildings: Insulation and with reference to the Buildings Research Establishment interim report entitled Fire performance of cladding materials research – experimental methodology and performance criteria, who the members are of the referenced project steering group.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224341","224341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064696","2019-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department plans to use the data it will hold on family circumstances through universal credit to provide more tailored support to parents in England on the types of childcare available to them.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224322","224322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064697","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2019 to Question 217589 on Buildings: Insulation and the interim report entitled, Fire Performance of Cladding Materials Research – Experimental methodology and performance criteria prepared by the Building Research Establishment for his Department, if he will publish the minutes of the meetings of the (a) Project Steering Group and (b) Project team.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224342","224342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064698","2019-02-26","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to (a) improve affordability and (b) reduce complexity for parents to access childcare support for people in low-income families.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224323","224323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064699","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 217589 on Buildings: Insulation and the interim report entitled, Fire Performance of Cladding Materials Research – Experimental methodology and performance criteria prepared by the Building Research Establishment for his Department, on what date his Department approved the bespoke testing methodology.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224343","224343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064700","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 217589 on Buildings: Insulation and the interim report entitled, Fire Performance of Cladding Materials Research – Experimental methodology and performance criteria prepared by the Building Research Establishment for his Department, if he will publish the (a) success and (b) failure criteria for the new bespoke test methodology when testing cladding and other building materials.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224344","224344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064701","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the correlation between changes in (a) local authority funding and (b) changes in the level of provision of local authority services, excluding social care, since 2010.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224324","224324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064702","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an assessment of the correlation between the (a) increased proportion of local authority spending on social care, (b) reduction in local authority overall spending on services other than social care and (c) decrease in local authority funding since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224325","224325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064703","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the proposed shipping route to be operated by DHL for products supplied to the NHS on a 24 to 72 hours timeframe in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal, what assurances he has sought from DHL that the issues which led to the supply-chain breakdown in 2018 that occurred during DHL's contract with Kentucky Fried Chicken have been resolved; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224317","224317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064704","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 217589 on Buildings: Insulation and the interim report of the Building Research Establishment for his Department entitled Fire Performance of Cladding Materials Research – Experimental methodology and performance criteria, whether materials that fail the bespoke test will be subject to further BS 8414 large scale tests.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224345","224345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064705","2019-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the geographic coverage of food banks throughout the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224299","224299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064706","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 217589 on Buildings: Insulation and with reference to the interim report of the Building Research Establishment (BRE) for his Department entitled Fire Performance of Cladding Materials Research – Experimental methodology and performance criteria, whether the BRE advised against the development of a bespoke testing methodology for insulation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224346","224346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064707","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 217589 on Buildings: Insulation and with reference to the interim report of the Building Research Establishment for his Department entitled Fire Performance of Cladding Materials Research – Experimental methodology and performance criteria, for what reasons the bespoke testing methodology does not include measurement of the production of toxic smoke from burning materials.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224347","224347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064708","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 217589 on Buildings: Insulation and with reference to the interim report of the Building Research Establishment for his Department entitled Fire Performance of Cladding Materials Research – Experimental methodology and performance criteria, if he will consider criteria for mechanical failure in any future large-scale tests his Department commissions.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224348","224348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064709","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Local Government Association report entitled Have we reached a ‘tipping point’?: Trends in spending for children and young people with SEND in England, what estimate he has made of the level of the national deficit on high needs block funding by the end of (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20, and (c) 2020-21.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224318","224318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064710","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of trends in spending on children in need of SEND provision in England over the next two years; what steps he is taking in response to reports of SEND funding deficits by local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224319","224319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064711","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of schools have run the Every Child a Reader (ECaR) programme in each year since that programme was introduced; what discussions he has had with head teachers about whether they have the resources they require to run the ECaR programme in (a) Brighton and Hove and (b) nationally; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224320","224320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064712","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether students who are granted European Temporary Leave to Remain would be eligible to access Government funding for under-18 education.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224326","224326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064713","2019-02-26","Treasury","2019-02-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts as a result of not complying with the criteria set out in the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224367","224367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064714","2019-02-26","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts as a result of not complying with the criteria set out in the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224368","224368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064715","2019-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts as a result of not complying with the criteria set out in the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224369","224369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064716","2019-02-26","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts as a result of not complying with the criteria set out in the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, in each year since the creation of his Department.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224370","224370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064717","2019-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many suppliers have been excluded from bidding for contracts due to their not meeting the criteria in his Department's Procurement Policy Note 03/14 in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224371","224371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064718","2019-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether a custody support plan that provides each young offender with a weekly review by a nominated officer is in place at HM Young Offenders Institute Feltham.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224340","224340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064719","2019-02-25","Department for International Development","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's publication entitled DFID Strategic Vision for Gender Equality, published in March 2018, what steps her Department is taking to integrate its work on modern slavery and on women and girls.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224355","224355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064720","2019-02-25","Department for International Development","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the particular effect of modern slavery on adolescent girls; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224356","224356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064721","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost has been to the NHS of treating injuries caused by excessive alcohol consumption each year since 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224315","224315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064722","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times European Health Insurance Cards were used by UK citizens abroad in the past year.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224302","224302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064723","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times European Health Insurance Cards were used by people over the age of 70 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224303","224303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064724","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many European Health Insurance Cards have been issued to people over the age of 70.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224304","224304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064725","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times European Health Insurance Cards were used by UK citizens abroad to support the treatment of pre-existing conditions in the last year.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224305","224305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064726","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of waste exporters who have not demonstrated that the importer of their waste operates to human health and environmental protection standards that are broadly equivalent to the standards within the EU.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224374","224374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064727","2019-02-26","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national offenders have been repatriated under the early removal scheme by country since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224314","224314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064728","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department made of the effectiveness of teaching early literacy through Phonics.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224308","224308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064729","2019-02-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has for a future review of the decision to end the export tariff for rooftop solar installations.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224327","224327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064730","2019-02-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations his Department has received from (a) members of the public and (b) civil society groups on the decision to end the export tariff for solar installations.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224328","224328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064731","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued to Clinical Commissioning Groups on the provision of medicines in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and what the responsibility is of Clinical Commissioning Groups ensure adequate supplies of medicines in that event.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224290","224290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064732","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2019 to Question 220230 on NHS: Drugs, whether he has plans to undertake a public consultation on the proposed Framework.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224335","224335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064733","2019-02-26","Cabinet Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many children under the age of 16 have had a (a) fatal and (b) non-fatal paracetamol overdose in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224372","224372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064734","2019-02-26","Cabinet Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many children under the age of 18 have had a (a) fatal and (b) non-fatal paracetamol overdose in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224373","224373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064735","2019-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason (a) child maintenance payments are allocated first to (i) enforcement charges and (ii) debt and then to children and (b) there is no provision to retrieve payments which have been allocated incorrectly by the system or manually.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224360","224360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064736","2019-02-25","Department for International Development","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the UK (a) provides and (b) plans to provide funding to the United Nations Road Safety Trust Fund.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224298","224298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064737","2019-02-26","Department for International Trade","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that new trade deals do not undermine the UK's existing (a) social and (b) environmental standards after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224361","224361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064738","2019-02-26","Department for International Trade","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that new trade deals do not affect the ability of the UK to (a) regulate in the public interest and (b) protect public services.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224362","224362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064739","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women whose home address is in North Wales served sentences of (a) less than six months and (b) six months or more at HMP Styal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224300","224300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064740","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women were on remand at HMP Styal from courts in North Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224301","224301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064741","2019-02-26","Department for International Trade","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential risks to the NHS as a result of future trade deals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224363","224363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064742","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the effectiveness of the Government's Prevent programme in the Romford constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224309","224309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064743","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has made of of the effect of foreign Islamic organisations that promote a Salfist Wahhabist ideology and violent extremism in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224310","224310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064744","2019-02-26","Department for International Trade","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will take steps to ensure that future trade deals will not make it easier for private companies to provide NHS services.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224364","224364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064745","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to protect children in the Romford constituency who are at risk of radicalisation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224311","224311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064746","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the HM Courts and Tribunals Service report, Evaluating our reforms: Response to PAC recommendation 4, published in January 2019, what areas of that service have achieved savings of £158 million.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224316","224316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064747","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Homes (Fitness for Human Habitation) Act 2018 to extend the terms of that Act to people who have been tenants of private landlords for longer than seven years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224313","224313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064748","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the cross-Government strategy on the costs of clinical negligence.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224312","224312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064749","2019-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Turkish counterpart on ending the isolation of Abdullah Ocalan in line with International and Turkish domestic law and bring an end to hunger strikes in that country.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224321","224321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064750","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2019 to Question 218743 on Cancer: Health Services, how the funding arrangement for sustainability and transformation plans (STP) will operate where a Cancer Alliance is aligned with more than one STP or integrated care system.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224292","224292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064751","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Cancer Alliance footprints will change in order to align with sustainability transformation plans and integrated care systems as stated in the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224293","224293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064752","2019-02-26","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that young carers are identified and adequately supported through their schooling.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224306","224306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064753","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that universities do not charge tuition fees to students undertaking industry placements in the UK or abroad as part of their studies.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224353","224353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064754","2019-02-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether it remains his policy that the NHS is the primary provider for cervical cytology screening in England.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224307","224307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064755","2019-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the evidential basis is for her oral contribution of 11 February 2018, Official Report, column 594, that food bank use had increased in the initial roll-out of Universal Credit because people had difficulty in accessing money on time; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224472","224472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064756","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the British Nationality Act 1981, how many cases of revoking British citizenship are under consideration by her Department.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224489","224489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064757","2019-02-26","Department for International Development","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's paper entitled, Single Departmental Plan - Results Achieved by Sector in 2012-2018, Family Planning, what steps her Department has taken to verify the numbers of illegal backstreet abortions provided by the Guttmacher Institute; and whether her Department has conducted a separate estimate of those abortions.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224485","224485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064758","2019-02-26","Department for International Development","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question HL12251 on Kenya: Marie Stopes International, if he will publish the conclusions of the investigation into alleged illegal abortions practices by Marie Stopes International in Niger.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224486","224486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064759","2019-02-26","Treasury","2019-02-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to classify as a priority in the next Spending Review, funding to reduce rough sleeping and homelessness.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224477","224477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064760","2019-02-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Rough Sleeping Strategy, published in August 2018, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) Safeguarding Adult Reviews are conducted when a person who sleeps rough (i) dies and (ii) is seriously harmed as a result of abuse or neglect and (b) the implementation of processes to (i) record and (ii) learn lessons from those deaths.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224478","224478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064761","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the report entitled, Protecting Children in 21st Century Conflict, published by Save the Children in February 2019, whether the recommendations in that report will be included in his Department's  Protection of Civilians Strategy.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224475","224475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064762","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Omani counterpart on the arbitrary detention of the Shuhuh 6 and other human rights violations in that country.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224476","224476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064763","2019-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been deducted from universal credit claimants' standard allowance in each month since April 2017.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224493","224493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064764","2019-02-26","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason he has withdrawn the European University Institute (EU Exit) Regulations 2019.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224487","224487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064765","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many multi-academy trusts have a Special Educational Needs Coordinator with responsibility for more than one school in the chain in (a) Hampshire, (b) Portsmouth and (c) England.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224491","224491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064766","2019-02-26","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the recruitment of adequate numbers of Special Educational Needs Coordinators.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224492","224492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064767","2019-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost of maintaining British bases in Cyprus has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224483","224483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064768","2019-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many permanent British personnel are stationed at British bases in Cyprus.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224484","224484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064769","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time is for a claimant to be referred to a work capability assessment by the Romford service centre in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224479","224479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064770","2019-02-26","Department for Education","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to seek UK membership of the European University Institute Convention after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224488","224488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064771","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to include asthma in the list of conditions which are exempt from the payment of prescription charges.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224470","224470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064772","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect on people's health of prescription charges for asthma medicines.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224471","224471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064773","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have migrated to universal credit in Havering in the most recent 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224480","224480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064774","2019-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to publish further guidance on pet travel to Europe after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224490","224490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064775","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which regulations cover the use of LED and Xenon car headlights.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224473","224473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064776","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what safety standards on headlamps will apply to  vehicles in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224474","224474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064777","2019-02-25","Department for International Trade","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to promote WTO reform and free trade after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224481","224481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064778","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department plans to take to increase standards for the care and protection of animals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224482","224482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064303","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Health Education England phase two cancer workforce plan co-ordinates with the workforce implementation plan in the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223778","223778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064304","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has provided to car insurance companies on the potential for a fee to be charged in respect of driving from Northern Ireland to the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223779","223779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064305","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with representatives from the higher education sector on reducing tuition fees.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223784","223784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064306","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the capital budget was used to support radiotherapy in 2018; and what proportion of the capital budget will not be committed by the end of the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223787","223787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064307","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding he has allocated to the Share Foundation's recovery programmes for Child Trust Fund accounts.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223788","223788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064308","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has plans he to meet the families of the 21 innocent victims of the 1974 Birmingham pub bombings to discuss their campaign for justice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223790","223790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064309","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received on alternative arrangements for breast cancer diagnostic and treatment procedures in the event that there is a shortage of radioisotopes in the UK.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223789","223789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064310","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Brazil on the future (a) human rights and (b) welfare of indigenous groups in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223791","223791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064311","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Philippines on proposals to lower the minimum age of criminal responsibility in that country to 12 years old.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223792","223792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064312","2019-02-25","Department for International Trade","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to ensure that guarantees on human rights form part of future trade negotiations with the Government of Hong Kong after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223793","223793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064313","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of promoting regional economic growth through the supply chain of large infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223794","223794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064314","2019-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled, Economic Cost of Invasive Non-Native Species on Great Britain, published by CABI in November 2010, what the cost to the public purse has been of Invasive Non-Native Species since 2010.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223795","223795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064315","2019-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what dates (a) power of entry and (b) species control provisions have been used under Section 14(4A) of the Wildlife and Countryside Act, as amended by Section 23 of the Infrastructure Act 2015.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223796","223796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064316","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Office for National Statistics publication, Labour productivity, UK: July to September 2018, published on 9 January 2019, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the lower and falling productivity defined by nominal GVA per unit of labour 2016-17 in the north of England.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223774","223774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064317","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Office for National Statistics publication, Labour productivity, UK: July to September 2018, published on 9 January 2019 whether the next Spending Review will allocate funding to tackle the effect of poor health outcomes in the North of England on that region’s levels of productivity.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223775","223775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064318","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to healthcare research in the north of England since 2015.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223776","223776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064319","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to use the NHS Long Term Plan to close the gap in health inequalities between the north and south of England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223777","223777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064323","2019-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish the incidents that have been recorded in non-compliance of The Wildlife and Countryside Act 1981 (prohibition on sale etc. of Invasive Non-native Plants) (England) Order 2014.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223797","223797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064324","2019-02-27","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to comply with the Ballast Water Management Convention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223798","223798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064325","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of microbiota assessments as an adjunct to (a) physical examinations, and (b) mental health examination on the accuracy of medical diagnoses.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223799","223799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064326","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is taking steps to raise awareness of the mechanisms by which disabled people can report discrimination in the event of being refused access to a taxi or private hire vehicle.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223800","223800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064327","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to encourage licensing authorities to provide mandatory disability equality training on the rights and needs of disabled passengers for taxi and private hire vehicle drivers.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223801","223801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064328","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that local authorities have sufficient resources to meet demand for older people’s care; and what steps he is taking to reduce levels of variation in available care across regions of England.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223802","223802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064329","2019-02-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many teenagers have (a) commenced and (b) graduated a National Citizenship Service programme in each of the last four years; and what the Government's target was for participation in that programme since 2011.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223803","223803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064330","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for its policies of the Coram Family and Childcare's survey on Older People's Care, published in December 2018, which found that over 4.3 million people aged 75 and over live in areas with inadequate social care to meet demand.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223804","223804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064331","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much HS2 Ltd spent on agency staff between 1 January 2018 and 30th June 2018; and how many agency staff were hired each such agency; and which agencies those agency staff were hired from.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223805","223805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064332","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to double the number of places on the PrEP Trial across all trial sites as soon as possible.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223806","223806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064333","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department will publish the spending over £25,000 from July 2018 to December 2018.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223807","223807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064334","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timescale is for the implementation of doubling the number of places on the PrEP Trial across all trial sites.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223808","223808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064335","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department plans to publish its guidelines for supporting human rights defenders.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223809","223809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064336","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is his Department's policy to support the creation of an international independent body to oversee dams holding mining waste as a result of the collapse of the Corrego do Feijao and Samarco dams in Brazil.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223810","223810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064337","2019-02-25","Department for International Trade","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which Governments have asked the UK Government for concessions on human rights standards in talks on the conclusion of bilateral trade deals.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223811","223811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064338","2019-02-25","Department for International Trade","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, the concessions on human rights standards what have been requested by the Governments of other countries in talks with the UK Government on the conclusion of bilateral trade deals.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223812","223812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064339","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason there has been a delay in doubling the number of places on the PrEP Trial across all trial sites.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223813","223813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064340","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has his Department made of the effecgt of the closure of Shine in Salford on the ability of Salford residents to access the HIV prevention drug PrEP under the PrEP Impact Trial.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223814","223814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064341","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the number of complaints that have been made under the HS2 complaints procedure since it was established with an outline of each complaint.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223815","223815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064342","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Prime Minister's letter to the Leader of the Opposition of 10 February 2019, what steps he plans to take to provide further financial support to communities that feel left behind.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223816","223816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064343","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support his Department makes available for families experiencing (a) adolescent-to-parent violence and abuse and (b) child-on-parent violence.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223817","223817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064344","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what framework social services use when dealing with (a) adolescent-to-parent violence and abuse and (b) child-on-parent violence.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223818","223818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064345","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support his Department makes available for siblings in families experiencing (a) adolescent-to-parent violence and abuse and (b) child-on-parent violence.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223819","223819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064346","2019-02-25","Cabinet Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what is the (a) total book value of the central Government estate in London and (b) rate payable on those properties.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223820","223820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064347","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reported incidents of (a) adolescent-to-parent violence and abuse and (b) child on parent violence were reported in (i) the St Helens local authority area, (ii) Merseyside and (iii) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223821","223821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064348","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the report entitled, Research into drivers of service costs in rural areas: national analysis of unit costs, published by LG Futures in December 2014, whether the conclusions of that report will be used as an evidence base in his Department's review of local government funding.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223822","223822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064349","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether incidents of (a) adolescent-to-parent violence and abuse and (b) child-on-parent violence are recorded as domestic abuse.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223823","223823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064350","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2019 to Question 215257, on NHS: drugs, what information his Department holds on the level of medicine shortages in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223824","223824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064351","2019-02-25","Attorney General","2019-02-20","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of staff employed by his Department are apprentices.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223825","223825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064352","2019-02-25","Cabinet Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff employed by in No. 10 Downing Street are apprentices.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223826","223826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064353","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff employed by his Department are apprentices.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223827","223827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064354","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of staff employed by his Department are apprentices.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223828","223828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064355","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households have been affected by each reform to working-age benefits and tax credits since 2010.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223829","223829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064356","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit claimants have not been in receipt of any benefits in the 180 days following a sanction decision.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223830","223830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064357","2019-02-25","Department for International Development","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that there is safe drinking water available in (a) Sri Lanka and (b) all other Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223831","223831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064358","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department plans to update the Government Strategy on the Protection of Civilians in Armed Conflict to include a specific focus on children.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223832","223832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064359","2019-02-27","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how he plans to use the next Spending Review to reduce economic inequalities between the north and south of England.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223833","223833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064360","2019-02-27","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the next Spending Review will include plans to review the level of investment in health research received by northern institutions.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223834","223834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064361","2019-02-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the new NHS funding settlement will be spent to takcle health inequalities between the north and south of England.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223835","223835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064362","2019-02-25","Department for International Trade","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 213459 on Department for International Trade: Internet, how many downloads have been made of the Local to Global podcast to date.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223836","223836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064363","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of deprivation of citizenship have been (a) considered and (b) confirmed in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223837","223837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064364","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department taking to (a) monitor and (b) tackle levels of antisemitism in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223838","223838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064365","2019-02-25","Cabinet Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to enable residents of care homes to participate in elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223839","223839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064366","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to support the Government of India after the Pulwama attack on 14 February 2019.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223840","223840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064367","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that private donations from the UK are not used to support and fund terrorism.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223841","223841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064368","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer on 14 February to Question 219561 on Endoscopy: Recruitment, how many of the 202 clinical endoscopists have now completed their training and are able to undertake procedures in flexible sigmoidoscopy.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223842","223842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064369","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the most recent calculations of average rents for two bedroom homes in each of the 152 Broad Rental Market Areas that have been used to calculate local rental market statistics, including the Local Housing Allowance.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223843","223843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064370","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether a bid for the provision of forensic training to the police may be refused due to a company also providing training to foreign nationals from countries either guilty of, accused of, or implicated in, serious human rights abuses; and whether any company has been refused on those grounds.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223844","223844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064371","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost to the public purse is of each universal credit appeal.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223845","223845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064372","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit appeals her Department has challenged in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223846","223846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064373","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his EU Settlement Scheme: Statement of Intent, when he plans to publish details on the immigration status of (a) EU citizen family members and (b) spouses of British citizen Crown servants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223847","223847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064374","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit appeals her Department has lost in each year since the introduction of that benefit.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223848","223848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064377","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy to refund the fees paid by EU citizens who have chosen to apply for UK citizenship rather than for settled status.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223902","223902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064378","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library the list of local authority areas which have bid successfully to begin local Innovation in Democracy pilots.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223903","223903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064379","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he applies the same standards for mothers and fathers when assessing Article 8 applications for leave to remain.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223904","223904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064380","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for visitor visas his Department has received since 2005.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223905","223905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064381","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2016 to Question 44231 on High Speed Two: Legal Costs, how much has been disbursed from the public purse in legal fees for solicitors, parliamentary agents, barristers and their staff working on behalf of HS2 Ltd since that date.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223906","223906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064382","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2015 to Question 16832 on High Speed 2 Railway Line, which legal advisers and barristers have been used by (a) HS2 Ltd and (b) his Department in relation to High Speed Two since 23 November 2015; and how much each such legal professional (i) has been paid and (ii) is owed.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223907","223907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064383","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many commonwealth soldiers in (a) Barnsley and (b) South Yorkshire have applied to bring one or more of their children to the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223908","223908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064384","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many commonwealth soldiers in (a) Barnsley and (b) South Yorkshire have had their applications to bring one or more of their children to the UK rejected in the last five years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223909","223909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064385","2019-02-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on how any surplus taken by the Government from the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme since 2010 has been used by his Department.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223910","223910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064386","2019-02-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how any surplus taken by the Government from the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme since 2010 has been spent.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223911","223911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064387","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants have been employed in primary schools in South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223912","223912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064388","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants have been employed in secondary schools in South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223913","223913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064389","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants have been employed in primary schools in Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223914","223914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064390","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants have been employed in secondary schools in Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223915","223915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064391","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many specialist support staff have been employed in primary schools in South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223916","223916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064392","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many specialist support staff have been employed in secondary schools in South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223917","223917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064393","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 23 November 2015 to Question 16832, what hourly rate has been agreed by his Department for each of the barristers that have carried out other HS2 work since 2010 as detailed in that answer; and if he will list those barristers against their hourly rate.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223918","223918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064394","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many specialist support staff have been employed in secondary schools in South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223919","223919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064395","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many specialist support staff have been employed in primary schools in Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223920","223920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064396","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many specialist support staff have been employed in secondary schools in Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223921","223921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064397","2019-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding the Armed Forced Covenant fund has granted to (a) Barnsley and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223922","223922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064398","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average number of days was for her Department to reassess existing entitlement to personal independence payment in (a) Barnley, (b) south Yorkshire and (c) nationally in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223923","223923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064399","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the number of days was for her Department to reassess entitlement to personal independence payment from that payment being granted in (a) Barnley, (b) south Yorkshire and (c) nationally in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223924","223924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064400","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of infrastructure works on the (a) M20 contraflow and (b) M26 alterations in 2019.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223925","223925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064401","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average number of days have been for her Department to re-assess entitlement to employment and support allowance from that allowance being granted in (a) Barnley, (b) south Yorkshire and (c) nationally in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223926","223926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064402","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding from the Homelessness Relief Fund was granted to (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) nationally in each year since that fund was established.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223927","223927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064403","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the ability of GTR to introduce a fast train service from Maidstone East to London in December 2019.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223928","223928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064404","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department provides on the issuing of fit notes by GP practices for welfare assessments.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223929","223929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064405","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had with counterparts in the EU to support improvements to the (a) road, (b) rail and (c) ports infrastructure in south eastern Ukraine.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223930","223930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064406","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what financial assistance the Government plans to allocate to Ukraine in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223931","223931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064407","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the funding per pupil at (a) primary and ( b) secondary school in Kent in (i) 2018-19 and (ii) 2019-20.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223932","223932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064408","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to publish a response to its consultation on Non-road mobile machinery and red diesel, published on 15 July 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223933","223933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064409","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the safety of Cellou Dalein Diallo in Guinea.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223934","223934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064410","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims qualified for Inheritance Tax exemption on agricultural property in 2018; what the location was of claim; and what the average income was of the recipients.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223935","223935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064411","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequacy of support for deaf schoolchildren in mainstream schools.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223936","223936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064412","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of (a) the number of beneficiaries of the main residence nil rate band of Inheritance Tax exemption in 2018, (b) where those beneficiaries are located and (c) what is the average income of those beneficiaries was.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223937","223937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064413","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims were made for Income Tax relief under the Enterprise Management Scheme in 2018; what the average amount was of those claim; how many claims were made in each region; and what the average income was of the claimants.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223938","223938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064414","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims were made for National Insurance tax relief under the Enterprise Management Scheme in 2018, what the average amount was of those claims; how many claims were made in each region; and what the average income was of the claimants.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223939","223939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064415","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims were been made for Patent Box corporation tax relief, what the average amount was of those claims; and which companies made those claims.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223940","223940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064416","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims were made for Inheritance Tax relief on business assets in 2018, what the average amount was of those claims; and what the average income was of the claimants.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223941","223941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064417","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims were made for Personal Dividend Allowance relief in 2018, what the average amount was of those claims; and what the average income was of the claimants.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223942","223942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064418","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of lowering the retirement age for part-time female workers that are carers for (a) older people and (b) family members with disabilities.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223943","223943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064419","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims were made for Vehicle Excise Duty exemption under the Exemption for Historic Cars relief in 2018, what the average amount was of those claims; and what the average income was of the claimants.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223944","223944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064420","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average income was of recipients of Income Tax relief under the Save as You Earn tax relief programme in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223945","223945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064421","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claims were made under the Enterprise Investment Scheme in 2018, and what the average income was of the claimants.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223946","223946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064422","2019-02-25","Attorney General","2019-02-20","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 213932 on Crown Prosecution Service: West Midlands, what the change has been in the caseload for the Crown Prosecution Service for each principal offence category in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223947","223947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064423","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who have returned from conflict in Syria have had their citizenship removed.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223948","223948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064424","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers were employed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223949","223949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064425","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who have returned from the conflict in Syria (a) held dual-British citizenship and (b) were British nationals.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223950","223950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064426","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) British nationals and (a) dual-British nationals returning from the conflict in Syria have had their British citizenship revoked.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223951","223951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064427","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times and on what dates the civil legal aid means test threshold has been evaluated since it was last reviewed and uprated.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223952","223952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064428","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times and on what dates the criminal legal aid means test threshold has been evaluated since it was last reviewed and uprated.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223953","223953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064429","2019-02-25","Attorney General","2019-02-20","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 11 of February 2019 to Question 217439 on Crown Prosecution Service: West Midlands, how many minor motoring cases there were in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223954","223954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064430","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an estimate of the number of people that have been excluded from legal aid eligibility as a result of the civil legal aid means test threshold not being uprated in line with inflation since 2008.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223955","223955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064431","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of people that have been excluded from legal aid eligibility as a result of the criminal legal aid means test threshold not being uprated in line with inflation since 2009.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223956","223956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064432","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil legal aid offers have not taken forward by the applicant following an assessment of the level of contribution that they will need to provide through the legal aid means test in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223957","223957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064433","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many grants of emergency legal aid have been revoked when contributions determined through the legal aid means test were not fulfilled in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223958","223958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064434","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the UK leaving the EU will affect the way in which medical technology is regulated in the UK; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the ability of UK citizens to travel abroad with dialysis machines.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223959","223959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064435","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which members of the (a) legal profession and (b) judiciary were consulted as part of the Government's most recent review of the (i) civil and (ii) criminal legal aid means test thresholds.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223960","223960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064436","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February to Question 217442 on Birmingham Prison: G4S, whether G4S (a) was required to pay any forfeitures as a result of the step-in and (b) paid during the period of the step-in.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223961","223961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064437","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February to Question 217442 on Birmingham Prison: G4S, what assessment he has made of the capacity of G4S to fulfil the terms of its contract to run that prison.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223962","223962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064438","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February to Question 217444 on Prisons: Crimes of Violence and Self-harm, what assessment his Department made for the reasons for trends in the level of (a) deaths, (b) assaults and (c) self-harm in prisons.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223963","223963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064439","2019-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason his Department has removed one MQ-9 Reaper unmanned aerial vehicle from service.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223964","223964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064440","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 187307 on Home Office: ICT, how many of those 352 contingent staff were employed by his Department for (a) zero to three, (b) three to six, (c) six to 12 and (d) more than (i) 12 and (ii) 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223965","223965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064441","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what evidence his Department received from external bodies on his Department’s review of the means testing requirement for legal aid at inquests involving the state in its review of legal aid for inquests report, published in February 2019.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223966","223966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064442","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what consultations his Department (a) sought and (b) held with bodies on its review of the means testing element of legal aid at inquests in its review of legal aid for inquests report, published in February 2019.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223967","223967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064443","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children under the age of 16 have had a (a) fatal and (b) non-fatal drug overdose in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223968","223968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064444","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 187307 on Home Office: ICT, if he will publish the agencies used to secure the 352 contingent staff; and how much money his Department spent with each of those agencies in relation to securing staff for the Common Platform programme since the start of that project.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223969","223969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064445","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has any (a) formal and (b) informal sharing agreements with police forces in relation to referrals relating to suspected benefit fraud.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223970","223970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064446","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 187307 on Home Office: ICT, if he will publish the roles of the 352 contingent staff.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223971","223971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064447","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children under the age of 18 that have had a (a) fatal and (b) non-fatal drug overdose in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223972","223972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064448","2019-02-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many abuses of a dominant market position by the three multinational firms that comprise 90 per cent of the UK domestic off grid LPG market have been investigated; and what the outcome was of those investigations.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223973","223973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064449","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of  the adequacy of the level of per pupil funding in England by his Department in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223974","223974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064450","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the combined total value was of sums sought from insurers by way of NHS recoupment by the Compensation Recovery Unit for the last two complete financial years under both the Road Traffic (NHS Charges) Act 1999 and the Health and Social Care (Community Health and Standards) Act 2003.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223975","223975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064451","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are being taken to encourage all major supermarket chains to introduce reduction targets for plastics.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223976","223976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064452","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will increase capital funding to expand provision at special schools in Essex.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223977","223977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064453","2019-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained arms control inspectors are employed by Her Majesty’s Government.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223978","223978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064454","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the protection of health professionals from violence perpetrated by Israeli security forces during the Great March of Return protests on the Gaza strip; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223979","223979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064455","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his counterpart in Israel on the concerns raised by Physicians for Human Rights Israel that cancer patients in Gaza continue to have their permits for travel in order to receive treatment withheld by the Israeli Government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223980","223980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064456","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2019 to Question 214530, whether the guidance for the new subjects of Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education and Health Education will refer to same-sex parents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223981","223981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064457","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the of the number of (a) GP practices offering cervical screening (i) outside and (ii) for limited periods during 9 to 5 working hours, (b) sexual health clinics that have stopped offering cervical screening tests and (c) vacancies for practice nurses trained to provide cervical screening; whether he has made an assessment of the effect on (A) screening rates and (B) cervical cancer cases of changes in the number of locations where individuals can obtain a cervical smear test; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223982","223982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064458","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the change in the the number of pupils with special educational needs and disabilities (SEND) permanently excluded from school in Essex in the last three years; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of pupils with SEND being permanently excluded.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223983","223983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064459","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of pupils with Education, Health and Care Plans attending (a) special schools and (b) mainstream schools in Essex in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223984","223984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064460","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what risk assessments his Department has made on proposals to place social workers in schools in the local authority areas of (a) Southampton, (b) Stockport and (c) Lambeth.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223985","223985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064461","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether (a) EU and (b) Irish citizens that have worked in the UK will continue to have their pensions uprated in line with UK pensioners in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223986","223986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064462","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed concrete sleeper factory in Bescot on air quality in the surrounding area.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223987","223987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064463","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has accrued to the public purse of deductions from universal credit claimants' standard allowance.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223988","223988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064464","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the (a) permissions and (b) legal assurances for clearances of vegetation planned to take place on 200 acres near Steeple Claydon Buckinghamshire by (i) HS2 Ltd (ii) contractors working for HS2 Ltd; and the dates on which they were obtained.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223989","223989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064465","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed concrete sleeper factory in Bescot on congestion in the surrounding area.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223990","223990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064466","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed concrete sleeper factory in Bescot on public health in the surrounding area.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223991","223991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064467","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of the EU Settlement Scheme on cross-border workers that live in Ireland but work in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223992","223992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064468","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, from which countries UK imports of live reindeer have been suspended in light of the recent incidence of chronic wasting disease; and on what date each country’s suspension came into force.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223996","223996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064469","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many holdings in the High Risk Bovine TB control area were interferon-gamma tested in 2018.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224019","224019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064470","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of women of reproductive age living in an area where the sexual and reproductive health budget has been reduced; what assessment he has made of the effect of the change to the public health budget on access to sexual and reproductive health services; what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the public health budget in advance of the forthcoming Spring Statement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224021","224021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064471","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many of the holdings that were interferon-gamma tested in 2018 in the High Risk Bovine TB control area in England were tested on account of (a) being located in an areas that had completed two years of successful badger population control, (b) there being clear evidence that repeated skin testing has failed to resolve a TB breakdown and (c) the APHA veterinary investigation concluding that the most likely transmission route for the affected herd was contact with infected cattle and that measures are in place to prevent further spread of disease from that source.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224023","224023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064472","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the planned timescale is for patients to access Spinraza treatment for muscular atrophy types 2 and 3.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224024","224024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064473","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on concluding a managed access treatment agreement for the use of Spinraza for patients with spinal muscular atrophy types 2 and 3.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224025","224025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064474","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which (a) organisations and (b) other Departments his Department shares personal data with that has been captured during the settled status application process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224026","224026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064475","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle the issue of the official name of Bulgarian citizens appearing in Cyrillic on their EU settled status applications as a result of the first line of their passport being written in the Cyrillic script.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224027","224027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064476","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applicants were unable to complete the application process for settled status during the second phase of the trial of the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224028","224028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064477","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applicants were granted pre-settled status during the second phase of the trial of the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224029","224029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064478","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to publicise to motorists who intend to travel to EU countries after the UK leaves the EU that they will need an insurance green card in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224030","224030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064479","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to publicise to motorists intending to travel to EU countries after the UK leaves the EU the consequences of not travelling with an insurance green card in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224031","224031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064480","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to publicise to motorists in Northern Ireland that they will need an insurance green card in order to drive in the Republic of Ireland in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224032","224032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064481","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has publicised the potential changes to accessing and paying for (a) dialysis and (b) other medical treatment in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224033","224033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064482","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the export of plastic waste to developing countries; and if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of a complete ban on plastic waste exports to developing countries.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224034","224034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064483","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has plans to support the imposition of independent electoral observers in the upcoming Turkish Parliamentary elections.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224035","224035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064484","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what palliative care is available to mothers whose unborn baby receives a diagnosis of a life-limiting disability and wishes to carry her baby to full term; and what plans his Department has to increase the availability of such services.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224036","224036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064485","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the feasibility of banning the use of non-recyclable plastics in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224037","224037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064486","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2019 to Question 218386, for what reasons he is not able to publish the full version of the Accession Agreement to the Asset Protection Agency.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224038","224038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064487","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish in unredacted form the Asset Protection Agency’s Framework Document, published on 7 December 2009.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224039","224039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064488","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the ACI EUROPE Airport Industry Connectivity Report 2018, published in June 2018 which reported that the UK’s direct connectivity has declined by 0.8 per cent between 2017 and 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224040","224040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064489","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of staff turnover in his Department on the effectiveness of project management.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224041","224041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064490","2019-02-25","Department for Transport","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on recruitment in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224042","224042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064491","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 206757 on Environmental Stewardship Scheme, how many of those agreements did not have any aftercare visits.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224043","224043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064492","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 206757, on Environmental Stewardship Scheme, how many of those visits occurred in the final year of the agreement.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224044","224044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064493","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential for (a) electoral fraud and (b) the violation of opposition parties by the authorities in Turkey during the upcoming parliamentary elections in that country; and if he will discuss those electoral issues with his counterpart in Turkey.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224079","224079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064494","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make public in unredacted form the 9 November 2011 document entitled Approval of the Asset Management Framework and Conflicts Management Policy, and related Modifications to the Accession Agreement.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224088","224088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064495","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much Her Majesty's Courts and Tribunal Service plans to spend on consultancies in total; and how much and on which consultancies that service plans to spend (a) more and (b) less than £50,000 in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224081","224081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064496","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the planned completion date is for the common platform programme.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224082","224082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064497","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to support employees who are due to lose their jobs as a result of the courts modernisation programme.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224083","224083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064498","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the reduction in staff as a result of the courts modernisation programme in (a) London, (b) Greater Manchester, (c) Bolton and (d) England.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224084","224084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064499","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is her Department's policy not to permit job centre staff to issue food bank referral forms to benefit claimants.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224080","224080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064500","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government plans to (a) hold and (b) publish the outcome of a future public consultation on the courts reform programme.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224085","224085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064501","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the responses received during the Judicial Ways of Working exercise will be (a) shared with the judges consulted and (b) published.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224086","224086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064502","2019-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 18 of the January 2019 HM Courts and Tribunals Service document entitled Putting people at the heart of reform: Response to PAC recommendation 2 which states that There will be clear proportionality – complex and serious cases will continue to be handled with the full majesty of the courtroom, what process he uses to make an assessment of proportionality when deciding which cases will take place in a courtroom.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224087","224087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064780","2019-02-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 216983 on Motor Vehicles: Manufacturing Industries, whether Vauxhall has (a) applied successfully, (b) applied unsuccessfully and (c) not applied for support through those programmes conducted independently of the Government.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224516","224516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064781","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of a shortage of radioisotopes on the number of breast cancer diagnostic and treatment procedures.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224533","224533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063615","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 220800 on Winter Fuel Payments, how many recipients returned their Winter Fuel Payment in the most recent 12 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 222578","222578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063834","2019-02-21","Treasury","2019-02-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to tackle the uncertainty of cross-border insurance arrangements in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 222769","222769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063840","2019-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dog attacks on humans there have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 222845","222845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063841","2019-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many outbreaks of legionnaires in turkeys there have been in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 222846","222846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063842","2019-02-21","Church Commissioners","2019-02-19","To ask the Right Honourable Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what humanitarian support the Church of England provides to people overseas that are persecuted for their Christian beliefs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 222847","222847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063843","2019-02-21","Department for Education","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of attacks on teachers by pupils in schools.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 222848","222848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063844","2019-02-21","Church Commissioners","2019-02-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to tackle homelessness.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909352","909352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063846","2019-02-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","What discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on including awareness-raising of the risks of pre-natal exposure to alcohol in the Government's alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909317","909317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063847","2019-02-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","What steps he is taking to prevent self-harm and suicide among children.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909318","909318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063848","2019-02-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","What steps he is taking to improve IT systems in GP surgeries.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909322","909322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063849","2019-02-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","What recent assessment he has made of the (a) value for money and (b) clinical outcomes of NHS treatments for musculoskeletal conditions.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909323","909323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063853","2019-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has for farming policy after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909370","909370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063854","2019-02-21","Church Commissioners","2019-02-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what recent discussions the Church of England has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on increasing the marriage allowance.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909357","909357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063910","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have had an operation for an artificial heart have been undertaken in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223052","223052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063913","2019-02-21","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Saudi Arabian citizens have applied for asylum in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223053","223053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063914","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps the NHS has taken to promote the health benefits of regular exercise.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223054","223054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063915","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people aged between 10 and 20 have had operations for kidney-stones in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223055","223055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063916","2019-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the North Sudanese Government on economic support for that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223056","223056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063917","2019-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for a divorce were lodged between Christmas 2018 and New Year 2019.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223057","223057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063918","2019-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions officials in his Department have had with their counterparts in the Scottish Government on trends in mortality rates for farmed salmon.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223058","223058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063919","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information the Government considered when setting the value of Contributions Based Job Seekers Allowance entitlement at £73.10 for people over 25.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223059","223059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063920","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of implementing a UK-wide scheme for the purchase and distribution of expensive drugs and medical supplies that are used to treat rare conditions.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223060","223060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063921","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will publish the findings of its analysis of operations at Dover port in relation to the EU Pet Travel Regulations.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223061","223061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063922","2019-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the letter of 14 January 2019, case reference SG11604, on Iain Kinloch, was sent to the Department for Work and Pensions; and whether that letter was read by the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State and Minister for Defence People and Veterans.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223062","223062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063923","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of requiring the owners of limited companies to provide company financial accounts when applying for universal credit on the ability of those people to complete their applications in a timely manner.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223063","223063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063924","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to the letter of 31 January 2019 from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central addressed to the Minister for Immigration on the matter of a constituent Mr Soofi.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223074","223074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063925","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department plans to respond to the letter of 31 January 2019 from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central, addressed to the Minister of State for Asia and the Pacific, on the matter of a constituent, Mr Soofi.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223075","223075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063926","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether a qualified witness independent of the relevant clinical commissioning group is required to be involved in a patient's continuing healthcare assessment.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223076","223076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063927","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to publish the social care Green Paper within the current Parliamentary Session.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223077","223077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063928","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the level of financial support that will be available to hill farmers through the Basic Payment Scheme or an alternative to that scheme by 2024.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223078","223078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063929","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the level of financial support that will be available to hill farmers through the Basic Payment Scheme or an alternative to that scheme by 2028.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223079","223079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063930","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timetable is for the roll-out of the replacement to the Basic Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223080","223080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063931","2019-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what date he plans to make the replacement to the Basic Payment Scheme available to all farmers.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223081","223081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063932","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, what assessment he has made of the effect of developments in digital care on the provision of pain pathway services.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223082","223082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063933","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prevent worsening chronicity of pain in people suffering from chronic pain.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223083","223083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063936","2019-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department paid from the public purse to claimants of personal independence payment during the appeals process in each of the the last two years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223108","223108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063937","2019-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans her Department has to give indefinite awards of personal independence payment to people with degenerative conditions.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223109","223109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063938","2019-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans her Department has to introduce online application forms for personal independence payments which allow claimants to scan and upload their documents.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223110","223110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063939","2019-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to employ more staff and reduce the length of time personal independence payment claimants have to wait for their appeal to be heard.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223111","223111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063940","2019-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment claimants lost their mobility entitlement for a motability car on moving from the disabled living allowance in the last two years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223112","223112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063941","2019-02-21","Department for Education","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle bullying in schools.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223113","223113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063942","2019-02-21","Department for Education","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has a policy to help tackle stress experienced by teachers.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223114","223114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063943","2019-02-21","Department for Education","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of universities on the proposed introduction of two year degree courses.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223115","223115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063944","2019-02-21","Department for Education","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking with the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy to help university graduates secure graduate job roles.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223116","223116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063945","2019-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the quality of new build homes produced by (a) large house builders, (b) medium house builders and (c) small house builders and (d) micro house builders.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223117","223117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063946","2019-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to support SME diversification into the off-site manufacturing sector for the construction of new build homes.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223118","223118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063947","2019-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the change in (a) speed of decision making and (b) overall performance of local authority planning departments since they were permitted to increase planning fees in January 2018.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223119","223119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063948","2019-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he will take to improve access to finance for small and medium-sized house builders.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223120","223120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063949","2019-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits to consumer protection of introducing a licensing scheme for UK construction companies and sole traders.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223121","223121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063950","2019-02-21","Department for Education","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to increase the quality of construction apprenticeships.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223122","223122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063951","2019-02-21","Department for Education","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect on productivity levels of (a) bricklaying, (b) plastering and (c) other core construction apprenticeships after (i) two years and (ii) three years of such apprenticeship training.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223123","223123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063952","2019-02-21","Department for Education","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to increase the proportion of Apprenticeship Levy vouchers that are able to be passed down the supply chain to smaller non-Levy paying companies.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223124","223124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063953","2019-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he will take to advance proposals to create an Antarctic Ocean Sanctuary in the Weddell Sea, following the failure to reach an agreement on such proposals at the meeting of the Commission for the Conservation of Antarctic Marine Living Resources in autumn 2018.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223125","223125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063954","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of links between cannabis use and mental health problems.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223126","223126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063955","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of GP practices are administered by healthcare companies based abroad.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223127","223127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063956","2019-02-21","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) skilled and (b) unskilled migrants that will be allowed to move to the UK each year after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223128","223128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063957","2019-02-21","Department for Transport","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to reduce the number of accidents involving bicycles on UK roads.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223129","223129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063958","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of GP consortia that are run for profit by overseas-based medical insurance firms.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223130","223130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063959","2019-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the introduction of additional (a) incentives, (b) capital allowances, and (c) financial support for research and development to support the manufacturing industry.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223131","223131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063960","2019-02-21","Department for International Development","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps she has taken to ensure the effectiveness Official Development Assistance.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223132","223132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063961","2019-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason there is an expiry date on the HM Armed Forces Veterans identification card.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223133","223133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063962","2019-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the length of sentences for convictions of dog smuggling.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223134","223134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063963","2019-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many incidences of dog smuggling there have been in each of the last 10 years; and from which countries those dogs were smuggled.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223135","223135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063964","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal combatants returning from conflicts abroad have been prosecuted in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223136","223136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063965","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2019 to Question 217544 on Spina Bifida: Surgery, if his Department will make it its policy to provide pain relief to unborn babies of a similar age undergoing a termination.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223137","223137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063966","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will list the offences with which each returning ISIS combatant, who has been prosecuted, has been charged with in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223138","223138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063967","2019-02-25","Cabinet Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much money has been spent from the public purse on services provided by (a) Deloitte, (b) Slaughter and May and (c) Mott MacDonald as recorded by his Department's spend analytic in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223139","223139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063968","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 187307 on Home Office: ICT, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the public purse of the 352 people classed as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223140","223140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063969","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 187307 on Home Office: ICT, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the public purse of (a) agency fees and (b) direct staff cost for the 352 people classed as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223141","223141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063970","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to prevent patients from being incorrectly denied access to medicinal cannabis.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223142","223142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063971","2019-02-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the equity of the announcement by the Health and Care Professions Council of its plan to increase its registration fees by 18 per cent from October 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223143","223143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063972","2019-02-25","Department for Education","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Minister is responsible for children's play services; and what steps the Government is taking on ensuring that the UK upholds Article 31 of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child on the right to play.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223144","223144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063973","2019-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the number of veterans who have served in the armed forces who reside in each local authority area.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223145","223145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063974","2019-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy to record the number of veterans who have served in the armed forces who reside in each local authority area.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223146","223146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063975","2019-02-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 220945 on Voluntary Work: Young People, (a) how much and (b) what proportion of the total budget of the National Citizen Service the Department estimates it will spend on advertising and marketing in the financial year (i) 2019-20 and (ii) 2020-21.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223147","223147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063976","2019-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many former members of the armed forces have served custodial sentences in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223148","223148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063977","2019-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the prison population has previously served in the armed forces.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223163","223163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063978","2019-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the proportion of veterans who have served in the armed forces that were in receipt of mental health services in 2018.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223166","223166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063979","2019-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people who were homeless in 2018 who had previously served in the armed forces.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223170","223170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063980","2019-02-25","Treasury","2019-02-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will hold a meeting with the hon. Member for Glasgow North East on the effect of the IR35 tax reforms on the personal finances of people living in Glasgow North East constituency.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223171","223171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063981","2019-02-21","Treasury","2019-02-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Enterprise Investment Scheme in helping domestic film production companies raise funding.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223172","223172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063982","2019-02-21","Treasury","2019-02-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to support domestic film production companies to raise funding.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223175","223175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063983","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 213466, how many complaints were received in relation to the personal independence payment assessment process in each calendar year since 2013.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223180","223180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063984","2019-02-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress the Government has made on the renewal of the National Occupational Standards for Youth Work which expire in 2020.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223181","223181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063985","2019-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of previous offences committed was by people given a custodial sentence of (a) up to six months and (b) six to 12 months in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223182","223182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063986","2019-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number was of previous community orders handed down to offenders sentenced to prison for (a) up to six months; (b) six to 12 months and (c) over 12 months in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223183","223183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063987","2019-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for which (a) offence and (b) offences each current prisoner serving a sentence of six months or less was imprisoned.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223184","223184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063988","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 218833 on Immigrants: Detainees, what the cost was of the escorting contract for immigration detainees in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223185","223185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063989","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that newly approved refugees are not subject to a break in support when their asylum support ends after 28 days.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223186","223186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063990","2019-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were sent to prison for not paying (a) the television licence and (b) a subsequent fine; and how many days each offender spent in prison in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223187","223187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063991","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he will bring forward legislative proposals to enshrine in law the right to appeal refusals of Settled or Pre-Settled status.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223188","223188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063992","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish his Department's guidance on how EEA citizens will be able to demonstrate their right to reside after 29 March 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223189","223189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063993","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department will take and what benchmarks his Department will use to evaluate the effectiveness of the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223190","223190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063994","2019-02-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance his Department has issued to (a) organisations and (b) businesses working for the Birmingham Commonwealth Games Organising Committee on becoming accredited by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage employer; and in what format that guidance was issued.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223191","223191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063995","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, further to the agreement signed with West Midlands councils to create the West Midlands Combined Authority (WMCA), if he will publish the amount of funding allocated to house-building; the time period for which that funding applies; what proportion of that funding has been transferred to the WMCA; and what proportion of that funding will be transferred in the next fiscal year.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223192","223192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063996","2019-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions he has received correspondence from the Mayor for the West Midlands on the (a) roll-out and (b) design of universal credit in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223193","223193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063997","2019-02-21","Treasury","2019-02-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2019 to Question 220289, Children: Maintenance, if she will provide further information on the overall care test used to determine entitlement to child benefit.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223194","223194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063998","2019-02-21","Treasury","2019-02-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect that an increase in the small producer's relief scheme to 30,000 litres would have on the growth of small cider producers in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223196","223196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1063999","2019-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what records her Department holds on the income of the 4.9 per cent of claimants who were not in receipt of any tracked benefits in the 180 days following a universal credit live service sanction decision.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223197","223197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064000","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department’s definition is of a coalfield community; and which local authority areas contain an identified coalfield community.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223198","223198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064001","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which funding programmes his Department makes available for specific use by coalfield communities; and how much funding has been allocated through those programmes in each  financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223199","223199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064002","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which funding programmes his Department makes available for specific use by coalfield communities; and how much funding has been allocated through those programmes in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223200","223200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064003","2019-02-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department’s strategy is for the regeneration of coalfield communities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223201","223201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064004","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to safeguard the welfare of Benjamin Gudza, a resident of the Barnsley Central constituency, who has been detained at Morton Hall detention centre and is due to be deported to Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223202","223202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064005","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to make adjustments for Benjamin Gudza’s learning difficulties and mobility problems, while he is in detention at Morton Hall.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223203","223203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064006","2019-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the sanctions against the Zimbabwean Government and other Designated Persons from Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223204","223204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1064007","2019-02-25","Home Office","2019-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment his Department has made of the risk to Zimbabwean nationals facing deportation to Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223205","223205"
