"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49509","2014-05-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of the 50 initial preferred bidders for probation services remain in the competition.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197569","197569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49510","2014-05-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many police cautions were issued in Brigg and Goole constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197598","197598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49511","2014-05-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of businesses in Brigg and Goole constituency that will be issued with staging dates for automatic enrolment between 1 April 2014 and 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197610","197610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49512","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women suffered health complications following abortion procedures in 2012.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197440","197440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49513","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 12 March 2014, Official Report, column 238W, on abortion and 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 31W, on abortion, if he will make it his policy that his Department collects data on the number of (a) neonatal deaths following a legal termination of pregnancy, (b) foetuses that show signs of life following an attempted termination and (c) such foetuses registered as live births; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197462","197462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49514","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 42W, on in vitro fertilisation, if he will provide specific references to the available evidence that no genomic DNA is found in the mitochondria but only in the cell nucleus; how their consideration that mitochondrial DNA is not part of the genome relates to the presentation of data on the human genome in the ENSEMBL and OMIM databases; what precise genetic modifications are applied to the eggs or embryos that would prevent any nuclear DNA from the egg or embryo donors from being inherited by the resulting child; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197463","197463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49515","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints about abortion clinics were made to the Care Quality Commission in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197439","197439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49516","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the results were of the Metropolitan Police investigation into the death of an unnamed woman in Slough on 21 January 2012 following an abortion performed by Marie Stopes International.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197461","197461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49517","2014-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications of an increase in the need for court reports arising from his Transforming Rehabilitation agenda on the workload of court staff.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197523","197523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49518","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a cap on data charges which can be imposed by mobile telephone operators.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197560","197560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49519","2014-05-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the decision was made to embark on an expansion of the Public Defender System advocates.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197516","197516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49520","2014-05-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress has been made on the review of partnership funding for flood defences; and when the results of this review will be published.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197579","197579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49521","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the future of community hospitals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197580","197580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49522","2014-05-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his department's policies of the findings of The Armed Forces & Society survey produced by Lord Ashcroft.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197613","197613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49523","2014-05-07","Department for Education","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of history lessons were taught by non-subject specialists in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197546","197546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49524","2014-05-07","Department for Education","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of secondary school students who studied the First World War as part of their (a) GCSE and (b) A-level studies in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197547","197547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49525","2014-05-07","Department for Education","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of secondary school students who studied the Second World War as part of their (a) GCSE and (b) A-level studies in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197548","197548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49526","2014-05-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of children aged under 16 years living in supported housing.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197549","197549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49527","2014-05-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received from HM Chief Inspector of Prisons about his plans to introduce secure colleges.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197550","197550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49528","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received from Ofsted on his plans to introduce secure colleges.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197625","197625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49529","2014-05-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of levels of public support for solar photovoltaic; and if he will make it his policy that there will be no changes to the level of support available for large-scale solar under the Renewable Obligation scheme until at least April 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197578","197578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49530","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of Child Support Agency cases subject to case closure which have child maintenance arrears based wholly or partly on an interim maintenance assessment; and what steps he is taking to re-evaluate the amount of arrears owed and to inform the non-resident parent and parent with care accordingly.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197481","197481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49531","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how often powers in the Child Support Information Regulations 2008 to require suppliers of gas and electricity to (a) provide the Child Support Agency with information to confirm the whereabouts of a non-resident parent and (b) obtain account information to assist enforcement action to recover child maintenance arrears have been used to date.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197482","197482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49532","2014-05-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims to the Independent Living Fund of what total value were made in each parliamentary constituency in the last year.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197483","197483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49533","2014-05-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of recipients of the Independent Living Fund (a) are in employment and (b) were in employment at the date of application.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197574","197574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49534","2014-05-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on the viability of public houses of the method by which business rates are currently calculated.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197572","197572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49535","2014-05-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department gives local authorities on considering the potential flooding risks to land in neighbouring local authorities when making planning decisions.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197573","197573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49536","2014-05-07","Department of Health","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each NHS trust and foundation trust spent on legal costs on individual employment cases in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197595","197595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49537","2014-05-07","Department of Health","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on making the term surgeon a protected title.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197513","197513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49538","2014-05-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Environment Agency expects to conclude its investigation into Churngold Recycling Ltd.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197571","197571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49539","2014-05-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Nigerian counterpart on the recent kidnapping of schoolgirls from Chibok, Nigeria.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197470","197470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49540","2014-05-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the current whereabouts of the children recently kidnapped from Chibok, Nigeria.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197469","197469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49541","2014-05-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what requests for assistance the Government has received in connection with the recent kidnappings from Chibok, Nigeria.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197472","197472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49542","2014-05-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions either orally or in writing he or his Ministers or officials in his Department have had with (a) Pfizer and (b) AstraZeneca in the last two months regarding any bid for AstraZeneca.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197493","197493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49543","2014-05-07","Prime Minister","2014-05-01","To ask the Prime Minister, what criteria he used to select those who he has instructed to review any bid for AstraZeneca.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197491","197491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49544","2014-05-07","Prime Minister","2014-05-01","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions either orally or in writing he or his Ministers or officials have had with (a) Pfizer and (b) AstraZeneca in the last two months regarding any bid for AstraZeneca.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197492","197492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49545","2014-05-07","Department of Health","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff are employed in (a) his Department, (b) NHS England and (c) Monitor to undertake work on or relating to competition issues; and what the cost of employing such staff was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197535","197535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49546","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that resources for mental health services meet the requirements of both adults and children.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197541","197541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49547","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that zero-hour contracts are not used in an exploitative manner.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197555","197555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49548","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to ensure that school lunches in academies and free schools meet the nutritional standards of those in the state sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197552","197552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49549","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to implement the recommendations of the Prison and Probation Ombudsman's (PPO) report on Learning from PPO Investigations: Risk factors in self-inflicted deaths in prisons.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197587","197587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49550","2014-05-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions the Prison Service Gold Command has been opened in each of the last 36 months; and what the nature was of each incident that caused it to be opened.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197468","197468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49551","2014-05-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his most recent estimate is of the average cost of housing an individual in (a) a probation hostel and (b) approved premises for 12 months.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197611","197611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49552","2014-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court buildings which were not counted as closed had fewer than five cases listed for each week in the preceding (a) three, (b) six and (c) 12 months at 31 March 2014; and what the location was of each such building.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197539","197539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49553","2014-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court buildings which were not counted as closed had no cases listed in the preceding (a) three, (b) six and (c) 12 months at 31 March 2014; and what the location was of each such building.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197536","197536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49554","2014-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the public purse of maintaining court buildings which are not listed as closed and which have no cases listed for (a) three, (b) six and (c) 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197537","197537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49555","2014-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the public purse of maintaining court buildings which are not listed as closed and which had fewer than five cases listed each week for (a) three, (b) six and (c) 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197538","197538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49781","2014-05-08","Department for Transport","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage safer cycling.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903904","903904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49797","2014-05-08","Department for Transport","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of Government policy on the level of car insurance premiums.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903899","903899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50200","2014-05-08","Department for Transport","2014-05-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve road safety for cyclists.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903890","903890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49175","2014-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy that a war widow's pension is provided for life to those awarded such a pension between 31 March 1973 and 5 April 2005.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197342","197342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49176","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential contribution of sustainable lighting systems to development in Africa; and if her Department will collaborate with Solar Aid to provide such systems to communities in Africa.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197345","197345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49177","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will provide support to the Bright Green Energy Group for distributing solar energy systems to rural communities in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197344","197344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49178","2014-05-06","Prime Minister","2014-04-30","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to his oral Answer of 30 April 2014, Official Report, column 824, what the evidential basis is for the statement that nuclear power is carbon-free.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197381","197381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49179","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with Israeli authorities on discrimination against UK citizens of Palestinian or Arab origin by Israeli border control.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197383","197383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49180","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Israeli government on extending to UK citizens of Palestinian origin visiting Israel similar concessions to those Israel has offered to the US administration in exchange for Israel's entry to the US visa waiver scheme.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197379","197379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49181","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned on diabulimia in teenagers and young adults.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197377","197377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49182","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the additional costs resulting from Israeli border, access and planning controls to UK-funded development projects in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197380","197380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49183","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the European Commission and her counterparts in EU member states on compensation requests to Israeli authorities for EU-funded aid projects demolished by the Israeli authorities.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197408","197408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49184","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications have been made in Oxfordshire under the National Assistance Act 1948 by people without resources to meet their requirements or whose resources must be supplemented in order to meet their requirements in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197243","197243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49185","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department publishes for pharmaceutical companies to ensure that the clinical trials they conduct are carried out ethically and safely.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197308","197308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49186","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many individual funding requests for the prescription of Duodopa to patients with Parkinson's disease were (a) made, (b) accepted, (c) accepted following an appeal and (d) rejected in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197325","197325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49187","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for a decision on an individual funding request for the prescription of Duodopa to a patient with Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197326","197326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49188","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of potential geographical variations in the handling of individual funding requests for the prescription of Duodopa to patients with Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197327","197327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49189","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of time spent by clinicians on producing and administering individual funding requests for the prescription of Duodopa to patients with Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197328","197328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49190","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the 100 most deprived wards as measured by the index of multiple deprivation are.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197424","197424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49191","2014-05-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-30","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the profile of the electors who were not data matched on (a) national government data bases and (b) local government data bases for purposes of individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197407","197407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49192","2014-05-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-30","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the merits of auto enrolment of young people at the time they are given their national insurance number.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197425","197425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49193","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people did not meet the 31 January 2014 deadline for making their tax return.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197291","197291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49194","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that as economic recovery takes hold proportionately more inward investment will be directed to areas beyond the South East.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197288","197288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49195","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints against GPs have resulted in a GP being struck off by the General Medical Council in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197289","197289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49196","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what level of assistance has been offered by UK personnel in efforts to locate the missing Malaysian airliner MH370.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197290","197290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49197","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the change has been in the number of passports which were (a) issued and (b) reported (i) lost and (ii) stolen between 2008 and 2013, by issuing passport office.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197287","197287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49198","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of support available to families with children with autism.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197412","197412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49199","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her priorities are for extending the scope of the National Crime Agency in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197414","197414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49200","2014-05-06","Northern Ireland Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will take steps to ensure the negotiations between her Department and Praxis result in the continuation of the Secret Garden Service provided by that organisation.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197413","197413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49201","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to bring forward regulations for the introduction of the ban on smoking in cars with children present.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197384","197384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49202","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to bring forward draft regulations for the introduction of standard packaging for tobacco products.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197385","197385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49203","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the St Lucia government on delays in the criminal justice system in homicide cases in that country.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197360","197360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49204","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he is making to encourage the government of St Lucia to take steps to progress the trial of the defendants accused of murdering Gloria Greenwood.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197361","197361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49205","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers were serving on detached duty in each month from January 2011 to January 2014.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197293","197293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49206","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent by his Department on travel and accommodation costs for prison officers serving on detached duty in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197294","197294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49207","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff in each prison in England and Wales were serving on detached duty in (a) January, (b) February and (c) March 2014.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197292","197292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49208","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) representatives or organisations offering free debt advice, (b) representatives of fee charging debt management organisations, (c) creditors and (d) the Insolvency Service on the potential effect of his Department's withdrawal from the Debt Management Plan Protocol guidance group.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197276","197276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49209","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason his Department will no longer participate in the Debt Management Plan Protocol guidance group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197277","197277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49210","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the future implementation of the Debt Management Plan Protocol.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197278","197278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49211","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's withdrawal from the Debt Management Plan Protocol guidance group on the development of future non-statutory debt solutions.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197279","197279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49212","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which meetings or telephone calls have taken place between Ministers and officials in his Department and (a) the Abu Dhabi Investment Authority, (b) BlackRock, (c) Capital Research, (d) Fidelity Worldwide, (e) GIC, (f) Henderson, (g) JP Morgan, (h) Kuwait Investment Office, (i) Lansdowne Partners, (j) Lazard Asset Management, (k) Och Ziff, Schroders, (l) Soros, (m) Standard Life, (n) Third Point and (o) Threadneedle since 2010 and what was discussed in any such discussions.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197329","197329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49213","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings or telephone calls have taken place between Ministers and officials in his Department with (a) the Abu Dhabi Investment Authority, (b) BlackRock, (c) Capital Research, (d) Fidelity Worldwide, (e) GIC, (f) Henderson, (g) JP Morgan, (h) Kuwait Investment Office, (i) Lansdowne Partners, (j) Lazard Asset Management, (k) Och Ziff, Schroders, (l) Soros, (m) Standard Life, (n) Third Point and (o) Threadneedle in relation to the flotation of the Royal Mail since May 2010; and what was discussed in such meetings.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197339","197339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49214","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which priority investors in Royal Mail have subsequently sold all or part of their holdings of shares since the date of flotation; and what estimate he has made of the level of profits made in each case.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197387","197387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49215","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on how many UK citizens are not being paid those Zimbabwean government pensions to which they are entitled; and what steps the UK Government is taking to end that default.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197409","197409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49216","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when officials of his Department in Harare last met the Zimbabwean government director of pensions to discuss distribution of the funds reserved for payment to overseas pensioners; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197410","197410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49217","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date officials of his Department were informed that arrangements had failed for a commercial bank to facilitate payments to overseas pensioners out of funds reserved by the government of Zimbabwe; and when he expects an alternative service provider to be in place.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197411","197411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49218","2014-05-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding the UK has given (a) directly and (b) indirectly to the European Space Agency in each of the last five years; what that funding was for; and what assessment he has made of the benefits arising from that funding to the UK.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197364","197364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49219","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of local authorities have higher than average not known rates for young people not in employment, education or training; and what steps he is taking to address such gaps in data.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197255","197255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49220","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to ensure that governors are disqualified when a school governing body is found guilty of disability discrimination.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197246","197246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49221","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what advice his Department provides to local authorities when a school governing body is found guilty of disability discrimination.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197247","197247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49222","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received on extending the powers provided to the National College for Teaching and Leadership for the investigation of historical incidents of abuse; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197270","197270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49223","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to implement the recommendations on support for the reading skills of oral deaf children in the Reading, Dyslexia and Oral Deaf Children report published by City University and the Nuffield Foundation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197272","197272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49224","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of sixth form colleges on the effects of reductions in education funding for 18 year olds on students with severe or complex disabilities.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197273","197273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49225","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effects of reductions in education funding for 18 year olds on students with severe or complex disabilities and who attend specialist schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197274","197274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49226","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools which cater for students with severe or complex disabilities have indicated to his Department that they plan to reduce provision for such students since December 2013; and what reasons have been given for these plans.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197275","197275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49227","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reason the empty home premium starts when a property first becomes empty rather than when a property is bought with the intention of renovating and occupying it.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197269","197269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49228","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of those classified disabled were seeking work in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197250","197250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49229","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average extra costs are incurred by disabled people as a result of their disability.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197251","197251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49230","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people classified as disabled left work as a result of their disability; and how many such people entered new work in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197252","197252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49231","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many schoolgirls were abducted in Chibok in north-eastern Nigeria on 14 April 2014; and what reports he has received on their current location.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197334","197334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49232","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss the abduction of schoolgirls in Chibok in north-eastern Nigeria on 14 April 2014 at the next European Union meeting of Foreign Ministers.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197335","197335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49233","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last discussed with his Nigerian counterpart the recent abduction of schoolgirls in that country; and when he next intends to raise this issue.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197337","197337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49234","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the Nigernian government in its efforts to protect schools in north-eastern Nigeria and to re-open schools that have closed for security reasons.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197336","197336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49235","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England will publish a tariff for stereotactic ablative radiotherapy.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197266","197266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49236","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress NHS England is making on improving access to stereotactic ablative radiotherapy for patients suffering with cancer of the prostate, liver, pancreas, spinal tumours and cancer of the head and neck.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197267","197267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49237","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to encourage NHS England to respond to the Oxford Radiosurgery Centre's request that NHS patients in Oxfordshire and surrounding counties who require radiosurgery be treated there.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197268","197268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49238","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been sent to hospitals in London for stereotactic radiosurgery treatment from (a) Oxfordshire, (b) Berkshire, (c) Buckinghamshire and (d) Wiltshire in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197271","197271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49239","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been sent to hospitals in Sheffield for stereotactic radiosurgery treatment from (a) Oxfordshire, (b) Berkshire, (c) Buckinghamshire and (d) Wiltshire in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197263","197263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49240","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 132W, on radiotherapy and with reference to section three of the guidance issued by Monitor on the Commissioning of Radiosurgery Services on 4 April 2014, which primary care trusts in the south west of England commissioned treatment with the Gamma Knife at University College London Hospital for patients before 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197298","197298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49241","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 132W, on radiotherapy and with reference to section three of the guidance issued by Monitor on the Commissioning of Radiosurgery Services on 4 April 2014, for what reasons NHS England is not funding patients to be treated with the Gamma Knife at University College London Hospital.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197299","197299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49242","2014-05-07","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average cost of a primary school meal was in 2013.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197434","197434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49243","2014-05-07","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many childcare places for disadvantaged two year olds have been created since September 2013.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197435","197435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49244","2014-05-07","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of additional catering staff needed in schools to deliver the extension of free school meals to all pupils in reception, year 1 and year 2 in September 2014.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197436","197436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49245","2014-05-07","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of the 20 per cent most disadvantaged two year olds who are currently taking up their free childcare place.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197433","197433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49246","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of whether to become a signatory to the UNESCO Convention on Underwater Cultural Heritage and the International Law of the Sea.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197238","197238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49247","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the letter dated 5 March 2014 from the Minister of State for Pensions to the hon. Member for Cardiff South and Penarth, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to make national insurance credits available for past periods for service spouses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197415","197415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49248","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the letter dated 5 March 2014 from the Minister of State for Pensions to the hon. Member for Cardiff South and Penarth, what estimate he has made of the number of service spouses who will be affected by his plans to bring forward legislative proposals to make national insurance credits available for past periods for service spouses.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197416","197416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49249","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he will next meet representatives of energy-intensive industries to discuss the EU Commission's draft Environmental and Energy State Aid Guidelines.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197358","197358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49250","2014-05-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many manufacturers of sub-15KW wind turbines are based in the UK; and what the value of exports from this sector was in 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197240","197240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49251","2014-05-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total cost was of support under the feed-in-tariff for (a) solar, (b) wind, (c) anaerobic digestion, (d) hydro and (e) the sub-15KW wind sector in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197241","197241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49252","2014-05-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to tariff levels and degression thresholds outlined in Phase 2B of the feed-in-tariff on manufacturing and employment in the sub-15KW wind sector.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197242","197242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49253","2014-05-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many turbines of capacity of sub-15KW were installed in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197244","197244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49254","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the reasons are for the time taken to answer question 191956 tabled for answer on 8 April 2014.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197366","197366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49255","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 194894, tabled for answer on 8 April 2014.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197367","197367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49256","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 April 2014, Official Report, column 677W, on VAT, how many VAT431C claims have been submitted in each of the (a) last eight years and (b) smallest time periods by which data is kept over the last eight years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197388","197388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49257","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 April 2014, Official Report, column 677W, on VAT, how many VAT431NB claims have been submitted in each of the (a) last eight years and (b) smallest time periods by which data is kept over the last eight years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197389","197389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49258","2014-05-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-30","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2014, Official Report, column 418W, on the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014, when the Electoral Commission will have finalised its guidance on the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014; and how many charities (a) have been and (b) will be consulted in the compilation of that guidance.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197395","197395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49259","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pregnant women in Scotland were granted section 4 support under the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 for reasons including that they were deemed unfit to travel in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197399","197399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49260","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pregnant women in Scotland are in receipt of section 4 support under the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999; how many such women were moved to different accommodation during pregnancy; how many weeks pregnant each such woman was when she was moved; what the reason for each such move was; and if a risk assessment of each such move was undertaken which included input from a treating clinician.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197427","197427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49261","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Brent Central of 31 March 2014, Official Report, column 411W on asylum, what the (a) gender and (b) age of each applicant represented in the table in Scotland was; and whether each such applicant had (i) family and (ii) dependants in Scotland.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197426","197426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49262","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the length of time was between the date of application by each pregnant woman in Scotland for section 4 support under the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 and the date of receipt by the applicant of that support.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197431","197431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49263","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pregnant woman in Scotland were denied section 4 support under the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 for reasons that included an assessment that they were fit to travel; and what the gestation stage of each such woman was when that decision was made in each of the five years to 2013-14.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197432","197432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49264","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, at what gestation stage each pregnant women in Scotland granted section 4 support under the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 received the decision to grant that support.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197400","197400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49265","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library a copy of all guidance and benchmarking criteria used by her Department, its contractors and agents when assessing the adequacy and suitability of placement accommodation allocated to pregnant women and nursing mothers in receipt of section 4 support under the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197401","197401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49266","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to ensure that pregnant women and nursing mothers in receipt of section 4 support under the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 are recognised as a vulnerable group when contracting and allocating placement accommodation.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197402","197402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49267","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will take steps to ensure that revenue created by shops in publicly-funded museums and galleries will be safeguarded following the repeal of section 52 of the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act 1988.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197351","197351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49268","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will take steps to ensure that publicly-funded museums do not breach new rules regarding the commercial exploitation of designs whose owners have had their rights revived following the repeal of section 52 of the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act 1988.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197349","197349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49269","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Intellectual Property Office's response to its call for evidence on the effect of the repeal of section 52 of the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act 1988 will be published.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197350","197350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49270","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure a smooth and effective transitional period for the repeal of section 52 of the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act 1988.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197352","197352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49271","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 237W, on large goods vehicles: speed limits, what progress has been made on the Government's further impact assessment of increasing the speed limit for hauliers from 40mph to 50mph.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197362","197362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49272","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2014, Official Report, column 242W, on tractors, if his Department will issue a response to the consultation on raising speed limits for low-speed tractors from 20mph to 25mph.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197363","197363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49273","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS England spent on tendering for clinical services in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197353","197353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49274","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much (a) NHS England, (b) Clinical Commissioning Groups, (c) Commissioning Support Units and (d) Monitor spent on consultancy workers in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197320","197320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49275","2014-05-06","Attorney General","2014-04-30","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 29 April 2014, Official Report, column 540W, on pornography: internet, how many prosecutions there have been under section 2 of the Obscene Publications Act 1959 since 2005 in which a person has been charged in connection with the distribution of R18 equivalent material on a website which allowed under-18s to see such material.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197390","197390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49276","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce exit checks to apply to non-scheduled international travel by air, sea and rail services.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197253","197253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49277","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) meetings she or Ministers in her Department have had with and (b) representations she has received from Kalayaan on tied domestic workers visas.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197249","197249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49278","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been removed from the UK under the Dublin Convention in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197239","197239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49279","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions probation staff have taken cases to employment tribunals on grounds of discrimination in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197347","197347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49280","2014-05-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the current contract for the post of Chief of Defence Materiel ends; and if he will make it his policy that the post of Chief Executive of Defence Equipment and Support be no longer merged with this post at that time.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197331","197331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49281","2014-05-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many journeys in the UK using (a) domestic helicopter services and (b) military helicopters were made by (i) the Chief of Defence Materiel and (ii) Ministers in his Department in each of the last four years; and what the annual cost has been of such journeys.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197324","197324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49282","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what powers the Child Maintenance Service has to address non-compliance by employers with a notice of deduction of earnings; and how many cases have there been of such non-compliance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197378","197378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49283","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department will take to engage with smaller (a) international non-government organisations and (b) non-governmental organisations in its future work on disability.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197330","197330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49284","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make accessibility and coverage of disability a core element of all her Department's funded programmes and monitor this across all currently funded programmes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197332","197332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49285","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many full-time equivalent staff in her Department have responsibility for disability policy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197333","197333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49286","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take in response to the withdrawal of the Israeli government from US-sponsored peace negotiations with the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197316","197316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49287","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the demolition on 2 and 3 April of EU-funded projects in Area C near the E1-settlement bloc; and whether he has demanded compensation following these actions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197317","197317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49288","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department gives alongside UK non-governmental organisations operating in the Occupied Palestinian Territories to assist in obtaining compensation from the Israeli authorities for projects demolished in Area C.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197319","197319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49289","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total cost of the feasibility studies for the (a) A303, A30 and A358 corridor, (b) A1 north of Newcastle, (c) A1 Newcastle to Gateshead western bypass, (d) A27 corridor and (e) A47.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197318","197318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49290","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Statement of 17 March 2014, Official Report, columns 53-4WS, on the Higgins Review, whether the review of connections from HS2 to the Continent announced in that statement will assure the provision of (a) a segregated double track link and (b) any other dedicated railway link between HS1 and HS2.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197418","197418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49291","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Statement of 17 March 2014, Official Report, columns 53-4WS, on the Higgins Review, what progress has been made on the review of connections from HS2 to the Continent announced in that Statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197417","197417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49292","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Statement of 17 March 2014, Official Report, columns 53-4WS, on the Higgins Review, whether the review of connections from HS2 to the Continent announced in that statement will take account of potential demand for domestic services between HS2 and HS1; and what assessment he has made of the likely level of such demand.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197419","197419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49293","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Statement of 17 March 2014, Official Report, columns 53-4WS, on the Higgins Review, who is undertaking the review of connections between HS2 and the Continent announced in that Statement; and when he expects the review to be completed.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197420","197420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49294","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library a code of practice on the circumstances in which recovery action will be taken for overpayments of universal credit, jobseeker's allowance and employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197338","197338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49295","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2014, Official Report, column 411W, on families: advisory services, how many couples were eligible for the relationship support trial (a) overall and (b) in each pilot area; how many couples took part in each such trial area; and what the underspend in the project has been spent on.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197313","197313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49296","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on the public funds available to local authorities of the creation of a Single Fraud Investigation Service.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197304","197304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49297","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answers of 29 April 2014, Official Report, columns 559-60W and column 560W, on schools: inspections, for what reason local authorities are inspected separately from schools maintained by local authorities but academies are not inspected separately from the head offices of academy chains.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197382","197382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49298","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure the retention of (a) rural post offices and (b) jobs in rural post offices.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197428","197428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49299","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward proposals to enable small businesses to claim a rates reduction to help them retain staff.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197429","197429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49300","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of China on the persecution of Christians in (a) Zhejiang Province and (b) elsewhere in eastern China.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197398","197398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49301","2014-05-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of black-backed gulls.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197396","197396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49302","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Iraq on its proposal to legalise the marriage of girls from nine years of age.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197397","197397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49303","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of premature deaths per year attributable to air pollution from diesel-fuelled vehicles; and what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges about ways of reducing such deaths.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197406","197406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49304","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on whether the use of painkillers increases the risk of a stroke.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197403","197403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49305","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on whether the use of shellfish supplements increases life expectancy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197404","197404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49306","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) the Royal Colleges and (b) pharmaceutical companies about the efficacy of anti-depressants.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197405","197405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49307","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) disability living allowance have died during the process of (i) assessment and (ii) appeal in the latest period in which figures are available.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197430","197430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49308","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise awareness among health professionals of the symptoms of brain tumours and their effects on children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197264","197264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49309","2014-05-06","Cabinet Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the five most common causes of infant mortality have been over the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197265","197265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49310","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) purpose and (b) cost of international travel undertaken for official purposes by (i) directors of Public Health England and (ii) members of its advisory board has been since 1 April 2012.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197368","197368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49311","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Public Health England has spent on the development and implementation of its Global Health Strategy since its inception.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197369","197369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49312","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many of his Department's agencies, non-departmental public bodies or sponsored bodies have developed their own global health strategies.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197370","197370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49313","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Public Health England has spent on consultancy workers in 2013-14.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197371","197371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49314","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the running costs are for each of the academic health science networks.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197372","197372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49315","2014-05-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to publish in full all monitoring data collected on the second year of the pilot badger culls in Gloucestershire and Somerset.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197283","197283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49316","2014-05-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he plans to take to ensure that he receives independent scientific advice on the safety, effectiveness and humaneness of the second year of the badger cull pilots in Gloucestershire and Somerset.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197284","197284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49317","2014-05-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what arrangements he plans to put in place to ensure that monitoring data collected on the second year of the pilot badger culls in Gloucestershire and Somerset is made available for independent scientific evaluation and analysis; and if he will make it his policy to receive and consider the conclusions of that analysis prior to deciding whether the culls should be extended to other areas subsequently.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197285","197285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49318","2014-05-08","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many HSA4 forms submitted in each month since 2010 are pending completion.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197391","197391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49319","2014-05-08","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the ability of non-registered medical professionals to gauge mental or physical health risks posed by a pregnancy for the purpose of judging whether or not the criteria of the Abortion Act 1967 are met.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197392","197392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49320","2014-05-08","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on reporting to the police suspected criminal acts committed by doctors that are discovered by his Department and NHS England.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197393","197393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49321","2014-05-08","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors were referred to the police for investigation for crimes relating to the Abortion Act 1967 in each of the last 10 years; and how many such referrals resulted in (a) charges and (b) convictions.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197394","197394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49322","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total yearly salary of each grade of the UK Visa and Immigration Directorate senior staff was on 1 April 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197260","197260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49323","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were employed by the UK Visa and Immigration Directorate on 1 April 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197261","197261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49324","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what budget is allocated to the UK Visa and Immigration Directorate.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197262","197262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49325","2014-05-06","Cabinet Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the total number of (a) private, (b) public and (c) third sector jobs in (a) Ashfield constituency, (ii) Nottinghamshire and (iii) the East Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197305","197305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49326","2014-05-06","Cabinet Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed in the construction sector in (a) the UK, (b) the East Midlands, (c) Nottinghamshire and (d) Ashfield constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197307","197307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49327","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate his Department has made of the level of unscrupulous money lending in (a) the UK, (b) East Midlands, (c) Nottinghamshire and (d) Ashfield in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197321","197321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49328","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in Ashfield constituency were homeless in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197256","197256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49329","2014-05-06","Women and Equalities","2014-04-30","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, which organisations have been awarded funding to conduct a review into homophobic, biphobic and transphobic bullying in schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197302","197302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49330","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of levels of self-harm in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) the East Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197245","197245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49331","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) nurses, (b) doctors and (c) surgeons have been employed at (i) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (ii) Nottingham University Hospitals in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197257","197257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49332","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many motorists were prosecuted for speeding offences in (a) Nottinghamshire and (b) Ashfield constituency in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197306","197306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49333","2014-05-06","Women and Equalities","2014-04-30","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, columns 578-9W, on equality, how many companies responded to the recent survey of companies participating in the Think Act, Report initiative; and what information her Department holds on which companies participating in that initiative (a) have conducted a gender pay audit in the last two years and (b) publish detailed gender pay gap information for each grade.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197286","197286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49334","2014-05-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he will answer question 188564 tabled on 13 February 2014 for Answer on 24 February 2014, and question 188387 tabled on 12 February 2014 for Answer on 26 February 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197346","197346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49335","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) inspections, (b) findings of non-compliance, (c) prosecutions and (d) convictions have been handled by HM Revenue and Customs to non-payment of the minimum wage in each region in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197359","197359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49336","2014-05-06","Attorney General","2014-04-30","To ask the Attorney General, how many cases of non-payment of the minimum wage were (a) referred to the Crown Prosecution Service from HM Revenue and Customs, (b) prosecuted and (c) prosecuted successfully in 2013-14 and each of the preceding three financial years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197340","197340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49337","2014-05-06","Attorney General","2014-04-30","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Crown Prosecution Service (CPS) has spent on staff overtime payments in each CPS area in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197280","197280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49338","2014-05-06","Attorney General","2014-04-30","To ask the Attorney General, whether the Serious Fraud Office has applied to HM Treasury for additional funding for its investigation into the Eurasian Natural Resources Corporation.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197281","197281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49339","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which countries the UK has asset sharing agreements for the purposes of freezing, confiscating and repatriating the proceeds of crime; and how many such agreements have been reached since 2010-11.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197341","197341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49341","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) elective and (b) emergency admissions with a (i) primary and (ii) secondary diagnosis of diabetes there have been in (A) England and (B) each commissioning area of responsibility; and what proportion of such admissions were of (1) a child under the age of 18 and (2) an adult aged 18 and over in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197348","197348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49342","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answers of 18 March 2014, Official Report, column 638, on Freedom of Information Act, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to designate the RSPCA as a public authority for the purposes of the Freedom of Information Act 2000; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197248","197248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49343","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of local authorities in England and Wales have plans in place for tackling potential child sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197312","197312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49344","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of urgent repairs to roads managed by the Highways Agency in (a) Huddersfield constituency, (b) Kirklees and (c) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197282","197282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49345","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many directions under section 94 of the Telecommunications Act 1984 have been issued, amended or renewed in this Parliament.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197254","197254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49346","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many private abortion clinics are situated on the premises of NHS hospitals in England; and how many such clinics are run by (a) BPAS and (b) Marie Stopes International.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197322","197322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49347","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time is between a defendant being charged and the first day of proceedings in court in cases of (a) domestic violence, (b) sexual abuse and (c) rape.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197386","197386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49348","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on allowing doctors and nurses who have a conscientious objection to supplying contraceptive drugs or devices which act after fertilisation to receive diplomas in sexual and reproductive health.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197301","197301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49349","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the Faculty of Sexual and Reproductive Health of the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists acts to accommodate doctors and nurses who have a conscientious objection to supplying contraceptive drugs or devices which act after fertilisation receive a diploma in sexual and reproductive health.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197373","197373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49350","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many summons for non-payment of council tax have been issued by each local authority in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197259","197259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49351","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much he has allocated to each local authority with responsibility for education to expand kitchens in order to provide free school meals for children under seven.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197258","197258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49352","2014-05-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to encourage car manufacturers to manufacture cars powered by road fuel gases for the UK market.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197296","197296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49353","2014-05-08","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information later than 2003 his Department has on the relative emissions from motor vehicles powered by road fuel gases.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197297","197297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49354","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to address the lack of compulsory dermatological training in the GP educational pathway.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197365","197365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49355","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with (a) Health Education England and (b) the Royal College of GPs on compulsory dermatological training for GPs since 4 December 2013.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197303","197303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49356","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the licensing of e-cigarettes.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197421","197421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49357","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has given consideration to licensing e-cigarettes as medicines.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197422","197422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49358","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will put restrictions in place to prevent the promotion of e-cigarettes to people under the age of 16 years.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197423","197423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49359","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on which occasions performance points were accrued by private prisons in 2013-14; for what reason the points were accrued; and what financial penalties were attached in each case.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197355","197355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49360","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what financial penalties have been levied against those running private prisons in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197356","197356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49361","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, at how many tribunal hearings on appeals over benefit claims in each of the last four years the relevant Department failed to send a presenting officer; and how many such hearings were lost by the Government.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197357","197357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49362","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) assaults and (b) serious assaults on staff per 1,000 prisoners there were in each prison in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197354","197354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49363","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the document Annual Bus Statistics: Revenue, Costs and Government Support Great Britain 2012-13 will be published.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197314","197314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49364","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much in each (a) funding stream and (b) region his Department has provided in subsidy to each bus operator in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197315","197315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49365","2014-05-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 37W, on rural areas: broadband, what the latest figures are for how much funding is for projects (a) granted, (b) under pre-contract approval and (c) still under consideration for funding.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197295","197295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49366","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the cases of the 67 doctors who were found to have pre-signed abortion referral forms following investigations by the Care Quality Commission in 2012 are referred to the police.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197311","197311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49367","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of regulatory changes allowing registered medical practitioners to form an opinion about the mental or physical health of a female patient without meeting or examining her; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197310","197310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49368","2014-05-06","Attorney General","2014-04-30","To ask the Attorney General, what discussions he has had with the Crown Prosecution Service about the pre-signing of abortion forms.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197309","197309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49369","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms his Department has in place to monitor standards in care homes for the elderly.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197374","197374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49370","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the use of CCTV in care homes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197375","197375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49371","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms are in place to allow families of patients in care homes to report concerns about standards of care.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197376","197376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49372","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the quality and content of advice published by independent abortion providers accords with that of his Department and the Royal colleges.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197323","197323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49373","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax has been collected from insolvency litigation (a) through the Specialist Investigation Unit and (b) in all other insolvency litigation cases handled by HM Revenue and Customs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197343","197343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49374","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of how much tax will be collected annually from insolvency litigation following reforms to insolvency litigation through the 2012 Legal, Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197300","197300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49636","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his Department's priorities are for provisions to be included in the forthcoming Modern Slavery Bill.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903852","903852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49662","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to ensure that assets of human traffickers are frozen within 48 hours of their arrest; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903856","903856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49663","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to expand the boundaries of the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903862","903862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49664","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on ensuring that legal aid is targeted at people with a strong connection to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Rob Wilson","Mr Rob Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903845","903845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48906","2014-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any restrictions exist in (a) Wales, (b) Scotland and (c) Northern Ireland on upland farms contaminated by radioactive fallout from the Chernobyl nuclear accident in April 1986.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196981","196981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48907","2014-05-01","Prime Minister","2014-04-29","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 28 April 2014, Official Report, column 473W, on Pakistan, whether Pakistan's possession of nuclear weapons and the prospects of Pakistan joining the Nuclear Non-proliferation Treaty were discussed at his 30 April 2014 meeting with the Prime Minister of Pakistan.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197010","197010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48908","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families in (a) London, (b) Hounslow Borough and (c) Brentford and Isleworth constituency, will benefit from the Government's tax free childcare policy.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197018","197018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48909","2014-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Environment Agency is taking to reduce the time taken to update its flooding maps after the completion of flood defence projects.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197043","197043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48910","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the palliative care service ratings for England were in the most recent period for which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197032","197032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48911","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost of seeing a dentist was in England in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197042","197042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48912","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the case for abolishing prescription charges in England.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197041","197041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48913","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a maximum charge for homecare and other non-residential social services.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197039","197039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48914","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the percentage change in the number of NHS beds in England was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197040","197040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48915","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nursing staff were in post in each year since 1999.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197121","197121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48916","2014-05-01","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-29","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what advice the Electoral Commission has given to electoral registration officers on the necessity of conducting local government data matching for the purposes of transition to individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197127","197127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48917","2014-05-01","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-29","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2014, Official Report, columns 305-6W, on electoral register, if the Electoral Commission will start to collect the number of visits that ERO's staff make to individual non-responding households as part of their activities to maintain the electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197057","197057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48918","2014-05-01","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-29","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 766W, on electoral register, in which cases numbers of electors registered to vote in the transition from individual electoral registration will be monitored at an electoral ward level.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197056","197056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48919","2014-05-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to put in place an inspection regime for the quality of education at private further education colleges.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196977","196977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48920","2014-05-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the budget for further education was in 2005-06.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197009","197009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48921","2014-05-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions on climate change he has had with his counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197015","197015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48922","2014-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Islington of 2 September 2013, Official Report, columns 294-5W, on Israel, what recent steps he has taken to raise allegations of corporate complicity in human rights abuses and international law violations by G4S in Israeli prisons with G4S.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197161","197161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48923","2014-05-01","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure the viability of the financial position of the North East Refugee Service; and for what reasons her Department has not yet paid exit costs to that organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197162","197162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48924","2014-05-08","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential benefits and risks of commercial mobile networks providing the emergency services communications network.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197008","197008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48925","2014-05-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what legislative vehicles the Government plans to use to implement the proposals to streamline regulatory and competition appeals.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197007","197007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48926","2014-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of the introduction of unbundled fibre to the cabinet and sub-loop bundling of residential broadband provision.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197016","197016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48927","2014-05-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will initiate a review of the fibre broadband wholesale pricing structure.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197017","197017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48929","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what incentives his Department has made available to small and medium-sized businesses to take on apprentices.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197164","197164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48930","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he has taken to encourage manufacturing in the UK since May 2010.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197138","197138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48931","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal measures he has taken to encourage small and medium-sized businesses in the UK since May 2010.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197139","197139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48932","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many berths are assigned to Royal Marines on board the (a) Queen Elizabeth Carriers, (b) Type 45 and (c) Type 26.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197060","197060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48933","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the dimensions will be of the cargo lifts on the (a) Queen Elizabeth Class carriers and (b) Type 26 Global Combat Ships.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197132","197132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48934","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the long-term future of the Puma helicopter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197133","197133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48935","2014-05-01","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial provision he is making available to schools in Bournemouth for expansion of kitchens to provide free school meals for under sevens.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197129","197129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48936","2014-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the average waiting times for (a) personal independence payments assessments and (b) work capability assessments conducted by Atos in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland and (iii) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196987","196987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48937","2014-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recovery actions in respect of child support arrears owed to the parent residing in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency were (a) commenced, (b) concluded successfully and (c) suspended in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196988","196988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48938","2014-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of households in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency whose incomes from benefits payments have reduced by (i) 10 per cent, (ii) between 20 and 49 per cent and (iii) 50 per cent or more since May 2010.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196989","196989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48939","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the recent decision by the Faculty of Sexual and Reproductive Health of the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists (RCOG) to refuse to allow doctors who have a conscientious objection to supplying certain abortive-type contraceptive drugs or devices to undertake and complete specialist training with the aim of gaining Membership of the Faculty of Sexual and Reproductive Healthcare of the RCOG.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197137","197137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48940","2014-05-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many complaints the Advertising Standards Authority has received about letting agencies failing to advertise their fees since November 2013.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197128","197128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48941","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) improvement notices in accordance with section 11, (b) prohibition orders in accordance with section 20, (c) hazard awareness notices in accordance with section 28 and (d) emergency remedial actions under section 40 or emergency prohibition orders under section 43 of the Housing Act 2004 have been issued by local authorities in England following the discovery of a category 1 hazard during a housing health and safety rating system inspection in the private rented sector in the last year.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197159","197159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48942","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households in the private rented sector were evicted under section 8 of the Housing Act 2004 in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197160","197160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48943","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many complaints have been received by the Housing Ombudsman service in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197131","197131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48944","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households are housed by local authorities in the private rented sector on (a) two year long contracts, (b) three year long contracts and (c) contracts longer than three years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197126","197126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48945","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his plans are for the future of the disabled students' allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197154","197154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48946","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the final cost of the capital sum to be raised to finance High Speed 2 to (a) Birmingham and (b) Leeds and Manchester.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197014","197014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48947","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of staff members employed by contractors delivering the Work Programme are paid less than the living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197136","197136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48948","2014-05-01","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, by what methods the National College of Teaching Leadership gathers information on the risk of sexual abuse at independent schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197117","197117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48949","2014-05-01","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what role the National College of Teaching Leadership plays with regard to investigations of allegations of historic, sexual abuse at independent schools for which they are now responsible.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197118","197118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48950","2014-05-01","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps are open to the National College of Teaching Leadership on receipt of information of an allegation of child abuse at an independent school.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197119","197119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48951","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints have been received about the NHS in England and Wales in each of the last three years; and on what grounds such complaints have been made.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196978","196978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48952","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have declared income on their income tax returns from (a) rent from a residential property, (b) rent from a furnished holiday letting, (c) rent from commercial properties and (d) income under the Rent a Room Scheme in the last tax year.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196979","196979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48953","2014-05-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current establishment is of Joint Force Command.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197195","197195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48954","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to section 3 of the guidance issued by Monitor on the Commissioning of Radiosurgery Services on 4 April 2014, if NHS England will publish the details of all contracts it has signed with providers of radiosurgery services in England.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197025","197025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48955","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to section 3 of the guidance issued by Monitor on the Commissioning of Radiosurgery Services on 4 April 2014, if he will require NHS England to publish the names of all referring consultants, patients groups, charities and any other service providers it consulted prior to making its decision not to allow patients to be treated with the Gamma Knife at University College London Hospital.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197024","197024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48956","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to section 3 of the guidance issued by Monitor on the Commissioning of Radiosurgery Services on 4 April 2014, if he will require NHS England to publish the objective evidence on which it based its decision not to allow patients to be treated with the Gamma Knife at University College London Hospital.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197023","197023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48957","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many absconders there were at each UK airport in each year since 2010; and how many and what proportion of such absconders were subsequently recovered.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197140","197140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48958","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many illegal stills or other set ups for distilling or brewing alcohol have been found in each institution in the prison estate in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197141","197141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48959","2014-05-01","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools in Devon have (a) applied for and (b) received academy status since 2010.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197037","197037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48960","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on community engagement in tidal energy developments.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197031","197031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48961","2014-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on flood defences in each county in the south west of England since 2010.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197036","197036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48962","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the draft National Pollinator Strategy as it relates to planning.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197034","197034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48963","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what total private investment in rail has been in each region of the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197012","197012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48964","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what data his Department collects on private investment in (a) rail infrastructure and (b) rolling stock in each region.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197013","197013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48965","2014-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy either that carrier bags containing a defined percentage of recycled plastics should be exempt from a levy on plastic bags, or that there should be no such exemptions at all.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196982","196982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48966","2014-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will estimate the number of jobs supported by the recycled plastics industry.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196983","196983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48967","2014-05-01","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will require local police forces to cover the costs of police presence at Remembrance Sunday events.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196984","196984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48968","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the responses to the Office of Low Emission Vehicles construction from organisations that called for artificial sound generators to protect pedestrians.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197214","197214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48969","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 April 2014, Official Report, column 460W, on NHS England, with reference to the people referred to in the Answer who have taken up jobs at NHS England from his Department, what their job titles and salary levels (a) were at his Department and (b) are at NHS England.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197187","197187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48970","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what expenditure his Department incurred on the (a) Broadband Delivery Programme, (b) Mobile Infrastructure Project, (c) Spectrum Clearance and Awards Programme and (d) Urban Broadband Fund (Super-Connected City Initiative) in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15 to date; and what further expenditure on each of those projects it expects to incur in (A) the remainder of 2014-15, (B) 2015-16, (C) 2016-17, (D) 2017-18, (E) 2018-19 and (F) 2019-20.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197157","197157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48971","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2014, Official Report, column 367W, on the River Thames: bridges, in what year or years the 30 million allocated to the Garden Bridge in the National Infrastructure Plan 2013 is projected to be spent.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197053","197053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48972","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in which parliamentary constituency each onshore wind planning application which he has received for determination during this Parliament is located.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197001","197001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48973","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to emphasise the importance of education provisions and support for disabled children, their teachers and families in order to ensure that Millennium Development Goal 2 is attained.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197192","197192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48974","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that people (a) with disabilities and (b) affected by disabilities are given full consideration in the Sustainable Development Goals and their attendant targets and indicators.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197193","197193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48975","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that people with one or more physical, sensory, intellectual or mental health impairment are explicitly mentioned in the Sustainable Development Goals and their attendant targets and indicators.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197194","197194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48976","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to promote the rights of women with disabilities and to ensure such women are empowered and achieve gender equality to the same extent as women without disabilities.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197191","197191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48977","2014-05-06","Department for Transport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 107W, to question 194746, on large goods vehicles: taxation, how many HGVs 94 per cent of UK HGVs paying the HGV user levy represents.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197146","197146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48978","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funding is currently allocated to the Youth Contract; and what proportion of that funding is allocated for wage incentives.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197151","197151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48979","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been paid out in wage incentives under the Youth Contract, by region, in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197150","197150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48980","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have benefited from Youth Contract wage incentives, by region, in each year since the Youth Contract was introduced.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197147","197147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48981","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent on consultants working on the Youth Contract in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197148","197148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48982","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent on (a) press, (b) marketing, (c) advertising and (d) other aspects of communications relating to the Youth Contract in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197149","197149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48983","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2014, Official Report, columns 307-8W, on children: day care, what the breakdown is for the 500 grants available to set up new nurseries, childminders for disabled children and after schools clubs; how many of the 4,417 applicants continue to have a childcare business; and what plans he has for the funding of the scheme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197189","197189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48984","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to reply to questions 192679, 192680 and 192681 on children: daycare, tabled on 18 March 2014 for answer on 24 March 2014.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197155","197155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48985","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make representations to the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence regarding its technology appraisal of ipilimumab.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197033","197033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48986","2014-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the situation in North Korea.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197029","197029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48987","2014-05-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many new businesses have been registered in Swindon since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197030","197030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48988","2014-05-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage more women to franchise their businesses.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197026","197026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48989","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to extend Pulse Oximetry screening for children.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197116","197116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48990","2014-05-01","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps her Department has taken to tackle domestic abuse.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197028","197028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48991","2014-05-01","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials in his Department are employed on zero-hours contracts.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 107180","107180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48992","2014-05-01","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Agency staff in (a) Scotland, (b) England, (c) Wales, (d) Northern Ireland and (e) the UK were (i) on zero-hours contracts and (ii) temporary staff in each of the last two years up to the most recent period for which records are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 107179","107179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48993","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much remains outstanding in child maintenance arrears by (a) UK parliamentary constituency area and (b) local authority area in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197190","197190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48994","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to announce the allocation of additional support to local authorities in England to support corporate counter-fraud activity.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197204","197204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48995","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the level of support available for sufferers of post-traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196991","196991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48996","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of deaths  in (a) Portsmouth, (b) Hampshire and (c) the South East attributed to air pollution in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196992","196992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48997","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of post-traumatic stress disorder on the ability of former services personnel to reintegrate into civilian life.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196990","196990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48998","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many responses were received to his Department's consultation on extending civil partnerships to opposite sex couples.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197111","197111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48999","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish the responses to the consultation on extending civil partnerships to opposite sex couples.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197112","197112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49000","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to extend civil partnerships to opposite sex couples.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197113","197113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49001","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he took to publicise the consultation on extending civil partnerships to opposite sex partners.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197114","197114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49002","2014-05-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which hon. Members he consulted about the consultation on extension of civil partnerships to opposite sex couples.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197115","197115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49003","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the PCS Union on the future of HM Revenue and Customs Debt Management and Banking operations.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196985","196985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49004","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to privatise HM Revenue and Customs Debt Management and Banking operations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196986","196986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49005","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are employed by HM Revenue and Customs in regional post rooms at each location in the UK.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196997","196997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49006","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the number of staff required at HM Revenue and Customs in Cumbernauld following his Department's decision to award the mail management contract to the EDM Group.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196998","196998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49007","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consultation his Department had with HM Revenue and Customs staff prior to awarding the mail management contract to EDM Group.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196999","196999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49008","2014-05-06","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the savings to the public purse provided by the recent award of the mail management contract to the EDM Group.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197000","197000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49009","2014-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people made requests of the pension tracing service to find lost pension pots in each year since May 2010; and how many of these were successful.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197021","197021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49010","2014-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the average UK saver of delaying the pensions charge cap from April 2014 to April 2015.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197020","197020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49011","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of the emails sent by his Department to schools on 3 April 2014 setting out guidance on keeping children safe have not been opened by the recipient to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197110","197110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49012","2014-05-01","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department issues on what criteria schools should use when deciding whether to employ an individual who does not possess a formal teaching qualification as a teacher.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197035","197035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49013","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidelines cover preoperative pregnancy checks in (a) the NHS and (b) private medical institutions.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197019","197019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49014","2014-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings he has had with (a) representatives of the Colombian government, (b) Colombian civil society and (c) Colombian businesses to discuss his Department's Action Plan on Business and Human Rights since its launch in September 2013.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 107176","107176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49015","2014-05-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his assessment is of the effect of his Department's Action Plan on Business and Human Rights since its launch in September 2013.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197163","197163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49016","2014-05-01","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-04-29","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the oral Answer of 6 February 2014, Official Report, column 348W, on Colombia, which representatives of Colombian trades unions he met during his visit to Colombia in February 2014.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197173","197173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49017","2014-05-01","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-04-29","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the oral Answer of 6 February 2014, Official Report, column 348W, on Colombia, what discussions he held with (a) business, (b) government and (c) civil society representatives regarding the Foreign and Commonwealth Office Action Plan on Business and Human Rights during his visit to Colombia in February 2014.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197174","197174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49018","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support the Government is giving to credit unions to help extend access to fair credit.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197059","197059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49019","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what satellites currently use facilities at West Freugh for data transmission.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197170","197170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49020","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Skynet 5 satellites can use facilities at West Freugh for data transmission.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197171","197171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49021","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions (a) photographs have been taken of intercepted aircraft on Quick Reaction Alert flights and (b) such photographs have been released to the public in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197167","197167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49022","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who authorises the public release of photographs of aircraft that are intercepted during Quick Reaction Alert flights.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197166","197166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49023","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what consideration his Department gave to procuring the Rangeless Airborne Instrumented Debriefing System with Collision Warning software for installation on the Tornado aircraft.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197168","197168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49024","2014-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, by whom the decision was taken not to proceed from the Technology Demonstrator Phase of the EASAMS collision warning system to Full Development and Production; and whether that decision was reflected in the relevant platform risk registers.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197169","197169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49025","2014-05-01","Department for Transport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reasons are for the changes to Network Rail's planned redevelopment of the western elevation of New Street Station, set out in planning application 2014/02551/PA to Birmingham City Council.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196980","196980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49026","2014-05-01","Cabinet Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average time taken to process applications for redundancy payment is through My Civil Service Pension; and what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197038","197038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49027","2014-05-01","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Written Statement of 9 April 2014, Official Report, column 1417WS, on qualifications reform, and the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 42W, on in vitro fertilisation, whether the study of the human genome as part of the revised content for GCSEs in science will involve pupils learning that genomic DNA is only found in the cell nucleus and that mitochondrial DNA is not part of the genome.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197055","197055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49028","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the meta-analysis by Huang Y et al. published in the journal Cancer Causes Control in November 2013, investigating the link between termination of pregnancy and breast cancer.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197022","197022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49029","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 42W, on In vitro fertilisation, (a) what the evidential basis is for his statement that no genomic DNA is found in the mitochondria but only in the cell nucleus, (b) what account he took of the data on the human genome available in the ENSEMBL and OMIM databases in preparing that statement and (c) what genetic modifications applied to the eggs or embryos would prevent any nuclear DNA from the eggs or embryo donor being inherited by the resulting child.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197061","197061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49030","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he gives on ensuring that all women seeking an abortion are given accurate, complete, balanced and up-to-date information regarding the potential health risks of the procedure.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197120","197120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49032","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) numbers of GP practices and (b) services offered by GP practices of removing performance indicators from the Quality Outcomes Framework.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197052","197052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49033","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the effects of the removal of the Minimum Practice Income Guarantee on (a) GP services and (b) the income of GPs; and if he will commission research on the range and extent on GP income in Tower Hamlets.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197051","197051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49034","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the waiting time is for new routine referrals to Ophthalmology in each NHS hospital trust area.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196995","196995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49035","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the waiting time is for a routine new referral to Ophthalmology in the Western Sussex Hospitals Trust area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196996","196996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49036","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if HM Revenue and Customs will share the evaluation of the Tax Credit Error and Fraud Adding Capacity trial with recognised trade unions.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197124","197124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49037","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been spent by HM Revenue and Customs on preparatory work for the outsourcing of Tax Credit Error and Fraud Adding Capacity to date.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197125","197125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49038","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Tax Credit Error and Fraud Adding Capacity trial involving the private company Transactis in 2013.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197122","197122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49039","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place in the Library a copy of the business case for the outsourcing of compliance checks on tax credits claims.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197123","197123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49040","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to roll out mobile telephone blocking technology across HM prisons estate.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197144","197144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49041","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the level of illegal use of cellular devices in UK prisons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197142","197142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49042","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cellular devices have been confiscated from prisons in each of the last five years by establishment.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197143","197143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49043","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with mobile telephone operators on operators terminating accounts shown to be illegally active within the HM prison estate.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197145","197145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49044","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what is the average (a) social rent and (b) Affordable Rent is for units funded under the Affordable Homes Programme in each region of the UK.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197134","197134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49045","2014-05-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average housing benefit award is for housing benefit claimants paying Affordable Rent under the Affordable Homes Programme in each region of the UK.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197135","197135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49046","2014-05-07","Department for Transport","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will provide an estimate of the costs of redoubling the section of the North Cotswold line between (a) Charlbury to Wolvercote Junction and (b) Evesham and Norton Junction.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197158","197158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49047","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of savings to the public purse arising from using Capita to administer personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197153","197153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49048","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of Capita in fulfilling its contract to administer personal independence payments.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197152","197152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49049","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2014, Official Report, column 793W, on disclosure of information, when he expects the Government's response to the Whistleblowing Framework call for evidence will be published.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197186","197186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49050","2014-05-01","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) managerial, (b) teaching and (c) clerical staff in schools in Enfield were paid more than (i) 42,000, (ii) 69,000 and (iii) 100,000 in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197130","197130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49051","2014-05-01","Cabinet Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people who are (a) employed on zero-hours contracts and (b) paid at a rate below that defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage in Warrington North constituency.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197165","197165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49052","2014-05-06","Department for International Development","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 28 April 2014, Official Report, columns 568-9W, on Pacific Islands, to Question 196375, how much support and under what categories her Department gave directly to Pacific Island countries in 2013-14.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197058","197058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49053","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2014, Official Report, column 548W, on female prisoners, which domestic violence programmes and interventions will be delivered in which prisons in 2014-15.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197011","197011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49054","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the number of surgical care practitioners on the training of junior doctors in surgery.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197050","197050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49055","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information patients are entitled to as to whether a medical operation will be undertaken by a fully surgically qualified member of staff.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196993","196993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49056","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many surgical care practitioners have practised in the NHS in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196994","196994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49057","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department takes into account the differences in the positions of men and women in preparing for retirement when devising its policy on pensions.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197054","197054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49058","2014-05-01","HM Treasury","2014-04-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent progress has been made on implementing the recommendations of the Office of Tax Simplification.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197027","197027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49059","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many self-harm incidents there were (a) in total and (b) per 1,000 prisoners in each prison in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197045","197045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49060","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital attendances there were from each prison in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197046","197046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49061","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital attendances there were from the (a) adult male, (b) adult female, (c) youth male, (d) youth female and (e) total prison estate in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197047","197047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49062","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) assault incidents, (b) serious assaults and (c) assault incidents per 1,000 prisoners there were in each prison in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197044","197044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49063","2014-05-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison staff were allocated to the handling, processing and checking of prisoners' post, in each prison, on 1 April in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197048","197048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49064","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what amount was generated by levies under the Prisoners' Earnings Act 1996 Levy in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197074","197074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49065","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the unit cost per offender in a (a) secure children's home, (b) young offender institution, (c) secure training centre and (d) the adult secure estate was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197075","197075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49066","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the unit cost per offender supervised by (a) youth offending teams and (b) the Probation Service was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197076","197076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49067","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average (a) net and (b) gross earnings were of each prisoner in each month in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197089","197089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49068","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many days were lost due to sick leave among teaching staff in (a) secure training centres and (b) young offender institutions in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197077","197077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49069","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many days in total were lost due to sick leave among all staff in (a) secure training centres and (b) young offender institutions in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197078","197078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49070","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many teaching staff in young offender institutions and secure training centres in 2013 had a formal teaching qualification.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197079","197079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49071","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full time equivalent teaching staff there were in total in young offender institutions and secure training centres in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197080","197080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49072","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the days staffing levels were against the (a) benchmark and (b) baseline staffing level at the time of the disturbance of HM Prison Northumberland on Saturday 29 March 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197062","197062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49073","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many days in total have been lost due to staff sickness in each prison in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197081","197081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49074","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of (a) those in prison and (b) those in prison who self-identified as Muslim were (i) under the age of 18, (ii) aged between 18 and 21, (iii) aged between 21 and 25, (iv) aged between 26 and 30, (v) aged between 31 and 40, (vi) aged between 41 and 50, (vii) aged between 51 and 65 and (viii) aged over 65 years on 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197090","197090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49075","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what shortfalls in staffing (a) including and (b) excluding temporary cover against Target B3 staffing levels there were at the time of the disturbance of HM Prison Northumberland on Saturday 29 March 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197063","197063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49076","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sexual assaults on prison staff there were in each prison in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197082","197082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49077","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what items prisoners are barred from purchasing with earned income.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197083","197083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49078","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what additional staffing requirements will arise in HM Prison Hull and HM Prison Chelmsford from the re-opening of closed wings; what the cost of this re-opening will be; and where any additional staff be sourced from.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197091","197091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49079","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were employed in work in jails on 1 April in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197084","197084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49080","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full time equivalent prison officers were employed and how many such staff were off sick at HM Prison Northumberland on Saturday 29 March 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197064","197064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49081","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were employed in work in the community on 1 April in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197085","197085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49082","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what extra capacity will be created by re-opening the closed wings at (a) HM Prison Hull and (b) HM Prison Chelmsford.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197092","197092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49083","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest amount earned by any prisoner in jail was in 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197086","197086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49084","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much will have been spent on maintining the closed wings at HM Prison Hull and HM Prison Chelmsford by the time both will re-open.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197093","197093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49085","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether HM Prison Northumberland was (a) contributing staff to and (b) receiving staff as part of the detached duty programme on Saturday 29 March 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197065","197065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49086","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what cap exists on the level of income a prisoner can earn inside jail.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197087","197087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49087","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent maintaining the closed wings at HM Prison Hull and HM Prison Chelmsford to date.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197094","197094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49088","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were subjected to levies under the Prisoners' Earnings Act 1996 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197088","197088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49089","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the re-opened wings at (a) HM Prison Hull and (b) HM Prison Chelmsford will take prisoners.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197095","197095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49090","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons the closed wings at (a) HM Prison Hull and (b) HM Prison Chelmsford were (i) closed and (ii) re-opened.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197096","197096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49091","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, at what time the disturbance at HM Prison Northumberland on 29 March 2014 began; when it ceased; how many prisoners were involved in that disturbance; what injuries were sustained by prisoners and officers; how many prison officers were used to quell the disturbance; and what resources external to the prison were called on to assist in quelling the disturbance.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197066","197066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49092","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the nationality was of (a) all people in prison and (b) people in prison who self-identified as Muslim on 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197069","197069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49093","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the proven re-offending rate was of (a) those released from prison and (b) those released from prison who self-identified as Muslim in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197070","197070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49094","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent purchasing additional prison places from existing privately run prisons in each month since 1 January 2014; from which prisons such additional spaces have been purchased; how many additional spaces were agreed; for how long each such additional space has been purchased for; and what the cost was for each space agreed.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197071","197071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49095","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults against prison staff there have been in HM Prison High Down in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197072","197072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49096","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many acts of prisoner on prisoner violence there have been in HM Prison High Down in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197073","197073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49097","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the staff turnover rate has been in (a) the prison estate and (b) HM Prison High Down in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197103","197103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49098","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of (a) all people in prison and (b) all people in prison who self-identified as Muslims on 1 January 2014 had (i) no previous custodial sentences, (ii) one previous custodial sentence, (iii) between two and five previous custodial sentences, (iv) between six and 10 previous custodial sentences and (v) over 10 previous custodial sentences.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197068","197068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49099","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the staff sickness rate has been in (a) the prison estate and (b) HM Prison High Down in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197104","197104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49100","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prisoners and (b) young adult prisoners were on suicide watch in HM Prison High Down on (i) 1 September 2013 and (ii) 1 April 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197105","197105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49101","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in HM Prison High Down on 1 April 2014 there were (a) in total, (b) aged under 18, (c) aged 18 to 20 and (d) aged 21 or over.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197106","197106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49102","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young adult prisoners were held in HM Prison High Down on 1 April (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013 and (d) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197107","197107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49103","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when HM Prison High Down has had to (a) close wings, (b) close workshops and (c) restrict family visits due to staff shortages since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197108","197108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49104","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when HM Prison High Down has been (a) a recipient of and (b) a contributor to the detached duty programme in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197109","197109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49105","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of (a) all people in prison and (b) all people in prison who self-identified as Muslims in 1 January 2014 were serving custodial sentences of less than (i) one month, (ii) three months, (iii) six months, (iv) 12 months, (v) 24 months, (vi) 60 months, (vii) 10 years and (viii) over 10 years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197067","197067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49106","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff of each grade were employed at HM Prison Northumberland on 1 April (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 107175","107175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49107","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2014, Official Report, column 406W, on prisons: postal services, how many incidents of (a) drug-related or (b) miscellaneous contraband were found in post received by prisoners in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197172","197172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49108","2014-05-01","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions are in place should any of the preferred bidders for the Community Rehabilitation Companies be found guilty of (a) a criminal offence relating to the conduct of business and (b) an act of grave misconduct in the period before any contracts are signed.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197101","197101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49109","2014-05-01","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any of the approved bidders for the Community Rehabilitation Companies have (a) been convicted of a criminal offence relating to the conduct of business and (b) committed an act of grave misconduct in the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197100","197100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49110","2014-05-01","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been spent on converting HM Prison The Verne for use as an immigration removal centre to date.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197102","197102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49111","2014-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what change in full time equivalent staff of each grade there has been at HM Prison Northumberland since the running of the prison was transferred to Sodexo.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197097","197097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49112","2014-05-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many prisoners reached (a) Key Stage 1, (b) Key Stage 2 and (c) Key Stage 3 qualifications in (i) English and (ii) mathematics whilst in prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197099","197099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49113","2014-05-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many prisoners did not have (a) Key Stage 1, (b) Key Stage 2 and (c) Key Stage 3 qualifications in (i) English and (ii) mathematics when they entered prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197098","197098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49114","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2014, Official Report, columns 352-3W, on asylum: children, if she will publish a breakdown by constituency of the number of unaccompanied asylum-seeking children in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197188","197188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49115","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the (a) fairness and (b) viability of reforming the firefighters' pension scheme allow members to retire on the basis of length of service rather than age.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 107177","107177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49116","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has (a) discussed with and (b) received any representations from the Fire Brigades Union regarding the adoption of a firefighters' pension scheme which would allow members to retire on the basis of length of service rather than age.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 107178","107178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49117","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will disaggregate the departmental operating costs in his Department's annual accounts to programme level for each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197049","197049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49118","2014-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in Venezuela.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197196","197196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49119","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will publish guidance for employers on reducing the causes of work-related stress.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197185","197185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49120","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require employers to undertake a systematic assessment of psychological risks in the workplace.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197183","197183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49121","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will commission an assessment of the causes of work-related stress.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197184","197184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49122","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that workers report work-related stress to their employers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197181","197181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49123","2014-05-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to enable employers to handle cases of employees suffering from work-related stress or other psychological problems affecting their work.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197182","197182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49124","2014-05-06","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what specific steps he will take to place the Maidstone and Tunbridge Wells NHS Trust on a stable and secure long-term financial footing.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197156","197156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49127","2014-05-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made in re-basing those elements of the armed forces based in Germany; and what recent discussions he has had with German federal and regional authorities on the practical logistics involved in such a withdrawal.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197002","197002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49128","2014-05-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the future acquisition requirements for intelligence surveillance, target acquisition and reconnaissance systems.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197004","197004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49129","2014-05-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's recruitment targets are for its Joint Cyber Reserve Unit.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197005","197005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49130","2014-05-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have had with their NATO counterparts on the establishment of a NATO-wide cyber capability.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197006","197006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49131","2014-05-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support business start-ups in (a) Coventry North East constituency and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197003","197003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49132","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many tenancy relations officers are currently employed by each local authority.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197199","197199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49133","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many environmental health officers are currently employed by each local authority.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197200","197200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49134","2014-05-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many landlords have been prosecuted in England for (a) illegal evictions and (b) harassment in the latest three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197201","197201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49135","2014-05-06","Home Office","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the proposal set out in Baroness Newlove's report, Our Vision for Safe and Active Communities, for a Bling Back scheme where money made from selling local drug dealers' assets is handed back to the neighbourhood.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197219","197219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49136","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his oral contribution of 2 April 2014, Official Report, column 908, on energy price freeze, how much investment there was in the electricity sector in each year between 1997 and 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197227","197227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49137","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 991, on energy supply, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the amount of electricity traded on the day ahead market has increased from five per cent to more than 50 per cent.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197233","197233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49138","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his oral contribution of 2 April 2014, Official Report, column 906, on energy price freeze, what the evidential basis is for the statement that energy bills rose by (a) 11 per cent a year in the last parliament and (b) 8 per cent a year in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197228","197228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49139","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his oral contribution of 2 April 2014, Official Report, column 908, on energy price freeze, if he will place in the Library a copy of Bloomberg's analysis of investment in renewables.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197221","197221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49140","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 990, on energy bills, how many households are forecast to receive assistance under the Energy Company Obligation (a) in each year between 2013 and 2017 and (b) in total.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197234","197234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49141","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 998, with which other countries his Department is working on the New Climate Economy report.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197229","197229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49142","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his oral contribution of 2 April 2014, Official Report, column 908, on energy price freeze, what the evidential basis is for the statement that average annual investment in renewables has more than doubled in the current Parliament compared with the previous one.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197222","197222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49143","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 990, on energy bills, what the evidential basis is for the statement that more households will receive assistance under the Energy Company Obligation as a result of proposed changes to that scheme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197235","197235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49144","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 982, on energy markets: competition, what measures his Department has introduced to deregulate the energy market since 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197230","197230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49145","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 998, if he will publish the terms of reference for the New Climate Economy report.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197236","197236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49146","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his oral contribution of 2 April 2014, Official Report, column 909, on energy price freeze, what the evidential basis is for the statement that independents' share of the retail market has increased from one per cent in 2010 to five per cent.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197223","197223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49147","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 998, when his Department expects work to begin on the New Climate Economy report; and when he expects that report to be published.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197237","197237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49148","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 994, on energy efficiency, how many of the 600,000 households that have received energy-efficiency improvements received assistance under the (a) Energy Company Obligation and (b) Green Deal.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197231","197231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49149","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his oral contribution of 2 April 2014, Official Report, column 908, on energy price freeze, what the evidential basis is for the statement that there is a pipeline of 187 billion of investment in the electricity sector.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197224","197224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49150","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his oral contribution of 2 April 2014, Official Report, column 908, on energy price freeze, what the evidential basis is for the statement that investment in the electricity sector has been, on average, 8 billion a year in the present Parliament.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197225","197225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49151","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 993, on energy efficiency, how many households in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area have received energy efficiency improvements under the Energy Company Obligation.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197232","197232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49152","2014-05-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his oral contribution of 2 April 2014, Official Report, column 908, on energy price freeze, how much investment there was in (a) renewable and (b) non-renewable sources of electricity in each year between 1997 and 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197226","197226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49153","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2014, Official Report, column 414W, on pre-school education, who the 43 early years providers are who have been granted full or partial exemptions from the learning and development requirements of the Early Years Foundation Stage framework.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197216","197216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49154","2014-05-06","Department for Education","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 April 2014, Official Report, column 284W, on children: day care, how many survey packs were sent out to (a) childminders and (b) parents; and when the surveys were completed.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197215","197215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49155","2014-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from the (a) Local Government Association, (b) Convention of Scottish Local Authorities and (c) Welsh Local Government Association on issues of staff protection, finance and timing in relation the proposal to establish a single fraud investigation service.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197205","197205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49156","2014-05-01","Department of Health","2014-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many whole-time equivalent podiatrists were employed in the NHS in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197207","197207"
