"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90589","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Government plans to respond to the report from the Law Commission entitled Patents, Trade Marks and Design Rights: Groundless Threats, published in April 2014.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208207","208207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90590","2014-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received in respect of LighterLife UK Limited.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208216","208216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90591","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support Leeds Business Week.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208150","208150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90592","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will bring forward proposals to make military exports to Saudi Arabia contingent on human rights reform in that country.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208151","208151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90593","2014-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the level of construction output in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208173","208173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90594","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of charities registered in the UK primarily or substantially funded from Middle Eastern sources; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208181","208181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90595","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what support his Department gives to private citizens who take legal action against electoral registration officers who do not conduct door to door canvassing of those households that do not return electoral registration forms.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208193","208193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90596","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which local authorities have (a) promoted online registration and (b) not promoted online registration since its introduction.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208194","208194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90597","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which local authorities have contacted his Department on the capability of their computer system to deal with electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208199","208199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90598","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if his Department will discuss with the Electoral Commission that body changing its target performance for completeness of the electoral register between 2014-15 and 2018-19 from completeness does not deteriorate to completeness is improved.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208225","208225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90599","2014-09-09","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what role the National Security Adviser has in relation to cyber-security.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208223","208223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90600","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many people have registered to vote online in each week since individual electoral registration was implemented.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208230","208230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90601","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent legal action his Department has taken against local authorities which have, on several occasions, not conducted door-to-door canvassing of households which do not return their electoral registration forms.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208229","208229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90602","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if his Department will ensure the key indicators for the effectiveness of the Electoral Commission include the actual number and proportion of UK citizens who are registered to vote.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208224","208224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90603","2014-09-09","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208302","208302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90604","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness in increasing the number of people registered to vote of the full canvass that took place in Northern Ireland between 2012 and 2013; and what guidance he provides to local authorities who do not conduct door-to-door canvassing for the purposes of electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208273","208273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90605","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment his Department has made of the trends in the number of unregistered voters between 2010 and 2014; and what targets his Department has to ensure that (a) completeness does not deteriorate and (b) completeness is improved over the next five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208274","208274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90606","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many and what proportion of electors have registered online in each local authority area since online registration was introduced.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208312","208312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90607","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208335","208335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90608","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any charities registered in the UK are donating funds or other support to Islamic State militants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208329","208329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90609","2014-09-08","Wales Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the benefits to the Welsh economy of holding the NATO summit in Newport.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208313","208313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90610","2014-09-08","HM Treasury","2014-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208349","208349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90611","2014-09-09","HM Treasury","2014-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2014, Official Report, column 1094W, on domestic visits, what domestic visits he has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208261","208261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90612","2014-09-08","HM Treasury","2014-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208293","208293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90613","2014-09-09","HM Treasury","2014-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) child tax credits and (b) working tax credits claimants in (i) Coventry, (ii) the West Midlands and (iii) England were paid in error in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208172","208172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90614","2014-09-09","HM Treasury","2014-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the statement by the Chief Secretary to the Treasury, reported in The Sunday Times on 31 August 2014, what provision will be made in the Autumn Statement 2014 to double the funding for tackling mobile blackspots; and what criteria will be used to decide which locations will benefit from that funding.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208163","208163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90615","2014-09-09","Church Commissioners","2014-09-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, for what reasons the land for sale at Binchester has been divided into two lots.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208262","208262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90616","2014-09-09","Church Commissioners","2014-09-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps are being taken to ensure continued public access to Binchester Roman Fort.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208263","208263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90617","2014-09-09","Church Commissioners","2014-09-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church Commissioners have set criteria excluding some bidders from the purchase of its land currently for sale near Bishop Auckland.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208259","208259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90618","2014-09-09","Church Commissioners","2014-09-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, for what reasons land owned by the Church near Bishop Auckland is for sale.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208260","208260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90619","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208303","208303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90620","2014-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to local authorities to date of claims made by property search companies for refunds of local land charges search fees as a result of the implementation of the 2003 European Directive on public access to environmental information and the Environmental Information Regulations 2004.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208276","208276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90621","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208336","208336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90622","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the report by the National Audit Office, Funding and structures for local economic growth, HC 542, published on 6 December 2013, what steps he has taken to implement recommendation 22f on page 13 of the report.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208306","208306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90623","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of new jobs that will be created by enterprise zones by 2015.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208307","208307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90624","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the proportion of affordable homes delivered through section 106 agreements on sites of fewer than 10 homes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208220","208220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90625","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of removing section 106 planning obligations from sites of fewer than 10 houses on the provision of affordable housing in rural areas.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208221","208221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90626","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers in the Welsh Government on tackling extremism; and whether he has any plans for a meeting with his counterparts in the administrations to discuss tackling extremism across the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208165","208165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90627","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the number of local authorities that have held referendums on increasing council tax above the threshold set by his Department.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208146","208146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90628","2014-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to make further financial payments to local authorities in respect of claims made against them by property search companies for refunds of local land charges search fees as a result of the implementation of the 2003 EC directive on freedom of information and the 2004 environmental information regulations.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208157","208157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90629","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the proposal submitted by Tenterden Town Council and Sevenoaks Town Council in February 2014 in relation to the Sustainable Communities Act 2007.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208158","208158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90630","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the representations he has received on his proposal to end check-off for trade union subscriptions for staff working in his Department.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208160","208160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90631","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of affordable homes delivered through section 106 agreements on sites of fewer than 10 homes in rural areas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208162","208162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90632","2014-09-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward proposals to enable people who are registered blind to  receive a discount on their television licence in the same way that people who are deaf do.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208145","208145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90633","2014-09-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to improve supporter involvement with football clubs.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208170","208170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90634","2014-09-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he met the Secretary General of the Qatar 2022 Supreme Committee for Delivery and Legacy; and what plans he has for future meetings.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208222","208222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90635","2014-09-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he and Ministers in his Department have had with Ministers in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the proposed reform of apprenticeships; what effect those discussions will have on his Department's projects and the work of their supply chain; and whether officials in his Department sit on programme boards managing that reform.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208208","208208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90636","2014-09-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, other than the members of the BBC Trust appointed to represent specific nations, how many of the existing Trust members have their main home outside London.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208205","208205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90637","2014-09-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many and what proportion of (a) directors or senior managers and (b) trustees of the National portfolio organisations for 2015-18 are of BAME background.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208256","208256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90638","2014-09-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many and what proportion of (a) directors or senior managers and (b) trustees of the Major Partner Museums 2015-18 are women.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208257","208257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90639","2014-09-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208337","208337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90640","2014-09-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208304","208304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90641","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the strength of the Regular Army A Reserve was in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208241","208241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90642","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) required and (b) actual number of Regular Army recruits in the (i) Household Cavalry and Royal Armoured Corps, (ii) Royal Artillery, (iii) Royal Engineers, (iv) Royal Signals, (v) Infantry and (vi) Army Air Corps was in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208243","208243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90643","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208278","208278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90644","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on establishing a credit union for military personnel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208271","208271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90645","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the number of Islamic State militants fighting in Syria and Iraq; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208272","208272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90646","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208338","208338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90647","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 14 May 2014, Official Report, column 613W, on war graves, what further progress has been made on discussions with the Commonwealth War Graves Commission on the transer of graves maintained by the Ministry of Defence to that Commissioner.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208305","208305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90648","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) voluntary redundancies, (b) compulsory redundancies, (c) voluntary exits and (d) involuntary exits from the Army there were in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208242","208242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90649","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) required and (b) actual number of Regular Army recruits was for the (i) Royal Logistic Corps, (ii) Royal Army Medical Corps, (iii) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers, (iv) Adjutant General's Corps (Provost), (v) Adjutant General's Corps (Staff and Personnel Support) and (vi) Royal Army Veterinary Corps in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208233","208233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90650","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army Reserves were in training in each financial year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208245","208245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90651","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost of Army (a) phase one and (b) phase two training was in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208246","208246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90652","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the target is for recruitment into the (a) Regular Army and (b) Army Reserve in the current financial year.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208247","208247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90653","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what targets for recruitment into the (a) Regular Army and (b) Army Reserve were set in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208248","208248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90654","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Regular reservists and (b) Army Reservists were called up to support Operation Telic in each year between 2002-03 and 2011-12.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208249","208249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90655","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Regular reservists and (b) Army Reservists are supporting Operation Herrick.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208250","208250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90656","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Regular reservists and (b) Army Reservists were called up to support Operation Herrick in each financial year between 2002-03 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208251","208251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90657","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) required and (b) actual number of Regular Army recruits was for the (i) Small Arms School Corps, (ii) Royal Army Dental Corps, (iii) Intelligence Corps, (iv) Royal Army Physical Training Corps, (v) Queen Alexandra's Royal Army Nursing Corps, (vi) Corps of Army Music and (vii) Senior Soldier Continuity Posts (Long Service) in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208232","208232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90658","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he was made aware by his US counterpart of the suspension of F35 engine deliveries as a result of subgrade titanium.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208244","208244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90659","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Regular: Reserve Cost Comparison Model.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208239","208239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90660","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the strength of the Regular Army Reserve of Officers was in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208240","208240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90661","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many army pensioners have been recalled to service under Section 52 of the Reserve Forces Act 1996 since 1997.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208238","208238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90662","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army Reserve recruits (a) passed and (b) failed (i) Phase One and (ii) Phase Two training in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208234","208234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90663","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) new recruits and (b) former regulars entered the Army Reserve in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208235","208235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90664","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the strength of the Regular Army Section Reserve was in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208236","208236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90665","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the strength of the Long Term Reserve was in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208237","208237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90666","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he and Ministers in his Department have had with Ministers in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the proposed reform of apprenticeships; what effect those discussions will have on his Department's projects and the work of their supply chain; and whether officials in his Department sit on programme boards managing the reform.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208209","208209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90667","2014-09-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what domestic visits he and his predecessor have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208176","208176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90668","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by his Office was in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208279","208279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90669","2014-09-08","Department for Education","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) her Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208280","208280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90670","2014-09-09","Department for Education","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 621W, on official visits, what domestic visits she and her predecessor have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208296","208296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90671","2014-09-08","Department for Education","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to reduce energy costs in her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208339","208339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90672","2014-09-08","Department for Education","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's report on Improving Permanence for Looked After Children, published in September 2013, what assessment she has made of the evidence from case studies cited on page 40 of that report, that local authorities can make significant financial savings through effective support for a child returning home from care; and if she will take full account of that evidence in her forthcoming response to the consultation on looked-after children.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208352","208352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90673","2014-09-09","Department for Education","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with the Welsh Government Minister for Education on tackling extremism and radicalisation in schools; and whether she has any plans for a meeting with her counterparts in the devolved administrations to discuss tackling extremism and radicalisation.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208164","208164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90674","2014-09-08","Department for Education","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what records are (a) maintained schools and (b) independent schools required to keep of instances where students have verbally abused a student with special educational needs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208159","208159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90675","2014-09-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when the member for Walsall North will receive a reply to his letter of 28 July 2014 to the Parliamentary Under-Secretary for Climate Change concerning the early closure of the Green Deal Home Energy Efficiency Improvement Fund.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208178","208178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90676","2014-09-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 618W, on official visits, what domestic visits he and his predecessor have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208298","208298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90677","2014-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution of 4 September 2014 by the Minister for Business and Enterprise, on sustainable energy, what the evidential basis is for the statement that nuclear power is zero-carbon energy.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208325","208325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90678","2014-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208340","208340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90679","2014-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of fuel poor households under the low-income high costs definition in (a) Wales and (b) Scotland with an energy performance certificate rating of (i) A, (ii) B, (iii) C, (iv) D, (v) E, (vi) F and (vii) G.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208327","208327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90680","2014-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of fuel poor households under the low-income high costs definition in (a) Wales and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208328","208328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90681","2014-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208281","208281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90682","2014-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) her Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208282","208282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90683","2014-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2014, Official Report, columns 626-7W, on official visits, what domestic visits she and her predecessor have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208297","208297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90684","2014-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce energy costs in her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208341","208341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90685","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the written statement of 4 September 2014, on Elliott Review, what budget the Food Crime Unit will be allocated for (a) setting up and (b) operating in financial years (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208365","208365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90686","2014-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the written statement of 4 September 2014, on Elliott Review, which departments will be represented on that group and at what level of seniority; what the membership will be of that group; and when that group will meet; what the terms of reference are of the cross-government group on Food Integrity and Food Crime.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208366","208366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90687","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the written statement of 4 September 2014, on Elliott Review, how many police officers will work in the Food Crime Unit.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208364","208364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90688","2014-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on enabling the recording of food crime as an identifiable category of crime in police databases.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208354","208354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90689","2014-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to her written statement of 4 September 2014, on the Elliott Review, what extra resources (a) her Department and (b) the Government will provide to the Food Standards Agency for the establishment and operation of the Food Crime Unit in financial year (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208361","208361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90690","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the written statement of 4 September 2014, on the Elliott Review, when the Food Crime Unit will be operational.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208360","208360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90691","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the written statement of 4 September 2014, on the Elliott Review, how many staff at each grade will be (a) recruited and (b) seconded to the Food Crime Unit.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208362","208362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90692","2014-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she and Ministers in her Department have had with Ministers in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the proposed reform of apprenticeships; what effect those discussions will have on her Department's projects and the work of their supply chain; and whether officials in her Department sit on programme boards managing the reform.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208210","208210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90693","2014-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to exchange scientific research with the Department of Agriculture in Northern Ireland on tackling bovine tuberculosis; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208227","208227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90694","2014-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions her Department has had with the government of Denmark about hunting cetaceans in the Faroe Islands.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208168","208168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90695","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on the detention of Abdulhadi Alkhawaja; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208155","208155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90696","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Bahrain about the detention of Maryam Al-Khawaja at Bahrain International Airport; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208156","208156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90697","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress with democratic reform in Egypt.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208149","208149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90698","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Burmese government on their treatment of the Rohingya.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208152","208152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90699","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the sources of rockets supplied to Hamas operating in Gaza; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208182","208182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90700","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the sources of supply to Islamic State militants of their weapons and training; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208183","208183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90701","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with his international counterparts to stop the war in Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208184","208184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90702","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much of Syria's chemical weapons arsenal (a) is intact and (b) has been destroyed to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208185","208185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90703","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Russian diplomats are serving with so-called diplomatic immunity in the Russian Embassy in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208186","208186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90704","2014-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether the actions of the Russian Federation in relation to Ukraine are compliant with the provisions of the Budapest Memorandum on Security Assurances.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208218","208218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90705","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the demobilisation and integration of former Beja Congress fighters into civil and military services is adequately supported.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208189","208189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90706","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of recent developments in Sudan's National Dialogue process.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208190","208190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90707","2014-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take through the Commonwealth and UN to secure Sri Lanka's compliance with the UN Human Rights Committee's resolution on the war crimes and civil rights investigation.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208355","208355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90708","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208342","208342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90709","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208283","208283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90710","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people over the age of 65 were diagnosed with dementia after being admitted to hospital as an emergency inpatient in England in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208265","208265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90711","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people over the age of 65 presented themselves to a clinician showing key symptoms of dementia in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208264","208264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90712","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on specialist assessment and diagnostic services for deaf British Sign Language users with dementia in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208269","208269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90713","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on dementia assessment for diagnostic purposes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208270","208270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90714","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many deaf British Sign Language users over the age of 65 were diagnosed with dementia after being admitted to hospital as an emergency inpatient in England in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208266","208266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90715","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of tests on animals conducted in the UK using mitochondrial replacement techniques in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208267","208267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90716","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208285","208285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90717","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will institute an awards scheme to recognise best practice among doctors who deliver training to medical students.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208322","208322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90718","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of places for medical students to undertake training in GP practices.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208308","208308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90719","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will arrange for a reply to be sent to the letter concerning a constituent sent by the hon Member for Walsall North to the Walsall Clinical Commissioning Group on 7 July 2014, which was sent on to NHS England Patient Experience Team in West Bromwich; and if he will inquire into the reasons for the time taken to send a substantive reply to that letter.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208177","208177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90720","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he and Ministers in his Department have had with Ministers in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the proposed reform of apprenticeships; what effect those discussions will have on his Department's projects and the work of their supply chain; and whether officials in his Department sit on programme boards managing the reform.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208211","208211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90721","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department will publish the results of the GP patient survey conducted on behalf of NHS England by Ipsos MORI.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208255","208255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90722","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients (a) were invited to participate in and (b) responded to the recent GP patient survey.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208254","208254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90723","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2014, Official Report, on the General Dental Council, if (a) his Department and (b) the Professional Standards Authority For Health and Social Care will publish its review of the business case for the increase in years charged by the General Dental Council; and if similar reviews will be published of the Care Quality Commission increase in fees to dental professionals.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208258","208258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90724","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of NHS trusts that provide nursery facilities for staff and patients.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208187","208187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90725","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of nurseries run by NHS trusts that (a) have closed since 2010 and (b) plan to close in the next three years.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208188","208188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90726","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle Islamophobia; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208153","208153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90727","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with (a) the French government, (b) local government in Calais and (c) ferry operators regarding illegal immigrants at Calais since 1 August 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208169","208169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90728","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports that her Department has returned to applicants in the last year have gone missing; and if she will estimate the annual cost to her Department of returning passports to applicants by (a) second-class post, (b) first-class post and (c) recorded delivery.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208231","208231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90729","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she and Ministers in her Department have had with Ministers in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the proposed reform of apprenticeships; what effect those discussions will have on her Department's projects and the work of their supply chain; and whether officials in her Department sit on programme boards managing the reform.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208212","208212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90730","2014-09-08","Department for Education","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department issues to schools on what action to take when a student with special educational needs is physically attacked by other pupils on school property.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208192","208192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90731","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of including fraud data as notified to the National Intelligence Bureau in crime maps produced by her Department.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208175","208175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90732","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees have been granted asylum in the UK since the start of the Syrian conflict in 2011; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208330","208330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90733","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of Russian citizens resident in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208331","208331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90734","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking with regards to supporters of Islamic State in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208332","208332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90735","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the name and job title was of the official who signed the European arrest warrant for the parents of Ashya King.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208309","208309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90736","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what expenditure has been incurred by UK police forces in the search for the parents of Ashya King; and how these costs will be met.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208310","208310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90737","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the statement by the Prime Minister of 1 September 2014, Official Report, column 24, on EU Council Security and Middle East, and with reference to the oral evidence of Mark Sedwill, Permanent Secretary, Home Office, to the Committee of Public Accounts of 9 October 2013, HC 663-i, whether data protection legislation in any EU country continues to prevent the disclosure of advance passenger information to the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208363","208363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90738","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce energy costs in her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208343","208343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90739","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) her Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208286","208286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90740","2014-09-08","House of Commons Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many children can be accommodated by the House of Commons crche; what proportion of that figure the average usage of the crche was in each of the last three years; and what the net profit or loss of the crche was in each of those years.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208353","208353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90741","2014-09-09","House of Commons Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the total cost has been of the Speaker's Commission on Digital Democracy; and how many people are employed to work on the Commission.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208179","208179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90742","2014-09-09","House of Commons Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what (a) expenses and (b) salary is paid to members of the Speaker's Commission on Digital Democracy.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208180","208180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90743","2014-09-09","House of Commons Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, who authorises expenditure for the Speaker's Commission on Digital Democracy; and out of which budget-heading such funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208217","208217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90744","2014-09-09","House of Commons Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, who authorised the secondment of a member of the House of Commons Library staff to work in Burma with the Burmese Parliament; how long this secondment has lasted; and how much the staff member has been paid in (a) salary and (b) expenses while on secondment.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208219","208219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90745","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of humanitarian conditions in eastern Sudan.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208191","208191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90746","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the UK's priorities are for humanitarian policy at the September 2014 session of the UN General Assembly.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208143","208143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90747","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to prioritise measures to improve the position of women and girls as part of her Department's development programmes.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208148","208148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90748","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) her Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208287","208287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90749","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to reduce energy costs in her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208344","208344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90750","2014-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208345","208345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90751","2014-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208288","208288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90752","2014-09-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which local authorities have contacted his Department on the capability of their computer systems to deal with individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208200","208200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90753","2014-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support his Department gives to private citizens who take legal action against electoral registration officers who do not conduct door-to-door canvassing of those households that do not return electoral registration forms.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208215","208215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90754","2014-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he and Ministers in his Department have had with Ministers in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the proposed reform of apprenticeships; what effect those discussions will have on his Department's projects and the work of their supply chain; and whether officials in his Department sit on programme boards managing the reform.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208213","208213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90755","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the terms of reference adopted by the Police Service of Northern Ireland to review on-the-run cases under Operation Red Field; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208228","208228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90756","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to establish a procedure for recording on a central register the use of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy as recommended in the Hallett Report published on 17 July 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208226","208226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90757","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) her Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208289","208289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90758","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to reduce energy costs in her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208346","208346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90759","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the timetable is for the full implementation of the Hallett Report's recommendations; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208315","208315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90760","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking in response to the breach of internal communications security in her Department relating to the leak of information to newspapers regarding her announcement to the Northern Ireland Affairs Committee on 3 September 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208316","208316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90761","2014-09-08","Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, how many official visits to Northern Ireland he has undertaken since May 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208317","208317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90762","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the current security threat posed by the Real IRA and other dissident republicans; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208318","208318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90763","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many international businesses she has met to discuss inward investment into Northern Ireland since her appointment as Secretary of State; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208319","208319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90764","2014-09-08","Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, how many meetings he has held at (a) Downing Street and (b) the House with elected representatives from Northern Ireland in 2014 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208320","208320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90765","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which recommendations of the Hallett Report have already been implemented; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208321","208321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90766","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by No. 10 Downing Street was in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208290","208290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90767","2014-09-09","Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with the First Minister of Wales on tackling extremism; and whether he plans to discuss the issue of tackling extremism at his next Joint Ministerial Council meeting.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208166","208166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90768","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that the protective security measures required for policing the NATO Summit in Wales will be removed as soon as possible after the conclusion of that summit.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208167","208167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90769","2014-09-09","Wales Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the potential financial benefits to Wales arising from holding the NATO Summit in Newport and Cardiff.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208174","208174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90770","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her press statement of 29 August 2014 on the threat level from international terrorism, what options will be available to staff at border control to deal with UK citizens refused re-entry to the UK because they are suspected of involvement in terrorist activities in Iraq or Syria.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208161","208161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90771","2014-09-08","Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to his Oral statement of 1 September 2014, Official Report, column 34, what the evidential basis is for his statement that the Saudi Arabian government has changed its approach on radicalisation around the world; and whether he considers that such changes have included a change in policy on providing funding for Islamist extremist groups.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208144","208144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90772","2014-09-09","Prime Minister","2014-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the National Security Council has reviewed the collective strategic impact of policy changes since its creation in 2010.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208171","208171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90773","2014-09-08","Scotland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by his Department was in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208291","208291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90774","2014-09-08","Scotland Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208347","208347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90775","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what estimate the Electoral Commission has made of the effect of a full canvass of electors in Northern Ireland in 2012 and 2013 on registration levels in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208311","208311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90776","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, with reference to the key success measures on page 14 of the Commission's Corporate Plan 2014-19, what the main targets for successful public awareness campaigns were; what the targets were for each of these campaigns; and whether subsequent targets are adjusted in the light of the results of each campaign.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208277","208277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90777","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what proportion of votes was cast by postal ballot in each local authority area of the UK in the last European election.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208275","208275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90778","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will publish its original timetable for research, printing and publication of the report into the accuracy and completeness of electoral registers published on 22 July 2014; and what the original target date for publication of that document was.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208202","208202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90779","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, when the Electoral Commission will publish its report on the completeness and accuracy of the 2014 electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208203","208203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90780","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will postpone its proposals on (a) photo identification for voters and (b) limitations on the handling of postal ballots until after the introduction of individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208204","208204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90781","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, when hard copies of the Electoral Commission's report into the completeness and accuracy of the electoral registers 2014 were placed in the Vote Office.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208195","208195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90782","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which Electoral Commission reports have been (a) placed and (b) not placed in the Vote Office in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208196","208196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90783","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which Electoral Commission regulation campaigns were deemed (a) appropriate and (b) inappropriate to be allocated targets for registration download.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208197","208197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90784","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which local authorities have contacted the European Commission on the capabilities of their computer system to deal with individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208201","208201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90785","2014-09-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, under what criteria the targets set for the electoral registration campaigns that were conducted by the Electoral Commission were deemed appropriate for targets for registration downloads.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208198","208198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90786","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to increase capacity at East Croydon station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208154","208154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90787","2014-09-09","Department for Transport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to provide a new rail halt at Kingsnorth in Ashford, Kent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208299","208299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90788","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the Transport Research Laboratory review of pedestrian walking speeds and time needed to cross the road; and whether he plans to update the current guidance on pedestrian crossings in response.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208314","208314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90789","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208348","208348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90790","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208292","208292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90791","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 6 March 2014, Official Report, column 942W, on road signs and markings, when he expects to publish his Department's review of the Traffic Signs Regulations and General Directions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208326","208326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90792","2014-10-15","Department for Transport","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the progress made by local authorities in increasing the provision of audio visual next stop and final destination on-board announcements on local buses through the Better Bus Area fund.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208367","208367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90793","2014-09-08","Wales Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208324","208324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90794","2014-09-08","Wales Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by his Department in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208294","208294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90795","2014-09-08","Wales Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208350","208350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90796","2014-09-08","Women and Equalities","2014-09-04","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by the Government Equalities Office was in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208284","208284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90797","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208295","208295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90798","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208351","208351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90799","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on the purchase of televisions in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208323","208323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90800","2014-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with the Poverty Truth Commission.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208356","208356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90801","2014-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent per head on training staff of his Department in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208357","208357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90802","2014-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education about ending the Youth Contract Wage Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208358","208358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90803","2014-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the security of staff at Jobcentre Plus offices.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208359","208359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90804","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the current level of the benefit cap; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208147","208147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90805","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he and Ministers in his Department have had with Ministers in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the proposed reform of apprenticeships; what effect those discussions will have on his Department's projects and the work of their supply chain; and whether officials in his Department sit on programme boards managing the reform.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208214","208214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90806","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Scotland have had DWP form DS1500 signed by their doctor to confirm they are terminally ill in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208206","208206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90807","2014-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when a decision will be made on the application made in November 2013 by Mrs Staltmeier of Christchurch for a personal independence payment.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208252","208252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90872","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that departments meet targets for clearing public records for transfer to the National Archives.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905297","905297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90949","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent jobs with the Civil Service or government agencies there were in Yorkshire in May 2010; and how many such jobs there are now.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905301","905301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91337","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to maintain the level of youth services provision.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905304","905304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91338","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent steps the Government has taken to promote social action and volunteering.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905306","905306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91339","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the summer 2014 National Citizen Service programmes.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905305","905305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90403","2014-09-08","Attorney General","2014-09-03","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 551W, on official visits, what domestic visits he and his predecessor have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208002","208002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90404","2014-09-08","Attorney General","2014-09-03","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions of (a) cyber and (b) cyber-enabled crimes have been initiated in each the last five years; and how many such prosecutions were successful.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208123","208123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90405","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to publish all the responses received to the Future of Apprenticeships in England: Funding Reform Technical Consultation, published in March 2014.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208118","208118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90406","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's priorities are in relation to the Digital Government Strategy in the individual performance objectives for 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208124","208124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90407","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 688W, on official visits, what domestic visits he has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208004","208004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90408","2014-09-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the recent trends in the number of university applications from students from disadvantaged or minority ethnic backgrounds.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207993","207993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90409","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) agency workers in executive agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208010","208010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90410","2014-09-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which organisations are the main occupants of his Department's properties at (a) Cannon House, Birmingham, (b) the NTI Building, Birmingham, (c) Queensway House, Billingham, (d) Stella House, Newcastle and (e) Westfield House, London; and what the value is of the total rent collected from all occupants in each of those buildings per year.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208022","208022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90411","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support the National Nuclear Laboratory's commercial opportunities abroad.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208039","208039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90412","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was spent on developing skills through training programmes and apprenticeships in the nuclear industry in each region of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208040","208040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90413","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people over 50 years old in each region and constituent part of the UK have been unemployed for over 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208076","208076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90414","2014-09-05","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what issues are currently under examination by the Horizon Scanning Programme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208051","208051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90415","2014-09-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will make it his policy to permit Local Enterprise Partnership Growth Deals to fund revenue as well as capital spending; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207995","207995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90416","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2014, Official Report, column 359W, on domestic visits, what domestic visits he has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208003","208003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90417","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, under what criteria the Big Society Network was contracted to run the Giving Summits.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208125","208125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90418","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Big Society Network has received for administering the Big Society Awards in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208126","208126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90419","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, against what criteria the Big Society Network was awarded the contract for running the Big Society Awards.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208127","208127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90420","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much has been given to the Big Society Network for the purpose of running the Giving Summit in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208128","208128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90421","2014-09-05","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what work the Horizon Scanning Programme has undertaken on the implications for environmental security of (a) an accident at a nuclear facility involving a large release of radiation and (b) the sabotage of a nuclear facility or nuclear cargo in transit by a terrorist group.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208053","208053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90422","2014-09-08","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance the Government Digital Service issues to department on minimum requirements for IT systems reliability and availability.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208089","208089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90423","2014-09-08","HM Treasury","2014-09-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent fiscal steps he has taken to support small and micro-sized businesses in Scotland.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208129","208129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90424","2014-09-08","HM Treasury","2014-09-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he has made on tackling tax avoidance in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208142","208142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90425","2014-09-08","HM Treasury","2014-09-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on the HMRC review into Simplified Import VAT Accounts.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207981","207981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90426","2014-09-08","HM Treasury","2014-09-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the ratio of average house prices to average wages was in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208073","208073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90427","2014-09-05","HM Treasury","2014-09-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the fuel discount scheme for rural communities.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207971","207971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90428","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what budget his Department has allocated to its Together in Service scheme.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208021","208021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90429","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what activities were undertaken by participants in his Department's A Year in Service scheme in 2012.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208023","208023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90430","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what activities are undertaken by participants in his Department's Together in Service scheme.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208024","208024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90431","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in receipt of (a) war disablement pension, (b) war widows pension, (c) war widowers pension, (d) guaranteed income payments, (e) survivor's guaranteed income payments he estimates pay increased council tax bills as a result of recent changes to council tax support in England.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208028","208028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90432","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average standard assessment procedure energy rating score of new build homes was in each quarter for which figures are available since April 2010.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208029","208029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90433","2014-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to promote community cohesion following the recent anti-Semitic incidents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208042","208042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90434","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning applications to develop urban green space have been approved in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208074","208074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90435","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many developments on designated urban green space have been approved under the National Planning Policy Framework, for which a local planning authority has not to set aside a five year supply of housing.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208081","208081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90436","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the rent arrears accrued by each registered social landlord in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208072","208072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90437","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) flats, (b) houses and (c) houses of multiple occupancy in the private rented sector in Warrington in each year since 2008; and what the cost was of privately renting a (a) one bedroom flat, (b) two bedroomed house and (c) room in a house of multiple occupancy in each such year.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208082","208082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90438","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support civic and voluntary organisations that promote integration and greater multi-ethnic understanding.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208056","208056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90439","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2014, Official Report, column 618W, on official visits, what domestic visits he has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208006","208006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90440","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total amount of uncollected council tax is in each London Borough in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207967","207967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90441","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many tenants exercised the right to buy in each local authority in Northumberland, Durham and Tyne and Wear in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207969","207969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90442","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of village or neighbourhood plans; and how many such plan have been lodged and accepted.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207990","207990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90443","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local planning authorities do not have an adopted local development framework in place.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208137","208137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90444","2014-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local planning authorities do not have an adopted local development framework in place.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208138","208138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90445","2014-09-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2014, Official Report, column 13W, on domestic visits, what domestic visits he and his predecessor has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208005","208005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90446","2014-09-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will have discussions with UEFA and FIFA on the Ebola infection risk arising from the decision to stage the Ivory Coast versus Sierra Leone football match on 6 September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208060","208060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90447","2014-09-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) agency workers in executive agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208011","208011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90448","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) management, (b) maintenance and (c) lost income costs of empty service accommodation were in each of the last five years; and what (i) size and (ii) type of properties have been vacant in that period.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208036","208036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90449","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to let the contracts for the managed service providers (MSP) before the end of September 2014; and if he will place relationship with the services and Defence Equipment and Support.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208062","208062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90450","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many nuclear warheads have been (a) lost and (b) lost and not recovered by NATO in the last 30 years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208050","208050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90451","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what process the Royal Navy uses when deciding the names of new vessels; and whether names of UK cities can be used for the Type 26.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208052","208052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90452","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Regular Army Reserve of Officers will play any role in his plans for an expanded Territorial Army; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Robertson","Sir Hugh Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208083","208083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90453","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members the Regular Army Reserve of Officers has.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Robertson","Sir Hugh Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208084","208084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90454","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the contract for the strategic business partnership between the Defence Infrastructure Organisation and Capita contains conditions on customer facing service and expected response times to enquiries.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208037","208037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90455","2014-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what current assessment he has made of the relevance of unreleased historical documents relating to Northern Ireland held at Swadlincote to the work of the Historical Enquiries Team in investigating cases from the past; and whether he plans to release these records to the National Archive under the Public Records Act 1958.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207980","207980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90456","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total budget of the Armoured Vehicles Programme has been in each year since 2010; and what estimate he has made of the budget of this programme in each year upto 2030.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208110","208110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90457","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to procure a class of Future Rapid Effects System Utility vehicles as part of the Armoured Vehicles Programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208112","208112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90458","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when a decision will be taken on the long-term future of Army Reserve bases which had originally been scheduled to be closed in 2016.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208104","208104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90459","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide details of each accident involving a nuclear weapon deployed outside of the US in support of NATO in the last 30 years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208054","208054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90460","2014-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department will spend in each year under the Challenger II Life Extension programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208108","208108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90461","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to broaden the number of foreign language subjects available to state school students in secondary education.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208097","208097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90462","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students in state schools secondary education obtained a GCSE in Mandarin Chinese in each year since Janaury 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208111","208111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90463","2014-09-09","Department for Education","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the role of schools in encouraging pupils to consider apprenticeships post-16.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207983","207983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90464","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will review the adequacy of current statutory guidance on the sharing of live birth data with children's centres.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208025","208025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90465","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking in response to research in the NSPCC's report, Returning home from care.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208034","208034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90466","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014, Official Report, column 551W, on disadvantaged pupils, what research her Department has commissioned into the role of special educational needs co-ordinators in decisions on how to spend the Pupil Premium; and for what reason no guidance was issued to schools on this matter.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208026","208026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90467","2014-09-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what further steps he plans to take to encourage the upgrade of boilers in off gas grid areas.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208043","208043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90469","2014-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many confidentiality agreements the Marine Management Organisation has sought in respect of third parties in (a) 2013-14 and (b) the current year.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208091","208091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90470","2014-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to ban the use of snares across the UK.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208115","208115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90471","2014-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will instruct the Marine Management Organisation (MMO) to publish the report on the investigation into the potential misuse or misapplication by the MMO of the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208090","208090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90472","2014-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on the Rural Community Broadband Fund initiative; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208116","208116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90473","2014-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether (a) she and (b) her predecessor had discussions with representatives of the agricultural and horticultural sectors on the potential effect on skills and recruitment into those sectors of the proposals to remove OCR environmental and land-based science from the curriculum; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207992","207992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90474","2014-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many quadcopters or similar remote controlled devices her Department has purchased; for what purpose such quadcopters were so purchased; and at what cost to the public purse such quadcopters were so purchased.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208032","208032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90475","2014-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she intends to publish the official report examining the causes of the 2013 horse meat scandal; and what the reason is for the delay in publication.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208030","208030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90476","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Saudi Arabian government over its financial and logistical support for Islamic State terrorists in Syria.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207997","207997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90477","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the effect of climate change on human rights in countries particularly affected by climate change.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208075","208075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90478","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he met the Secretary General of the Qatar 2022 Supreme Committee for Delivery and Legacy; and what plans he has for future meetings with that official.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208009","208009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90479","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on a link between pro-Russian rebels in Ukraine and the Russian government.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208105","208105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90480","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on further sanctions against Russia.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208107","208107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90481","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the situation in Lesotho; and what steps he is taking to support the reinstatement of democracy in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208095","208095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90482","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to protect staff working in HM embassies from security threats.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208094","208094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90483","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contingency plans are in place for the eventuality that Russia continues to place troops in Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208093","208093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90484","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the strength of business relations between the UK and Estonia.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208098","208098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90485","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the Israeli government in its campaign against Hamas.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208099","208099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90486","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have died in hospital in England from diseases contracted overseas since January 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208114","208114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90487","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the Health Protection Agency study on the health effects of emissions from municipal waste incinerators to be published.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208139","208139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90488","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to inform the public of the risk of contracting diseases from household pets.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208109","208109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90489","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has assessed or commissioned on whether e-cigarette vapour carries health risks to bystanders.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208087","208087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90490","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy on the regulation of mitochondrial replacement techniques of the conclusion of the public hearing of the US Food and Drugs Administration's Cellular, Tissues and Gene Therapies Advisory Committee on oocyte modification in assisted reproduction for the prevention of transmission of mitochondrial disease.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208088","208088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90491","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate potential savings to the NHS from more widespread use of e-cigarettes.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208086","208086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90492","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the reconfiguration of health services in Worcestershire and its effects on Alexandra Hospital, Redditch.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207986","207986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90493","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on the banning of smoking in cars and other vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207988","207988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90494","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on named GPs for NHS patients under the age of 75.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207968","207968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90495","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with the insurance industry on the allocation of monies for research into the elimination of mesothelioma.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207987","207987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90496","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the next step is in the commissioning of a specialised service after a positive recommendation by the Prescribed Specialised Services Advisory Group (PSSAG); whether services recommended for commissioning by PSSAG in September 2014 will be funded from April 2015; when the PSSAG recommendations on the application for a specialised service for Alpha-1 Antitrypsin Deficiency will be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208035","208035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90497","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he authorised the recent increase in the Cancer Drug Fund annual budget; and whether (a) the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group and the Direct Commissioned Service Committee and (b) the Patient and Public Voice Assurance Group were consulted before that decision was taken.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208020","208020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90498","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last discussed with the head of the UK Border Force the effectiveness of exit and entry checks in disrupting flows of those who are believed to be travelling to or returning from committing acts of terrorism overseas.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208027","208027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90499","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many quadcopters or similar remote controlled devices her Department has purchased; for what purpose such quadcopters were so purchased; and at what cost to the public purse such quadcopters were so purchased.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208031","208031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90500","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) agency workers in executive agencies which report to her Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208012","208012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90501","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the support given to the Cardiff Prevent priority area by the Office of Security and Counter Terrorism.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208017","208017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90502","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last discussed steps to tackle extremism with Ministers in the Welsh Government; and when the next such meeting is planned.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208018","208018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90503","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of (a) the All Wales Prevent Board and (b) the Wales CONTEST Board.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208019","208019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90504","2014-09-12","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to address the recent increase in anti-Semitism; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208041","208041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90505","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people had UK passports issued to them or renewed less than six months before they are known to have travelled to commit terrorist offences abroad in the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208045","208045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90506","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what she anticipates will be achieved by the trial of the new stop and search scheme by West Mercia Police.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207982","207982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90507","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of reforms proposed by her Department to the Riot (Damages) Act 1986 on the level of compensation paid to businesses.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208001","208001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90508","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of the closure and hours reductions of public counters at police stations.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207984","207984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90509","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the role of crime agencies in caring for and supporting people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207985","207985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90510","2014-09-05","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of British citizens who have travelled to (a) Syria and (b) Iraq and returned to the UK since January 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208100","208100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90511","2014-09-05","Cabinet Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the number of cyber-attacks on Government IT systems since January 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208102","208102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90512","2014-09-05","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been victims of anti-Semitic abuse which was reported to the police since January 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208103","208103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90513","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who absconded after apprehension by UK Border Force staff at ports of entry in each of the last three years were subsequently captured.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208121","208121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90514","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people detained at border ports of entry in each of the last three years were granted temporary admission.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208122","208122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90515","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were detained at border points of entry for (a) having a false passport, (b) having incorrect visa authorisation and (c) any other reason in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208119","208119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90516","2014-09-08","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people absconded from ports of entry after being stopped by UK Border Force staff in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208120","208120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90517","2014-09-05","Home Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to secure UK borders against terrorists travelling from overseas.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208096","208096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90518","2014-09-05","House of Commons Commission","2014-09-03","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what fees were charged by Saxton Bampfylde for the recruitment of the position of Clerk of the House and Chief Executive.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208047","208047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90519","2014-09-08","House of Commons Commission","2014-09-03","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many (a) direct, (b) outsourced and (c) agency employees on the Parliamentary estate are (i) paid less than the London living wage and (ii) employed on a zero-hours contract.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208038","208038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90520","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent support she has provided to countries in West Africa to help them with the recent ebola outbreak.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208068","208068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90521","2014-09-05","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the financial contribution to humanitarian aid and reconstruction in Gaza is spent on the purchase of goods and services from Israel.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208048","208048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90522","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to provide further support to West African countries to deal with the ebola outbreak.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208069","208069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90523","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the briefing given by Mdecins Sans Frontires at the UN on 2 September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208070","208070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90524","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with Mdecins Sans Frontires on the recent ebola outbreak.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208071","208071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90525","2014-09-05","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will promote innovative medical technologies and product development partnerships as part of the post-2015 development agenda.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208064","208064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90526","2014-09-05","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she plans to take to promote integrated healthcare structures and policy in the UN's post-2015 development agenda.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208063","208063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90527","2014-09-08","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is giving to (a) Sierra Leone and (b) other countries in West Africa to them help counter the outbreak of Ebola; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208085","208085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90528","2014-09-05","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what action her Department is taking to help tackle the ebola epidemic in West Africa; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208061","208061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90529","2014-09-05","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the level of UK aid in Ukraine since January 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208106","208106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90530","2014-09-05","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her international counterparts on including product development partnerships in the post-2015 development agenda.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208065","208065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90531","2014-09-05","Department for International Development","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on the potential role of product development partnerships in the post-2015 development agenda.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208066","208066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90532","2014-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will seek to ensure that the courts' administrations when a defendant has been given a custodial sentence do not send confidential information to an address where there is a risk it might be read by unauthorised persons such as a new tenant but instead to a person nominated by the prisoner such as next-of-kin or to the prisoner's legal representative.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208067","208067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90533","2014-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the regulation of claims management companies for insurance purposes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207972","207972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90534","2014-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of tobacco-related fraud in (a) Medway, (b) Kent and (c) England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207998","207998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90535","2014-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people received a custodial sentence for selling illicit tobacco in (a) Medway, (b) Kent and (c) England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207999","207999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90536","2014-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of repeat offenders for selling illicit tobacco.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208000","208000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90537","2014-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copy of the National Annual Report of Magistrate Training mentioned in the Quarter 3 performance report of the Judicial College; and whether subsequent training reports will be published.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207996","207996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90538","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Defence since 16 October 2013 regarding the release of documents relating to Northern Ireland held at Swadlincote under the 30 year rule.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207977","207977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90539","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the First and Deputy First Minister in Northern Ireland; and what issues were discussed.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207978","207978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90540","2014-09-08","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the First and Deputy First Minister in Northern Ireland regarding the killings in Ballymurphy in West Belfast in August 1971.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207979","207979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90541","2014-09-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she had with US Senator Gary Hart when he visited Northern Ireland in the last week of August 2014; and what the subjects were for discussion.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207974","207974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90542","2014-09-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Justice and the Minister of Justice in Northern Ireland on the regulation of claims management companies in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207975","207975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90543","2014-09-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what (a) discussions and (b) correspondence she has had with the Parades Commission on summer parades in North Belfast since 11 July 2014.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207973","207973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90544","2014-09-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will undertake a review of the condition of the RUC George Cross Association memorial at the National Memorial in Staffordshire; and if she will takes steps to ensure that resources are allocated for the upkeep and maintenance of that memorial.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208057","208057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90545","2014-09-05","Prime Minister","2014-09-03","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to his Statement of 1 September 2014, Official Report, column 34, what the evidential basis is for his statement that the Saudi authorities have changed their approach on radicalisation around the world; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208049","208049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90546","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that foreign drivers are subject to the same penalties as British drivers upon failure to produce relevant CPC documentation.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207991","207991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90547","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps are being taken to ensure safety on Northern Rail and TransPennine Express trains running driver-only operations.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207965","207965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90548","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many complaints his Department has received from people in Northern Ireland about the DVLA since July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208059","208059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90549","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the confidence of drivers in the information conveyed by dot matrix information signs on motorways and trunk roads.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208046","208046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90550","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Highways Agency has been subject to legal challenge by a local authority in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208080","208080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90551","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of (a) men, (b) women and (c) child cyclists suffered (i) fatal and (ii) serious injuries in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208079","208079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90552","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) direct employees, (b) outsourced workers and (c) agency workers in executive agencies which report to his Department are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208013","208013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90553","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of whether the new Northern Franchise will take account of increased connectivity to Reddish South and Denton arising from the better use of existing infrastructure through those stations.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208033","208033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90554","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that motorway information signs convey information that is up-to-date and accurate.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208055","208055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90555","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were injured as a result of staff negligence at railway stations in each year since January 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208101","208101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90556","2014-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the National Rail framework agreement published on 1 September 2014, when he plans to lay the draft regulations to make Network Rail subject to the Freedom of Information Act 2000; and under what parliamentary procedure he plans to ask the House to approve those regulations.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208117","208117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90557","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the National Rail framework agreement published on 1 September 2014, when the National Audit Office will have access to Network Rail's accounts.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208092","208092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90558","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) land and (b) buildings of what value belonging to the Coastguard Service have been sold since May 2010.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208130","208130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90559","2014-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reasons are for the time taken to lay regulations to make Network Rail subject to the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208131","208131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90560","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the benefit-cost ratios for each of the schemes funded in the 1.5 billion works commissioned to improve the A14.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208132","208132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90561","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what weighting was given to environmental benefits when calculating the benefit-cost ratio for each of the schemes funded in the 1.5 billion works commissioned to improve the A14.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208133","208133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90562","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were killed on unmanned rail track crossings in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208113","208113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90563","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the methodology behind the benefit-cost ratios calculated for each of the schemes funded in the 1.5 billion works commissioned to improve the A14.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208134","208134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90564","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions officials in his Department have had with Network Rail on the timetable for temporary closure of Blackpool North station in relation to the electrification of line track in the last two months.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208140","208140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90565","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions officials in his Department have had with Network Rail on the implications of the works at and around Blackpool North station for (a) capacity, (b) flexibility and (c) frequency of services in and out of Blackpool North station.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208141","208141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90566","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish in full the public responses to the consultation on the future franchise proposals covering routes currently served by Northern and Transpennine Express trains; and if he will publish, either in summary or full, the responses to that consultation before any decision on the award of the new franchises.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208135","208135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90567","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many businesses have been created with help from the New Enterprise Allowance; and how many of those businesses have sustained operations for more than 52 weeks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208044","208044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90568","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy that a person in receipt of carer's allowance may claim that allowance for each person cared for.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208016","208016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90569","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which recommendations made by the Work Programme Best Practice Group have been (a) fully implemented, (b) partially implemented and (c) not implemented; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208078","208078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90570","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent on the Flexible Support Fund in each region of the UK in each year since it was introduced.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208077","208077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90571","2014-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions his Department has had discussions with the Social Development Department in Northern Ireland on the implementation of the welfare reforms in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208058","208058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90572","2014-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the personal independence payment application process is accessible to deafblind people who are unable to make a claim over the telephone or complete paper forms.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207966","207966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90573","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there has been in the level of arrears in the social housing sector since April 2013.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207989","207989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90574","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value is of payments made directly to landlords for universal credit claimants in (a) total and (b) each local authority.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208007","208007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90575","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of universal credit claimants have a payment made directly to their landlord.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208008","208008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90576","2014-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the latest performance rating assigned to universal credit by the Major Projects Authority is.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207970","207970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90577","2014-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that it communicates with deafblind people in accessible ways, including information about preferred means of communication and sending information in the formats requested by deafblind claimants.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207976","207976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90578","2014-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, column 278W, on personal independence payment, what progress he has made since that Answer on ensuring that no applicant for personal independence payment waits more than 16 weeks for an assessment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207994","207994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90579","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he will take to ensure that evaluations of the Work Programme look at its performance for ethnic minority jobseekers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208014","208014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90580","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the carer's allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208015","208015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91124","2014-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of recent changes to legal aid.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905251","905251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91125","2014-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the Government's strategy is on the future of the Probation Service.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905255","905255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91126","2014-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what forecasts the Government has made of future trends in the prison population.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905252","905252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91127","2014-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of his plans for youth custody on (a) young children and (b) girls.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905254","905254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91128","2014-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there will be sufficient prison places available for those offenders given custodial sentences over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905253","905253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90237","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the likelihood of use by Israeli forces of equipment containing UK components in breaches of international humanitarian law in the West Bank and Gaza Strip; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207825","207825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90238","2014-09-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what effect the introduction of 24 Plus Advanced Learning Loans has had on student participation levels.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207828","207828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90239","2014-09-08","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the extent to which employers use self-employed staff to avoid paying national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207809","207809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90240","2014-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the level of variation of health and safety regulations between local authorities and of the effect of such variation on small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207810","207810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90241","2014-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) civilian staff of his Department based in the UK, (b) military personnel based in the UK, (c) civilian staff of his Department based in Saudi Arabia and (d) military personnel based in Saudi Arabia were employed by the (i) Saudi Arabian National Guard Communications Project and (ii) Ministry of Defence Saudi Armed Forces Project on 1 April 2014; and what the function is of each of those projects.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207819","207819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90242","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's press notice of 16 July 2014 on pupil premium reform, to which 87 local authorities where performance of disadvantaged pupils is a concern the Minister of State for Schools wrote.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207950","207950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90244","2014-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that laws relating to the export of live animals are adhered to at ports; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207829","207829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90245","2014-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions there have been in England and Wales in the last five years for failure to comply with the collar and tag requirements in the Control of Dogs Order 1992.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207820","207820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90246","2014-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the level of biomass power generation in the UK located in (a) urban areas and (b) areas of above average atmospheric pollution; and if her Department will publish that information.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207821","207821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90247","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of his Department's work on climate change; and what future steps his Department plans to take to support international action on climate change.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207805","207805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90248","2014-09-08","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of regulation of the comestic industry; and whether he plans to propose further regulations relating to that industry.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207808","207808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90249","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the policy of the NHS is on providing hearing aids for adults with mild to moderate hearing loss.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207818","207818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90250","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect that proposed changes to tariffs for Renal Dialysis in Monitor's 2015/16 National Tariff Payments System: Engagement on national prices consultation would have on health outcomes for kidney patients.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207813","207813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90251","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with patients' groups on changes to tariffs for Renal Dialysis in Monitor's 2015/16 National Tariff Payments System: Engagement on national prices consultation.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207814","207814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90252","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to make stakeholders aware of its 2015/16 National Tariff Payments System: Engagement on national prices consultation.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207815","207815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90253","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the efficacy of Return to Practice courses by healthcare providers to address workforce supply needs and alleviate the need for the recruitment of health professional staff from overseas.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207816","207816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90254","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will adopt the latest Inflammatory Bowel Disease Standards Group standards for the care of patients with the condition.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207822","207822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90255","2014-09-05","Home Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date section 65 of the Immigration Act 2014 will be brought into force.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207807","207807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90256","2014-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of courtrooms do not have induction loops installed.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207804","207804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90257","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to make an announcement on improvements to the Nottingham to Lincoln line.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207826","207826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90258","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost of proposals to turn the Highways Agency into a public company.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207827","207827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90259","2014-09-04","Department for Transport","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the need for extra capacity on the Crewe-Derby rail line.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207817","207817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90260","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of whether Merseyrail has an appropriate emergency response plan to deal with a terrorist attack on the rail network; and on what date the last Merseyrail emergency response drill was carried out.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207806","207806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90261","2014-09-05","Department for Transport","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date he plans to publish the conclusions to research into tyre-ageing on buses and coaches that he commissioned in December 2013.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207824","207824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90262","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the roadworks on the M1 motorway north of junction 28 to be completed and the stretch of the M1 between that junction and the M18 to be totally devoid of roadworks.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207811","207811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90263","2014-09-08","Department for Transport","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason the Highways Agency closed the M180 in August 2014; and if he will direct the Highways Agency to take steps to prevent a re-occurrence of that closure during future holiday periods.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207812","207812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90264","2014-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the total overpayments being collected by the Financial Assistance Scheme from recalculations of annual entitlement related to services after 1997 and any changes to annuity or notional annuity income.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207917","207917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90265","2014-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department issues on the funding and allocation of support for deaf people in work.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207823","207823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90266","2014-09-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that graduates have the right skills for the jobs available.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207834","207834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90267","2014-09-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with small and medium-sized enterprises on the planned changes to the funding of the apprenticeship scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207865","207865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90268","2014-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the demand for biomass for combustion in the UK is met by imports.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207889","207889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90269","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information he holds on the proportion of wood pellets imported from North America that were derived from roundwood in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207891","207891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90270","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information he holds on the level of wood pellet imports from (a) the USA and (b) Canada in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207892","207892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90271","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of late payments on small and medium-sized businesses (SMEs); and whether his Department plans to bring forward any further measures to assist in SMEs with cash flow.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207890","207890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90272","2014-09-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made in carrying out an equality analysis on proposals to change the disabled students' allowance.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207902","207902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90273","2014-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many youth rate jobseeker's allowance claimants have been referred for sanction while they undertake a traineeship since August 2013.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207912","207912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90274","2014-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps are taken against a claimant of youth rate jobseeker's allowance who leaves a traineeship before it was completed.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207935","207935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90275","2014-09-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applications are made on average before (a) a white and (b) an ethnic minority applicant secures an apprenticeship.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207941","207941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90277","2014-09-05","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many occasions HM Revenue and Customs has formally objected to the renewal of a retailer's alcohol licence for selling illicit tobacco in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207964","207964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90278","2014-09-05","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many arrests HM Revenue and Customs has made in (a) Medway and (b) Kent for offences relating to the sale of illicit cigarettes in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207962","207962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90279","2014-09-05","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many occasions a lottery retailing licence has been removed for selling illicit (a) cigarettes and (b) alcohol in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207963","207963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90280","2014-09-05","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of cigarettes on which tax has not been paid in (a) Gillingham and Rainham constituency, (b) Kent and (c) England in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207961","207961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90281","2014-09-05","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether households comprising (a) one disabled parent unable to work and another parent in work and (b) a single disabled parent will be entitled to receive help through tax free childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207930","207930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90282","2014-09-04","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the money accrued to the public purse through VAT paid on the repair and maintenance of protected buildings.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207896","207896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90283","2014-09-04","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the money accrued to the public purse through VAT paid on approved alterations to protected buildings in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207897","207897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90284","2014-09-04","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs tax reviews of large companies have revealed instances of significant evasion in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207833","207833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90285","2014-09-04","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Excise Payment Security System has been approved for use by individual retail petrol filling stations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207850","207850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90286","2014-09-04","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been disbursed to oil supply companies for the repayment of duty on petrol subject to vapour recovery since January 2013.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207842","207842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90287","2014-09-04","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Excise Payment Security Systems have been approved for retail petrol filling stations in 2014.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207843","207843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90288","2014-09-04","HM Treasury","2014-09-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many small and medium-sized businesses have been subject to an HM Revenue and Customs tax review in each of the last three years; and in how many cases such a review has revealed significant errors in the accounts of such a business.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207832","207832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90289","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many expressions of interest were (a) received and (b) considered by his Department in response to the locally-led Garden Cities Prospectus before 1 September 2014.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207857","207857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90290","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons his Department's work with local areas to understand barriers to building new locally-led garden cities as set out in the Garden Cities Prospectus is overdue in starting.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207858","207858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90291","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how frequently the information on the current status of actions in his Department's business plan shown on www.transparency.number10.gov.uk/business-plan/2 is updated; and when that information was most recently updated.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207861","207861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90292","2014-09-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will issue guidance to the Planning Inspectorate on decisions where the location of a planning appeal is within an Area of Outstanding Natural Beauty.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207849","207849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90293","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will review the way in which local authorities carry out their responsibilities for corporate parenting and take any steps needed to ensure that training for councillors involved in that role is both adequate and up-to-date.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207873","207873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90294","2014-09-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that all councils review their procedures for dealing with the sexual exploitation of children following the report on Rotherham Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207872","207872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90295","2014-09-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of rent arrears accrued by each registered social landlord in (a) Liverpool and (b) Liverpool Riverside in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207915","207915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90296","2014-09-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions (a) he and (b) Ofcom have had with BT on increases in charges for line rental and broadband products.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207831","207831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90297","2014-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps are taken to ensure that ammunition used on firing ranges is fully and properly accounted for; and what amount of ammunition has not been accounted for in each of the three services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207920","207920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90298","2014-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what commercial, project management and engineering role vacancies there were in his Department (a) in March 2014 and (b) on the latest date for which data is available.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207918","207918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90299","2014-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made towards meeting the assumed savings in the (a) Complex Weapons Programme and (b) Submarine Enterprise Performance programme; and how much has been saved through each such programme to date.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207919","207919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90300","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the results of the report on her Department's childminder agency pilots.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207947","207947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90301","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish detailed information on what work her Department has undertaken to implement paragraphs 10.49 and 10.55 of the Government's Review of the Prevent Agenda, published in June 2011; and if she will publish any assessments conducted into the effectiveness of that work.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207953","207953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90302","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Education Act 2011 in achieving the aims set out in paragraph 10.53 of the Government's Review of the Prevent Agenda, published in June 2011.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207954","207954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90303","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) childminders and (b) parents responded to the IPSOS Mori and Ecorys survey on childminder agencies; when the results of the survey will be published; and how likely (i) childminders and (ii) parents who responded to the survey were to use a childminder agency.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207951","207951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90304","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that children who have been looked after because of abuse or neglect receive appropriate support and monitoring to prevent further abuse when they return home.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207911","207911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90305","2014-09-05","Department for Education","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the large nursery chains offer funded places for two year olds as part of the Government's free 15 hours of early education for disadvantaged two year olds; and how many such places are offered in England.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207942","207942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90306","2014-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will place in the Library a copy of the internal review by her Department which upheld an appeal against the use of regulation 12(5)(c) of the Environmental Information Regulations 2004 in relation to the results of the post-mortems carried out on badgers killed during the pilot culls.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207957","207957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90307","2014-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will place in the Library a copy of the internal review by her Department which upheld an appeal against the use of regulation 12(5)(c) for the protection of intellectual property to prevent the release of the results of the post-mortems carried out on badgers killed during the pilot culls.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207952","207952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90308","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the threat to the safety of British seafarers and others from piracy (a) in the Gulf of Guinea and (b) elsewhere; and what his strategy is for reducing that threat.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207946","207946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90309","2014-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in the Maldives; and if he will make representations to the government of that country on the kidnap of the journalist Ahmed Rilwan Abdulla.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207944","207944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90310","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the UN is taking to highlight the ongoing persecution of Christian communities in the Middle East and assist those so persecuted.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207878","207878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90311","2014-09-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assist in the maintenance of peace and stability in Lesotho.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207877","207877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90312","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will fund the provision of a minimum of 1.5 specialist irritable bowel syndrome nurses per 250,000 people.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207847","207847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90313","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with professional medical bodies on the implications for the NHS of research on the effects of taking aspirin on the likelihood of heart attacks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207836","207836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90314","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the challenges experienced by NHS hospitals in recruiting consultant radiologists.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207830","207830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90315","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to section 17 of the NHS Terms and Conditions of Service handbook, amendment number 33, what assessment he has made of the effects of the change in the fuel allowance to 20 pence per mile on retention of nurses in the NHS.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207860","207860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90316","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the decrease in incidence of (a) HIV, (b) tuberculosis and (c) malaria continues.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207835","207835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90317","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to fund hearing aids for people with mild to moderate hearing loss; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207841","207841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90318","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged (a) 30 to 40, (b) 41 to 60 and (c) over 60 have been diagnosed with varicose veins in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207837","207837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90319","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in what age group have been funded for proton beam therapy in each of the last five years; and in what location each person was so treated.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207871","207871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90320","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the quantum of premature death in the UK caused by the emission of wood smoke; and whether he plans to publish that information.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207855","207855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90321","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs (a) excluding retainers and registrars and (b) including retainers but excluding registrars there were in the financial year (i) 2009-10 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207856","207856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90322","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of radiologists in training.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207854","207854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90323","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups currently commission specialised multiple sclerosis centres.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207925","207925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90324","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the physical care of patients in mental health facilities is safeguarded.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207926","207926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90325","2014-09-05","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will have discussions with the travel insurance industry about including cover for mental health problems as standard in travel insurance policies.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207927","207927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90326","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged over 50 were on NHS hospital waiting lists for in-patient treatment on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr John Whittingdale","Mr John Whittingdale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207898","207898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90327","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate (a) his Department and (b) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) have made of the savings to the NHS which have resulted from NICE rejecting treatments for routine use on the NHS; if he will list for each medicine which NICE has rejected for use on the NHS in the last four years the estimated cost saving which resulted from that decision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207914","207914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90328","2014-09-04","Department of Health","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Eddisbury of 8 July 2014, Official Report, column 237W, on medical treatments, which appraisals conducted by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence in the last four years resulted in a recommendation to use a medicine on the NHS and specified criteria for starting and stopping treatment with that medicine; which starting and stopping criteria were applied in each case; for what conditions each such treatment was recommended in each case; what the estimated eligible patient population was for each recommended treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207916","207916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90329","2014-09-05","Home Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total amount spent on the Prevent programme was in each of the last five years; and how much of that was allocated via local authorities in each such year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207956","207956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90330","2014-09-05","Home Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of rape on university campuses were reported to the police in each year since 2004; and how many reported cases led to successful prosecutions.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207936","207936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90331","2014-09-05","Home Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many organisations have received funding from her Department to deliver the Channel programme in each of the last five years; and what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the programmes delivered by each such organisation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207904","207904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90332","2014-09-05","Home Office","2014-09-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been referred to the Channel strand of the Prevent programme in each of the last five years; how many people completed the programme to which they were referred in each of those years; how many of those people were referred to the Channel programme because they were feared to have been radicalised abroad or taken part in terrorist-related activity abroad; what the (a) gender and (b) age was of those referred to the Channel programme; and how many people from each region were so referred.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 207905","207905"
