"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444171","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Carbon Price Floor tax on energy intensive industries.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22137","22137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444172","2016-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to fund the development of clean energy sources.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22024","22024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444173","2016-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what support her Department plans to provide to ensure that proposed biomass combined heat and power schemes are not affected by changes to the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22041","22041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444174","2016-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria her Department plans to use to determine which biomass combined heat and power schemes receive support under the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22042","22042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444175","2016-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when her Department plans to publish the terms of reference for its Renewable Heat Incentive consultation.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22043","22043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444176","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of particulate matter pollution; and what account her Department took of such trends when developing its air quality plan.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22045","22045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444177","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to issue guidance on the maximum length of time that a charging Clean Air Zone could be operated on a voluntary basis.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22046","22046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444178","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding will be allocated to local authorities to undertake scoping studies related to the establishment of Clean Air Zones.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22047","22047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444179","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will set standards for the implementation of a low emission strategy in those areas currently exceeding EU nitrogen dioxide emissions limits which will not be part of the five Clean Air Zones.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22048","22048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444180","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will simplify the fishing licence regime to expand fishing as a sport.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22080","22080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444181","2016-01-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department plans to review its policy on the safety of private firework use in residential areas.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22049","22049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444182","2016-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the total paid out by his Department in flood compensation grants to households who were not entitled to such payments in the last six weeks.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22026","22026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444183","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce the occurrence of ash dieback disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22023","22023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444184","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's policy is on the use of neonicotinoids, when that policy was last updated; and what plans she has to revise that policy.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22166","22166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444185","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has allocated to (a) capital investment in and (b) maintenance flood protection schemes in (i) Barnsley East constituency, (ii) Barnsley, (iii) South Yorkshire and (iv) Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22167","22167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444186","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of her Department's budget for (a) capital investment and (b) maintenance flood protection schemes in (i) Barnsley East constituency, (ii) Barnsley, (iii) South Yorkshire and (iv) Yorkshire and the Humber in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22169","22169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444187","2016-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21375 on flooding control: per capita costs, what official data sets were used for her calculations in that Answer.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22215","22215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444188","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what financial support her Department provides to livestock farmers to mitigate the development of antibiotic resistance; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22094","22094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444189","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will renew its strategy for the abolition of the death penalty.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22083","22083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444190","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold discussions with his counterparts in the government of (a) Jamaica and (b) Trinidad and Tobago on the abolition of the death penalty.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22075","22075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444191","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will update his Department's travel advice guidance on the safety of women travellers to (a) Germany and (b) Austria to take account of recent events in those countries.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22151","22151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444192","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the extension of the term of office of the President of the Kurdistan Regional Government in Iraq, following the legal expiration of his term of office.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22139","22139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444193","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant the Answer of 4 December 2015 to Question 18424, whether the Syrian-led negotiations under UN auspices have begun; what the status is of these talks; and which parties are involved in such talks.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22106","22106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444194","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed with his Kurdish counterparts the detention of Esa Barzani and other critics in Kurdistan.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22127","22127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444195","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Kurdistan counterpart on the current status of the parliament of the Kurdistan region of Iraq.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22128","22128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444196","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on whether the speaker of the parliament of the Kurdistan region of Iraq is being impeded in fulfilling his role.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22129","22129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444197","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the UN to ensure the promotion of gender parity, equality and diversity in the selection process for the next Secretary General.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22208","22208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444198","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the UN to ensure a more open and transparent selection process of the next Secretary-General.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22209","22209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444199","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons his Department has decided not to include Saudi Arabia in its Strategy for the Abolition of the Death Penalty.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22222","22222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444200","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Government's current strategy on Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22185","22185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444201","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the money received from the European Union Solidarity Fund has been returned to the EU in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22220","22220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444202","2016-01-18","HM Treasury","2016-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money the UK has received from the European Union Solidarity Fund in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22219","22219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444203","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance his Department has issued for holidaymakers to advise them to take out appropriate winter sports insurance cover.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22144","22144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444204","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political, economic and security situation in the Kurdistan region of Iraq.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22140","22140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444205","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the reasons for the prolonged recess of the parliament of the Kurdistan region of Iraq.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22141","22141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444206","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) Afghan and (b) Pakistani government on reducing the influence of the Taliban in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22018","22018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444207","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the UN and other agencies on (a) encouraging the establishment of an international, independent and impartial mechanism to investigate allegations of violations of international humanitarian and human rights law in Yemen and (b) applying pressure on parties to the conflict in Yemen to end the use of explosive weapons in populated areas.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22037","22037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444208","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received any reports of any potential breaches of international humanitarian law from UK personnel working with the Saudi military.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22031","22031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444209","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Saudi Arabia about the death sentence of Abdullah al-Zaher.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22029","22029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444210","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to publish the next quarterly progress report to the House on Syria.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22030","22030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444211","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the UN and the International Criminal Court to ensure they take action in cases in which civilian populations are besieged and deprived of food and medicines as a method of waging war.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22057","22057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444212","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of China on its recent decision to land civilian planes on Fiery Cross reef in the disputed South China Sea.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22062","22062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444213","2016-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision of China to land civilian planes on Fiery Cross reef in the disputed South China Sea on regional relationships.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22063","22063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444214","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress his Department has made on representations to the Italian government on guaranteeing that UK citizens working as teachers at universities in Italy who have had financial aspects of their contracts breached by their employers receive redress and equitable treatment.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22055","22055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444215","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability of access to fertility treatments in the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22070","22070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444216","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients at North Tees and Hartlepool NHS Foundation Trust received fertility treatments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22071","22071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444217","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to increase awareness of (a) arthritis and (b) other musculoskeletal conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22088","22088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444218","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were diagnosed with primary refractory acute megakaryoblastic leukaemia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22013","22013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444219","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on the provision of precautionary mastectomies for women who have not been diagnosed with breast cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22014","22014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444220","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with (a) anxiety and (b) depression in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22015","22015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444221","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on steps to reduce the fat intake of people with diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22007","22007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444222","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people there were with epilepsy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22008","22008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444223","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with incontinence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22009","22009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444224","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to make the Attiva device for the treatment of people with diabetes available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22010","22010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444225","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to provide paramedics with on-the-spot blood diagnostic devices for the detection of medical conditions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22011","22011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444226","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many children have died due to accidents related to blind cords in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22012","22012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444227","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the negative interim NICE Appraisal Committee Decision on nivolumab for squamous non-small cell lung cancer on patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22162","22162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444228","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients are receiving nivolumab for locally advanced or metastatic squamous non-small cell lung cancer in (a) England and (b) Strangford; and when NICE plans to complete its appraisal of that drug.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22163","22163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444229","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that NICE work with the manufacturers of nivolumab to ensure patients with lung cancer can access that medicine at the earliest opportunity.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22164","22164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444230","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce errors in the dispensing of aseptic pharmaceutical products.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22179","22179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444231","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of aseptic pharmaceutical medication error within the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22180","22180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444232","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has a policy on standardising the dose branding of aseptic pharmaceutical products across all health trusts.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22181","22181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444233","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential role of technology in reducing aseptic pharmaceutical medication error.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22182","22182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444234","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when HIV Pre-Exposure Prophylaxis will be made available on the NHS to men who have sex with men.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22187","22187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444235","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people in England accessing HIV Pre-Exposure Prophylaxis through private provision.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22188","22188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444236","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department took to publicise the recent NHS Mandate Consultation.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22200","22200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444237","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the status is of Operational Resilience Capacity Planning for 2014-15; and what the status is of the retained funding for flu vaccinations for clinicians in the independent sector.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22193","22193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444238","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average hospital waiting time was for NHS patients in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Yorkshire and the Humber since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22210","22210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444239","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents of accident and emergency departments diverting admissions to other hospitals there were in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22211","22211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444240","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2016 to Question 20755, when the visits to clinical commissioning groups referred to in that question are planned to start; and when he expects the findings of such visits to be reported to him.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22206","22206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444241","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients were admitted to mental health beds in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010; and how many such patients in each location were diverted to other hospitals for admission over the same period.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22212","22212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444242","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many children in (a) England and Wales, (b) London and (c) each London borough died from asthma in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22107","22107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444243","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to promote independent mental health advocacy.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22086","22086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444244","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals in (a) Devon and (b) Cornwall have round the clock mental health support.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22087","22087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444245","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 26 November 2014 to Question 215220, what information his Department holds on further research on the use of dogs to detect cancer.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22156","22156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444246","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21144, anti-depressants: children, when the capability referred to is expected to be introduced; and whether anti-depressants will be included in the information concerned.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22160","22160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444247","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in England and Wales are on long-term prescriptions of more than four weeks for benzodiazepines.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22161","22161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444248","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health trusts (a) Simon Stevens and (b) Sir Bruce Keogh have visited in each year since their appointments as Chief Executive and Medical Director respectively of NHS England; and on what dates they visited which health trusts in which locations.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22157","22157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444249","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of extra funding for relationship support of 11 January 2016, how many hours of support will be provided to each couple; and whether there will be a financial cost to each couple for that support.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22158","22158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444250","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21142, when (a) the provisional data referred to will be finalised and (b) the next set of data will be released.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22159","22159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444251","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken, subsequent to its accepting recommendation 274 of the Francis report on the Mid Staffordshire NHS Foundation Trust Public Enquiry, published on 6 February 2013, to (a) issue guidance to NHS Trusts and their legal advisers and (b) monitor implementation of that guidance on disclosure of information to coroners, patients and families.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22149","22149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444252","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase awareness of Pulmonary Arterial Hypertension.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22074","22074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444253","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on medical nutrition in end of life care in each of the last five years; and what estimate he has made of such spending in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22111","22111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444254","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to recruit and retain embryologists in the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22072","22072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444255","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission a review into the working hours of junior doctors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22117","22117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444256","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will mandate that nutrition is written into all national care pathways for long-term conditions.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22114","22114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444257","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department and (b) NHS England is taking to ensure that patients who cannot consume food in the normal way are receiving the correct treatment through tube and sip feeds.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22112","22112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444258","2016-01-18","Department of Health","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to ensure that medical nutrition is integrated into end of life care pathways in clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22113","22113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444259","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2015 to Question 8917, what recent assessment she has made of the performance of the Disclosure and Barring service; and what the average processing time is for disclosure applications.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22099","22099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444260","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national offenders were removed from Northern Ireland in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22154","22154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444261","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20367, what the educational basis is of adults adopting safer online behaviours; and under what cost headings the Cyber Streetwise campaign spent its funds in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22101","22101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444262","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what she has allocated to the Strategic Communications Plan supporting the Psychoactive Substances Bill.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22184","22184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444263","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to encourage volunteers to monitor CCTV to help the police service.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22186","22186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444264","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants for asylum who have been served with a deportation or removal order have been allowed safe passage back to the UK after the order has taken effect in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22136","22136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444265","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on reducing the illegal movement and sale of high-powered semi-automatic weapons.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22017","22017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444266","2016-01-18","Home Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the terrorism threat level for events at major sports stadiums.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22064","22064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444267","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many recorded suicides there were by (a) men of black and minority ethnic background and (b) women of black and minority ethnic background in each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22059","22059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444268","2016-01-18","Cabinet Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many recorded suicides there were by (a) men under 18, (b) men aged 18 to 30, (c) men aged over 30, (d) women under 18, (e) women aged 18 to 30 and (f) women aged over 30 in each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22060","22060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444269","2016-01-14","Department for International Development","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding and other support her Department has given for UN agencies, non-governmental agencies and civil society to (a) identify children at risk of human rights violations in Yemen, (b) support the development and implementation of programmes to secure the release and rehabilitation of children associated with armed groups and (c) respond to other violations of children's rights in that country.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22039","22039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444270","2016-01-14","Department for International Development","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the access of (a) all children in Yemen and (b) children displaced by the conflict in that country to high-quality education.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22040","22040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444271","2016-01-14","Department for International Development","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken with the UN and others to establish a regular, scheduled UN-facilitated cargo flight service into Yemen.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22038","22038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444272","2016-01-14","Department for International Development","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure the economic empowerment of women in the developing world.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22195","22195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444273","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to introduce a Victims' Law since May 2015.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22199","22199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444274","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to his contribution during the Urgent Question on 11 January 2016, Official Report, column 1573, when he was first made aware of the allegations made by Panorama about Medway Secure Training College.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22204","22204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444275","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications by grandparents for permission to apply for a child arrangement order were active in the final quarter of 2015.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22214","22214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444276","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times pest controllers have been called to each prison and youth estate in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22108","22108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444277","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) prosecuted, (b) convicted and (c) given a prison sentence for money laundering in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22147","22147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444278","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) largest fine levied and (b) longest prison sentence handed down in respect of a conviction for money laundering has been in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22148","22148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444279","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce tele-teaching in prisons and young offending facilities to improve general education and reduce reoffending rates.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22076","22076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444280","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government plans to review legislation on joint enterprise.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22058","22058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444281","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the Armed Forces Covenant applies to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22172","22172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444282","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of the Armed Forces Covenant has been enacted in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22173","22173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444283","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the reasons for delays in the full implementation of the Armed Forces Covenant in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22174","22174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444284","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) number and (b) quality of Overseas Territories' adoptions of public registers of beneficial ownership since his meetings with them on 15 June 2013 and his letter to them on 24 April 2014.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22027","22027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444285","2016-01-18","Scotland Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22067","22067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444286","2016-01-18","Scotland Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Statement of 11 January 2016 on the Smith Commission Agreement, HCWS458, what the (a) dates, (b) minutes and (c) outcomes was of any discussions or meeting held since 28 November 2014 on issues relating to asylum seekers with (i) Home Office Ministers and (ii) Ministers or Officials of the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22198","22198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444287","2016-01-18","Scotland Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Written Statement of 11 January 2016, HCWS458, what steps his Government has taken to implement the Smith Commission's recommendation to explore the possibility of introducing formal schemes to allow international higher education students graduating from Scottish further and higher education institutions to remain in Scotland and contribute to economic activity for a defined period of time; whether he has consulted with Scottish further and higher education institutions on this matter; and (c) for what reasons his Department has not discussed this matter with the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22102","22102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444288","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2015 to Question 21125, what estimate he has made of the remaining track that will be electrified in connection with the programmes and projects that will go ahead for delivery by 2019 and were referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22103","22103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444289","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of passengers forecast to use the rail network in each of the next 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22093","22093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444290","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the economic effect of delays to rail services into London Victoria from the Sussex coast in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22121","22121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444291","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the total amount of time passengers were delayed on rail services from the Sussex coast into London Victoria in 2015.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22120","22120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444292","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to extend railway network services between London and Okehampton.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22085","22085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444293","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applicants there were to the Advanced Biofuel Demonstration Competition; how many such applicants were successful; and what funding under what structure each successful applicant received.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22116","22116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444294","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated cost to his Department has been of evaluating the Airports Commission's Final Report since 1 July 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22175","22175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444295","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has received representations from the Mayor of London on his concerns about the number of private hire vehicles being licensed each month in London.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22142","22142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444296","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has conducted a comparative assessment of the loss of life as a result of an aircraft crashing on approach or arrival at Heathrow and Gatwick airports.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22134","22134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444297","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to provide the Mayor of London with the powers to place a cap on private hire vehicles in London.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22143","22143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444298","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to take account of lower fuel costs in its reform of the Bus Service Operators Grant.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22133","22133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444299","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether a further review of the tunnel boring machine advance rates for the High Speed 2 Chiltern tunnel has yet taken place.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22205","22205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444300","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21012, what repairs there have been to Tadcaster Bridge to date; and whether finance for any repairs will be found from (a) the Road Investment Strategy and (b) a contingency fund.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22216","22216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444301","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the full costs of repairing the Lamington Viaduct will be met by Network Rail's insurance cover.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22202","22202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444302","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the new Northern franchisee will take to establish a North East Business Unit for rail services.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22203","22203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444303","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22066","22066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444304","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will discuss with the Highways Agency the time taken to (a) programme and (b) complete highway works on the M54 in Shropshire.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22079","22079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444305","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will have discussions with the Highways Agency on (a) improving arrangements to clear litter and flytipping on the M67 and M60 around the Denton Interchange and (b) repairing defective lighting columns along the M67 and M60 around the River Tame.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22068","22068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444306","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment Network Rail has made of the costs and benefits of replacing level crossings with bridges on its England network.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22056","22056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444307","2016-01-18","Department for Transport","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21128, whether his Department plans to make additional funding available to help repair local highway infrastructure damaged by the winter floods of 2015-16.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22054","22054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444309","2016-01-18","Women and Equalities","2016-01-12","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many people of each gender have worked as special advisers in the Government Equalities Office since 2010.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22065","22065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444310","2016-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many claimants for personal independence payment have been asked to pay for a letter from their GP explaining their impairments or disability whilst being moved from disability living allowance to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22081","22081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444311","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department gives to Jobcentre Plus staff on alerting applicants to the possibility of applying for universal credit by telephone rather than online.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22051","22051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444312","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of recipients of their first universal credit payment received an advance payment of that credit in 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22052","22052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444313","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in each parliamentary constituency will be affected by the new benefit cap from April 2016; and what the mean amount of benefit capped will be in each constituency.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22201","22201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444314","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average wait has been for the first universal credit payment following receipt of a successful application since the introduction of that credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22218","22218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444315","2016-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that staff dealing with universal credit are on the same rates of pay once staff from HM Revenue and Customs are transferred to his Department.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22135","22135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444316","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21337, for those claimants who will see a change, what the average weekly change will be for those claimants who will see a change in their universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22100","22100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444317","2016-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cold weather payments have been made in each constituency in each year since their introduction; and what the total value of such payments has been.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22115","22115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444318","2016-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance is provided to GPs on charging patients for letters used to apply for benefits and transition from disability living allowance to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22082","22082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445253","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the cost, operational capacity and reliability of the F-35 programme.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903063","903063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445254","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to encourage recruitment of cadets.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903070","903070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445255","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he is having with his Russian counterpart on improving collaboration on defence affairs.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903064","903064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445256","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to service members' pay and allowances on morale in the armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903066","903066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445257","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has been in contact with representatives of the 70,000 moderate fighters on the ground in Syria.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903069","903069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445258","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his priorities are for the acquisition of defence equipment over the next two years.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903065","903065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445259","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Brimstone missiles have been used by the RAF in Syria since 2 December 2015.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903067","903067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445260","2016-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much accrued to the public purse from sales of arms to Saudi Arabia in 2015.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903071","903071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/445605","2016-01-20","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the security situation in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903074","903074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446119","2016-01-20","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps the Government is taking to support charities in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903086","903086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446120","2016-01-20","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the value to the economy in Northern Ireland of membership of the EU single market.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903085","903085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446121","2016-01-20","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how the Government plans to commemorate in Northern Ireland the centenary of the battle of the Somme.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903088","903088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/446122","2016-01-20","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to support the Police Service of Northern Ireland and the security services in tackling terrorism in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903087","903087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443679","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 19 December 2006 to an oral question from the former hon. Member for North Devon, on Nuclear Weapons, Official Report, column 1902W, what plan his Department has for ensuring an adequate supply of tritium to maintain the UK's nuclear weapons' capability until 2055; and what the projected cost of those plans is.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21972","21972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443680","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date the most recent stocktake between the UK and the US under the 1958 Mutual Defence Agreement took place; where that meeting was held; what matters were discussed at that meeting; and where and when the next such meeting is scheduled to take place.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21802","21802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443681","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what conditions the Government considers need to be met for the UK to divest itself of nuclear weapons through international negotiations.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21803","21803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443682","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where Exercise Astral Climb 2015 took place; and where Exercise Astral Bend 2016 will take place.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21800","21800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443683","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the costs were of operating the Truck Convoy Heavy Duty in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21801","21801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443684","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the reply of 17 March 2011, Official Report, column 514W, on radioactive materials transport, whether the practice of displaying radioactive materials hazard warning signs on vehicles carrying special nuclear materials will continue following the retirement from service of High Security Vehicles.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21986","21986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443685","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals on the introduction of (a) call-in and (b) scrutiny arrangements for the Greater Manchester Combined Authority.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21796","21796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443686","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which areas of the UK show recent evidence of residual radiation from the Chernobyl disaster.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21747","21747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443687","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to require local authorities to conduct a needs assessment of local sexual health and contraceptive services before issuing tenders.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21778","21778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443688","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what forecast he has made of the return on spending on preventative sexual and reproductive health spending in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21779","21779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443689","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department plans to monitor progress against the targets in its Framework for Sexual Health Improvement in England.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21812","21812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443690","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been undertaken of the effect on sexual and reproductive health services of reductions in the Public Health Grant to local authorities for 2015-16 and the measures in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 relating to the public health system.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21813","21813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443691","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evaluation he (a) has made or (b) plans to make of the effect of local authority commissioning of long acting reversible contraceptives (LARC) in primary care on the number of GP surgeries offering LARC fitting and removal.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21814","21814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443692","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will publish an accountability structure of the responsibilities regarding sexual and reproductive health for each government department and arm's length body.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21815","21815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443693","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what system of monitoring is in place to ensure that local authorities meet their duty to commission open access, confidential services for sexually transmitted infections and contraception.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21816","21816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443694","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged between 15 and 18 took their own lives in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21874","21874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443695","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to establish the veracity of recent reports that the North Korean government has capacity for a hydrogen bomb making facility.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21892","21892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443696","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the numbers of sham (a) marriages and (b) civil partnerships since March 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21871","21871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443697","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will direct the civil contingencies secretariat to ensure there is liaison with the devolved nations on best practice procedures in its area of practice.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21890","21890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443698","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce a further savings bond for people over 65.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21891","21891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443699","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of progress in implementing the OECD Base Erosion and Profit Shifting Action Plan.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21872","21872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443700","2016-01-14","Department for International Development","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress has been made to further develop clean water programmes in sub-Saharan Africa in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21893","21893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443701","2016-01-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many people aged 50 and over were recruited by her Department in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21873","21873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443702","2016-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has any plans to change the social fund funeral payment in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21875","21875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443703","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet representatives of the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Muscular Dystrophy and Muscular Dystrophy UK to discuss the provision of hydrotherapy for people with muscle-wasting conditions.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21846","21846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443704","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she attends the Cabinet committee on flooding.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21998","21998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443705","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with the Bank of England regarding risks to financial stability that arise as a consequence of climate change.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21999","21999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443706","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Dutch government ahead of the publication of the Programme of the Netherlands Presidency of the Council of the EU.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21870","21870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443707","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason the UK no longer has a strategy on opposing the death penalty; and whether the Government plans to publish a new strategy.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21761","21761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443708","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Written Answer of 7 January 2016 to Question 20867, what the response was of the government of Saudi Arabia to concerns raised by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State and the UK Ambassador on the recent mass executions.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21764","21764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443709","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2016 to Question 21408, when the Government plans to reach a decision on funding for the National Illegal Money Lending Team.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21963","21963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443710","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government has made of whether the TTIP trade deal will make the UK more vulnerable to lawsuits; if the Government will insist that TTIP does not contain provisions which would allow similar lawsuits to be brought in the UK; and if the Government will reconsider its support for TTIP in response to that lawsuit.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22006","22006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443711","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to address the forecast rise in household debt as defined by the Office for Budget Responsibility on page 69 of its November 2015 report, the Economic and Fiscal Outlook.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21832","21832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443712","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received since September 2015 on the level of household debt; and on what dates he received those representations.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21830","21830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443713","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received since September 2015 on (a) consumer debt and (b) personal loans.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21831","21831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443714","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's revised planned expenditure is for 2015-16 following the recent transfer of responsibility for fire and rescue services to the Home Department.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21849","21849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443715","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the annual budget for the Extremism Analysis Unit is.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21751","21751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443716","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the remit of the Extremism Analysis Unit is.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21752","21752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443717","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff are employed (a) full-time and (b) part-time in the Extremism Analysis Unit; and at which grade each such member of staff is employed.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21987","21987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443718","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many press and public relations staff are employed by his Department; how many of those employees are paid more than (a) 50,000 and (b) 100,000; and what the total expenditure was in press and public relations by his Department in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21966","21966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443719","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many press and public relations staff are employed by her Department; how many of those employees are paid more than (a) 50,000 and (b) 100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by her Department in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21967","21967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443720","2016-01-14","Scotland Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many press and public relations staff are employed by his Department; how many of those employees paid more than (a) 50,000 and (b) 100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by his Department in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21968","21968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443721","2016-01-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many press and public relations staff are employed by her Department; how many of those employees are paid more than (a) 50,000 and (b) 100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by her Department in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21974","21974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443722","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many press and public relations staff are employed by his Department; how many of those employees are paid more than (a) 50,000 and (b) 100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by his Department in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21970","21970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443723","2016-01-13","Wales Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many press and public relations staff are employed by his Department; how many of these employees are paid more than (a) 50,000 and (b) 100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by his Department in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21975","21975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443724","2016-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many press and public relations staff are employed by his Department; how many of those employees are paid more than (a) 50,000 and (b) 100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by his Department in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21969","21969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443725","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times limited removal directions have been used since the policy of giving such directions came into effect on 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21859","21859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443726","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of falling oil prices on the UK's net international investment position.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21860","21860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443727","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will discuss with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change (a) providing more funding through and (b) improving the effectiveness of the feed-in tariff incentive regime for smaller on-site anaerobic digestion in order to encourage cost-effective on-site treatment of food and farming residues and to reduce carbon emissions from the production of food.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21737","21737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443728","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to support the development of small-scale on-site renewable solutions in the agri-food sector, based on residues from food factories and farm slurries and crop residues.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21848","21848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443729","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ban bio-degradable food processing and farm residues from disposal to landfill.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21847","21847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443730","2016-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that benefit claimants who are sanctioned receive a written notification of the sanction before their benefit payment is withdrawn.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21965","21965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443731","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the 290 million that the Prime Minister announced on 11 January 2016 to help new and expectant mothers combat poor mental health is additional funding, over and above existing budgets.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21776","21776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443732","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to (a) end the 14 regional markets for electricity distribution and (b) introduce a national market for electricity distribution.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21705","21705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443733","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse has been of housing and supporting migrants who arrived (a) in October 1998 and (b) on 21 October 2015 in the RAF Dhekelia and RAF Akrotiri Sovereign Base Areas in Cyprus.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21720","21720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443734","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many requests for arms export licences to Saudi Arabia (a) have been made, (b) were rejected by the Export Control Organisation (ECO), (c) were granted by the ECO and (d) were revoked after being granted in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21721","21721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443735","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Skills Funding Agency has provided for ESOL Plus Mandation courses in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21719","21719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443736","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2015 to Question 902116, how much additional financial support in winter resilience money the NHS received in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15; and on what dates in those years that additional support was allocated.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21718","21718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443737","2016-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if her Department will liaise with Ofgem in taking steps to ensure that savings accrued to suppliers are returned to consumers in lower prices.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21915","21915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443738","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been employed on a zero-hours contract in (a) Mid Sussex constituency, (b) West Sussex, (c) the South East and (d) the UK in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21961","21961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443739","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish the evidential basis that underpinned the decision on the allocation of funding to Phase 2 and Phase 3 of the Leeds flood defence scheme in 2011.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21759","21759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443740","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of flood defence spending in Leeds.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21760","21760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443741","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any of the costs associated with events that he spoke at on 7 January 2016 at (a) St David's Hotel and (b) Salt Bar were met from the public purse.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21923","21923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443742","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many civil servants attended his speeches at (a) St David's Hotel and (b) Salt Bar on 7 January 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21924","21924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443743","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether invitations to the event at which he spoke on 7 January 2016 at St David's Hotel were issued by his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21925","21925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443744","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many civil servants accompanied him on his visit to Cardiff on 7 January 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21926","21926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443745","2016-01-13","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of former care leavers living in unsuitable accommodation.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21845","21845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443746","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2016 to Question 20602, how many of the 183 Ministry of Defence public relations staff referred to are (a) based in Scotland, (b) have duties relating to Scotland.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21964","21964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443747","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has made an assessment for the implications for his policy of the merits decision by the US Air Force to extend weight restrictions of F-35 Lightning II pilots until 2018; and whether his Department has issued similar guidelines for UK pilots.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22003","22003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443748","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the purpose was of the visit of his officials to the USS Ronald Reagan on 8 January 2016; and what the rank of the visiting officials was.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21988","21988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443749","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) assets and (b) personnel of his Department took part in Exercise Platinum Lion in collaboration with the US, Romanian and Bulgarian armed forces.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22000","22000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443750","2016-01-14","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with her ministerial colleagues on improving the quality of sex and relationship education in schools.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21877","21877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443751","2016-01-14","Women and Equalities","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with her ministerial colleagues on increasing the number of BME police officers.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21879","21879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443752","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of employment tribunal fees on the ability of individuals to bring forward discrimination claims.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21876","21876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443753","2016-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many carers were (a) in receipt of and (b) have an underlying entitlement to carer's allowance as a result of caring for someone who is in receipt of (i) attendance allowance, (ii) personal independence payment and (iii) disability living allowance.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21795","21795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443754","2016-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of carer's allowance were in receipt of (a) attendance allowance and (b) personal independence payment in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21794","21794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443755","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19906, by whom Lady Justice Macur's report is being considered.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21819","21819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443756","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19906, when he expects to publish Lady Justice Macur's report.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21820","21820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443757","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19906, for what reasons the Government is considering the report of Lady Justice Macur prior to its publication.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21818","21818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443758","2016-01-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 53 of the Statement of Funding Policy 2015, who the recipients of expenditure on broadcasting and media bodies were in 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21973","21973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443759","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has an official statement of the UK's relationship with Bahrain and the Bahraini government.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21768","21768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443760","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Bahrain on (a) the treatment of opposition leaders in that country and (b) medical facilities available to Hassan Mushaima.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21958","21958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443761","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with opposition politicians and groups in Bahrain.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21959","21959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443762","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many grants his Department awarded to projects for which the range of values in the Department's benefit-cost ratio assessment included negative values in each of the last six years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21766","21766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443763","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to publish a full impact assessment of the Government's proposal for clean air zones.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21782","21782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443764","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reason passenger cars have been exempted from the proposed clean air zones in her Department's plan to reduce nitrogen dioxide emissions.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21783","21783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443765","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to empower local authorities in proposed clean air zones to charge private cars which do not comply with EU vehicle emission standards.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21784","21784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443766","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to announce details of the responsibilities to be imposed on the five cities in which clean air zones will be introduced.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21785","21785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443767","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of nitrogen dioxide pollution in the UK is caused by emissions from private cars.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21781","21781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443768","2016-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what contingency plans her Department has put in place in the event of one or more stakeholders in the Hinkley Point C project being unable to raise sufficient funding to complete development.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21904","21904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443769","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the construction industry who already pay into the Construction Industry Training Board Levy scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21833","21833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443770","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that businesses which contribute to the Construction Industry Training Board Levy scheme do not also pay the apprenticeship levy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21834","21834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443771","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many deaths in prison were caused by the use of legal highs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21829","21829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443772","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many recorded attacks there were against prison officers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21996","21996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443773","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of attempted suicide there were in prisons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21997","21997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443774","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many deaths in prisons were caused by attacks by other prisoners in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21798","21798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443775","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on training prison officers to help prisoners with mental health issues in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21799","21799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443776","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for funding by his Department of regimental museums over the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21736","21736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443777","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve the attendance of reservists at weekly drills, training exercises and medical assessments.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21901","21901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443778","2016-01-14","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans she has to participate in events to commemorate the centenary of the (a) Easter Rising and (b) Battle of the Somme.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21902","21902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443779","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students studying higher education in further education colleges received maintenance grants in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21886","21886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443780","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students studied higher education in further education colleges in each constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21887","21887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443781","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if the Government will issue issuing an apology to the indigenous people of Australia for British nuclear tests carried out on their land in the 1950s and 1960s.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21757","21757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443782","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many claims under the plug-in grant scheme for (a) cars and (b) vans have been accepted in each quarter since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21898","21898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443783","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of average annual pay growth in (a) 2016, (b) 2017, (c) 2018, (d) 2019 and (e) 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22002","22002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443784","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to provide an answer to Question 18568, tabled by the hon. Member for East Ham on 2 December 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21821","21821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443785","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passengers have used high-speed rail services from London St Pancras station in each year since such services started.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21962","21962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443786","2016-01-14","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of passengers who will (a) access Crossrail services via Stratford station and (b) pass through Stratford station on Crossrail services in each of the first three years after Crossrail services commence.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21775","21775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443787","2016-01-13","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) GCSE, (b) AS and (c) A-level exam results have (i) increased, (ii) decreased and (iii) stayed the same following an appeal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21749","21749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443788","2016-01-13","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to ensure that exams are marked accurately on the first occasion.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21750","21750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443789","2016-01-13","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) GCSE, (b) AS and (c) A-level exam results have been appealed against in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21748","21748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443790","2016-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what mechanism residents can challenge a local authority's assessment of the adequacy of drainage systems for a new housing development where they believe it will contribute to additional flooding in an area which has recently flooded.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21916","21916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443791","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will provide guidance to residents whose homes have been flooded in circumstances where the failure of a local agency, local authority or private company to maintain the water management infrastructure adequately can be demonstrated, on how those residents can seek redress or compensation.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21917","21917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443792","2016-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will review the guidelines on sustainable drainage system requirements under planning policy for new developments in areas with recorded incidents of flooding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21906","21906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443793","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the purpose is of flood action groups established in areas that have experienced recurring flooding; and whether her Department has made an assessment of the effectiveness of such groups improving residents' protection from flooding.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21907","21907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443794","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will take steps to introduce a single point of emergency contact during incidents of flooding to improve the co-ordinated response to such incidents; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21905","21905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443795","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for colonoscopy to detect bowel cancer.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21838","21838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443796","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the uptake of bowel screening was under the National Screening Programme for bowel cancer in England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21839","21839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443797","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the (a) frequency of false (i) positives and (ii) negatives from the National Screening Programme for bowel cancer and (b) the effect of such false positives and negatives on waiting times for colonoscopy.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21837","21837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443798","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2015 to Question 18808, what assessment he made of the conclusion by the Independent Cancer Taskforce in its 2015 report entitled Achieving world class outcomes for cancer: A strategy for England 2015-2020 that faecal immunochemical testing has extremely poor rates of detection for precancerous polyps.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21788","21788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443799","2016-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the transition to the equalised state pension for women affected by those changes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21865","21865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443800","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions his Department has had with its counterparts in Northern Ireland on the integration of minority communities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21866","21866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443801","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingency arrangements her Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21942","21942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443802","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21943","21943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443803","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency arrangements her Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21946","21946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443804","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21945","21945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443805","2016-01-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21938","21938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443806","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21939","21939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443807","2016-01-13","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what contingency arrangements her Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21940","21940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443808","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what contingency arrangements her Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21941","21941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443809","2016-01-13","Attorney General","2016-01-11","To ask the Attorney General, what contingency arrangements the Law Officers' Departments have made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21934","21934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443810","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21933","21933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443811","2016-01-13","Church Commissioners","2016-01-11","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what contingency arrangements the Church Commissioners have made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21936","21936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443812","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21937","21937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443813","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21955","21955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443814","2016-01-13","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21935","21935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443815","2016-01-13","Wales Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21956","21956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443816","2016-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21957","21957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443817","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21954","21954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443818","2016-01-13","Women and Equalities","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what contingency arrangements the Government Equalities Office has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21944","21944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443819","2016-01-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what contingency arrangements her Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21951","21951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443820","2016-01-13","Leader of the House","2016-01-11","To ask the Leader of the House, what contingency arrangements his Office has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21950","21950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443821","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21949","21949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443822","2016-01-13","Scotland Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what contingency arrangements his Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21953","21953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443823","2016-01-13","Prime Minister","2016-01-11","To ask the Prime Minister, what contingency arrangements 10 Downing Street has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21952","21952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443824","2016-01-13","House of Commons Commission","2016-01-11","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what contingency arrangements the House of Commons Commission has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21947","21947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443825","2016-01-13","Department for International Development","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what contingency arrangements her Department has made for the eventuality of a majority leave vote in the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21948","21948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443826","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what processes are in place to ensure that people with mental health problems have applications for start-up loans considered fairly.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21932","21932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443827","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 11 January 2016, whether the 400 million of investment announced for crisis home resolution teams in communities is in addition to the (a) 1.25 billion investment for perinatal and children and young people's mental health announced by the then Deputy Prime Minister in March 2015 and (b) 600 million investment for mental health announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21921","21921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443828","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 11 January 2016, how much of the proposed 1.4 billion mental health support funding for young people over the next five years has already been allocated.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21922","21922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443829","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 11 January 2016, whether the 290 million of investment announced for perinatal mental health care is in addition to the (a) 1.25 billion investment for perinatal and children and young people's mental health announced by the then Deputy Prime Minister in March 2015 and (b) 660 million investment for mental health announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21919","21919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443830","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 11 January 2016, whether the 247 million of investment announced for liaison mental health services in emergency departments is in addition to (a) the 1.25 billion investment for perinatal and children and young people's mental health announced by the then Deputy Prime Minister in March 2015 and (b) the 600 million investment for mental health announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21920","21920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443831","2016-01-14","Prime Minister","2016-01-11","To ask the Prime Minister, how many mental health services he has visited since May 2010; and what the (a) date and (b) location was of each such visit.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21918","21918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443832","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with organisations representing small businesses on its plans to introduce quarterly tax returns for businesses by 2020.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21851","21851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443833","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of savings that will accrue to UK businesses from his Department's  plans to introduce quarterly tax returns for business by 2020.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21850","21850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443834","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time taken by NHS England is to process (a) individual funding requests and (b) clinically critically urgent funding applications; and whether there is a mechanism to expedite this process for time-sensitive preventative treatments.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21780","21780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443835","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when any Ministers in his Department last met Chagossian representatives; and when they next plan to do so.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21979","21979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443836","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will ensure that his (a) Department will not enter into negotiations with Argentina without the full consent of the Falkland Islands government and (b) Department's position remains to deny any transfer or reduction of British sovereignty over the Falkland Islands without the full consent of the Falkland Islanders.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21980","21980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443837","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to encourage an increase in migration to the UK from Australia to the levels of such migration prior to 2008.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21703","21703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443838","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that any extra workload due to plans to require the filing of quarterly tax returns by small businesses does not reduce profits and productivity for such small businesses.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21985","21985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443839","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to combat the (a) decline in the use of local shopping centres and (b) fall in employment rates by local shopping centres; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21981","21981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443840","2016-01-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of the decline in the broadcast of free-to-air sport on the accessibility of sport to young people.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21983","21983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443841","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will take steps to expand the number of places in medicine courses in universities.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21982","21982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443842","2016-01-13","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2016-01-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the maximum permitted spending by each campaign will be during the final weeks of campaigning on the referendum on EU membership; and what steps the Electoral Commission plans to take to ensure that spending by each campaign is subject to the same limit.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21704","21704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443843","2016-01-13","Department for International Development","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, further to the Answer of 26 October 2015 to Question 12448, what criteria are used by her Department to determine the amount of aid provided to emerging economies like China and India.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22005","22005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443844","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that recent refugee arrivals from the Middle East and North Africa are assimilated into British society and culture.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21984","21984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443845","2016-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many national insurance numbers have been issued to migrants from Eastern European countries in the last two years; how many of those numbers are being used; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22004","22004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443846","2016-01-14","Attorney General","2016-01-11","To ask the Attorney General, what recent steps the CPS has taken to improve the conviction rate for violence against women and girls.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21908","21908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443847","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the outturn cost was of the Reading Station Area Redevelopment project.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21826","21826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443848","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on seating capacity of the Great Western Main Line electrification project.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21827","21827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443849","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on (a) the peak seat capacity (b) demand for rail services between Reading to London Paddington during each peak morning hour.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21797","21797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443850","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he last held discussions with the National Trading Standards Board on plans to reduce funding for Illegal Money Lending Units.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21811","21811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443851","2016-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to fund co-ordination of the seabird census planned for 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21765","21765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443852","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nationals of members state of the European Economic Area have registered with the (a) Health and Care Professions Council, (b) General Optical Council, (c) General Osteopathic Council and (d) General Chiropractic Council since June 2014.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21895","21895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443853","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 15 December 2015 to Questions 18901 and 18902, what the source is of the statement that 71 of the 131 neonatal critical care services now meet required staffing ratios; and if he will place a copy of the source document in the Library.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21722","21722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443854","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will consider issuing guidance restricting the taking of photos and videos following the Shoreham air show crash.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21706","21706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443855","2016-01-13","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make representations to exam boards to remove the five per cent marking for spelling and grammar for dyslexic students.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21707","21707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443856","2016-01-13","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that decisions of the Independent Appeals Panel do not allocate places in excess of a school's planned admission numbers.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21708","21708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443857","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to establish an independent body to monitor the salaries of council staff.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21712","21712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443858","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will remove the fuel duty escalator on liquefied petroleum gas.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21714","21714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443859","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reduce the level of VAT applicable to construction companies involved in the conversion of non-residential buildings to residential use.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21711","21711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443860","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Highways Act 1835 to allow for the use of self-balancing scooters, segways and z-boards on roads.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21710","21710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443861","2016-01-13","Women and Equalities","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with businesses on increasing the gender balance on corporate boards.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21713","21713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443862","2016-01-13","Women and Equalities","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will take steps to increase the reporting of gender balance on corporate boards.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21709","21709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443863","2016-01-14","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's consultation, Out-of-school education settings: call for evidence, published on 26 November 2015, what definition her Department uses for (a) supplementary schools, (b) tuition centres, (c) intensive education and (d) the eight hours threshold for inspection.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21881","21881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443864","2016-01-14","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to include within its proposals for registration and inspection of out-of-school education settings (a) annual holiday clubs and (b) communal religious groups.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21882","21882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443865","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to produce further guidance on the definition of extremism used in her Department's Counter-Extremism Strategy, Cm 9148, published in October 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21880","21880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443866","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the implications are for the provisions of the Public Order Act 1986 of her Department's Counter-Extremism Strategy, Cm 9148, published in October 2015 and its definition of extremism.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21883","21883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443867","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to consult faith groups on the criteria and processes for decisions that will be made on whether expressions of belief are considered extreme for the purposes of its counter-extremism strategy and policies resulting from that strategy.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21884","21884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443868","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 10867, how many of the complaints were (a) referred to his Department's solicitors and (b) resulted in compliance with the Overseas Companies Regulations 2009.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21734","21734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443869","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2015 to Question 17801, what the evidential basis is for his statement that civil service job satisfaction remains high and wellbeing has increased.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21817","21817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443870","2016-01-13","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Autumn Statement and Summer Budget 2015, paragraph 2.172, what estimate he has made of the rent that the Cabinet Office will need to pay to the Government Property Unit for its own buildings.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21787","21787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443871","2016-01-13","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which debt collection agencies are used by the Debt Market Integrator.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21740","21740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443872","2016-01-13","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what stakes are held in the Debt Market Integrator by private sector partners.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21746","21746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443873","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, paragraph 3.54, whether the Debt Market Integrator will take over the services currently contracted out to Concentrix; whether Concentrix is permitted to bid for the new contract; and what the timetable is for tendering.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21762","21762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443874","2016-01-13","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Autumn Statement and Summer Budget 2015, paragraph 2.172, what the (a) annual income and (b) running costs of the Government Property Unit is.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21731","21731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443875","2016-01-13","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what bids were received for the Debt Market Integrator contract.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21739","21739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443876","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times he published data relating to his Department's staff salaries in the calendar year 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21909","21909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443877","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2015 to Question 18409, whether the organogram on his Department's website is now up to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21910","21910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443878","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many medical negligence cases with a value of damages less than 25,000 there have been in each of the last five years in which (a) costs exceeded damages and (b) costs were challenged.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21978","21978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443879","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many intervention providers her Department has approved as part of its Channel Programme.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21896","21896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443880","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many intervention providers for the Channel Programme are pending approval.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21897","21897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443881","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library a copy of the process for approving intervention providers under the Channel programme and the timetable for that process.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21823","21823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443882","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Recommendation 8 of his Department's Triennial Review of the NHS Litigation Authority (NHS LA), published in July 2015, when he expects the NHS LA to publish its evaluation report of its pilot mediation programme.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21786","21786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443883","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the apprenticeship levy will apply to charities who employ more than 250 people.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21733","21733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443884","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the previously published Carbon Price Support rates of 30t/CO2 in 2020 and 70t/CO2 in 2030, at 2009 prices, remain in place.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21842","21842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443885","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the freeze on carbon price floor rates to end.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21843","21843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443886","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the rates for carbon price support in (a) 2020 and (b) 2030.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21844","21844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443887","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which port, harbour and coastal locations in the UK have a National Grid connection enabling a power plant connection of over 300MW.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21841","21841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443888","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on which occasions officials of his Department have met representatives of the Royal Bank of Scotland in each of the last five years; and what topics were discussed at each such meeting.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21836","21836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443889","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what resources his Department has spent on HM Government Strategy for Abolition of the Death Penalty, revised in October 2011 in each year since its publication; and what resources his Department plans to spend in each year of the current spending review period.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21767","21767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443890","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on HM Government Strategy for Abolition of the Death Penalty, published October 2011.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21763","21763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443891","2016-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to set a levy of at least three per cent of gross working premium on insurers to fund the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payments Scheme.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21753","21753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443892","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many IT contractors engaged by HM Revenue and Customs work through a personal service company.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21867","21867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443893","2016-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency planning his Department is undertaking to prepare for the possibility of a leave vote in the forthcoming referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21929","21929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443894","2016-01-14","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what contingency planning his Department is undertaking to prepare for the possibility of a leave vote in the forthcoming referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21928","21928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443895","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency planning her Department is undertaking to prepare for the possibility of a leave vote in the forthcoming referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21927","21927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443896","2016-01-14","Prime Minister","2016-01-11","To ask the Prime Minister, what contingency planning the Civil Service is undertaking to prepare for the possibility of a leave vote in the forthcoming referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21931","21931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443897","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what contingency planning his Department is undertaking to prepare for the possibility of a leave vote in the forthcoming referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21930","21930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443898","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to establish an inquiry into the use of perfluorochemicals in fast-food packaging.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21723","21723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443899","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department made to the Saudi Arabian government on Sheikh Nimr al-Nimr (a) prior to and (b) after his execution.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21903","21903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443900","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on Saudi Arabia's use of counter-terrorism laws; and whether such laws are being used legitimately to tackle terrorism or to supress political and religious opposition.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21853","21853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443901","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Saudi Arabian authorities on the cases of (a) Raif Badaw, (b) Waleed Abu al-Khair and (c) Ashraf Fayadh.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21852","21852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443903","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to protect legally privileged communications from surveillance.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21911","21911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443904","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he made of the potential effect on government revenues of changes to personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 before announcing those changes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21828","21828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443905","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) title and (b) date is of each memorandum of understanding signed by a Government department with another country since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21735","21735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443906","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he made of the potential effect on court fee income of the announcement in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 on changes to personal injury laws and procedure before making that announcement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21805","21805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443907","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of how much motor insurance premiums reduced after the changes introduced by the Jackson civil litigation reforms and the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21717","21717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443908","2016-01-13","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the implications for the Government's policy on the Low Commission's reports, Tackling of the findings of the Advice Deficit, published in 2014, and Getting it Right in Social Welfare Law, published in 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21808","21808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443909","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of the number of court staff and resources required in the cases involving litigants in personal injury claims of changes to personal injury laws and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21807","21807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443910","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on court fees income of the changes to personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21810","21810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443911","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been received from prisoners of pest infestation in prisons in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21809","21809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443912","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he plans to take to ensure new litigants in person as a result of changes to personal injury laws and procedures announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 are able to meet the requirements of the personal injury portal.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21804","21804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443913","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the recommendations of the Low Commission on formulating a national strategy for advice and legal support in England and Wales in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21758","21758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443914","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the status is of the Serious Fraud Office's investigation into G4S over fraud in the prisoner tagging contracts.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21994","21994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443915","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will launch an independent investigation of the circumstances of the abuse that has been reported at Medway Secure Training Centre.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21995","21995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443916","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date he last met insurance company representatives to discuss issues relating to personal injury claims; who was present at that meeting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21806","21806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443917","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on the operation of the new arrangements for obtaining medical reports in road traffic claims of the changes to personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21824","21824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443918","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding her Department received from the International Climate Fund in (a) 2012, (b) 2013, (c) 2014 and (d) 2015.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21991","21991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443919","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how the methodology for prioritising which countries receive funding from the International Climate Fund has been set; and what plans she has to ensure this methodology is regularly reviewed for best practice.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21989","21989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443920","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many projects her Department is currently managing that have been developed with funding from the International Climate Fund.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21990","21990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443921","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on reforming the EU Emissions Trading Scheme.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21976","21976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443922","2016-01-13","Department for International Development","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that official development assistance funding is prioritised for poverty reduction projects.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21993","21993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443923","2016-01-13","Department for International Development","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the official development assistance budget was given to the International Climate Fund in (a) 2012, (b) 2013, (c) 2014 and (d) 2015.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21992","21992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443924","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to increase public awareness of the need for holidaymakers to take out travel insurance.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21840","21840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443925","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications in which (a) towns, (b) cities and (c) regions for Tier 2 (General) restricted Certificate of Sponsorship have been rejected on the grounds that the job is in an establishment which provides a take-away service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21728","21728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443926","2016-01-19","Church Commissioners","2016-01-11","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what recent progress has been made on (a) residential development and (b) infrastructure planning on Church Commissioner land allocated as an urban extension by Peterborough City Council at (i) Paston Reserve and (ii) Norwood; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21889","21889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443927","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the National Living Wage on the provision of adult social care.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21822","21822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443928","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place in the Library HM Revenue and Customs' full workings, including the methodology, modelling and assumptions, which underpinned the figures included in the Tobacco Levy Consultation, published in September 2015, on the tobacco levy yield after behavioural effects.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21716","21716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443929","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many RAF missions have been flown over Syria.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21862","21862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443930","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will deploy the RAF to provide humanitarian support to the people of Syria through the use of air drops.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21861","21861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443931","2016-01-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the Government's plans to commemorate (a) the First World War and (b) the Battle of the Somme.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21863","21863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443932","2016-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in (a) Warrington and (b) the North West were (i) investigated and (ii) prosecuted for failure to pay the national minimum wage in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 22001","22001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443933","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refused asylum seekers were granted, continued on, or were reinstated onto support under section 4 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 in Scotland after lodging an appeal with the First-tier Tribunal (Asylum Support) in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21769","21769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443934","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum decisions identified as critically flawed in her Department's Quality Audit in the last 12 months were (a) reconsidered by officials as a consequence of that finding, (b) overturned as a result of that reconsideration and (c) overturned on appeal.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21770","21770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443935","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum decisions identified as seriously flawed in her Department's Quality Audit in the last 12 months were (a) reconsidered by officials as a consequence of that finding, (b) overturned as a result of that reconsideration and (c) overturned on appeal.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21771","21771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443936","2016-01-14","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many seriously or critically flawed decisions were identified in the  Quality Audit of her Department's asylum decisions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21772","21772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443937","2016-01-13","Department for International Development","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to secure the agreement of all parties to permit access for food and other vital supplies to the residents of Madaya and other settlements in Syria in which a civilian population is being besieged by combatant forces.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21856","21856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443938","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to participants in the Syrian peace process to encourage them to consider a statement urging an end to the use of long-term siege of civilian populations in Madaya and other such settlements.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21724","21724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443939","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the profile of applications to the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency for access to vehicle ownership data for the purpose of enforcing parking penalties was each month in the last five years.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21725","21725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443940","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 20630, if he will publish the initial findings of the London and South Coast Rail Corridor Study covering the establishment of a Brighton Mainline 2.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21835","21835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443941","2016-01-14","Cabinet Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the five most common causes of deaths were in (a) England and Wales and (b) each London borough in (i) 2014, (ii) 2010, (iii) 2005 and (iv) 2000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21774","21774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443942","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on agency nurses by each NHS trust in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21971","21971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443943","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of total health spending in (a) London and (b) each London borough was allocated to general practice in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21773","21773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443944","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on (a) sexual health, (b) drug and alcohol and (c) smoking public health initiatives in (i) England and Wales, (ii) London and (iii) each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21900","21900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443945","2016-01-14","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the nurse vacancy rate was on 1 December (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015 in (i) London and (ii) each health trust in London.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21899","21899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443946","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness amongst healthcare professionals of complex regional pain syndrome.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21754","21754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443947","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage research into a cure for complex regional pain syndrome.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21755","21755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443948","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to help sufferers of complex regional pain syndrome.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21756","21756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443949","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length was of a social security appeal heard by an appeals tribunal in each year from 2010-11 to date.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21912","21912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443950","2016-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the length was of the longest social security appeal heard by an appeals tribunal for appeals lodged in each year from 2010-11 to date.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21913","21913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443951","2016-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients in the (a) work related activity group and (b) support group were also in receipt of the severe disability premium in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21914","21914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443952","2016-01-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to improve access to Welsh subtitling for learners and people with accessibility needs.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21869","21869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443953","2016-01-13","Wales Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will meet the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport to discuss access to Welsh subtitling for learners and people with accessibility needs.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21868","21868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443954","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what measures the Government plans to take to reduce (a) carbon emissions and (b) air pollution from shipping moored (i) off Enderby Wharf and (ii) in other inshore UK waters.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21729","21729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443955","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will ensure that any exploitation of shale gas in the UK is (a) a substitute for, and not in addition to, imported gas and (b) does not lead to an increase in carbon emissions.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21730","21730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443956","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on UK businesses of the Berry Amendment to US legislation on contract policy.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21715","21715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443957","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the carbon emissions and air pollution from diesel shipping moored (a) off Enderby Wharf, Greenwich and (b) in other inshore UK waters.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21857","21857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443958","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to reduce (a) carbon emissions and (b) air pollution from maritime transport and air transport.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21858","21858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443959","2016-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department last audited the management of Northumbria Probation Service by Sodexo.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21777","21777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443960","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his North Korean counterpart on the recent nuclear weapons tests conducted in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21878","21878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443961","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of sanctions measures imposed on North Korea in the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21825","21825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443962","2016-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to broker negotiated ceasefires to allow the creation of aid corridors across Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21888","21888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443963","2016-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to increase the amount of housing stock owned by councils; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21885","21885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443964","2016-01-14","Department for International Development","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21331, if she will publish the progress reports received to date from funded agencies in receipt of Syria crisis response funds.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21960","21960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443965","2016-01-13","Attorney General","2016-01-11","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been prosecuted under the (a) Communications Act 2003, (b) Malicious Communications Act 1988 and (c) Protection from Harassment Act 1997 for offences committed online.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21855","21855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443966","2016-01-13","Attorney General","2016-01-11","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been prosecuted under the (a) Communications Act 2003, (b) Malicious Communications Act 1988 and (c) Protection from Harassment Act 1997 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21854","21854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443967","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were treated by gamma knife radiosurgery machines (a) in England and (b) at each hospital in the last three years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21744","21744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443968","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many gamma knife radiosurgery machines there are in (a) use, (b) NHS hospitals and which are privately owned and (c) private hospitals.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21745","21745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443969","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the Government measures the number of incidents of harassment, threatening and abusive behaviour which occur online.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21864","21864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443970","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that internet service providers and social media organisations co-operate with the police to combat incidents of cyber bullying and harassment.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21726","21726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443971","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of existing legislation for tackling incidents of cyber bullying and harassment.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21727","21727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443972","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will introduce a ban on unstaffed tanning salons in England similar to that introduced in Wales, Scotland and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21743","21743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443973","2016-01-13","Department for Education","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of (a) morale in the teaching profession, (b) long-term prospects for teacher recruitment and retention and (c) the potential effect of increases in pupil numbers on (i) morale and (ii) recruitment and retention in that profession.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21741","21741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443974","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will introduce a ban on plastic microbeads in cosmetic products similar to that introduced in the US.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21742","21742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443975","2016-01-13","Department for International Development","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2015 to Question 16005, on malnutrition, how the Government plans to measure progress on its commitment to nutrition for 50 million people by 2020.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21732","21732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443976","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to close HM Prison Bristol.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21738","21738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443977","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many days of gas supply are available from the gas storage facilities.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21977","21977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443978","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether developers of carbon capture and storage projects can access funding through the Levy Control Framework.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21789","21789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443979","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which coal-fired power stations her Department expects to close before 2020.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21792","21792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443980","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total cost to the public purse had been of developing carbon capture and storage technology.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21793","21793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443981","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost to the public purse was of developing proposals for a new carbon capture and storage project at Peterhead.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21790","21790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443982","2016-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost to the public purse was of developing proposals for a new carbon capture and storage project in Yorkshire.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21791","21791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444099","2016-01-14","Attorney General","2016-01-11","To ask the Attorney General, what recent steps the Crown Prosecution Service has taken to improve the conviction rate for rape and domestic violence.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903029","903029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444308","2016-01-14","Women and Equalities","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of men who die as a result of suicide.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903015","903015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444774","2016-01-14","Women and Equalities","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with her ministerial colleagues on securing long-term funding for domestic violence services.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903020","903020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/444822","2016-01-14","Women and Equalities","2016-01-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress the Government is making on negotiating the removal of VAT on women's sanitary products.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903022","903022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443396","2016-01-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions the Government has had with the devolved administrations on increasing social mobility since May 2015.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21618","21618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443397","2016-01-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications for his polices of the conclusions of the Joseph Rowntree Foundation report, entitled Monitoring Poverty and Social Exclusion 2015, published in November 2015 that (a) the number of people working part-time who wish to work full-time is higher than in 2009 and (b) 600,000 people on temporary contracts want permanent contracts, compared to 400,000 people before the recession.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21622","21622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443398","2016-01-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information the Government holds on the proportion of small businesses that have ceased trading after experiencing flood damage in the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21658","21658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443399","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what date the second wave Area Reviews for further education college providers he plans to commence.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21697","21697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443400","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which colleges he plans are to be included in (a) the third wave Area Reviews for Lancashire (Pennines) further education colleges and (b) in the fourth wave Area Reviews for Lancashire (Coastal) further education colleges.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21698","21698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443401","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on income to insurance companies of the changes to personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21699","21699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443402","2016-01-13","Cabinet Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to (a) encourage greater use of email and (b) implement other measures to reduce costs in communication by government departments.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21684","21684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443403","2016-01-12","Cabinet Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the evaluation and recommendations of the Law Commission on the Advice Services Transition Fund.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21627","21627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443404","2016-01-12","Cabinet Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to introduce a pilot scheme to evaluate the potential use of social impact bonds for the provision of advice services.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21637","21637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443405","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21616","21616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443406","2016-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he made of the effect on VAT receipts of changes to personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 before making that announcement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21652","21652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443407","2016-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he made of the effect on recoupment of NHS treatment costs of the announcement in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 of changes to personal injury law and procedure before making that announcement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21659","21659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443408","2016-01-13","HM Treasury","2016-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses benefited from R&D tax credits in 2014-15; what the cost of R&D tax credits was to his Department in that year; and what the return on investment was of R&D tax credit expenditure for his Department.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21685","21685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443409","2016-01-13","Church Commissioners","2016-01-08","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, which Anglican churches within the Diocese of Blackburn were damaged by flooding in December 2015; and what the extent of damage to each such church was.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21700","21700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443410","2016-01-13","Church Commissioners","2016-01-08","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps Anglican congregations within the Diocese of Blackburn have taken to help people affected by flooding that took place over Christmas 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21701","21701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443411","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will take steps to introduce a single point of emergency contact during incidents of flooding to improve the co-ordinated response to flooding incidents where residents are currently required to contact the responsible agency based on the source of the flood waters; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21693","21693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443412","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will reconsider the decision that West Lancashire Borough Council be allowed the special levy contribution towards the operation of an Internal Drainage Board to take account of the recent flooding in West Lancashire.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21678","21678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443413","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals for a statutory duty for fire and rescue services to respond to flooding.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21650","21650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443414","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage zero-carbon housing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21687","21687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443415","2016-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment of the Government's plans to cap housing benefit for tenants in supported housing at the local rate of Local Housing Allowance.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21640","21640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443416","2016-01-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his polices of the conclusion of the Joseph Rowntree Foundation report, entitled Monitoring Poverty and Social Exclusion 2015, that the number of people living in poverty who depend on housing in the private rented sector has doubled in the last decade.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21620","21620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443417","2016-01-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the conclusion of the Joseph Rowntree Foundation Report entitled, Monitoring Poverty and Social Exclusion 2015, that the rise in homeless households from 40,000 to 53,000 between 2009-10 and 2014-15 was primarily due to families reaching the end of their private rented tenancies.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21625","21625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443418","2016-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the regular army's shortfall against (a) trained strength requirement and (b) its recruitment intake target has been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21668","21668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443419","2016-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Brimstone missiles have been used in Syria since 2 December 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21646","21646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443420","2016-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which countries British military personnel are embedded.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21610","21610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443421","2016-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on Israeli products in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21683","21683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443422","2016-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the end of year budget surplus or deficit was for each further education college in London in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21634","21634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443423","2016-01-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to page 86 of her Department's publication, Review of the Feed-in Tariffs Scheme: Government response, published in December 2015, what work her Department is undertaking to better understand the whole-system impacts of different electricity technologies; when she plans to complete and publish such work; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21645","21645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443424","2016-01-12","HM Treasury","2016-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to provide tax reliefs similar to those provided to businesses that contribute to flood defence schemes to landowners and farmers who assist in managing flood risk through soil management, investment in flood defences and water storage.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21626","21626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443425","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will set up a flood partnership group for Lancaster, chaired by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs with membership from local authorities, the Environment Agency and community flood defence groups.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21631","21631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443426","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people of each gender work in her Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21615","21615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443427","2016-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations her Department made to the recent meeting of the EU Fisheries and Agriculture Council; and for which species support was given at that meeting for quotas exceeding those recommended by scientific advice.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21667","21667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443428","2016-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many stocks for which the UK has quotas were fished (a) at and (b) below maximum sustainable yield on the last date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21665","21665"
