"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784871","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the level of sewage in rivers and to maintain habitat and species in and around rivers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111641","111641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784872","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the benefits to the environment of building homes with timber.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111552","111552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784873","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the Government is working with international partners to ensure that the wildlife in the Antarctic region is protected from expanding krill fisheries.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111540","111540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784874","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to issue a correction to comments he made about Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe in his evidence to the Foreign Affairs Committee on 1 November 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111595","111595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784875","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in Turkey on the protection of (a) freedom of assembly, (b) freedom of the press, (c) LGBT rights and (d) other human rights.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111573","111573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784876","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111575","111575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784877","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent over-fishing in the South Georgia seas.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111585","111585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784878","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in Nigeria on the protection of (a) LGBT rights, (b) other human rights and (c) freedom of speech.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111574","111574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784879","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Syria.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111572","111572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784880","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Rakhine State, Myanmar.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111569","111569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784881","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on the number of Nigerian Christians who have been killed in Nigeria in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111643","111643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784882","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) discuss with the Moroccan Ambassador to the UK and (b) instruct the UK Ambassador in Rabat to investigate the reasons for the expulsion of five MEPs from the Non-Self-Governing Territory of Western Sahara.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111689","111689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784883","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in Russia on (a) human and (b) LGBT rights.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111577","111577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784884","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the state of (a) human rights, (b) LGBT rights, (c) the freedom of the press and (d) freedom of assembly in Russia.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111578","111578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784885","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the Eritrean Government to respect the right to peaceful protest in that country.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111636","111636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784886","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Eritrean Government on reports that several protestors were killed by security services in Asmara on 31 October 2017.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111635","111635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784887","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Malaysian counterpart for the Malaysian Human Rights Commission Public Inquiry to consider the abductions of Christians over the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111591","111591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784888","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Indian Government on the murder of Sultan Masih in the North Western State of Pubjab; and what progress is being made to bring the people responsible for that murder to justice.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111592","111592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784889","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of humanitarian airdrops in Eastern Ghouta in the event that the Assad regime continues to block UN land access for aid provision.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111608","111608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784890","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111478","111478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784891","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which members of the Government will attend the next meeting of the Quint nations on Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111504","111504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784892","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many members of staff are employed to support the UK Ambassador to Yemen in Ridyah.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111491","111491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784893","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111798","111798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784894","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his oral contribution of 28 March 2017, Official Report column 117, and page 5 of his Department's consultation paper, Public consultation on the United Kingdom's future legal framework for imposing and implementing sanctions, published in April 2017, for what reasons the Government did not consult on how future UK sanctions policy will be aligned with that of the EU before publication of the Sanctions and Anti-Money Laundering Bill.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111741","111741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784895","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 18 of his Department's consultation paper, Public consultation on the United Kingdom's future legal framework for imposing and implementing sanctions, published in April 2017, and subsection 2 of Clause 1 of the Sanctions and Anti-Money Laundering Bill, for what reasons the Government did not consult in public on the purposes for which sanctions may be used before the publication of the Sanctions and Anti-Money Laundering Bill.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111742","111742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784896","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to subsection 2 of Clause 1 of the Sanctions and Anti-Money Laundering Bill, for what reasons the list of purposes for which the Government may impose sanctions does not include an explicit commitment to promoting human rights.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111743","111743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784897","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the UN Human Rights Council's 36th Session Report, on human rights in Sudan, whether the Government supports the position of the UN Human Rights Council to plan for the eventual transition of the Independent Expert's mandate from that of Independent Expert to another appropriate UN human rights mechanism.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111732","111732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784898","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to paragraph 1.9 of his Department's consultation response, Public consultation on the United Kingdom's future legal framework for imposing and implementing sanctions: government response, published in August 2017, under what circumstances the Government would consider it appropriate to legislate directly for UK Overseas Territories and Crown dependencies on implementing sanctions in those territories and dependencies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111740","111740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784899","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which heads of Government in the (a) Overseas Territories and (b) Crown dependencies he has contacted since the release of the Paradise Papers.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111695","111695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784900","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to paragraph 23 of UN Security Council Resolution 2371, what recent assessment he has made of the progress toward implementation of Interpol-UN Security Council special notices on sanctions on North Korea.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111670","111670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784901","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts in other countries on the implementation of the red notice issued by Interpol in relation to persons suspected of involvement in the death of Kim Jong Nam in Malaysia on 13 February 2017; and what recent assessment he has made of progress towards locating and extraditing such persons in accordance with that red notice.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111671","111671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784902","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the recent claim by the head of Microsoft that the Government of North Korea was responsible for the WannaCry cyber attack in May 2017.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111672","111672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784903","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to paragraph 1.9 of his Department's consultation response, Public consultation on the United Kingdom's future legal framework for imposing and implementing sanctions: government response, published in August 2017, what the outcomes were of his consultations with UK Overseas Territories and Crown dependencies on the future legal framework for implementing sanctions in those territories; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111746","111746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784904","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to paragraph 1.9 of his Department's consultation response, Public consultation on the United Kingdom's future legal framework for imposing and implementing sanctions: government response, published in August 2017, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of implementation of sanctions in UK Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111745","111745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784905","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to paragraph 4.5 of his Department's consultation response, Public consultation on the United Kingdom's future legal framework for imposing and implementing sanctions: government response, published in August 2017, if he will make it his policy to publish annual reviews of autonomous UK sanctions regimes after the provisions of the Sanctions and Anti-Money Laundering Bill come into force.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111744","111744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784906","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the contract to administer training grants for GPs through Primary Care Services England was outsourced in September 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111696","111696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784907","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions GP trainees have not been paid by the firm Capita since September 2015: how many GP trainees have been affected by such non-payment; and what the amount is that has not yet been paid.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111697","111697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784908","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings he or Ministers of his Department have held with Capita in the last three years; and what was discussed at each such meeting.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111698","111698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784909","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to reimburse GP trainees who have not been paid by Capita since September 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111699","111699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784910","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the evaluation of the HPV vaccination pilot for men who have sex with men.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111700","111700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784911","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his comments on the Andrew Marr BBC TV programme on 29 October 2017, on psychological therapies, which UK therapies the Swedish authorities have expressed an interest in replicating; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111758","111758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784912","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to hold NHS England and NHS Improvement to account about the failure of the NHS to meet the 18-week referral to treatment target since February 2016.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111718","111718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784913","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff employed by mental health trusts were previously employed by primary care trusts in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111756","111756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784914","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to assess the quality of hospital-provided patient transport services.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111737","111737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784915","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his oral evidence to the Health Select Committee, on Work of the Secretary of State for Health, on 31 October 2017, Q62, HC523, which locked mental rehabilitation wards he has visited since he took office; and on what dates those visits were made.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111757","111757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784916","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has altered the eligibility for patients receiving free transport to hospital.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111734","111734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784917","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111799","111799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784918","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage investment in dental technology in low-income areas.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111462","111462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784919","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many consultations on adult social care have been commissioned by his Department in the last 20 years; and if he will provide a list of those consultations.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111449","111449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784920","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 30 January 2017 to Question 61799, on in vitro fertilisation, what the timetable is for the implementation of the benchmark price for IVF.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111529","111529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784921","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111480","111480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784922","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce regional variation in the commissioning of IVF services in the NHS.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111528","111528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784923","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) affordability and (b) accessibility of medicines which are produced through publicly-funded medical research.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111610","111610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784924","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce standardised financial reporting measures for each medicine procured by the NHS.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111612","111612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784925","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many sight tests were carried out on the NHS in each clinical commissioning group area in the last 12 months for which data is available; and how many referrals for treatment there were for (a) AMD, glaucoma, (c) cataract and (d) diabetic eye disease in each such area in that same period.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111660","111660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784926","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent from the public purse on each category of eye research by the (a) National Institute for Health Research and (b) Medical Research Council in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111659","111659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784927","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with medical research organisations on the potential use of stem cells research and gene therapies to improve eye treatments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111661","111661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784928","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people living with glaucoma; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce their sight loss.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111637","111637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784929","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of products that will be considered for breakthrough status through the Accelerated Access Pathway in the next financial year.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111599","111599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784930","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the pharmaceutical industry on the cost effectiveness criteria for new treatments seeking breakthrough designation through the Accelerated Access Pathway.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111600","111600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784931","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the take-up of flu vaccination in people with chronic respiratory disease.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111655","111655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784932","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential relationship between the uptake of the flu vaccination in people with chronic respiratory disease and hospital admission rates for people with that disease.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111657","111657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784933","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the criteria are for patients to be appointed as a member of the Accelerated Access Collaborative.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111601","111601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784934","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many men have received the HPV vaccine through the HPV vaccination pilot for men who have sex with men; and how many such men received (a) one dose, (b) two doses or (c) three doses of the vaccine.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111653","111653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784935","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many EU nationals have left jobs in the NHS since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111664","111664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784936","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of post-traumatic stress disorder were diagnosed in (a) the UK and (b) London in 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111667","111667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784937","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency with a primary diagnosis of ophthalmological condition in each month of the last seven financial years.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111681","111681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784938","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the waiting times have been for cataract surgery in each clinical commissioning group in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111662","111662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784939","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency with a primary diagnosis of contusion or abrasion in each month of the last seven financial years.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111682","111682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784940","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the Accelerated Access Pathway to consider treatments for rare diseases, including muscle-wasting conditions, to be considered for fast-track breakthrough designation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111598","111598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784941","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pregnant women were admitted to hospital with vitamin D deficiency in each (a) English region and (b) parliamentary constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111555","111555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784942","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on the implementation of the Cancer Strategy; and what resources from the public purse he has allocated for that implementation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111561","111561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784943","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans =he-she has to reform the process for (a) appraisal and (b) funding of life-extending medicines for cancer patients.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111560","111560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784944","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Public Health England is taking to promote its guidance on the benefits to people of taking a daily vitamin D supplement in the autumn and winter months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111556","111556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784945","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were admitted to hospital with malnutrition as a (a) primary or (b) secondary condition in (i) England, (ii) each clinical commissioning group and (iii) each parliamentary constituency in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111554","111554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784946","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to hospital with malnutrition as a (a) primary or (b) secondary condition in (i) England, (ii) each clinical commissioning group and (iii) each parliamentary constituency in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111553","111553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784947","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve patient access to preventative drugs for breast cancer.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111559","111559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784948","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to (a) encourage and (b) fund research into new antibiotics to tackle antimicrobial resistance.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111558","111558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784949","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will set out the work of women's mental health taskforce to date.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111626","111626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784950","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to introduce the matchstick procedure to treat lung cancer on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111623","111623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784951","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list by police force area the (a) number of officers of superintendent rank or above in each local force and (b) proportion of each local police force's warranted strength that is of superintendent rank or above.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111622","111622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784952","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how her Department manages the Dubs scheme for child refugees; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111663","111663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784953","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which companies she has licensed to investigate the use of medical cannabis as a medicine.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111651","111651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784954","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what voluntary financial contributions the Government has made to support the work of Interpol in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111674","111674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784955","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with officials from Europol on the progress of that organisation's investigations into possible North Korean involvement in the WannaCry cyber attack in May 2017; and what steps she is taking to support those investigations.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111673","111673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784956","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has commissioned any reports into the use of medical marijuana.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111638","111638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784957","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that refugees have access to English language classes after their arrive in the UK.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111586","111586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784958","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which public telephone lines for her Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111481","111481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784959","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police horses there are in each police constabulary in the UK.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111489","111489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784960","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people applied for the superintendent direct entry scheme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111492","111492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784961","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to launch the next round of the next direct entry scheme for superintendent recruitment.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111493","111493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784962","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of leave to remain for the spouse of a British citizen are currently awaiting a decision.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111494","111494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784963","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time taken was to process a visa for a spouse of a British citizen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111495","111495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784964","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in her Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111800","111800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784965","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration cases involving rejected claims for asylum were overturned on appeal in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111736","111736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784966","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to use data on identities and current whereabouts gathered from children in the Jungle refugee camp in Calais before its demolition; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111669","111669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784967","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications have been received each week for discretionary leave to remain as a survivor or other individual directly affected by the Grenfell Tower fire since 5 July 2017.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111739","111739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784968","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in her Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111801","111801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784969","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he will take to protect access to generic medicines in low and middle-income countries when trade agreements are negotiated after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111466","111466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784970","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which public telephone lines for her Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111482","111482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784971","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the overseas aid budget in cash terms in the next financial year.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111588","111588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784972","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to programmes combating malaria in each of the last five financial years; and whether her Department plans to protect the current level of funding in real terms over the next five financial years.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111656","111656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784973","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to contain the spread of treatment-resistant strains of malaria in developing countries.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111654","111654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784974","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will publish the joint value for money guidance for UK Official Development Assistance agreed with HM Treasury to complement Managing Public Money.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111690","111690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784975","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her US counterpart on the potential effect of proposed reductions in the State Department's budget on global efforts to combat TB in developing countries.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111649","111649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784976","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to her counterpart in the US on that country's commitment to combatting TB in developing countries.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111650","111650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784977","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the programmes which it funds to support the distribution of malaria nets do not use insecticides to which mosquitos have become resistant.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111648","111648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784978","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 108373, what the names are of the 13 schools in Gaza directly funded by the UK in December 2011.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111539","111539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784979","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that humanitarian aid reaches civilians in the beseized area of East Ghouta.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111616","111616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784980","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how the Government is fulfilling its commitment as set out by the Grand Bargain where the UK pledged continuous leadership to provide education for children in crises and support to all partners who have extensive access to parts of Syria which have suffered the worst of the current crisis.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111617","111617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784981","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support internally displaced persons, including women and children, in the Syrian conflict.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111618","111618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784982","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support children with disabilities in Syria.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111619","111619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784983","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the UK response to the humanitarian crisis in Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111576","111576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784984","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of UK aid to Rakhine State and Myanmar.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111570","111570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784985","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of UK aid to Syria.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111571","111571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784986","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that the Drugs for Neglected Diseases initiative provides for products that are affordable for patients.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111579","111579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784987","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to his oral contribution of 5 September 2017, Official Report, column 18, on upskirting, what recent advice he has received on the creation of a specific sexual offence of upskirting.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111596","111596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784988","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted for assault in NHS hospitals have received a custodial sentence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111590","111590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784989","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111484","111484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784990","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women in prison have received an adjudication for refusing to (a) transfer to a different prison and (b) move to a different wing within a prison.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111505","111505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784991","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to respond to the recommendations made in the Lammy Review, published on 8 September 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111499","111499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784992","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the risk assessment conducted prior to the part-privatisation of the probation service.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111506","111506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784993","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of people who lost their job after being recalled to prison in each quarter in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111503","111503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784994","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total amount of funding allocated by the Government for legal representation to victims of the Grenfell Tower fire and their families was on 3 November 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111444","111444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784995","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people are managed by community rehabilitation companies in each constituency in England and Wales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111445","111445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784996","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on probation in each of the last five years; and how much of that expenditure was allocated to (a) the National Probation Service and (b) community rehabilitation companies in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111446","111446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784997","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what contingency plans his Department has put in place in the event that a community rehabilitation company terminates its contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111447","111447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784998","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111803","111803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784999","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made towards achieving its target of employing 2,500 extra prison officers by the end of 2018.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111735","111735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785000","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2017 to Question 10017, on youth custody: restraint techniques, how many injuries were sustained by young people in young offender institutions who were later transferred to mental health services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111760","111760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785001","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of restraint against children in young offender institutions there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111759","111759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785002","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which public telephone lines for his Office's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111485","111485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785003","2017-11-13","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111804","111804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785004","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-06","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2017 to Question 109011, which Cabinet colleagues she met to discuss Bombardier and its business interests in the US prior to the visit of the Secretary of State for International Trade to the US in July 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111455","111455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785005","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-06","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2017 to Question 109011, which (a) people and (b) organisations she met to discuss Bombardier and its business interests in the US prior to the visit of the Secretary of State for International Trade to the US in July 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111456","111456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785006","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what reporting mechanism the Government has in place for its trade envoys.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111652","111652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785007","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-06","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she has had with the (a) Chancellor of the Exchequer, (b) Financial Secretary to the Treasury, (c) Foreign Secretary and (d) Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster on the Paradise Papers.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111694","111694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785008","2017-11-13","Scotland Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111805","111805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785009","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111806","111806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785010","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 20 July 2017, on rail update, HCWS85, if he will publish the evidential basis for the claim that it is no longer necessary to electrify every line to achieve the same significant improvements to journeys.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111720","111720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785011","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 20 July 2017, on rail update, HCWS85, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of (a) commissioning and (b) maintaining (i) electric trains which would have been used on the lines which no longer will be electrified and (ii) the bi-mode trains which will now be used on those lines in pence per vehicles mile.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111721","111721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785012","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108962, on transport: per capita costs, if he will provide equivalent data for 2016-17 onwards.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111722","111722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785013","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the Legal Working Group on Seafarers and the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111717","111717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785014","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent staff are currently employed by (a) Transport for London, (b) Transport for the North and (c) Rail North.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111668","111668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785015","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 20 July 2017, HCWS85, on rail update, which models of (a) electric trains which would have been used on the lines will no longer be electrified and (b) bi-mode trains will now be used on those lines.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111766","111766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785016","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 20 July 2017, HCSW85, on rail update, whether an assessment has been carried out on the potential effect of bi-modal train technology on (a) levels of nitrogen oxides and (b) air pollution levels in the north of England.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111765","111765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785017","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Highways England's Growth and Housing Fund spent in each NUTS 1 region of England and Wales in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111665","111665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785018","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the statistical release Annual Bus Services: England 2015-16, if he will set out bus mileage figures for (a) local authority supported services and (b) commercial services for each NUTS 1 region in England in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111666","111666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785019","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to review the issuing of Certificates of Equivalent Competency to non-UK resident officers in the British merchant shipping industry.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111550","111550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785020","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to reduce rail journey times between York and Harrogate.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111580","111580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785021","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111486","111486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785022","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding for rail electrification between Didcot and Oxford.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111543","111543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785023","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress is being made on developing alternative fuel trains.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111614","111614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785024","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November  2017 to Question 110091, on taxis: disability, what his Department's definition is of vulnerable individuals; and whether that definition includes blind or partially sighted people.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111530","111530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785025","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train stations have waiting rooms which are fully accessible.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111518","111518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785026","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparative assessment he has made of the seating capacity provided by the Meridian and HST trains servicing the East Midlands franchise and bi-mode trains which will replace those trains.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111613","111613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785027","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will mandate Northern Rail to operate replacement buses on the Furness line in circumstances where cancelled or reduced services affect children's ability to travel to and from school.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111609","111609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785028","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) BAME people, (b) disabled people and (c) women work for Network Rail.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111523","111523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785029","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which railway stations do not have step-free access.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111524","111524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785030","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many railway stations (a) have and (b) do not have step-free access.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111525","111525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785031","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the financial return to the public purse from the sale of Network Rail land and assets in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111526","111526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785032","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people aged (a) under 20, (b) 21 to 30, (c) 31 to 40, (d) 41 to 50, (e) 51 to 60 and (f) over 61-years old work for each train operating company.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111519","111519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785033","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people aged (a) under 20, (b) 21 to 30, (c) 31 to 40, (d) 41 to 50, (e) 51 to 60 and (f) over 61-years old work for Network Rail.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111520","111520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785034","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of train stations which have toilets which are accessible.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111521","111521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785035","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) people, (b) BAME people and (c) women work for each train operating company.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111522","111522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785036","2017-11-13","Wales Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of devolution of air passenger duty to Wales in (a) job creation in Wales and (b) the overall performance of the Welsh economy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111658","111658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785037","2017-11-13","Wales Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111808","111808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785038","2017-11-13","Women and Equalities","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what childcare facilities her Department makes available for its staff; how much her Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those facilities in the last 12 months; and how many of her Department's staff use those facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111678","111678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785039","2017-11-13","Women and Equalities","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will review the management and funding of the Equality and Human Rights Commission after recent redundancies.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111627","111627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785040","2017-11-13","Women and Equalities","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, which public telephone lines for the Government Equalities Office's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111479","111479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785041","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants of universal credit in full service areas by each stage of roll-out, including pilots, have gained (a) full and (b) part-time employment.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111532","111532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785042","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111488","111488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785043","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of mandatory health and work conversations on the health and wellbeing of disabled claimants which take place after the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111508","111508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785044","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 30 March 2017 to Question 69316, on universal credit, what plans he has to ensure that the children of people who are not incentivised to work by universal credit do not live in poverty.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111548","111548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785046","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with motor neurone disease who have been awarded the enhanced rate for the care and mobility components of personal independence payments have been subject to a reassessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111458","111458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785047","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of attempted online claims for universal credit have been timed out in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111448","111448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785048","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in North West Durham constituency who previously qualified for disability living allowance have not been awarded personal independence payments following an assessment by the Independent Assessment Services.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111630","111630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785049","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether people who agree voluntarily to move from existing benefits to universal credit forego the right to any transitional protection against a loss of income.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111597","111597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785050","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment (PIP) claimants with terminal illnesses and life-shortening diseases (a) were declared ineligible for PIP following assessment (b) appealed that decision successfully at tribunal.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111567","111567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785051","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the personal independence payment process on the health and wellbeing of claimants.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111562","111562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785052","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of long-term sick and disabled personal independence payment (PIP) claimants taking repeated PIP tests and assessments of the health and wellbeing of claimants; and what the cost to the public purse has been of such repeat tests and assessments since they were instituted.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111563","111563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785053","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the abolition of lifetime awards of disability living allowance on the health and wellbeing of claimants.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111564","111564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785054","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of the roll-out of universal credit on the health and wellbeing of disabled claimants who are currently claiming enhanced disability premium and severe disability premium.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111565","111565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785055","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the personal independence payment process complaints system.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111566","111566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785056","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of assessments for (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payments went to appeal in North West Durham constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111677","111677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785057","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has set targets for increasing the number of existing benefit claimants who are voluntarily moved to universal credit ahead of the planned date for their migration.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111605","111605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785058","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former claimants of disability living allowance in North West Durham constituency who have been unsuccessful in their claim for personal independence payments have been waiting more than (a) six weeks, (b) three months and (c) six months for their appeal to be heard.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111676","111676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785059","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 5 April 2017 to Question 69580, on personal independence payment: epilepsy, of the 7,100 re-assessment claims for people with a primary disabling condition of epilepsy, how many of those initial decisions were (a) upheld and (b) overturned.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111634","111634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785060","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what percentage of decisions on employment and support allowance and personal independence payments were overturned in North West Durham constituency on (a) mandatory reconsideration and (b) appeal in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111675","111675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785061","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to implement the recommendations of his Department's report on Improving Lives: Helping Workless Families, published in April 2017.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111633","111633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785062","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what childcare facilities his Department makes available for its staff; how much his Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those facilities in the last 12 months; and how many of his Department's staff use those facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111679","111679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785063","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been asked voluntarily to move from receiving existing benefits to universal credit in advance of their planned migration in (a) Newcastle upon Tyne, (b) the North East and (c) England in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111606","111606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785064","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111809","111809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785065","2017-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people deemed fit to work by Work Place Assessments changed status within a 12 month period in the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111773","111773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785066","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 2 November 2017, HCWS218, on social security, how existing personal independence payment (PIP) claimants who were considered ineligible for support as a result of previous PIP assessment guidelines will be (a) identified and (b) assessed according to the updated PIP assessment guidelines.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111727","111727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785067","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 2 November 2017, HCWS218, on social security, how many previously unsuccessful personal independence payment (PIP) claimants are now eligible for PIP under the updated PIP assessment guidelines.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111728","111728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785068","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 2 November 2017, HCSW218, what additional training and support will be made available to personal independence payment (PIP) assessors and other relevant healthcare professionals in light of the updated PIP assessment guidelines.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111710","111710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785069","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 2 November 2017, HCSW218, when the updated guidance will be applied to new and existing personal independence payment claimants; and when those claimants will receive the additional support outlined in that Statement.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111711","111711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785070","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the General Data Protection Regulation on small businesses.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111775","111775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785071","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111791","111791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785072","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that all licensing agreements for medicines made by the NHS are placed on a publicly-accessible database.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111607","111607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785073","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that public interest conditions are included and enforced in all publicly-funded medical research contracts and agreements.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111602","111602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785074","2017-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent meetings officials his Department have had with the Federation of Master Builders on late payment of small and medium-sized enterprises in the construction sector.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111705","111705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785075","2017-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of small and medium-sized enterprises in the construction sector which have had to wait more than four months for payment by their customers.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111704","111704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785076","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what funding his Department has allocated to research into the development of small-scale nuclear reactors in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111615","111615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785077","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of small-scale nuclear reactors to the provision of electricity in the UK.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111549","111549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785078","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to extend the Register of Beneficial Ownership to British Overseas Territories; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111541","111541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785079","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has for additional support to assist vulnerable people with their energy bills in winter 2017-18; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111459","111459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785080","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the preparation and publication of the independent report, entitled Cost of energy, published on 25 October 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111460","111460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785081","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111469","111469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785082","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish a response to the Government's Post Office network consultation of November 2016.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111531","111531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785083","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111483","111483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785084","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2017 to Question 109062, whether the Government plans for the trade remedies investigating authority to be operational by the end of March 2019.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111497","111497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785085","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to encourage World Trade Organisation (WTO) members to meet their obligations under Article 25 of the WTO's Agreement on Subsidies and Countervailing Measures.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111498","111498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785086","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if the UK will be required to reapply to the World Trade Organisation after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111584","111584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785087","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what research his Department has commissioned to support the development of the economic interest test which is to be used as part of the trade remedies investigation.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111647","111647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785088","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what form the economic interest test to be used as part of the trade remedies investigation will take.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111646","111646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785089","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111802","111802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785090","2017-11-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111797","111797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785091","2017-11-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to his Department's Freedom of information response DEX000585 of 29 September 2017, on sector studies, on which date each of the studies in the initial exercise was completed.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111763","111763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785092","2017-11-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111477","111477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785093","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government plans to take as a result of information in the Paradise Papers relating to companies that hold existing government contracts.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111779","111779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785094","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department employed after 24 June 2016 hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111841","111841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785095","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the total sum of revenue that it has forgone due to the successive freezes to fuel duty since 2011.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111790","111790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785096","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to announce the allocation of funding by the Independent Dormant Assets Commission.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111843","111843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785097","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of committing a proportion of the funding from the Independent Dormant Assets Commission to prepare charities for compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111844","111844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785098","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 5.11 of the Spring Budget 2017 that the Government will explore the appropriate tax treatment for diesel vehicles, and will engage with stakeholders ahead of making any tax changes at Autumn Budget 2017, what tax treatment measures the Government has explored; and which stakeholders the Government has engaged with on that matter.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111852","111852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785099","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 20 of the Government's UK plan for tackling roadside nitrogen dioxide concentrations, what progress the Government has made on considering a change to the tax treatment of new diesel vehicles.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111853","111853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785100","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of existing legislation to allow landlords to access let properties to rectify problems that threaten the safety of other residents and the wider community.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111820","111820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785101","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the Government decided that the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre should not be located at the Imperial War Museum.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111709","111709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785102","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support the Premier League uphold its rule that states an individual who owns a stake of 10 per cent or more in one club cannot hold a single share in another club.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111776","111776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785103","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the telephone helpline for small businesses on the General Data Protection Regulation, run by the Information Commissioner's Office, will be open to small charities.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111845","111845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785104","2017-11-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to extend her Department's support for smaller charities to include training on data protection before the introduction of the General Data Protection Regulation in May 2018.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111842","111842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785105","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many flying hours have been logged on (a) Merlin, (b) Wildcat, (c) Apache, (d) Gazelle, (e) Chinook, (f) Puma, (g) Lynx, (h) Bell 212 and (i) Defender aircraft under Joint Helicopter Command in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111823","111823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785106","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many flying hours have been logged on (a) Merlin, (b) Wildcat, (c) Apache, (d) Gazelle, (e) Chinook, (f) Puma, (g) Lynx, (h) Bell 212 and (i) Defender aircraft under Joint Helicopter Command in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111824","111824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785107","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to reduce Joint Helicopter Command's basing footprint.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111827","111827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785108","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Joint Helicopter Command overseas training exercises have been cancelled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111825","111825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785109","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained pilots from (a) the Royal Navy Fleet Air Arm, (b) the Commando Helicopter Force, (c) the Army Air Corps, (d) RAF units and (e) formations under Joint Helicopter Command have left the regular armed forces in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111829","111829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785110","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many flying hours the (a) Royal Navy Fleet Air Arm, (b) Commando Helicopter Force, (c) Army Air Corps and (d) Royal Air Force pilots under Joint Helicopter Command have flown in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111846","111846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785111","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many pilots have joined (a) the Royal Navy Fleet Air Arm, (b) the Commando Helicopter Force, (c) the Army Air Corps, (d) RAF units and (e) formations under Joint Helicopter Command in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111830","111830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785112","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to commemorate the Battle of Beersheba in 1917.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111831","111831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785113","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Joint Helicopter Command exercises have been held in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111828","111828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785114","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Joint Helicopter Command overseas training exercises have been cancelled in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111826","111826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785115","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many unrecorded or illegal school exclusions were reported to her Department in the last academic year.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111784","111784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785116","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance has been issued by her Department to ensure that school governors give appropriate consideration to autism and SEND when considering exclusion appeals.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111787","111787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785117","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many cases of serious misconduct by headteachers have been reported to her Department by the National College for Teaching and Leadership in each of the last three years; and how many of those cases included inappropriate exclusions.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111788","111788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785118","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department plans to publish draft regulations on single animal establishment licences.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111822","111822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785119","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what conversations his Department has had with the HM Revenue and Customs taskforce on puppy and kitten online sales.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111821","111821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785120","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to approve hydrogen cell technology to power taxis in England.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111833","111833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785121","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with the Moroccan Ambassador to the UK the need for an independent investigation into the death of Minatu Ahl Shikh.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111836","111836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785122","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what stepsher Department is taking to commemorate the Battle of Beersheba in 1917.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111832","111832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785123","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish the total fee income of the British Embassy in Iran for (a) Legal Proceedings, (b) Emergency Assistance and (c) Other Services in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111778","111778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785124","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of recent reports that aid convoys are being blocked from entering the Eastern Ghouta region in Syria on the humanitarian situation in that region.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111817","111817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785125","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many full-time equivalent members of staff work within the Counter Proliferation and Arms Control Centre; and how many such members of staff are working on secondment from (a) his Department, (b) the Department for International Trade, (c) the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy and (d) other Government departments.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111751","111751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785126","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent reports of aerial bombardments, including against schools, on the humanitarian situation in the Eastern Ghouta region in Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111818","111818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785127","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish a response to the latest charges against Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe following her appearance before the Iranian Revolutionary Court on November 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111819","111819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785128","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total budget allocated by his Department for projects under the Government's counter-proliferation programme was in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111752","111752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785129","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total budget allocated by the Government for projects under the (a) Global Threat Reduction Programme and (b) International Biological Security Programme was in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17 and (iii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111753","111753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785130","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total amount of Government financial support for projects established under the Global Partnership Against the Spread of Weapons and Material of Mass Destruction has been in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111754","111754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785131","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to subject autonomous UK sanctions regimes to periodic independent review after the provisions of the Sanctions and Anti-Money Laundering Bill come into force.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111747","111747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785132","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to section 3.1 of his Department's guidance, Counter Proliferation Programme objectives, published in March 2017, for what reasons single-country projects are no longer eligible for support unless the target countries can self-fund the relevant proposals.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111748","111748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785133","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to paragraph 7.17 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Counter Proliferation and Arms Control Centre in consolidating expertise and decision-making on international counter-proliferation and arms control issues from across government.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111749","111749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785134","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the merits of providing aid drops to alleviate food and medical supply scarcity in the Eastern Ghouta region in Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111815","111815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785135","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the work of Europol in assisting with the implementation of multilateral sanctions; and what plans the Government has to continue working with that organisation on implementing sanctions after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111750","111750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785136","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Russian counterpart on the ability of aid convoys to enter the Eastern Ghouta region in Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111816","111816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785137","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people were undertaking a senior healthcare support worker (maternity support) apprenticeship at level 3 within an NHS trust at the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111839","111839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785138","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship training providers are ready to deliver the senior healthcare support worker (maternity support) apprenticeship at level 3.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111840","111840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785139","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths resulted from (a) breast, (b) cervical and (c) prostate cancer in (i) 2015-16 and (ii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111847","111847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785140","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 13 April 2016 to Question 32737, on malnutrition, whether he plans to revise national guidance on food supplements.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111712","111712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785141","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2017 to Question 10723, on waiting lists, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the NHS takes all reasonable steps to offer patients who are waiting more than 18 weeks for elective care a suitable alternative provider.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111785","111785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785142","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) applications and (b) awards of costs against local authorities in relation to tribunals involving SEND appeals have been made in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111786","111786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785143","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which NHS trusts have made apprenticeship levy payments since 6 April 2017; and how much has been paid since that date (a) by each NHS trust and (b) in total by all NHS trusts.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111837","111837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785144","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much NHS trusts have paid apprenticeship training providers since 6 April 2017; how much of that spending has been on senior healthcare support worker (maternity support) apprenticeships at level 3; and how many people have started that such apprenticeship since 6 April 2017.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111838","111838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785145","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how long is the average waiting time for a double knee replacement operation on the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111856","111856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785146","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people, by gender, undergoing a community programme approach received follow-up post-discharge support from a mental health hospital within (a) 48 hours and (b) seven days in 2016-17.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111850","111850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785147","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people, by gender, received follow-up post-discharge support from a mental health hospital within (a) 48 hours and (b) seven days in 2016-17.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111851","111851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785148","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who are entitled to discretionary leave to remain as a survivor or other individual directly affected by the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111755","111755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785149","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made on the (a) availability of food and medical supplies to civilians and (b) safety of those people providing such supplies in the Syrian De-Escalation Zones.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111814","111814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785150","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aid has been provided by the UK to civilians in the Eastern Ghouta region in Syria in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111813","111813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785151","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the unduly lenient sentence scheme.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111834","111834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785152","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Russian passport holders are currently serving sentences in British prisons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111777","111777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785153","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the Government plans to spend on the Congestion relief programme in each NUTS 1 region of England and Wales.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111780","111780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785154","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the final recommendations from the Legal Working Group on seafarers and the national minimum wage are.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111713","111713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785155","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how his Department plans to invest in major road schemes identified by Transport for the North which are not part of the Strategic Road Network; and whether such schemes will be considered as potential investments in the Government's 2020-2025 Road Investment Strategy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111781","111781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785156","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much (a) Network Rail, (b) Transport for London, (c) his Department, (d) Transport for the North and (e) Rail North have spent on advertising in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111783","111783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785157","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many supported bus service routes have been (a) downgraded or (b) withdrawn in each NUTS 1 region of England in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111782","111782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785158","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has (a) allocated and (b) plans to allocate to (i) Transport for London, (ii) Transport for the North and (iii) Rail North in each year from 2012-13 to 2020-21.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111812","111812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785159","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total value of spending for projects in the 2015 to 2020 Road Investment Strategy is in each NUTS1 region of England and Wales.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111789","111789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785160","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the six major road schemes in the 2015-2020 Road Investment Strategy that Highways England is pausing, how many of those schemes are in northern England, broken down by NUTS 1 region; and if he will commit to resuming all six of those schemes at a future date.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111810","111810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785161","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the 16 major road schemes in the 2015-2020 Road Investment Strategy that Highways England is delaying are in northern England, broken down by NUTS 1 region.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111811","111811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785162","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with stakeholders on the redevelopment of Oxford railway station.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111848","111848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785163","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the performance of bi-mode Class 800 trains on the Great Western route.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111849","111849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785164","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 2 November 2017, on social security, HCWS218, whether his Department plans to undertake a full review of the Personal Independence Payments (PIP) Assessment Guide to take account of all relevant Upper Tribunal rulings relating to PIP.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111723","111723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785165","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 2 November 2017, on social security, HCWS218, whether new and existing claimants will have to wait until 2022-23 for any additional support they are entitled to under the updated  Personal Independence Payments Assessment Guidelines.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111724","111724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785166","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 2 November 2017, on social security, HCWS218, whether a fast-tracked reassessment process will be made available for previously personal independence payment (PIP) applicants with epilepsy within the updated PIP Assessment Guidelines.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111726","111726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785167","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 2 November 2017, on social security, HCWS218, whether previous personal independence payment (PIP) applicants with epilepsy who were unsuccessful under the previous PIP Assessment Guidelines will have their claims automatically reassessed in accordance with the updated PIP Assessment Guidelines.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111725","111725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785168","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of applying a disregard for Armed Forces Pensions when considering the eligibility for income-related benefits for former members of the Armed Forces.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111854","111854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785169","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will introduce a boiler replacement scheme for terminally ill people in receipt of a contribution-based benefit who are denied access to existing schemes where eligibility is determined through receipt of an income-related benefit.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111855","111855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785170","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will update the guidance to HM Revenue and Customs National Minimum Wage Enforcement Team officials on seafarers and the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111715","111715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785171","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons officials of his Department did not attend the meeting of the Legal Working Group on seafarers and the national minimum wage held at the Department for Transport on (a) 22 February and (b) 1 November 2017.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111714","111714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785172","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will place a copy in the Library of the service level agreement between his Department and the HM Revenue and Customs National Minimum Wage Enforcement Team.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111716","111716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/785173","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to reply to the letter of 14 June 2017 from the hon. Member for Weston-Super-Mare on behalf of Organic Milk Supplies Co-operative Ltd about exports to the US and the EU.","Biography information for John Penrose","John Penrose","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111835","111835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783146","2017-11-07","Cabinet Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Government will establish a group of Ministers and officials to discuss proposals for the long-term funding of social care.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111274","111274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783147","2017-11-07","Cabinet Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111278","111278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783148","2017-11-07","Cabinet Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of Government procurement from small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111304","111304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783149","2017-11-07","Cabinet Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the merits of reducing the voting age to 16 and the effect such a change would have on democratic participation.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111305","111305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783150","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of (a) joining up existing disability registers with the electoral register and (b) recording preferences on accessing information on the electoral register.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111331","111331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783151","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of eligible people not on the electoral register for the last five general elections in (a) the UK and (b) Nottingham North.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111332","111332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783152","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of people in work in (a) Greater Manchester, (b) the North West and (c) Denton and Reddish constituency earn less than the full-time equivalent of the national living wage.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111409","111409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783153","2017-11-15","Cabinet Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of tracking military personnel who are serving overseas on the electoral register.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111440","111440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783154","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid through working tax credits to people in the Denton and Reddish constituency in each year from 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111398","111398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783155","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been collected by HM Revenue and Customs in VAT from companies that had previously received Enterprise Investment Scheme tax relief in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111407","111407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783156","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been collected by HM Revenue and Customs in corporation tax from companies that had previously received Enterprise Investment Scheme tax relief in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111393","111393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783157","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been collected in Pay as You Earn income from companies that had previously received Enterprise Investment Scheme tax relief in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111394","111394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783158","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of child exploitation by criminal gangs across Merseyside.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111303","111303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783159","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the rise in beer duty in the March 2017 Budget (a) on the price of beer for consumers and (b) in tax revenue.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111352","111352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783160","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding the Welsh Government has received from the apprenticeship levy in the first year of its implementation.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111338","111338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783161","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the amount allocated to the Welsh Assembly under the apprenticeship levy is calculated.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111339","111339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783162","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2017 to Question 109593, what representations he has made to representatatives of the banking sector on the accessibility of full banking services for SMEs when their bank branch closes.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111345","111345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783163","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much apprenticeship levy funding has been collected in Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111337","111337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783164","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the further report of the Financial Conduct Authority on Royal Bank of Scotland's treatment of small and medium-sized enterprises to be published.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111358","111358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783165","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2017 to Question 110240 on the Royal Bank of Scotland, what plans he has to extend the responsibilities of the Financial Conduct Authority to oversee business lending.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111359","111359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783166","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111291","111291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783167","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the Home Secretary on police funding to tackle gun crime and serious and organised crime across Merseyside.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111308","111308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783168","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111279","111279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783169","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department's public bodies spent on employees partly or wholly employed on trade union duties in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111400","111400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783170","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of (a) fraud and (b) financial error in (i) his Department, (ii) its executive agencies and (iii) its non-departmental public bodies in each year from 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111401","111401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783171","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Oral contribution of Lord Ahmad of Wimbledon on 23 March 2015, Official Report, column GC331, what progress has been made on undertaking a review of the impact of changes to the selective licensing of houses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111411","111411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783172","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the affordable housing budget was in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111424","111424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783173","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 108119, on job creation: enterprise zones, how many jobs enterprise zones were planned to create in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111426","111426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783174","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 108916, on families: disadvantaged, what the specified interval periods will be for reporting on the national evaluation.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111427","111427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783175","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 108916, on families: disadvantaged, when the decision was made to make the troubled families programme subject to a comprehensive national evaluation; and which Minister made that decision.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111428","111428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783176","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2017 to Question 109734, on private rented housing: safety, if he will publish the minutes of the working group on electrical safety in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111442","111442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783177","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2017 to Question 109733, on social rented housing: disability, how many adaptations were completed in each year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111441","111441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783178","2017-11-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if the Government will publish the full description of BT's voluntary offer to deliver the Universal Service Obligation for broadband, the Government's response to that offer and the timetable for the release of those publications.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111397","111397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783179","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109291, if she will collect information on the number of local newspapers across the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111297","111297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783180","2017-11-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of her Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111281","111281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783181","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what definition her Department uses for the phrase archiving in the public interest.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111381","111381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783182","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to reintroduce public library standards.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111382","111382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783183","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the importance of libraries to social mobility.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111383","111383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783184","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of library closures on local communities.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111384","111384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783185","2017-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to place new orders for Hawk Trainers for the Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111375","111375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783186","2017-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111280","111280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783187","2017-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109676, on military bases: fire prevention, on how many occasions a Minister from his Department has met the Director General Defence Safety Authority to discuss fire safety at military bases in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111425","111425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783188","2017-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any additional funds will be allocated to the Trident replacement programme in the 2017-18 financial year which have not already been budgeted for.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111415","111415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783189","2017-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will give consideration to retaining UK aerospace design and manufacturing capability by taking into account supply chains when purchasing new aircraft.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111413","111413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783190","2017-11-07","Department for Education","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to develop an informed and co-ordinated range of child-centred services and support to ensure positive outcomes for the children of mothers serving short-term prison sentences.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111404","111404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783191","2017-11-07","Department for Education","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of average class sizes in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency, (b) the North West and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111306","111306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783192","2017-11-07","Department for Education","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of her Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111282","111282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783193","2017-11-07","Department for Education","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to add Holocaust education to all key stages of the national curriculum.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111269","111269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783194","2017-11-07","Department for Education","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what arrangements she has put in place to ensure local democratic accountability of multi-academy trusts.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111272","111272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783195","2017-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111283","111283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783196","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations his Department has received on whether placing geographical indicators for products on a UK legal basis through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill will mean that those indicators are recognised by EU member states; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111369","111369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783197","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish his plans for peat restoration.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111367","111367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783198","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's timetable is for the introduction of a new farm policy.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111351","111351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783199","2017-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 108716, on trees: imports, for what reasons the UK intercepts a higher proportion of harmful organisms than other EU countries.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111333","111333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783200","2017-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 108716, on trees: imports, what powers the UK Plant Health Authority has to ban imports of trees carrying harmful organisms.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111334","111334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783201","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on section 230 of the US Communications Decency Act 1996.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111325","111325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783202","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his policy is on the potential inclusion of section 230 of the US Communications Decency Act 1996 in any US-UK free trade deal.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111326","111326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783203","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support The Gambia to rejoin the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111327","111327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783204","2017-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he was made aware of meetings in Israel held by the Secretary of State for International Development in August 2017; and what information he has since been given about what was discussed at those meetings.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111361","111361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783205","2017-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111284","111284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783206","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that trade negotiations include low and middle-income countries in Africa when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111319","111319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783207","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the Gambia's transition to democracy.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111322","111322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783208","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met their counterparts in the (i) EU and (ii) US to discuss the case of Raif Badawi in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111410","111410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783209","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has to ensure that Commonwealth nations help to tackle economic problems and to embed democracy in (a) the Gambia and (b) other low and middle-income countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111436","111436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783210","2017-11-07","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 110492, on NHS: computer software, what that 21 million will be spent on and over what period of time.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111395","111395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783211","2017-11-07","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many penalty charges have been issued in respect of wrongly claiming NHS prescriptions in each of the last 36 months; and what proportion of those fined were in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111406","111406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783212","2017-11-07","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the delay in the launch of the London sexually transmitted infection testing services on (a) patient access to sexually transmitted infection testing in London and (b) London council's public health budgets.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111311","111311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783213","2017-11-07","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions Public Health England has had on the London Sexual Health Transformation Programme; with which parties those discussions have taken place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111309","111309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783214","2017-11-07","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment has been made of the effect on testing rates for sexually transmitted infections of the London Sexual Health Transformation Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111310","111310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783215","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the report by the Nuffield Trust and the Health Foundation on the consistent gap between the dental health of the rich and poor.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111295","111295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783216","2017-11-07","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department will take to monitor and publicise progress towards adding 21,000 posts and 19,000 additional mental health staff by 2020.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111275","111275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783217","2017-11-07","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111285","111285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783218","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability of the children's influenza vaccine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111356","111356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783219","2017-11-07","Department of Health","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when in the last 12 months he has received representations on the London Sexual Health Transformation Programme from (a) MPs and (b) other interested parties; what the content of those representations was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111340","111340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783220","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for the roll-out of the police welfare service for Northamptonshire Police.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111368","111368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783221","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986, how many project licence applications the Home Office rejected in 2016, 2015 and 2014.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111372","111372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783222","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants (a) took and (b) failed the Life in the UK test in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111389","111389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783223","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of regulated animal procedures conducted in 2016 were funded, or part-funded, by registered charities.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111373","111373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783224","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce use of live animals in experiments.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111374","111374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783225","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of her Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111286","111286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783226","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will amend legislation on births, deaths and marriages to remove the requirement to register DNA of a deceased father on a birth certificate where paternity is not contested.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111270","111270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783227","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has received any formal complaints on the conduct of the Independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111296","111296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783228","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce dangerous journeys for unaccompanied child refugees with family in the UK.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111408","111408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783229","2017-11-07","Department for International Development","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 110167, on Department of International Development: visits abroad, whether that Answer applies to both journeys.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111396","111396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783230","2017-11-07","Department for International Development","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111287","111287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783231","2017-11-07","Department for International Development","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will list the meetings she held in Israel during August 2017; who was present at those meetings; and what was discussed at each of those meetings.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111363","111363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783232","2017-11-07","Department for International Development","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings she has had in Israel with which officials since June 2017.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111343","111343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783233","2017-11-07","Department for International Development","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings she has had in the West Bank with Palestinian Authority officials since June 2017.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111344","111344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783234","2017-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to review the personal injury discount rate.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111371","111371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783235","2017-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111289","111289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783236","2017-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to support prisons to participate in (a) Holocaust Memorial Day, (b) Black History Month and (c) National Hate Crime Awareness Week.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111268","111268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783237","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many community orders for non-violent offences have been made in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111316","111316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783238","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many community orders for violent and sexual offences were made last year.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111317","111317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783239","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children and young people aged 18 to 24 have been granted legal aid under the exceptional care funding mechanism in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111318","111318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783240","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent from the public purse on legal aid for asylum seekers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111387","111387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783241","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will reduce the qualifying period for filterable childhood convictions from five and a half years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111405","111405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783242","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will propose reforms to the system for disclosure of youth criminal records to remove barriers to rehabilitation.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111423","111423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783243","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of implementing a new approach for disclosing the criminal records of young adults.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111419","111419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783244","2017-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions to public sector vacancies.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111417","111417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783245","2017-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review the current rehabilitation periods under the Rehabilitation of Offenders Act 1974, particularly in the case of Detention and Training Orders and Youth Rehabilitation Orders.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111418","111418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783246","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will replace the single list of non-filterable offences with customised lists relevant to broad areas of employment, professional activity and licences.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111422","111422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783247","2017-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on educational providers not using information about spent criminal records to deny access to courses for young people.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111420","111420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783248","2017-11-07","Home Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will remove the rule preventing the filtering of multiple convictions.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111421","111421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783249","2017-11-13","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what childcare facilities his Department makes available for its staff; how much his Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those facilities in the last 12 months; and how many of his Department's staff use those facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111298","111298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783250","2017-11-07","Prime Minister","2017-11-03","To ask the Prime Minister, when she was made aware of meetings in Israel held by the Secretary of State for International Development in August 2017; and what information she has since been given about what was discussed at those meetings.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111362","111362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783251","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what childcare facilities 10 Downing Street makes available for its staff; how much 10 Downing Street spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those facilities in the last 12 months; and how many of 10 Downing Street's staff use those facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111299","111299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783252","2017-11-07","Prime Minister","2017-11-03","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2017 to Question 9603, on Prime Ministerial visits, where the requested information has been made publicly available.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111313","111313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783253","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his oral contribution of 1 November 2017, Official Report, column 811, on tax avoidance, if he will set out the sources of the 160 billion in additional compliance revenues.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111439","111439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783254","2017-11-13","Scotland Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what childcare facilities his Department makes available for its staff; how much his Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those facilities in the last 12 months; and how many of his Department's staff use those facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111300","111300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783255","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what childcare facilities his Department makes available for its staff; how much his Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those facilities in the last 12 months; and how many of his Department's staff use those facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111301","111301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783256","2017-11-16","Department for Transport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the two-year gap between current high speed trains becoming non-compliant in 2020 and new bi-mode trains being available in 2022.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111370","111370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783257","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans there are to improve capacity and speed on rail connections between Sheffield and Manchester.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111390","111390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783258","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the level of awareness among air passengers of the entitlement of a refund of air passenger taxes to the consumer when a passenger does not travel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111355","111355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783259","2017-11-07","Department for Transport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Government will facilitate testing and limited commercial trials of personal delivery devices to attract high technology companies to the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111341","111341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783260","2017-11-07","Department for Transport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential of semi-autonomous personal delivery devices to (a) reduce emissions and congestion and (b) assist those with mobility issues to enjoy increased independence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111342","111342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783261","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the barriers to through-ticketing for luggage across different airlines and within individual airlines.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111273","111273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783262","2017-11-07","Department for Transport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111290","111290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783263","2017-11-07","Department for Transport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is his Department's policy to establish a passenger ombudsman.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111403","111403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783264","2017-11-13","Wales Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions his Department has had with the Welsh Government on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Welsh economy.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111330","111330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783265","2017-11-13","Wales Office","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what childcare facilities his Department makes available for its staff; how much his Department spent (a) overall and (b) per child on those facilities in the last 12 months; and how many of his Department's staff use those facilities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111302","111302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783266","2017-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to make an assessment of the provision of homeless accommodation specifically designed for women experiencing multi-disadvantages such as domestic violence and mental illness.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111414","111414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783267","2017-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to improve the transitional process from prison to release for women.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111402","111402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783268","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to review the PIP2 form and the requirement that it be returned to his Department within four weeks.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111429","111429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783269","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what disability-specific training personal independence payment assessors receive to enable them to adapt their communication and assessment methods so that claimants can better understand and take part in their assessment.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111433","111433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783270","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what venues were used for assessments for personal independence payments in Manchester in the last 12 months; and what assessment his Department made of the accessibility of those venues before choosing them.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111434","111434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783271","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Manchester Gorton constituency have been denied a home assessment for their personal independence payment claim; and what reasons were given for those decisions.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111435","111435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783272","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's Personal Independence Payment Assessment Guide, paragraph 1.5.4, what recent assessment he has made of compliance with the guidance on cases that should not require a face-to-face consultation by assessors; and what estimate he has made of the number of claimants who were invited to attend unnecessary face-to-face assessments in the most recent 12-month period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111443","111443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783273","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to review its policy on exemptions from reassessment for personal independence payments claimants.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111431","111431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783274","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 108024, whether the Independent Case Examiner's Office plans to increase the number of full-time equivalent staff investigating complaints from women adversely affected by the increase in state pension age.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111437","111437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783275","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has published to raise awareness of requesting a home assessment for personal independence payments applicants.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111432","111432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783276","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the HM Revenue and Customs Jointly Managed Engagement Team is the same as the Late, Missing and Incorrect RTI project, referred to in the reply of 26 September 2017 from his Department's Freedom of Information Team, ref Fol 3556, to Mr John Slater; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111438","111438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783277","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to review the personal independence payments claims process.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111430","111430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783278","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints relating to women born in the 1950s and affected by changes in state pension age have been rejected by the Independent Case Examiner's Office.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111385","111385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783279","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints relating to women born in the 1950s and affected by changes in state pension age have been fully reviewed by the Independent Case Examiner's Office.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111386","111386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783280","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has been made of the main reasons why employers repeatedly report earnings late; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111388","111388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783281","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the rate of child poverty has been in each year from 2010 to 2017; and what the rate of child poverty is forecast to be in each year from 2018 to 2020.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111276","111276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783282","2017-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111292","111292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783283","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate his Department has made of the average time taken to process a personal independence payment application.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111320","111320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783284","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of incorrectly filled out personal independence payment applications by assessors in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111321","111321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783285","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111277","111277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783286","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what definition of trade secrets will be used for the purposes of implementation of the European Trade Secrets Directive.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111271","111271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783287","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has for UK participation in the EU emissions trading system after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111324","111324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783288","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to safeguard jobs at the Vauxhall plant in Ellesmere Port.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111293","111293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783289","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the findings of the recent report from the North West Business Leadership Team on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on manufacturing in the region; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111294","111294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783290","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 109028, on biometrics: databases, how many organisations have been found to be in breach of the regulations referred to.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111379","111379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783291","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2017 to Question 106492, on small businesses: technology, how small businesses can use research and development tax credits to support adoption of Industry 4.0 technologies.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111380","111380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783292","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to strengthen and promote the British aerospace industry.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111376","111376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783293","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2017 to Question 9915, on Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport: science, which working groups with relevant industry and academic experts are currently in operation.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111378","111378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783294","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to allow UK companies in the space sector to retain full participation in (a) Copernicus, (b) Galileo and Egnos, (c) Govsatcom, (d) Iris, (e) the Space Situational Awareness programme and (f) Space Surveillance and Tracking in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111360","111360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783295","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of mentoring services to small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111346","111346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783296","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to set up a mentoring service for mentors to small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111347","111347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783297","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department has spent on mentors to small and medium-sized enterprises in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111348","111348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783298","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what further regulations he plans to lay in respect of the Small Business Commissioner.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111349","111349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783299","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to improve employment benefits and protections for self-employed people working in low-skilled sectors.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111350","111350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783300","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to increase the use of geothermal energy in the UK.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111323","111323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783301","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to allow the UK space industry to have continued access to research and development (a) funding, (b) expertise and (c) facilities currently provided at EU level after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111365","111365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783302","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with representatives of the UK space sector supply chain on the effect of leaving the (a) single market and (b) customs union on that industry.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111366","111366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783303","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the privatisation of Royal Mail on the provision of postal services.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111364","111364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783304","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the policy proposals outlined in the independent report Cost of energy published on 25 October 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111357","111357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783305","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on consumer purchasing power of the UK leaving the EU without having agreed a trade deal with the EU.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111336","111336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783306","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on consumer rights of the UK leaving the EU without having agreed a trade deal with the EU.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111335","111335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783307","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2017 to Question 7012, what progress has been made towards publishing the Future Capabilities of the UK Steel Sector study.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111353","111353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783308","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the outcome of the Government's Post Office network consultation.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111354","111354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783309","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to prioritise the use of clean, renewable energy over traditional energy sources; and what steps are being taken to avoid wind farms being turned off and constraint payments made.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111412","111412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783310","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to ensure digital transformation programmes are affordable for (a) small and medium-sized enterprises and (b) charities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111391","111391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783311","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the level of investment by businesses in digital transformation.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111392","111392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783312","2017-11-07","Department for International Trade","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, on how many occasions (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met their counterparts in the US to discuss a UK-US free trade arrangement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111399","111399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783313","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether UK products will continue to be subject to EU trademark and design registrations after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111314","111314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783314","2017-11-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether notified bodies in the UK will carry out conformity assessments for products exported from the UK to the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111315","111315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783315","2017-11-07","Department for International Trade","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many delivery partners his Department has.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111312","111312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783316","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the UK will participate in the European Unitary Patent and the EU Unified Patent Court after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111264","111264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783317","2017-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the UK will remain a member of the European Patent Office after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111265","111265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783318","2017-11-07","Department for International Trade","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he will set up business engagement groups for exporters and potential exporters on a (a) country and (b) sectoral basis.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111266","111266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783319","2017-11-07","Department for International Trade","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what funding his Department has made available to support the work of delivery partners in (a) the English regions and (b) overseas.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111267","111267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783320","2017-11-07","Department for International Trade","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of his Department's spend in the last year has been with Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111288","111288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783321","2017-11-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking to ensure the maintenance of employment rights in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111307","111307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783322","2017-11-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with the Welsh Government on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Welsh economy.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111329","111329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783323","2017-11-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department has produced an impact assessment of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Welsh economy.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111328","111328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783324","2017-11-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the benefits and opportunities available to the British aerospace industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111377","111377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/783325","2017-11-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Legatum Institute, or any representative from that Institute, has taken part in any meetings in Brussels as part of a UK Government delegation in the last two years.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111416","111416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782623","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what performance information the Government collects on its contracts with strategic suppliers; and how frequently such information is collected.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111030","111030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782625","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether a memorandum of understanding exists between the Government and each of its strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111031","111031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782626","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what process the Government follows to identify new and emerging suppliers of goods and services for the Government.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111032","111032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782627","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the Government has made of savings accrued to the public purse as a result of the spending control process with government suppliers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111033","111033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782628","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for how many strategic suppliers his Department collects quarterly suppliers returns.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111034","111034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782629","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness and (b) capacity of Crown Representatives to strategic suppliers to undertake their duties in relation to that strategic suppliers role in addition to their other responsibilities.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111079","111079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782630","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the public purse disbursed in contracts with Government strategic suppliers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111082","111082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782631","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of EU-EEA citizens living in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111178","111178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782633","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to respond to Question 108821, tabled on 19 October 2017 by the hon. Member for Ellesmere Port and Neston.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111181","111181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782634","2017-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2017 to Question 109056, on Fracking: planning permission, whether he intends to make those changes to planning law through the use of primary or secondary legislation; and when he intends to bring forward that legislation.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111182","111182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782635","2017-11-06","Cabinet Office","2017-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans his Department has to increase the sale of public land surplus to the Government's requirements.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111227","111227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782636","2017-11-06","HM Treasury","2017-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's preparations for the UK leaving the EU with (a) an agreement on future partnership and (b) no agreement with the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111218","111218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782637","2017-11-06","HM Treasury","2017-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many EU-EEA citizens are currently recorded within HM Revenue and Customs' tax and tax credit system.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111176","111176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782638","2017-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many national insurance numbers issued to EU-EEA citizens are currently active.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111177","111177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782639","2017-11-06","HM Treasury","2017-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what provisions have been made to replace the role of the European Securities and Markets Authority, the European Banking Authority and the European Insurance Occupational Pension Authority in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111174","111174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782641","2017-11-06","HM Treasury","2017-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been raised from fuel duty in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111101","111101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782642","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a list of the HM Revenue and Customs offices scheduled for closure.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111060","111060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/782643","2017-11-07","HM Treasury","2017-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral evidence given by Andrew Bailey of the Financial Conduct Authority before the Treasury Select Committee on 31 October 2017, if he will make an assessment of the robustness of the methodology adopted by Global Restructuring Group in its valuation of businesses and determination of fees.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111069","111069"
