"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123602","2019-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 25 April 2019 to Questions 245922 and 245923, how he measures the success of the UK's support for democracy and human rights in Somaliland.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248749","248749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123603","2019-05-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the number of customers who switched suppliers of (a) LPG and (b) mains gas in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248702","248702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123604","2019-05-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment  his Department has made of the effectiveness of the regulation of the LPG market by the Competition and Markets Authority.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248703","248703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123605","2019-05-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 April 2019 to Question 238377, whether he plans to make mitigation payments to lower-paid MoD personnel based in England in relation to the Scottish rate of income tax.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248706","248706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123606","2019-05-02","Department for International Development","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the number of Palestinian health workers in Gaza allegedly killed by Israeli Defence Force actions in the last two years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248708","248708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123607","2019-05-02","Department for International Development","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Israeli blockade of Gaza on (a) infant mortality rates, (b) levels of malnutrition, (c) instances of communicable diseases per 100,000 people and (d) prevalence of diseases related to poor sanitation in that territory.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248709","248709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123608","2019-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of Government green energy projects in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248710","248710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123609","2019-05-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to assess the level of racism directed at sports players by spectators.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248711","248711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123610","2019-05-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to prevent race-related crime at sports fixtures.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248712","248712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123611","2019-05-02","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the merits of the use of the exceptional hardship exception for the sentencing of drivers who would otherwise be disqualified from driving.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248664","248664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123612","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, at what stage in the franchise process the decision was taken to exclude Stagecoach from bidding for the East Midlands franchise.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248647","248647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123613","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assurances Abellio have provided his Department in relation to the pensions of staff employed on the East Midlands line.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248648","248648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123614","2019-05-01","Department for Education","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the Disabled Students' Allowance assistive technology procurement proposal on students with (a) low incidence disabilities and (b) vision impairment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248764","248764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123615","2019-05-01","Department for Education","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the list of approved equipment for Disabled Students' Allowance.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248765","248765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123616","2019-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the availability of courses for prisoners serving Imprisonment for Public Protection sentences to prepare to demonstrate their suitability for release to the Parole Board.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248729","248729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123617","2019-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners serving Imprisonment for Public Protection sentences are currently held in segregation units.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248730","248730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123618","2019-05-02","Department for International Development","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will support the urgent humanitarian evacuation out of Libya of refugees and migrants held in detention centres in that country.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248760","248760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123619","2019-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of reoffending.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248731","248731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123620","2019-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons have had (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five and (f) more than five governors or acting governors in post since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248732","248732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123621","2019-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will support search and rescue operations in the Mediterranean for people trying to flee Libya.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248761","248761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123622","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will increase the number of vulnerable refugees and asylum-seekers from Libya receiving resettlement in the UK.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248762","248762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123623","2019-05-02","Department for International Development","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support vulnerable migrants in Libya.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248763","248763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123624","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps is his Department taking to tackle gangs using diggers to rip out ATM machines from rural shops.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248626","248626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123625","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cars were reported stolen in the last two years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248627","248627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123626","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were arrested for carrying a dangerous weapon in 2018.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248628","248628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123627","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to tackle prank calls made to the emergency services.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248629","248629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123628","2019-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted for selling drugs in the last two years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248630","248630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123629","2019-05-01","Department for International Trade","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase food and drink exports from Northern Ireland to (a) Asia (b) South America and (c) Africa.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248631","248631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123630","2019-05-01","Department for International Trade","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions has he had with his counterparts overseas on the export of UK pharmaceutical products.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248632","248632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123631","2019-05-01","Department for International Trade","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase foreign direct investment into Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248633","248633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123632","2019-05-01","Department for International Trade","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much his Department has spent on advertising in each of the last two years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248634","248634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123633","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what contingency plans his Department has implemented in the event that Bristow's Helicopters Ltd is unable to fulfil its obligations on search and rescue.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248700","248700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123634","2019-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether local authorities have a duty to identify the role of companion animals in an individual’s care and support plan and needs assessment.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248692","248692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123635","2019-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit payments were subject to deductions above the maximum cap of 40 per cent in the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248697","248697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123636","2019-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claimants for universal credit received two weeks’ run-on housing benefit while waiting for their first payment (a) in the last six months and (b) in the last month for which information is available.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248698","248698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123637","2019-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of claimants of universal credit who have a deduction for housing rent arrears in the first month of their claim in the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248699","248699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123638","2019-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Israel in response to the UN independent Commission of Inquiry’s findings that there were reasonable grounds to conclude that 35 children attending protests in Gaza between 30 March and 31 December 2018 were killed unlawfully by Israeli security forces.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248666","248666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123639","2019-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to help ensure there is an (a) independent, (b) transparent and (c) thorough investigation into each child fatality that occurred during protests in Gaza between 30 March and 31 December 2018.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248667","248667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123640","2019-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the reported firing of tear gas into an elementary school in the Israeli-controlled area of Hebron city by Israeli forces on 21 February 2019.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248668","248668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123641","2019-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent representations she has made to her Israeli counterpart on the reported destruction of three water connections supplying water to the West bank in February 2019.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248669","248669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123642","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of accidents involving (a) personal injury and (b) death on (i) permanent all-lane running sections and (ii) dynamic all-lane running sections of smart motorways in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248613","248613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123643","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department uses for the spacing of emergency refuge lay-bys on (a) permanent and (b) dynamic all-lane running sections of smart motorways.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248614","248614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123644","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the timing of the implementation of dynamic all-lane running on smart motorways.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248615","248615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123645","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the locations of (a) permanent and (b) dynamic all-lane running sections of smart motorways.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248616","248616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123646","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the disqualification of Stagecoach from three rail franchise bids, what recent assessment he has made of the viability of the rail franchise system.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248670","248670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123647","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the disqualification of Stagecoach from three rail franchise bids, what steps is he taking to help protect the (a) jobs and (b) terms and conditions of all staff employed by Virgin Trains West Coast.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248671","248671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123648","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the disqualification of Stagecoach from three rail franchise bids, what steps he is taking to help ensure that the jobs and terms and conditions of all staff employed by sub-contractors for Virgin Trains West Coast are protected.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248672","248672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123649","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether a train guard will be retained on every train in the next West Coast Main Line franchise contract.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248673","248673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123650","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the current catering provision will be (a) maintained and (b) expanded in the next West Coast Main Line franchise contract.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248674","248674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123651","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the current ticket office provision will be (a) maintained and (b) expanded in the next West Coast Main Line franchise contract.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248675","248675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123652","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the current level of provision of station staff will be (a) maintained and (b) expanded in the next West Coast Main Line Franchise contract.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248676","248676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123653","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the disqualification of Stagecoach from three rail franchise bids, whether Virgin Trains will retain the West Coast Main Line franchise until March 2020.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248677","248677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123654","2019-05-02","Department for Education","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money was allocated from the public purse towards the provision of free school meals in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in the most recent financial year for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248590","248590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123655","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the disqualification of Stagecoach from three rail franchise bids, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the compliance of the remaining bidders for the West Coast Main Line franchise.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248678","248678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123656","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on job (a) numbers and (b) roles of staff employed by Virgin Trains West Coast of the disqualification of Stagecoach from three rail franchise bids.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248679","248679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123657","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on job (a) numbers and (b) roles of staff employed via subcontractors on the Virgin Trains West Coast line of the disqualification of Stagecoach from three rail franchise bids.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248680","248680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123658","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions officials in his Department have had with the Pensions Regulator on the decision to disqualify Stagecoach from bidding on three rail franchises.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248681","248681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123659","2019-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she publish guidance on what triggers a natural migration to universal credit.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248643","248643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123660","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to help safeguard the pensions of rail workers employed by (a) Stagecoach and (b) Virgin Trains.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248682","248682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123661","2019-05-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Written Statement of 17 December 2018, Official Report HCWS1184, when he plans to bring forward detailed proposals on tackling uncertainty around employment status.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248558","248558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123662","2019-05-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, as part of the Foreign and Commonwealth Office’s 2019 Media Freedom Campaign, what steps he is taking to address Amnesty International concerns about press freedom in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248644","248644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123663","2019-05-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to encourage more environmentally conscious house-building that takes into account established trees and local bird populations.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248601","248601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123664","2019-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on that country’s Middle East peace plan.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248719","248719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123665","2019-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will establish an independent inquiry on the reasons his Department and Natural England decided on the proposal to revoke General Licences 04/05/06.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248559","248559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123666","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions his Department has had with faith leaders regarding the Tier 5 religious worker visa.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248722","248722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123667","2019-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2019 to Question 239872, for what reason the Prime Minister’s announcement on 27 January 2016 on locating the Holocaust Memorial in Victoria Tower Gardens did not refer to the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation’s recommendation that the Memorial and the Learning Centre should be co-located.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248580","248580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123668","2019-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2019 to Question 239870, on what dates the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation first spoke to representatives of the (a) Royal Parks, (b) Department of Culture, Media and Sport and (c) Westminster City Council about the possibility of the Holocaust Memorial being located in Victoria Tower Gardens; and whether in each case the conversation also covered the proposed Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248581","248581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123669","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people receive prompt repayment of the NHS Health surcharge for failed spousal visa applications.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248723","248723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123670","2019-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answers of 7 March 2019 to Question 229626 and 10 April 2019 to Question 239872, on what date in January 2016 the Government received from the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation its recommendation that the Holocaust Memorial and the Holocaust Learning Centre should be located in Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248582","248582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123671","2019-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Social Security and Child Support Tribunal appeals have taken longer than 52 weeks for a determination, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248645","248645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123672","2019-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2019 to Question 239868 on the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre, for what reason the answer did not indicate whether the criteria for the site were altered.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248583","248583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123673","2019-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2019 to Question 239869 on the location of the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Centre, for what reason that Answer did not indicate which of the criteria were met.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248584","248584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123674","2019-05-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether it is the Government’s policy that all the existing entrances to Victoria Tower Gardens will continue to be available to the public during the same hours as they are currently after the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre have been built.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248585","248585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123675","2019-05-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what conditions he has (a) imposed and (b) indicated an intention to impose on the planned use of part of Victoria Tower Gardens for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248586","248586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123676","2019-05-02","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase passenger journeys on public transport in the regions to reduce CO2 emissions.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248646","248646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123677","2019-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases involving sexual assault were granted compensation by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248636","248636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123678","2019-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many qualifying relatives have been awarded compensation by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248637","248637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123679","2019-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made a cost-benefit analysis of advancing the development of (a) better diagnostics and (b) new antibiotics.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248602","248602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123680","2019-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) child, (b) dependency, (c) funeral and (d) bereavement compensation payments were made by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248638","248638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123681","2019-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of payments provided by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme were (a) child, (b) dependency, (c) funeral and (d) bereavement compensation payments in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248639","248639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123682","2019-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of claims under the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme were rejected as a result of the injury not qualifying for compensation in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248640","248640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123683","2019-05-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that UK data security is protected in respect of the involvement of Huawei in the development of the UK's 5G network.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248759","248759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123684","2019-05-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent each year since 2010-11 on ensuring that Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme claimaints have been able to obtain the evidence required for their claim.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248641","248641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123685","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the overall cost to the police service of policing football matches in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248750","248750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123686","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what financial support his Department provides to police forces for the policing of football matches.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248751","248751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123687","2019-05-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions (a) he and (b) his departmental officials have had with Essex county council on its (i) proposed closure of libraries and (b) statutory duty to provide a comprehensive and efficient library service under the Public Libraries and Museums Act 1964.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248605","248605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123688","2019-05-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many exemptions have been made under the people with significant control register; and for what reasons those exemptions have been made.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248713","248713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123689","2019-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate the Government has made of the cost of clearance of fly-tipped materials by local authorities in England during 2017-18.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248704","248704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123690","2019-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fly-tipping incidents were reported by local authorities in England in 2017-18.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248705","248705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123691","2019-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he holds information on when the hon. Member for West Lancashire will receive a response to correspondence sent to Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust on 19 December 2018 regarding mental health care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248620","248620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123692","2019-05-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229152 on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund, if he will introduce the consultation on the design of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund before the House rises for the summer recess.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248693","248693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123693","2019-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted under section (a) 168 and (b) 170 of the Equality Act 2010 for refusing to take an assistance dog in a taxi or private hire vehicle in (i) 2017 and (ii) 2018.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248758","248758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123694","2019-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the level of opioid prescription rates per 100,000 people in each local authority area in England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248592","248592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123695","2019-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether getting a cat as a pet is recommended to individuals as part of their individual care and support plan.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248694","248694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123696","2019-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether an individual in receipt of a personal budget as part of a care and support plan can allocate funds from that budget to funding care for their pets.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248695","248695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123697","2019-05-02","Treasury","2019-04-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 April 2019 to Question 247049 on Manufacturing Industries, what proportion of the £4 billion allocated to preparations on the UK leaving the EU is being spent supporting manufacturers facing uncertainty.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248683","248683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123698","2019-05-02","Department for Education","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to provide statutory guidance to schools on the use of isolation rooms for students.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248755","248755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123699","2019-05-01","Cabinet Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will list all current Executive Agencies.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248565","248565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123700","2019-05-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his oral contribution of 7 January 2019, Official Report, column 69, for what reasons the  Social Care Green Paper was not published before April 2019; and what his Department's timescale is for the publication of that document.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248593","248593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123701","2019-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department took in response to the increased number of complaints to the Independent Case Examiner from women affected by the state pension age increase between October 2016 and November 2018.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248717","248717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123702","2019-05-02","Department for International Development","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department provides to (a) the democratic process in Sudan and (b) help ensure participation in that process by opposition parties.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248571","248571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123703","2019-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Food Foundation's Children’s Future Food Inquiry report published on 24 April 2019, what steps the Government is taking to support children who live in food insecure households.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248684","248684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123704","2019-05-02","Department for Education","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to provide meals for children accessing (a) free childcare and (b) pre-school provision.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248685","248685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123705","2019-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to further protect county farm smallholdings from precipitant sale; and what recent discussions he has had with local authorities on this matter.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248572","248572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123706","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress he has made on the e-borders programme; and whether the UK will have an electronic border control system when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248707","248707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123707","2019-05-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have sold off (a) all and (b) more than 50 per cent of  council smallholdings since 1997.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248573","248573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123708","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he will take to support improving key roads that are official diversion routes for motorways that are not in the major road network.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248733","248733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123709","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to enable local communities in cooperation with the police to use information accrued from ANPR to prosecute drivers who regularly break the speed limit.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248574","248574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123710","2019-05-01","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the President of the Board of Trade on the effect on trade of improving the Reading to Gatwick Airport road corridor through the building of an M31.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248734","248734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123711","2019-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 April 2019 to Question 243355 on Pension Credit, how many times was the online pension credit toolkit accessed in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248594","248594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123712","2019-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 April 2019 to Question 243355 on Pension Credit, for what reason information on Departmental budgets for promoting pension credit take-up rates are unavailable; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248595","248595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123713","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the recent shooting at the San Diego synagogue, what urgent steps he is taking to provide additional funding for security at places of worship.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248748","248748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123714","2019-05-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2018 to Question 198912 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service: Enforcement, what the cost to the public purse has been of the Approved Enforcement Agency procurement exercise.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248737","248737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123715","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to regulate the use of facial recognition technology, including at airports.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248656","248656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123716","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, by what date the updated guidelines for the Surveillance Camera Code of Conduct will be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248657","248657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123717","2019-05-02","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when facial recognition technology for security checks for all passengers travelling through Heathrow Airport will be fully rolled out.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248658","248658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123718","2019-05-02","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by what date facial recognition technology for security checks will be rolled out to airports that serve less than five million passengers per year.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248659","248659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123719","2019-05-02","House of Commons Commission","2019-04-29","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many times on average on a working day each bathroom or lavatory was cleaned in Portcullis House in (a) 2019 and (b) 2009.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248591","248591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123720","2019-05-02","Cabinet Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2019 to Question 246989 on European Parliament: Elections and the Answer of 18 May 2018 to Question 143730 on European Parliament: Elections, for what reason his Department was able to publish an estimate of the savings accrued to the public purse of not holding the election, but not able to publish an estimate of holding the elections.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248635","248635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123721","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been allocated to the Serious Violence Implementation Task Force programme in each region.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248687","248687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123722","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his 15 April 2019 speech on protecting young people's futures, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on future funding for the Crime Prevention Data Lab.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248688","248688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123723","2019-05-02","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he signed the memorandum of intent with Saudi Arabia for 48 Typhoon aircraft in March 2018; and what the name was of the Saudi counter-party to that memorandum.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248754","248754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123724","2019-05-02","Department for Transport","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the new Abellio train franchise for the East Midlands will deliver improvements in (a) seat capacity, (b) fares and (c) connectivity north from Kettering.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248617","248617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123725","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the recently announced funding for protecting places of worship has been allocated.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248689","248689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123726","2019-05-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2019 to Question 213368, when the Government plans to publish its consultation on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248686","248686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123727","2019-05-02","Attorney General","2019-04-29","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 11 April 2019 to Question 910352 on Terrorism: Prosecutions, if he will (a) review the type of data that the CPS collates and (b) introduce a new category under terrorism-related offences for returning terrorist fighters.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248618","248618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123728","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints against the actions of the Independent Office for Police Conduct have been made since its inception in January 2018.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248566","248566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123729","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints against the actions of the Independent Police Complaints Commission were made in each year between 2005 and 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248567","248567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123730","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints the Independent Police Complaints Commission (a) received, (b) opened investigations into and (c) concluded investigations and reported on in each year between 2005 and 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248568","248568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123731","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints the Independent Office for Police Conduct (a) received, (b) opened investigations into (c) concluded investigations and have yet to report and (d) concluded investigations and reported on since its establishment in January 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248569","248569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123732","2019-05-02","Home Office","2019-04-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) (i) staff employed by, (ii) vacancies as of 31 December in and (iii) investigations conducted by each professional standards department in each police authority in England and Wales and (b) investigations into each such department in each such authority by an external oversight body in each year since 2005; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248570","248570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105984","2019-04-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many financial mitigation payments have been made to MoD personnel based in Scotland in relation to the Scottish rate of income tax; and at what salary level those payments began.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 238377","238377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105283","2019-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what Department plans he has to replicate the infrastructure investment priorities of the European Regional Development Fund once the UK leaves the EU structural funds.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237075","237075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123347","2019-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the minutes of the universal credit programme board for June 2017, what plans she has for the universal credit system to interface with social media providers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247977","247977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123348","2019-04-30","Department for International Trade","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase the export market of UK beverages.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247993","247993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123349","2019-04-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to reduce the number of tanks.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247994","247994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123350","2019-05-01","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the (a) names, (b) unitary charges and (c) cost of all PFI funded schools in Newham.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248039","248039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123351","2019-05-01","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which PFI progamme includes the Deanery CE High School in Wigan; and who the shareholders of the Special-Purpose Vehicle for that school are.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248040","248040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123352","2019-05-01","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the (a) names, (b) unitary charges, (c) costs and (d) project names of all the Building Schools for the Future wave 4 phase 3 Schools in Oldham.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248041","248041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123353","2019-05-01","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the (a) names, (b) unitary charges, (c) costs and (d) project names of all PFI funded schools in Redcar.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248042","248042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123354","2019-05-01","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the (a) names, (b) unitary charges, (c) costs and (d) project names of all PFI funded schools in Stockport.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248043","248043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123355","2019-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of the recent escalation of military activity in Al Dhale'e, Yemen, on the implementation of the UN-led peace process.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247978","247978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123356","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of lung cancer among people that have never smoked cigarettes.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248070","248070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123357","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils who (a) were and (b) were not eligible for pupil premium in their last year of compulsory secondary school (i) entered at least one A level, (ii) achieved three or more A-levels, (iii) achieved grades ABB or better at A level, and (iv) achieved A*A*A or better at A-level in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248071","248071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123358","2019-04-30","Department for International Development","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the outcome was of her discussions with the UN and NGO partners on improving access to tranexamic acid for women with post-partum haemorrhage.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248054","248054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123359","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been granted settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Newport East constituency.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248018","248018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123360","2019-05-01","Home Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme have been refused in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Newport East constituency; and what the reasons were for refusal.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248019","248019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123361","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking with businesses to prevent employee's exposure to (a) asbestos and (b) carcinogens in the workplace.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247982","247982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123362","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of lung cancer diagnosis among non-smokers.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247983","247983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123363","2019-04-30","Department for International Development","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department’s priorities are for the replenishment period and strategy review with Gavi, The Vaccine Alliance.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248000","248000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123364","2019-04-30","Department for International Development","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to provide marginalised children with access to vaccines.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248001","248001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123365","2019-04-30","Department for International Development","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is taking steps to promote competition in the vaccines market.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248002","248002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123366","2019-04-30","Department for International Development","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to increase price transparency for vaccines.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248003","248003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123367","2019-04-30","Home Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much Lancashire Constabulary spent on providing policing resources to sporting events throughout Lancashire in (a) 2018 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247984","247984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123368","2019-04-30","Home Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police horses have died as a result of injuries sustained whilst on active duty in (a) England and (b) Lancashire in each of the in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247985","247985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123369","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to identify a potential link between perinatal mental illness and emotional and behavioural problems in children.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248004","248004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123370","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of NHS services to (a) identify and (b) treat perinatal mental illnesses.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248005","248005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123371","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential link between perinatal mental illness and emotional and behavioural problems in children.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248006","248006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123372","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to respond to the consultation on the cost-effectiveness methodology for vaccination programmes.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248007","248007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123373","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of vaccination in England.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248008","248008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123374","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on public health of changing the dosing schedule for pneumococcal conjugate vaccine from three to two doses.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248009","248009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123375","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the uptake of (a) new and (b) underused vaccines to tackle antimicrobial resistance.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248010","248010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123376","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support local health leaders to address inequalities in the cancer pathway.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248011","248011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123377","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the NHS Long Term Plan in achieving the Government’s commitment to end variation in end-of-life care by 2020.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248012","248012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123378","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the time frame for improving cancer outcomes in the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248013","248013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123379","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions to ensure that the needs of cancer patients are addressed in the benefits system.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248014","248014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123380","2019-04-30","Home Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to review the requirement for holographic ID for the purchase of alcohol.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248072","248072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123381","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to address vacancy rates in the NHS cancer workforce.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248015","248015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123382","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on the potential effect of proposed changes to the immigration system on the health and social care workforces.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248016","248016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123383","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to protect harbour porpoises from being trapped in gillnets.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247986","247986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123384","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of closing Crown post offices and franchising services to WHSmith on the sustainability of the post office network.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248017","248017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123385","2019-05-01","Cabinet Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contracts the Government holds with Staffline PLC.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248044","248044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123386","2019-05-01","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-04-26","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, for what reasons the deadline for EU citizens to change their status to vote in European elections in the UK was set to 12 working days before polling day rather than six in guidance issued by the Commission.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248046","248046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123387","2019-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to repatriate UK citizens in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247995","247995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123388","2019-05-01","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-04-26","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what changes to the process by which EU citizens become eligible to vote in European elections in the UK were recommended by the Commission.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248047","248047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123389","2019-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to protect UK citizens in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247996","247996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123390","2019-05-01","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-04-26","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Commission has issued on making changes to the process for inviting EU citizens resident in the UK to participate in European elections in the UK in view of the short timescale.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248048","248048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123391","2019-05-01","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-04-26","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Commission has provided to the Cabinet Office on making additional central funding available to electoral registration officers to ensure that EU citizens are aware of the steps they need to take in order to participate in the European elections in the UK.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248049","248049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123392","2019-05-01","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-04-26","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Commission plans to issue guidance to returning officers on making available at polling stations on 2 May 2019 the UC1/EC6 form for EU citizens eligible to vote in the European elections in the UK..","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248050","248050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123393","2019-04-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-04-26","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Commission plans to provide to electoral registration officers on the acceptability of scanned or photographed UC1/EC6 forms in order to make changes to the electoral register ahead of European elections in the UK.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248051","248051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123394","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the potential volume of waste water from hydraulic fracturing operations in the event that the industry develops as proposed in the government's energy policy. Choose one","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248060","248060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123395","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the potential number of waste water facilities that will be needed to (a) treat and (b) dispose of waste water generated from hydraulic fracturing operations in the event that the industry develops as proposed in the Government's energy policy.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248061","248061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123396","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the potential amount of (a) waste water sludge, (b) sand and (c) filter cake produced from (i) hydraulic fracturing operations and (ii) associated water treatment in the event that the industry develops as proposed in the Government's energy policy.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248062","248062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123397","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the number of landfill sites needed to dispose of (a) waste water sludge, (b) sand and (c) filter cake produced from (i) hydraulic fracturing operations and (ii) associated water treatment in the event that the industry develops as proposed in the Government's energy policy.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248063","248063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123398","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many waste water facilities in the UK are permitted to treat waste water from hydraulic fracturing operations.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248064","248064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123399","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many landfill sites in the UK are permitted to dispose of (a) waste water sludge, (b) sand and (c) filter cake produced from hydraulic fracturing operations.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248065","248065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123400","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of universal waste water treatments sites that are (a) capable and (b) permitted to treat all variations of waste water content generated from hydraulic fracturing operations.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248066","248066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123401","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what process did waste water go through in order to be (a) treated and (b) disposed of following hydraulic fracturing operations in 2018.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248067","248067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123402","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on when in hydraulic fracturing operations the operator knows which type of water treatment and disposal facilities will be needed for the (a) treatment and (b) disposal of the waste water.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248068","248068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123403","2019-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the waiting time for patients with Ehlers–Danlos syndromes to see a specialist.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248055","248055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123404","2019-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve the diagnosis time for patients with Ehlers–Danlos syndrome.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248056","248056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123405","2019-04-30","Department for International Development","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in addition to recently announced humanitarian assistance, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the immediate and the long-term development needs in Zimbabwe are met after Cyclone Idai.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247991","247991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123406","2019-04-30","Department for International Development","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support climate change resilience programes in Zimbabwe after Cyclone Idai.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247992","247992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123407","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the National Audit Office report, The apprenticeships programme, published on 6 March 2019, HC 1987, what assessment he has made of the future financial sustainability of the apprenticeship levy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248020","248020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123408","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2019 to Question 243426, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of levy funds in employers’ accounts that will (a) expire and (b) be spent on apprenticeships before they expire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248021","248021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123409","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships there are in non-levy paying businesses; what other Government programmes will be funded by expired apprenticeship levy funds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248022","248022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123410","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has received representations from employers on the effect of the 20 per cent off-the-job training standard on delivering apprenticeships.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248023","248023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123411","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2019 to Question 243426 on apprenticeships: Taxation, what steps his Department is taking to increase the amount of apprenticeship levy funds that employers are using; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248024","248024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123412","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of employer apprenticeship levy funds that will be used in (a) 2019, (b) 2020, (c) 2021 and (d) 2022; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248025","248025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123413","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department made before the introduction of the apprenticeship levy of the (a) proportion of apprenticeship levy funds that employers would use, (b) number of apprenticeships that would be delivered and (c) amount of employer apprenticeship levy funds that would be unspent between 2017 and 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248026","248026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123414","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship starts have been funded by unspent employer levy funds in (a) 2018 and (b) to the end of March 2019.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248027","248027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123415","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the Government’s progress on delivering three million apprenticeships by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248028","248028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123416","2019-05-01","Women and Equalities","2019-04-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many applications have been made to the EnAble Fund.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248038","248038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123417","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the importance of Level 2 and Level 3 apprenticeships in delivering three million apprenticeships by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248029","248029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123418","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria his Department is using to assess the performance of the apprenticeship levy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248030","248030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123419","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2019 to Question 243420, what data the Government uses to determine the number of (a) apprenticeships delivered in each sector and (b) apprenticeship levy funded apprenticeships delivered in each sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248031","248031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123420","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the apprenticeship levy is being spent on MBA or equivalent qualifications.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248032","248032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123421","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the highest amount is of apprenticeship levy funds that an employer can spend for a single apprenticeship.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248033","248033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123422","2019-04-30","Treasury","2019-04-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2019 to Question 243425, what proportion of the £8.8 billion his Department estimates will be paid into the apprenticeship levy between 2019 and 2022 will be spent on apprenticeships; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248034","248034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123423","2019-04-30","Treasury","2019-04-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of (a) reducing the amount employers pay into the apprenticeship levy and (b) extending the amount of time before funds expire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248035","248035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123424","2019-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the development of local food plans.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248052","248052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123425","2019-04-30","Treasury","2019-04-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to run a budget (a) surplus or (b) deficit for the apprenticeship levy in (i) 2019, (ii) 2020, (iii) 2021 and (iv) 2022; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248036","248036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123426","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the future financial sustainability of the apprenticeship levy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248037","248037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123427","2019-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which countries require UK citizens to purchase travel insurance as a condition of entry.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248057","248057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123428","2019-04-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the process for councils to dispose of property assets is; whether councils must demonstrate best value; and what the obligations of the council where a property is being transferred to a wholly owned subsidiary of that same council are.","Biography information for Chris Philp","Chris Philp","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248058","248058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123429","2019-05-01","Cabinet Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his oral contribution to the November hearing of the Joint Committee on the National Security Strategy, that he could absolutely provide assurance that money from the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund is not being used to fund activities that might lead to the death of people in other countries, what assessment he has made of whether reports of the use of that funding for specialist anti-terror courts in Pakistan is incompatible with his statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247981","247981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123430","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential role of dentists and oral health professionals in supporting the diagnosis of diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247979","247979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123431","2019-05-01","House of Commons Commission","2019-04-26","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, whether Huawei equipment is used in the parliamentary (a) telecoms and communications network and (b) security and surveillance network.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248073","248073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123432","2019-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to (a) the Russian Ambassador in London and (b) his Russian counterpart on the recent decree allowing residents in occupied Eastern Ukraine to obtain Russian passports; and what discussion he has had with his Ukrainian counterpart on UK support for that country's territorial integrity.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247987","247987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123433","2019-05-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to (a) tackle age-bias in recruitment and (b) ensure that older workers are offered training and development opportunities.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247988","247988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123434","2019-05-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to include methane in the UK's net-zero emissions targets.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247989","247989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123435","2019-05-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Lebanese counterpart on the status of Syrian refugees living in Lebanon since May 2015 when the UN Human Rights Commission suspended registration of those refugees.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248053","248053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123436","2019-05-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April to Question 242927, how the Government is ensuring the exclusion of regulatory provisions from the Business Impact Target as relating to the safety of tenants, residents and occupants in buildings that stem from, or relate to, Government’s response to the Grenfell tragedy, reviews, inquiries or working groups; which regulatory objects and subjects have been excluded in this way; and which units are responsible for ensuring this exclusion.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248069","248069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123437","2019-05-01","Department for International Development","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the role of UK aid in building co-operation with developing countries to limit global temperature rise to 1.5°C.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248074","248074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123438","2019-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what advice his Department provides to care homes on the use of funded nursing care payments for the fee charged to self-funded residents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247980","247980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123439","2019-05-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to publish the names of employers who do not pay the national minimum or national living wage.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248059","248059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123440","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will estimate the cost of equalising widows’ and children’s pension benefits for female teachers who served prior to 6 April 1988.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248075","248075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123441","2019-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 April 2019 to Question 242165 on NHS: drugs, whether the drug distribution issues have been resolved.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248045","248045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123442","2019-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which interested organisations his Department contacted to explain that General Licences (GL 04/05/06) were to be Judicially Reviewed but that in his Department's opinion were sound in (a) February, (b) March and (c) April.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247976","247976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123443","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his oral contribution of 8 April 2019, Official Report, column 26, how the system of second opinions on the prescribing of medical cannabis oil will be organised; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247998","247998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123444","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his oral contribution of 8 April 2019, Official Report, column 26, who will be responsible for offering patients a second opinion on prescribing medical cannabis oil.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247999","247999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123445","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the (a) dates, (b) attendees and (c) topics of meetings his Department has had with representatives of the formula milk industry in 2018 and 2019 to date.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247997","247997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123446","2019-05-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the review into screening for risk of sudden cardiac death has commenced.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247990","247990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122954","2019-04-25","Department for International Trade","2019-04-25","What plans he has to ensure that the poorest countries in the world are able to take part fairly in global trade.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910519","910519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122955","2019-04-25","Department for International Trade","2019-04-25","What steps he is taking to increase the UK's proportion of global trade with India.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910520","910520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122956","2019-04-25","Department for International Trade","2019-04-25","What assessment he has made of the potential economic effect of US retaliatory trade actions on the UK ceramics sector.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910522","910522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122957","2019-04-25","Department for International Trade","2019-04-25","What plans he has to ensure that the poorest countries in the world are able to take part fairly in global trade.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910523","910523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122959","2019-04-25","Women and Equalities","2019-04-25","When the Government plans to establish the taskforce to tackle period poverty in the UK.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910544","910544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122960","2019-04-25","Women and Equalities","2019-04-25","When the Government plans to publish its response to the Gender Recognition Act consultation.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910545","910545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123023","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential link between the consumption of ready-made meals and heart disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247699","247699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123024","2019-04-29","Cabinet Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many men have died as a result of an Abdominal aortic aneurysm in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247700","247700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123025","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to increase public awareness of gum disease and tooth loss.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247701","247701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123026","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) men and (b) women in each age group have been classified as having asthma in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247702","247702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123027","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with Raynaud syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247703","247703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123028","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce incidences of bullying and harassment in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247704","247704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123029","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people with diabetes have had an amputation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247705","247705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123030","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the take-up of vaccinations for children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247706","247706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123031","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were admitted to hospital with food poisoning in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247707","247707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123032","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2019 to Question 225506 on Prisons: Education, how many offenders were engaged in learning and skills in prisons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247708","247708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123033","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will take steps to help retain Post Office branches where the Network Transformation Programme funding is insufficient to sustain the branch in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland, and (d) each region of England.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247729","247729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123034","2019-04-29","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure older people are able to build and maintain savings for retirement.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247730","247730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123035","2019-04-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to improve the (a) availability and (b) affordability of housing for older renters.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247731","247731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123036","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government on the provision of local health services, such as GP practices, in planning guidelines for new housing.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247769","247769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123037","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has had discussions with Cherwell District Council and the Oxfordshire Clinical Commissioning Group on providing additional GP services for new housing proposed in the Cherwell Local Plan.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247770","247770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123038","2019-04-30","Department for International Development","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the level of support for the United Nations resolution 2467 on sexual violence in conflict.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247577","247577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123039","2019-04-30","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2019 to Question 244194, whether his Department makes an assessment of the national insurance contributions of SMEs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247778","247778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123040","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to inform young people of progress of the Government's Clean Growth Strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247582","247582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123041","2019-04-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many rough sleepers there were in (a) Birmingham, (b) Coventry, (c) Dudley, (d) Sandwell, (e) Solihull, (f) Walsall and (g) Wolverhampton local authority areas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247599","247599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123042","2019-04-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many council housing units are planned to be built in (a) Birmingham, (b) Coventry, (c) Dudley, (d) Sandwell, (e) Solihull, (f) Walsall and (g) Wolverhampton local authority areas over the next five years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247600","247600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123043","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what targets the Government has set for the UK to reduce carbon dioxide emissions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247583","247583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123044","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he last met international counterparts to discuss climate change; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247584","247584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123045","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he next plans to meet international counterparts to discuss climate change; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247585","247585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123046","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the use of plastic; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247586","247586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123047","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each constituency have incomplete national insurance records for their pension because they have omitted to pay the contributions in past contributory years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247595","247595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123048","2019-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to tackle the intimidation and harassment of BBC Persian journalists by the Iranian authorities.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247735","247735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123049","2019-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department’s policy is on the involvement of Chinese telecoms firm Huawei in the construction of the UK's 5G data network.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247736","247736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123050","2019-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department provides financial support to assist in the repatriation of the bodies of British victims of terrorism killed abroad.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247737","247737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123051","2019-04-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many walk-ins there were to each Army Careers Centre in the last financial year.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247752","247752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123052","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have provided further submissions for their asylum claims after initially having their claim refused in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247574","247574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123053","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the scope is of the Oil and Gas Authority’s scientific analysis of the data gathered during the shale gas operations and Preston New Road; what data will be included in the Authority's analysis; and whether the conclusions of that analysis will be accompanied by recommendations for future regulation of the UK shale gas industry.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247762","247762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123054","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many times the Oil and Gas Authority has carried out scientific analysis of data from UK oil and gas operations in each of the last five years; and from which sites that data was taken.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247763","247763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123055","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timeframe is for the Oil and Gas Authority’s analysis of data from shale gas operations at Preston New Road; and if he will publish the conclusions of that analysis when it is concluded.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247764","247764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123056","2019-04-30","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April to Written Question 179072 on Home Office: Contracts, for what purpose gagging clauses have been included in contracts drawn up between his Department and (a) charities, (b) voluntary sector organisations, (c) social enterprises and (d) companies.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247542","247542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123057","2019-04-29","Department for Education","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of funding available to support teacher recruitment beyond 2024.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247782","247782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123058","2019-04-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to launch the Rural Gigabit Connectivity programme.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247601","247601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123059","2019-04-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role the Government has in the appointment of ambassadors to the UK.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247663","247663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123060","2019-04-29","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for the Cabinet Office of 24 April 2019, Official Report column 743, what arrangements the Treasury has negotiated with civil servants employed in HMRC in order to permit higher wage increases than the proposed 1 per cent to 1.5 per cent pay award.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247738","247738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123061","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish for consultation the draft service specifications for children and young people’s cancer services.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247664","247664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123062","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2019 to Question 242045 on Post Offices: Costs, what the strategic parameters set by the Government are.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247610","247610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123063","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant the Answer of 16 April 2019 to Question 242042 on Post Office: ICT, what plans he has to change the strategic parameters set by the Government.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247611","247611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123064","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many times Ministers in his Department met the Senior Independent Director of Post Office Limited in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247612","247612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123065","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many times Ministers in his Department met the Chief Executive of Post Office Limited in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247613","247613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123066","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many times Ministers in his Department have met the Chief Finance & Operations Officer of Post Office Limited in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247614","247614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123067","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many times Ministers in his Department have met each of the four Non-Executive Directors of Post Office Limited in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247615","247615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123068","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many times Ministers in his Department have met the Company Secretary of Post Office Limited in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247616","247616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123069","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether (a) Ministers or (b) senior officials in his Department made representations to the Honours Committee on the appointment of a CBE to the role of chief executive of the Post Office in 2019.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247617","247617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123070","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department made of any potential conflicts of interest arising from his chairmanship of Post Office Limited.prior to the appointment of Tim Parker as Chairman of the Board of HM Courts & Tribunals Service.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247618","247618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123071","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timeframe is to bring forward legislative proposals for regulations for compensatory payments for people that have moved to universal credit and lost legacy benefit severe disability premium payments.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247654","247654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123072","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department last met with representatives of British Canoeing on access on Inland Waterways; and what assessment he has made of the potential merits of granting canoeists the same level of access rights on inland waterways in England as is granted in Scotland.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247567","247567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123073","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the statutory right of navigation on water in relation to shared access for recreation.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247568","247568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123074","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many square kilometres of countryside were covered by access arrangements and available to the public before the introduction of the Countryside and Rights of Way Act 2000.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247569","247569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123075","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the ability to secure locally agreed access arrangements to facilitate greater public access to the countryside, before the introduction of the Countryside and Rights of Way Act 2000.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247570","247570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123076","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) average waiting time and (b) longest waiting time was for a mandatory reconsideration after a personal independence payment assessment in (i) the UK, (ii) Wales and (iii) Newport East constituency in each of the last seven years for which data is available.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247655","247655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123077","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of Prevent nominals are university students.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247620","247620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123078","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of Prevent nominals are school children.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247621","247621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123079","2019-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults on staff took place in each prison in each quarter from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247717","247717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123080","2019-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many serious assaults on staff took place in each prison in each quarter from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247718","247718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123081","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the level of availability of knives on social media shopping apps.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247622","247622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123082","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) assaults and (b) serious assaults on staff were recorded in each prison in each quarter from 2010 to 2018 by the type of weapon used.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247719","247719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123083","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) assaults and (b) serious assaults on staff were recorded in each prison in each quarter from 2010 to 2018 by the type of injury inflicted.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247720","247720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123084","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many band three to five prison officers with less than three years’ experience left the prison service by each prison in each quarter from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247721","247721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123085","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many band three to five prison officers with three or more years’ experience left the prison service by each prison in each quarter from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247722","247722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123086","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure sufficient income in greyhound racing to safeguard the welfare of greyhounds throughout their career and into retirement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247623","247623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123087","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many band three to five prison officers who left the prison service in each year from 2010 to 2018 had been assaulted (a) zero to four weeks, (b) four to eight weeks and (c) eight to 12 weeks before their departure.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247723","247723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123088","2019-04-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the selection process will be for the new chairman of Building Better, Building Beautiful commission.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247624","247624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123089","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the environmental cost of waste crime in the Borough of Havering.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247625","247625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123090","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will allocate additional funding to support charities providing direct services to people with ME in London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247626","247626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123091","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to encourage victims of attempted rape to report that crime to the police.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247665","247665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123092","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of former UK citizens that are able to access to the Legal Aid Scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247627","247627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123093","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support is available to victims of attempted rape during the process of bringing their case to the police.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247666","247666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123094","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a vicarious liability for estate owners in relation to (a) the actions of gamekeepers and (b) the illegal killing of birds of prey.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247781","247781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123095","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits of changing the maximum nicotine content of 20 mg/ml currently allowed in vaping products in the event that the UK leaves the EU Tobacco Products Directive.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247628","247628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123096","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of Prevent nominals are from the Borough of Havering.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247629","247629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123097","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to tackle waste crime including (a) illegal exports of waste, (b) fly-tipping and (c) the burning of waste.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247605","247605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123098","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the potential effect of the Maritime and Coastguard Agency’s proposals for older UK passenger boats on (a) businesses (b) investment and (c) skilled engineering jobs in boatyards.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247691","247691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123099","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's January 2019 Clean Air Strategy, what assessment he has made of the (a) effect on air quality of the Renewable Heat Incentive programme and (b) implications of that effect for the future of that programme.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247755","247755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123101","2019-04-29","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to mark the 75th Anniversary of the D-Day Landings.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247630","247630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123102","2019-04-29","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of discrimination on trends in the level of people from ethnic minorities in the armed forces.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247631","247631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123103","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 April 2019 on Question 240941, whether the PrEP Impact Trial website is updated each day.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247575","247575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123104","2019-04-30","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of taxation and mortgage relief changes for buy to let property on the reported increase in the number of properties that are holiday lets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247662","247662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123105","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve the diagnosis of autism in women.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247783","247783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123106","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will remove the responsibility for race horse welfare from the British Horseracing Authority and award it to a new, government-appointed, independent body.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247761","247761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123107","2019-04-29","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Memorandum of Understanding with Cyprus on UK defence and security.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247632","247632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123108","2019-04-29","Department for Transport","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to tackle the use of (a) taxis and (b) private hire vehicles being used to transport victims of child sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247633","247633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123109","2019-04-29","Cabinet Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to increase voter (a) registration and (b) turnout at European Union Elections in 2019 in the event that the UK has not left the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247634","247634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123110","2019-04-29","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what customs checks are performed at Dover Port on outgoing freight traffic; what the average time taken for such checks is per vehicle; what customs checks he plans to carry out in the event that the UK leaves the EU on 31 October 2019 without an agreement for (a) vehicles with no export documentation, (b) vehicles which have completed a customs declaration on the New Computerised Transit System and (c) vehicles operating under the Transports Internationaux Routiers Treaty and with a customs declaration made on the new transit system; and if he will make a statement","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247765","247765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123111","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle misinformation in anti-vaccine literature.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247635","247635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123112","2019-04-29","Cabinet Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has plans to relocate public sector jobs from Central London to the Outer London Borough of Havering.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247636","247636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123113","2019-04-29","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timeframe is of UK aircrew to finish training to fly the Poseidon MRA Mkl (P-8A).","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247637","247637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123114","2019-04-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the Sri Lankan security services as a result of the terrorist attack on Christians on 21 April 2019.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247638","247638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123115","2019-04-29","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans to prohibit Spanish firm, Navantia, from bidding for the contract to build Royal Navy support ships.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247639","247639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123116","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of banning the sale of pointed knives as a means of reducing knife crime.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247604","247604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123117","2019-04-29","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Memorandum of Understanding between the UK and India, what further steps he is taking to  strengthen bilateral security and defence cooperation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247640","247640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123118","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of (a) augmented reality headsets and (b) innovative technologies to deliver improvements in the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247641","247641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123119","2019-04-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many registered houses of mulitple occupancy there are in (a) the Borough of Havering and (b) London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247642","247642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123120","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to expand existing public health and prevention services in community pharmacies in order to support the aims of the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247688","247688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123121","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate engagement between GPs and community pharmacies as part of the Government’s plan to refer patients with minor illnesses from NHS 111 to pharmacies.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247689","247689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123122","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much coal the UK has imported for each of the last three years; and from which countries coal has been imported.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247753","247753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123123","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much coal was used in industry for each of the last three years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247754","247754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123124","2019-04-29","Department for International Development","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether more UK aid will be provided to Sudan in response to the military coup.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247643","247643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123125","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 to allow rehoming organisations to rehome banned section 1 dogs.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247571","247571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123126","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the scientific evidence is for determining that the four breeds of dog banned under the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 pose more of a risk to the public then other dog breeds.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247572","247572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123127","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with animal welfare organisations on the rehoming of dogs banned under section 1 of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247573","247573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123128","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the volume of consumer electronics that end up in landfill.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247693","247693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123129","2019-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether rights under the UN Convention on Rights of Disabled People will continue to have primacy in UK law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247771","247771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123130","2019-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a comprehensive consultation process (a) has or (b) will take place with disabled people and their representative groups, as required under Article 4.3 the UN Convention on Rights of Disabled People (UNCRDP), before any change in the status of the UNCRPD in UK law.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247772","247772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123131","2019-04-29","Women and Equalities","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress her Department has made in extending protection for people with mental health conditions; and what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of amending the Equality Act 2010 so that employees who experience fluctuating mental health conditions are better protected.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247773","247773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123132","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department issues on the processing of consumer electronics in landfill after metals have been harvested from them.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247694","247694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123133","2019-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people of pensionable age have had disability living allowance removed since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247695","247695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123134","2019-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people of pensionable age have been successful in applying for personal independence payment since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247696","247696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123135","2019-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people who have had disability living allowance removed and are of pensionable age have been successful in applying for personal independence payment since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247697","247697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123136","2019-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to support efforts to tackle the spread of false information on emergency contraception in Honduras.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247578","247578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123137","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent deforestation in (a) Brazil, (b) the Democratic Republic of Congo and (c) Indonesia.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247579","247579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123138","2019-04-30","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2019 to Question 244196 on Treasury: Gender Impact Assessment, whether he will publish the guidance on equality impact assessments available on HMRC’s intranet.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247779","247779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123139","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2019 to Question 242927, how the Government is ensuring the exclusion of regulatory provisions from the Business Impact Target in relation to the safety of (a) tenants (b) residents and (c) occupants in buildings as a result of the Government’s response to the Grenfell tragedy, reviews, inquiries or working groups; which regulatory objects and subjects have been excluded in this way; and which units within the Government and regulators are responsible for ensuring this exclusion.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247780","247780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123140","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Health and Care Professions Council equality impact assessment process for its recent decision to increase registrations fees.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247580","247580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123141","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of apprenticeships in the construction sector.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247581","247581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123142","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the level of reserves held by The Caxton Foundation were, prior to their winding up in 2018; and how those reserves were distributed.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247602","247602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123143","2019-04-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has plans to discuss with the Department for Transport the potential transfer of litter picking duties on major trunk roads from local district councils to Highways England.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247774","247774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123144","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish a response to EDM 2296 on providing financial restitution to born in the 1950s women.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247728","247728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123145","2019-04-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made with the Rural Connected Communities Project; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of using North East Bedfordshire as a pilot area for that initiative.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247603","247603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123146","2019-04-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on reports that the Israel Defense Forces recently exposed a Hezbollah cell preparing an attack on Israel.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247742","247742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123147","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of amending Section 63A of the Terrorism Act 2000 to extend extrajudicial jurisdiction to the offence of a UK national supporting a proscribed organisation while overseas.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247667","247667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123148","2019-04-29","Department for Education","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils who (a) were and (b) were not eligible for free school meals in their last year of compulsory secondary school (i) entered at least one A level, (ii) achieved three or more A-levels, (iii) achieved grades ABB or better at A level, and (iv) achieved A*A*A or better at A-level in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247784","247784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123149","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of foreign ownership of abattoirs in England.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247668","247668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123150","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many compensation payments have been received by NHS staff as a result of sexual assaults committed against them by patients in the each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247669","247669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123151","2019-04-30","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the consultation on proposals for using and allocating the UK Shared Prosperity Fund will be published.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247743","247743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123152","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance his Department has issued to police forces on the enforcement of the offence of public nuisance.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247670","247670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123153","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits on introducing a specific category of visa for recognised religious clergy.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247671","247671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123154","2019-04-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on proposals to (a) protect and (b) improve the rights of leaseholders in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247698","247698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123155","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that the police investigate all reported crime.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247672","247672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123156","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking with Cabinet colleagues to ensure that the voluntary sector has the required information to signpost people who may be showing signs of domestic abuse to find appropriate assistance.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247709","247709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123157","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patient and health professional organisations are engaged in the Department's working group on medicinal cannabis.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247543","247543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123158","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy not to adopt the proposal by the EU to classify vegetarian and vegan burgers and sausages as discs and tubes.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247673","247673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123159","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to allow patient-led and third sector organisations to obtain patient data free of charge in order to populate data registries.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247544","247544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123160","2019-04-29","Department for Education","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education what steps she has taken to promote entrepreneurship among female pupils in school.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247710","247710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123161","2019-04-29","Department for Transport","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish an update on the Roads Investment Strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247674","247674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123162","2019-04-29","Department for Transport","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247545","247545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123163","2019-04-29","Women and Equalities","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what support the Government is providing to small businesses to promote awareness of what constitutes workplace harassment; and what steps she is taking to help small businesses tackle such harassment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247711","247711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123164","2019-04-29","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247546","247546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123165","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247547","247547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123166","2019-04-29","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247548","247548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123167","2019-04-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247549","247549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123168","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247550","247550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123169","2019-04-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247551","247551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123170","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247552","247552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123171","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247553","247553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123172","2019-04-29","Cabinet Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247554","247554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123173","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247555","247555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123174","2019-04-29","Wales Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247556","247556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123175","2019-04-29","Scotland Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247557","247557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123176","2019-04-29","Department for Education","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247558","247558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123177","2019-04-29","Attorney General","2019-04-25","To ask the Attorney General, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247559","247559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123178","2019-04-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247560","247560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123179","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the time applicants wait for their first payment of universal credit; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247576","247576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123180","2019-04-29","Department for International Trade","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247561","247561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123181","2019-04-29","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the New Computerised Transit System incorporates an interface with Automatic Number Plate Recognition systems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247766","247766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123182","2019-04-29","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the New Computerised Transit System incorporates an interface with Automatic Number Plate Recognition systems.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247767","247767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123183","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the welfare standards of animals that are not stunned before slaughter in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247644","247644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123184","2019-04-29","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2019 to Question 226084 on Beverage Containers: Taxation, upon which particular submissions made to the Government's call for evidence were his Department's conclusions based.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247660","247660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123185","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support global action to tackle the illegal wildlife trade.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247645","247645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123186","2019-04-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has plans to obligate internet broadband companies to be more transparent on achievable speeds.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247606","247606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123187","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to lift the EU ban on the use of chlorothalonil after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247646","247646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123188","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) food and (b) drink sold in Government Departments is from (i) UK and (ii) fair trade sources.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247712","247712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123189","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April to Question 245965 on Recycling: Schools, if he will make an estimate of the number of schools which have to pay for their own recycling collections.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247775","247775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123190","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will conduct a review of the existing protections for victims of serious violent crime which specifically consults those affected or bereaved by knife crime attacks.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247744","247744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123191","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to deter people from fishing without a licence.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247647","247647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123192","2019-04-29","Department for International Trade","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent progress he has made on increasing the level of trade with east Asian countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247713","247713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123193","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has asked the Prime Minister to convene a COBRA meeting in response to the increase in knife attacks in the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247745","247745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123194","2019-04-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of creating a mandated system with mandated compensation to address customers' complaints about broadband.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247607","247607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123195","2019-04-29","Department for International Trade","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits to British businesses of the £1 billion increase in support on offer from UK Export Finance for British firms exporting to Iraq.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247648","247648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123196","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made recent representations to the Sentencing Council to ensure that (a) repeat weapons offenders who are found guilty of murder or manslaughter serve their full sentence and (b) sentencing guidelines in respect of knife crimes are kept under regular review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247746","247746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123197","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2019 to Question 245965 on Recycling: Schools, if he will make an assessment of the environmental effects of charging schools for recycling collections.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247776","247776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123198","2019-04-29","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to implement Baroness Newlove's recommendations for the overhaul of Criminal Injuries Compensation Law.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247747","247747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123199","2019-04-29","Department for International Trade","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to build on existing trade relationships with Latin America and the Caribbean.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247649","247649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123200","2019-04-29","Department for Education","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will set up an independent inquiry into school exclusions, pupil referral units and their links to serious violence.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247748","247748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123201","2019-04-30","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of EU citizens in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Newport East constituency who are eligible to apply for settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247656","247656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123202","2019-04-30","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU citizens in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Newport East constituency have applied for settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247657","247657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123203","2019-04-29","Department for Transport","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to encourage planners and local authorities to prioritise active travel when building new roads.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247740","247740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123204","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the current reporting mechanism is between the Government and the Post Office.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247619","247619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123205","2019-04-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government has stopped planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247650","247650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123206","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of Local Welfare Assistance Schemes; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247562","247562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123207","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent on Local Welfare Assistance Schemes in each of the last nine years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247563","247563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123208","2019-04-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the numbers of council housing tenants living without a (a) fridge, (b) freezer, (c) washing machine, and (d) cooker in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247564","247564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123209","2019-04-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people in privately rented property living without essential household items.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247565","247565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123210","2019-04-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the view that no deal is better than a bad deal remains the Government's policy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247651","247651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123211","2019-04-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage Housing Associations to retain essential household items within properties during a change of tenancy.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247566","247566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123212","2019-04-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to mandate local authorities to ringfence funding for statutory youth workers and services.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247749","247749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123213","2019-04-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether it remains Government policy for the UK to leave the (a) Single Market and (b) Customs Union.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247652","247652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123214","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will hold discussions with representatives of (a) Operation Shutdown, (b) bereaved family members, (c) grassroots and other youth and community groups and (d) other stakeholders on the Government's public health approach to tackling the increase in knife crime.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247750","247750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123215","2019-04-29","Department for International Development","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the Government's priorities are for the UN Secretary-General’s 2019 Climate Change summit.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247589","247589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123216","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to improve co-ordination with the Metropolitan Police in tackling the (a) trafficking, (b) grooming and (c) abuse of children.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247751","247751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123217","2019-04-29","Department for International Development","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much Official Development Assistance has been allocated to humanitarian aid projects as a result of extreme weather events since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247590","247590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123218","2019-04-29","Department for International Development","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to secure international action on tackling climate change.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247591","247591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123219","2019-04-29","Department for International Development","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department (a) has taken and (b) plans to take to support partner Governments in Africa to implement the conditions of the Kampala Convention; and what steps she is taking to encourage those countries who have not yet signed up to that convention to do so.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247592","247592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123220","2019-04-29","Department for International Development","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to create a national strategy on migration and forced displacement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247593","247593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123221","2019-04-29","Cabinet Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2019 to Question 910478, what the twelve new public bodies are that will be located outside London.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247739","247739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123222","2019-04-29","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government's analysis concurs with the finding of credit rating agency DBRS that the UK economy could withstand the UK leaving the EU without a deal with its AAA rating intact.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247653","247653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123223","2019-04-30","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what legislative time conditions are in place for employers to report employees' earnings to HMRC; and what powers HMRC has to penalise employers who do not meet those conditions.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247732","247732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123224","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effects on universal credit claimants of her Department calculating universal credit entitlement using income from earnings reported by an employer (a) paid during an assessment period in which they were not earned and (b) as a single payment but which were paid as a multiple payment.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247733","247733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123225","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on employers reporting employees' income to HMRC (a) late and (b) in the wrong assessment period for universal credit.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247734","247734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123226","2019-04-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic means the UK has within the Commonwealth to help countries tackle climate change.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247594","247594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123227","2019-04-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department communicated to representatives of Oxfordshire County Council that the B4044 Community Path was not necessary to unlock new homes under the council's housing infrastructure fund bid.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247777","247777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123228","2019-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the number of suicide prevention practitioners in prisons.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247608","247608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123229","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what financial incentives are available to his Department to help increase the number of people applying for medicine courses.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247789","247789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123230","2019-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the rate of attrition of prison officers.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247756","247756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123231","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 15 April 2019 to Questions 242653 and 242654, for what reason his Department has not removed the White-Fronted Goose from schedule 2 of the Wildlife and Countryside Act 1981 given that that goose is endangered on a similar level to the Greenland White-Fronted Goose.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247537","247537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123232","2019-04-30","Cabinet Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of non-UK nationals employed in the services export sector in the UK.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247690","247690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123233","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to help improve diagnosis of Aortic Dissection.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247675","247675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123234","2019-04-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 15 April 2019 to Questions 242653 and 242654, what criteria his Department uses to distinguish between the (a) Greenland and (b) European White-Fronted Goose to avoid accidental killings of the Greenland sub-species.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247538","247538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123235","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the frequency of CT scanning in relation to aortic dissection; and what plans he has to increase the speed of access to that service.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247676","247676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123236","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what specialist aortic surgery facilities there are in the UK; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing more specialist aortic surgery centres.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247677","247677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123237","2019-04-30","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government's plans to publish its new alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247661","247661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123238","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many game birds are kept in barren cages; and what legal recourse is available in relation to people caught keeping game birds in those cages.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247714","247714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123239","2019-04-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many inspections of game bird farms were undertaken by (a) the Animal and Plant Health Agency and (b) local trading standards in 2018; and how many of those visits resulted in an animal welfare prosecution.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247715","247715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123240","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase (a) access and (b) referral rates for genetic services.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247678","247678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123241","2019-04-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing additional specialist blood pressure clinics.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247679","247679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123242","2019-04-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department holds information on the amount of Government funding allocated to women's refuges for each calendar year after 2013.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247658","247658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123243","2019-04-29","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department is currently or has been part of a trial for the EU’s Coordinated Annual Review on Defence.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247680","247680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123244","2019-04-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department holds information on the amount of Government funding planned for women's refuges for the next calendar year.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247659","247659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123245","2019-04-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons his Department has not made a determination on whether to call in Adur District Council planning application AWDM/0961/17 on New Monks farm; and when he plans to make an announcement on that application.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247539","247539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123246","2019-04-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which European defence structures the Withdrawal Agreement makes provision for the UK to remain in after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247681","247681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123247","2019-04-30","Department for Education","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what regulations are in place to ensure that schools provide fresh water for their pupils; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247540","247540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123248","2019-04-29","Ministry of Defence","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the Government plans to ensure that the UK does not become part of the EU’s military unification project in the event that the UK remains in the European Defence Agency, the European Defence Fund, the European Defence Industrial Development Programme and the Permanent Structured Co-operation programme.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247682","247682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123249","2019-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the recent escalation of military activity in Al Dhale in Yemen on the Stockholm process.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247541","247541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123250","2019-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the new probation contracts will include break clauses to ensure that those contracts can be terminated at no cost to the public purse in the event that private companies fail to reduce re-offending rates.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247757","247757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123251","2019-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to help ensure that the judiciary is more representative of society.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247758","247758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123252","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support is available to British Citizens applying under the British Subjects Facilities Act 1915.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247786","247786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123253","2019-04-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has developed a strategy for the implementation of new on-shore wind farms.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247787","247787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123254","2019-04-29","Department for International Trade","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent steps he has taken to increase the UK's proportion of trade with Tunisia.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247788","247788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123255","2019-04-30","Treasury","2019-04-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many promoters of tax avoidance schemes have complied with their obligations under the disclosure of tax avoidance scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247724","247724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123256","2019-04-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking in response to the findings and recommendations of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse’s investigation into child custodial institutions.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247716","247716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123257","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 April 2019 to Question 240581 on NHS: Pensions, what level of interest is applied to annual allowance charges paid through the scheme pays facility of the NHS Pension.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247725","247725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123258","2019-04-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to secure the release of British citizen Jagtar Singh Johal since his imprisonment in India in 2017.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247726","247726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123259","2019-04-30","Women and Equalities","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what transgender groups and charities the Government consulted as part of its consultation on the Gender Recognition Act 2004.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247759","247759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123260","2019-04-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of women from black and minority ethnic backgrounds at the highest level of business.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247760","247760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123261","2019-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of times the online pensioner toolkit was accessed in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247596","247596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123262","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of diagnosed mental health conditions in children in each National Statistics socio-economic classication in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247597","247597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123263","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the addiction rates of the 10 most commonly prescribed opioid drugs in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247598","247598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123264","2019-04-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the prospects for peace between Israel and the Palestinian Occupied Territories.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247768","247768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123265","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many CCGs (a) achieved and (b) did not achieve the turnaround target of 98 per cent of patients receiving their cervical screening results within 14 days of having a test in the last month for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247785","247785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123266","2019-04-29","Cabinet Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Departments have contracts with Amazon Web Services for cloud hosting services; and what proportion of the G-Cloud cloud hosting budget was spent on Amazon Web Services in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247587","247587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123267","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many residential and nursing homes have closed permanently (a) nationally and (b) in the North West region since 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247683","247683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123268","2019-04-29","Cabinet Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what companies provide cloud hosting services to the Government; and what proportion of the G-Cloud cloud hosting budget was spent on each of those companies in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247588","247588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123269","2019-04-29","Department for Education","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department holds data on hidden exclusions.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247741","247741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123270","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many residential and nursing home beds were available in each of the last five years in the (a) UK and (b) North West.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247684","247684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123271","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 April 2019 to Question 242728, whether he plans to increase the number of older people accessing psychological therapies.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247609","247609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123272","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many local authorities have a suicide prevention (a) group and (b) strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247685","247685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123273","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many specialist inpatient services for older adult mental health patients have closed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247686","247686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123274","2019-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of anorexia nervosa patients have died prematurely each year (a) from complications arising from that condition and (b) by suicide in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247687","247687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1123275","2019-04-29","Home Office","2019-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to the enquiry of 20 February 2019 to UKVI from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central on behalf of her constituent, Mr Walid Chegra.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247727","247727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122559","2019-04-24","Cabinet Office","2019-04-24","What steps his Department is taking through the Government Digital Service to tackle the spread of fake news.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910479","910479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122561","2019-04-24","Cabinet Office","2019-04-24","When he last met with Ministers from the Scottish Government; and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910481","910481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122562","2019-04-24","Cabinet Office","2019-04-24","What steps he is taking to strengthen the Union.","Biography information for Chris Philp","Chris Philp","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910482","910482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122564","2019-04-24","Cabinet Office","2019-04-24","If he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the Electoral Commission’s decision that a new investigation into the Vote Leave campaign would not be in the public interest.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910484","910484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122565","2019-04-24","Cabinet Office","2019-04-24","Whether the Government will conduct further voter ID pilots; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910485","910485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122620","2019-04-29","Department for Education","2019-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the increase in funding for special needs provision meets the needs of the visually impaired.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 246913","246913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122621","2019-04-29","Cabinet Office","2019-04-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason the Government objected to the Hereditary Titles (Female Succession) Bill on 22 March 2019.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 246970","246970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122622","2019-04-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the gender pay gap in his Department.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247110","247110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1122623","2019-04-29","Treasury","2019-04-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the £50,000 and £60,000 thresholds for the high-income child benefit charge.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247129","247129"
