"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506495","2016-04-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Ambassador to Panama has held any meetings with representatives of the firm Mossack Fonseca since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32961","32961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506496","2016-04-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the level of EU subsidies provided to sugar manufacturers.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32924","32924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506497","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to promote provision of international support to the Government of National Accord in Libya in (a) governing effectively, (b) managing that country's security situation, (c) achieving political unity and (d) achieving international recognition.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32930","32930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506498","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has made representations to the Palestinian Authority on reported payments by that authority to Palestinian prisoners in Israel.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32928","32928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506499","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Maldivian government about freedom of the press in that country.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32933","32933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506500","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of political prisoners in the Maldives.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32932","32932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506501","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the influence of ISIS in Yemen; and what steps his Department is taking with regional allies to curb that influence.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33203","33203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506502","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of UK nationals in prison in other EU countries.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33139","33139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506503","2016-04-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the legality of the death sentence handed down to Andrew Tsege in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33222","33222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506504","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, 28 January 2016, Official Report, column 426, on arms sales to Saudi Arabia, how many (a) arms export licences have been awarded to Saudi Arabia and (b) reviews of arms sales to Saudi Arabia have been conducted in 2016.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33214","33214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506505","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received on the involvement in human rights abuses of police officers from the United Arab Emirates who have been trained by UK police officers.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33119","33119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506506","2016-04-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to require UK Overseas Territories to create and publish registers showing the beneficial owners of companies registered in those territories.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33115","33115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506507","2016-04-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps at the Anti-Corruption Summit being held in London in May 2016 to press for an international agreement on stricter rules concerning tax havens and beneficial owners.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33116","33116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506508","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to introduce a national register of children with cerebral palsy that includes data on the number of children identified with that condition.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33122","33122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506509","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to help raise awareness of practical obstetric multi-professional training among medical professionals.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33123","33123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506510","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to help improve awareness of cerebral palsy amongst health practitioners.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33125","33125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506511","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what specialist support is available for health visitors in diagnosing and referring children with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33124","33124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506512","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 27141, by which criteria his Department plans to determine NHS support funding for community pharmacies under the Pharmacy Access Scheme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33132","33132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506513","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 27141, what timetable he has set for the introduction of a Pharmacy Access Scheme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33133","33133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506514","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 27141, what estimate he has made of the number of independent pharmacies which will lose their NHS support funding as a result of the Pharmacy Access Scheme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33134","33134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506515","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what programmes are in place to reduce the number of babies born with a low Apgar score.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33121","33121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506516","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Minister for Social Care's oral contribution of 3 December 2015, Official Report, column 608, what progress his Department has made on putting in place a national ambition to reduce the number of adults sent out-of-area for acute inpatient mental health care.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33113","33113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506517","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether HIV pre-exposure prophylaxis will be made available on the NHS to people who have (a) been raped and (b) had underage sex.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33093","33093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506518","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the administrative costs as a proportion of spending were of (a) the Royal Devon and Exeter Hospital and (b) every other acute hospital in England in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33112","33112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506519","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what regional variation there has been in the proportion of shifts which have not been filled since the introduction of national price caps for NHS agency staff.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33089","33089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506520","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the criteria are for a person to be eligible to receive HIV pre-exposure prophylaxis on the NHS.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33091","33091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506521","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the locations are of the pre-exposure prophylaxis for HIV test sites; and what criteria were used to determine those locations.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33092","33092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506522","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2016 to the hon. Member for St Albans to Question 30492, on maternity services: EU nationals, if he will take steps to collect and publish before 23 June 2016 estimates of the numbers of nationals of other EU member states who have used NHS maternity services in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33102","33102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506523","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2016 to the hon. Member for St Albans to Question 30494, on general practitioners: EU nationals, if he will take steps to collect and publish before 23 June 2016 estimates of the numbers of nationals of other EU member states registered with a GP in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33103","33103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506524","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2016 to the hon. Member for St Albans to Question 30493, on health services: EU nationals, if he will take steps to collect and publish before 23 June 2016 estimates of the numbers of nationals of other EU member states who received acute care at hospital trusts in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33104","33104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506525","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct West London Mental Health Trust to consider mothballing or other alternatives to dismantling the Corsellis Brain Collection.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33043","33043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506526","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have avoided disability from stroke due to the measures contained in the National Stroke Strategy.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33023","33023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506527","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the quality and variation of rehabilitation available to stroke survivors.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33024","33024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506528","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many stroke survivors are currently in receipt of local authority-funded adult social care.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33025","33025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506529","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the quality and geographical variability of speech and language therapy available to stroke survivors in England.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33026","33026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506530","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with clinical commissioning groups on the provision of support to people with mild to moderate dementia to allow them to remain in their own homes as long as possible.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33149","33149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506531","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people receiving social care in (a) Dartford and (b) Kent who are entitled to public funding to support that care.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33147","33147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506532","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of specialist dementia (a) residential and (b) nursing home places in Kent.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33148","33148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506533","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential health risks of the use of lasers by driverless vehicles.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33237","33237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506534","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adults were refused NHS treatment on the basis of their immigration status in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33194","33194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506535","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has for the future levels of bursaries and salary support for trainee child and adolescent psychotherapists.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33168","33168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506536","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of e-cigarette users who have (a) resumed smoking and (b) purchased vaping supplies from black market sources.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32943","32943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506537","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what help is available to people with hepatitis C infection from contaminated blood.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32941","32941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506538","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken in response to the findings of the first set of operational data collected by NHS England on wheelchair services; and what steps he is taking to ensure that short-term wheelchair loans are available for people waiting for provision of NHS wheelchairs.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32929","32929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506539","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) demographic factors, (b) deprivation level factors and (c) factors of difference in distance from target market forces he took into account when determining the funding allocated for (i) Vale of York CCG, (ii) NHS West Cheshire, (iii) NHS North East Essex, (iv) NHS South Warwickshire, (v) NHS Canterbury and Coastal, (vi) NHS Lincolnshire West and (vii) NHE East Riding of Yorkshire.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32944","32944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506540","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that patients with chronic acute urinary tract infections can access appropriate treatment on the NHS.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32883","32883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506541","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to work with Muscular Dystrophy UK on increasing access to hydrotherapy pools for people with muscular dystrophy and neuromuscular conditions.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32975","32975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506542","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will designate NHS Improvement as a public authority for the purposes of the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32973","32973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506543","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration his Department is giving to the fast tracking for treatment for vocational drivers with obstructive sleep apnoea as part of NICE's approach to clinical guidelines and quality standards.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33056","33056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506544","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has placed a requirement on Manchester Mental Health and Social Care Trust to pay off its deficit.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33009","33009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506545","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the new junior doctor contract on the recruitment and retention of junior doctors.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33069","33069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506546","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the new junior doctor contract on recruitment to acute medicine.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33070","33070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506547","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage more people to become practice nurses.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33007","33007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506548","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the contribution of the Corsellis Brain Collection to medical research and health improvement in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33042","33042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506549","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy for palliative care funding to provide universal access to bereavement services for bereaved families of children and young people.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33063","33063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506550","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to require health commissioners to make publicly available information on how they commission palliative care for children and young people across their locality.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33065","33065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506551","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will carry out an assessment of the potential (a) health, (b) economic and (c) social effects of its proposals to reduce community pharmacy funding.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33087","33087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506552","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2016 to Question 30491 on A&E departments: EU nationals, whether he plans to collate or estimate the information requested.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33011","33011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506553","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure provision of sustainable and long-term funding for (a) children's hospice sector and (b) other voluntary sector end-of-life care services.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33062","33062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506554","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that all health and social care staff involved in providing care to children and young people with life-shortening conditions receive specialist training.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33064","33064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506555","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what analysis his Department or NHS England has undertaken of the potential effect on medical research of dismantling the Corsellis Brain Collection; and if he will place any such analysis in the Library.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33041","33041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506556","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the structure is of NHS Property Services and to whom they report.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33002","33002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506557","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the planned timetable is for the scoping exercise for special provisions, including fast tracking for treatment, for people with obstructive sleep apnoea who drive for a living.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33057","33057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506558","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been undertaken of the effect on the earnings of people employed under the Experts by Experience programme of implementing the new Care Quality Commission contracts on 1 February 2016.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32991","32991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506559","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of toxocariasis have been identified in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32699","32699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506560","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2016 to Question 31409, on Trauma and the report of the work of the Children and Young People's Mental Health Taskforce, Future in Mind, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that children and young people who have been sexually abused or exploited receive a comprehensive specialist initial assessment and referral to appropriate services providing evidence-based interventions according to their need.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32700","32700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506561","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) average and (b) maximum waiting time was for an electric wheelchair through NHS Wheelchair Services after being determined eligible to receive one in 2014-15.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32695","32695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506562","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the waiting time to receive an electric wheelchair through NHS Wheelchair Services after being determined eligible to receive one.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32696","32696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506563","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to further investigate the deaths at Gosport War Memorial Hospital; and whether any future inquiry will be statutory in nature.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32697","32697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506564","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Infant Formula and Follow-on Formula Regulations 2007 to ensure that customers can use discount vouchers to purchase formula in supermarkets.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32711","32711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506565","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential effect of the Tobacco and Related Products Regulations 2016 on costs to the NHS in the year ending May 2017.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32702","32702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506566","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential effect of the Tobacco and Related Products Regulations 2016 on costs to the NHS in each year between May 2017 and the end of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32703","32703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506567","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England requires mental health and social care trusts to monitor the effect on service users of service closures.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32772","32772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506568","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff in his Department have received autism awareness training.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32757","32757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506569","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the funding formula for GP surgeries on surgeries in (a) Huddersfield and (b) Kirklees.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32753","32753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506570","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he made of the funding needs of (a) university health centres and (b) other GP surgeries with atypical patient profiles in applying the core funding formula for GP surgeries.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32754","32754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506571","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from (a) university health centres and (b) other GP surgeries with atypical patient profiles on funding formula changes.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32755","32755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506572","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2016 to Question 32057, on Epilepsy Death, for what reasons his Department made the decision to retire quality and outcomes framework indicators EP002 and EP003 in 2014.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32720","32720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506573","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department plan to attend the UN General Assembly high-level meeting on HIV/AIDS at the UN headquarters in New York in June 2016.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32739","32739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506574","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to make oral contraceptive pills available without a doctor's prescription.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32670","32670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506575","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to increase the number of bedded inpatient services for young people with mental health conditions.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32671","32671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506576","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements his Department has put in place to ensure that long-term funding is available for the transfer of care for people with learning disabilities from inpatient facilities to community care settings outlined in NHS England's Transforming Care programme.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32675","32675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506577","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to implement the recommendations of the Boorman Review of NHS health and well-being services, published in November 2009.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32676","32676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506578","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 32013, what sanctions will apply to NHS maternity units which do not reduce their rates of stillbirth and neo-natal death.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32850","32850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506579","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups and local authorities are jointly commissioning children's palliative care as set out in the Children and Families Act 2014.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32911","32911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506580","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to recommendation three of the report Operational productivity and performance in English NHS acute hospitals: Unwarranted variations, published in February 2016, when he expects NHS Improvement to publish a list of the top 10 medicines with savings opportunities for trusts to pursue; what methodology will be used to develop that list and whether it will be subject to consultation; whether that list will include medicines prescribed in primary care; what steps NHS Improvement will take to monitor performance of trusts against that list; whether he intends that NHS Improvement will intervene in those trusts failing to realise savings opportunities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32859","32859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506581","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost of treating a patient with (a) hepatitis C, (b) cirrhosis and (c) hepatitis C and cirrhosis has been in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32899","32899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506582","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients with hearing loss (a) in each age group, (b) who (i) were and (ii) were not eligible for free prescriptions and (c) treated by each of the Any Qualified provider suppliers in Norfolk were treated by (A) Norwich, (B) South Norfolk and (c) North Norfolk Clinical Commissioning Group in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chloe Smith","Chloe Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32879","32879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506583","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on what evidence should be used to determine basic treatment for people presenting with acute urinary tract infections.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32882","32882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506584","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each local authority has spent on short breaks in the last 12 months; and how many hours of such support those local authorities provided in that period in total.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32881","32881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506585","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had on the (a) positive and (b) negative effects of e-cigarettes on people who try to stop smoking.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32878","32878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506586","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many verbal and physical assaults on NHS staff have been recorded in the last three years.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32877","32877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506587","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many migrants from other EU countries work in the NHS in London.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32953","32953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506588","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many migrants working in the NHS have no recourse to public funds.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32954","32954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506589","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people working in the NHS were refused NHS treatment on the basis of their immigration status in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32955","32955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506590","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were refused pregnancy termination on the basis of their immigration status in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32956","32956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506591","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adults were refused chemotherapy on the basis of their immigration status in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32957","32957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506592","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were refused chemotherapy on the basis of their immigration status in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32958","32958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506593","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many outpatient (a) paediatric ophthalmology, (b) ophthalmology, (c) medical ophthalmology, (d) optometry and (e) orthoptic follow-up appointments for children under 19 years of age were (i) cancelled and (ii) missed because the patient did not attend in 2014-15.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32776","32776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506594","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many outpatient (a) paediatric ophthalmology, (b) ophthalmology, (c) medical ophthalmology, (d) optometry and (e) orthoptic first appointments for children under 19 years of age were (i) cancelled and (ii) missed because the patient did not attend in 2014-15.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32777","32777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506595","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to change the (a) role of, (b) responsibilities of and (c) funding allocated to strategic health authorities.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32778","32778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506596","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on the number of dentists in Dartford able to accept new NHS patients.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32781","32781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506597","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors and (b) nurses have been recruited by Dartford and Gravesham NHS Trust in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32782","32782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506598","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department and NHS England have had with the National Information Board on developing a digital maternity tool as recommended in the National Maternity Review.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32823","32823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506599","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle premature mortality among people on the autism spectrum who do not have co-occurring learning disability.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32831","32831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506600","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with autism were admitted to hospital as an emergency in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32832","32832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506601","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidelines are in place for the diagnosis of primary hyperparathyrodism; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce misdiagnosis of that condition.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32836","32836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506602","2016-04-13","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the state of morale among junior doctors.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33254","33254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506603","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many migrants from other EU countries work in the NHS in England.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33247","33247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506604","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on overseas recruitment exercises in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33200","33200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506605","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP appointments were missed in (a) Calderdale and (b) England in each year since 2010; and what the estimated cost of those missed appointments was to the NHS.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33201","33201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506606","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were refused NHS treatment on the basis of their immigration status in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33193","33193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506607","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of what constitutes a safe level of exposure of electromagnetic fields from mobile telephone use for (a) the population as a whole and (b) young people.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33238","33238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506608","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of changes in the level of expenditure on agency, bank or locum staff since the introduction of national price caps for NHS agency staff.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33241","33241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506609","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of changes in the number of nursing, medical and other shifts that have not been filled since the introduction of national price caps for NHS agency staff.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33242","33242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506610","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) trusts that have breached the national price caps for NHS agency staff and (b) times those price caps have been breached since their introduction.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33243","33243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506611","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP appointments were available in (a) Calderdale and (b) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33202","33202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506612","2016-04-13","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce safeguards to prevent local authorities whose offices are used for HM Passport Office remote interviews from increasing the charge for using their accommodation.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33181","33181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506613","2016-04-13","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what safeguards are in place for HM Passport Offices which use local government buildings to conduct remote first time passport interviews to ensure the continuity of that service if those buildings are vacated by that local government.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33182","33182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506614","2016-04-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of unlawful marketing of knives in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32817","32817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506615","2016-04-13","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) deportation and (b) forced removal processes were halted after the intended deportee had boarded their deportation flight and before that flight had departed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32813","32813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506616","2016-04-13","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department plans to allocate to the College of Policing for (a) digital media investigators and (b) the mainstreaming cyber-crime training in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32815","32815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506617","2016-04-13","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been received by (a) her Department, (b) police forces, (c) the CPS and (d) HM Courts and Tribunal Service under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32816","32816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506618","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2016 to Question 29659, how many UK citizens have been prosecuted by the Financial Action Task Force for money laundering abroad since 2010.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32780","32780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506619","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what modelling she has conducted to assess the likelihood of the emergency brake mechanism to control immigration from the rest of the EU into the UK being utilised in the next five years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32895","32895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506620","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will undertake a review to establish the reasons for the Government underestimating the numbers of migrants from A2 countries when transitional controls on migration from those countries were relaxed and abolished on 1 January 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32893","32893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506621","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass asylum accommodation contract with G4S for the region of North East England and Yorkshire and Humber, how many faults were reported or identified from Compass inspections for each contractual pay period in 2014-15 and 2015-16; and how many such faults were not resolved within the agreed contractual timescales.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32856","32856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506622","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass asylum accommodation contract with Clearsprings Ready Home Limited for the region of Wales and South West England, how many faults were reported or identified from Compass inspections for each contractual pay period in 2014-15 and 2015-16; and how many such faults were not resolved within the agreed contractual timescales.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32854","32854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506623","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass asylum accommodation contract with G4S for the region of Midlands and East England, how many faults were reported or identified from Compass inspections for each contractual pay period in 2014-15 and 2015-16; and how many such faults were not resolved within the agreed contractual timescales.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32855","32855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506624","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass asylum accommodation contract with Clearsprings Ready Home Limited for the region of London and South East England, how many faults were reported or identified from Compass inspections for each contractual pay period in 2014-15 and 2015-16; and how many such faults were not resolved within the agreed contractual timescales.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32853","32853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506625","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass asylum accommodation contract with Serco for the region of Scotland and Northern Ireland, how many faults were reported or identified from Compass inspections for each contractual pay period in the years 2014-15 and 2015-16; and how many such were not resolved within the agreed contractual timescales.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32851","32851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506626","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass asylum accommodation contract with Serco for the region of North West England, how many faults were reported or identified from Compass inspections for each contractual pay period in 2014-15 and 2015-16; and how many such faults were not resolved within the agreed contractual timescales.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32852","32852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506627","2016-04-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans for the proposed 1,000 immigration skills charge to apply to NHS nurses.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32688","32688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506628","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people of each nationality are awaiting deportation.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32683","32683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506629","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether holders of Latvian non-citizen status are considered to be EEA nationals for the purposes of immigration policy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32738","32738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506630","2016-04-13","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 15 March 2016 to Questions 30647 and 30649, what the evidential basis is for the statement that her Department's policy enables thousands of people each year to be reunited with their families in the UK; and how many extended family members seeking family reunion have been granted asylum in exceptional circumstances by the Entry Clearance Officer in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32719","32719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506631","2016-04-13","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what insurance cover her Department and police forces make available for special constables who are injured on duty and require long-term compensation for loss of earnings.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32724","32724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506632","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are currently awaiting the results of asylum (a) claims and (b) appeals.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32992","32992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506633","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to (a) shorten the immigration appeals process and (b) reduce the number of immigration appeals.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32993","32993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506634","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many judicial reviews against her Department have (a) been initiated and (b) were successful since 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32996","32996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506635","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of immigration appeals have been successful in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32995","32995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506636","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse of the assisted voluntary return scheme was in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32994","32994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506637","2016-04-13","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to caseworkers on handling applications from international students to study at UK colleges and universities in a way that ensures the applicants are not disadvantaged by accusation of fraud in English language tests made by ETS.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33039","33039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506638","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 31 March 2016 to Question 31313, on immigration controls: EU nationals, whether any of the people refused entry have subsequently been permitted to enter the UK.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33005","33005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506639","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31329, on deportation: EU nationals, how many EEA foreign national offenders awaiting deportation have been waiting (a) less than one month, (b) one to three months, (c) three to six months, (d) six to nine months, (e) nine to 12 months, (f) one to two years and (g) more than two years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33096","33096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506640","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31329, on deportation: EU nationals, what the nationality is of the EEA foreign national offenders awaiting deportation.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33097","33097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506641","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31329, on deportation: EU nationals, how many of the EEA foreign national offenders awaiting deportation are (a) in immigration removal centres, (b) in custody or other form of detention, (c) on bail and (d) living in the community.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33099","33099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506642","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31329, on deportation: EU nationals, how many EEA foreign national offenders were awaiting deportation in December of each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33098","33098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506643","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31330, on deportation: EU nationals, how many EEA foreign national offenders deported have subsequently re-entered the UK in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33100","33100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506644","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2016 to Question 31475, on deportation: EU nationals, how many EEA foreign national offenders deported on the basis of a criminal conviction have subsequently re-entered the UK in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33101","33101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506645","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 31 March 2016 to Question 31313, on immigration controls: EU nationals, what monitoring is in place to prevent people refused entry from entering the UK.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33006","33006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506646","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average cost to the public purse was of processing a UK visitor visa through centres in China in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32984","32984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506647","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many harassment warning notices were issued by police forces in the last 12 months for which figures are available; and how many people who received such notices were subsequently prosecuted for harassment offences.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32982","32982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506648","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK visitor visas were issued in China in (a) 2012, (b) 2013, (c) 2014 and (d) 2015.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32983","32983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506649","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the quantity of cannabis recovered from cannabis factories in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32979","32979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506650","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on reconsidering the cases of people who had their leave to remain wrongly cancelled, or who were wrongly detained or removed, on the basis of allegations of fraud in English language tests made by ETS in response to the Upper Tribunal ruling in Qadir v Secretary of State, 23 March 2016.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32974","32974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506651","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nationals of non-EU member states have been refused entry to the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32931","32931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506652","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of language analysis testing of asylum applicants; and if she will carry out a review of her Department's policy on such testing.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33195","33195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506653","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will grant the Brain family residing in Dingwell, Scotland leave to appeal the decision to deport them from the UK whilst remaining domiciled in the UK; and if she will take steps to permit members of that family to maintain their employment until that appeal has been decided.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33234","33234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506654","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police forces take longest to process applications from the Disclosure and Barring Service; and what the average processing time for such application is for each police force in England.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33231","33231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506655","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on priority categories in Disclosure and Barring Service checks.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33232","33232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506656","2016-04-13","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications have been received from Turkish nationals in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33219","33219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506657","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police custody suites in the UK have technology to allow live-link interpretation; and what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of such interpretation.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33155","33155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506658","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the value of fines issued to lorry drivers under section 32 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 has been in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33150","33150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506659","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many appeals against fines to lorry drivers under section 32 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 there have been in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33151","33151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506660","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total cost of defending judicial reviews brought against her Department has been since 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33213","33213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506661","2016-04-12","Cabinet Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many third generation children living in Britain are not British citizens.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33217","33217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506662","2016-04-12","Cabinet Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many third generation children of Jamaican descent living in Britain are not British citizens.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33218","33218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506663","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Equality (Language Analysis - Palestinian, Syrian and Kuwaiti Testing) Authorisation (No. 2) 2013, whether the Government plans to revise the existing three exceptions.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33137","33137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506664","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Equality (Language Analysis - Palestinian, Syrian and Kuwaiti Testing) Authorisation (No. 2) 2013, whether any further nationalities have been added to the list of exceptions.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33138","33138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506665","2016-04-13","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the provision of medical supplies, water, food and emergency shelter for internally displaced people and children in Yemen.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33128","33128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506666","2016-04-13","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is taking steps to ensure that UK aid spent in Africa supports small-scale organic farmers.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33051","33051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506667","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to support Syria's economy after the end of the current conflict in that country.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33094","33094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506668","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of public country-by-country reporting of corporation tax details by multinational companies on the economies of developing countries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33169","33169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506669","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure that public country-by-country reporting of corporation tax benefits developing countries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33170","33170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506670","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to paragraph 1.59 of the Budget 2016, from which projects and programmes the 650 million reduction in Official Development Assistance will come.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32939","32939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506671","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that UK Government aid to the Palestinian Territories is not used to help finance violence or terrorism.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32922","32922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506672","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department plans to provide for humanitarian assistance in the Central African Republic in the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32884","32884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506673","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanisms for oversight her Department has for UK Government aid to the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32923","32923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506674","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Supporting Syria Conference 2016, to whom and by what mechanisms the Government's funding pledges at that conference will be made.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33095","33095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506675","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage (a) development of oil and mineral production and (b) other economic development within South Sudan.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33073","33073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506676","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department plan to attend the UN General Assembly high-level meeting on HIV/AIDS at the UN headquarters in New York in June 2016.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32740","32740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506677","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department plan to attend the UN General Assembly high-level meeting on HIV/AIDS at the UN headquarters in New York in June 2016.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32746","32746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506678","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the UK contribution has been to the UN's emergency relief fund for Yemen since its creation.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32680","32680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506679","2016-04-13","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has provided to tackle dengue fever.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32828","32828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506680","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what measures she is taking to assist humanitarian agencies in distributing food and supplies to people affected by the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32786","32786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506681","2016-04-13","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her foreign counterparts on efforts to tackle dengue fever.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32829","32829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506682","2016-04-13","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of dengue fever on the development of developing countries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32830","32830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506683","2016-04-13","Department for International Development","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding the Ethical Trading Initiative (ETI) received from the Government in the last three years; for what reasons that funding is provided; against what criteria the decision to fund that organisation was made; and what obligations the ETI places on its member companies with respect to freedom of association and collective bargaining.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33184","33184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506684","2016-04-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether prisons record whether inmates are registered as organ donors; and what protocols are in place for donation of organs after a death in custody.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33183","33183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506685","2016-04-12","Cabinet Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what consultations his Department had with (a) the Scottish Prison Service, (b) Scottish Ministers and (c) the Prison Officers Association on the transfer of Prison Officers' Pensions from Classic to the Alpha Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33240","33240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506686","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) written and (b) other contacts he or Ministers in his Department had with senior executives at (a) AXA UK, (b) Ageas UK, (c) General Insurance, (d) Direct Line Insurance and (e) Admiral Insurance between 1 September and 26 November 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32803","32803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506687","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many medically qualified panel members of HM Courts and Tribunals services in the North East of England are orthopaedic specialists.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32860","32860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506688","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 30119, on aviation: lasers, what proportion of those cases ended in prosecution in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32959","32959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506689","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions have been secured under the Gangmasters (Licensing) Act since its introduction in 2004.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32919","32919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506690","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 1.143 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, how the Government defines the term claims culture.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32687","32687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506691","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many nationals of other EU member states who have been victims of violent crime in the UK have been compensated as a result of EU legislation in each year since 2010; and how much that compensation amounted to.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32690","32690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506692","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department's review of criminal driving offences will consider changes to the distinction between careless and dangerous driving offences.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32666","32666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506693","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the terms of reference of his Department's review of criminal driving offences.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32667","32667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506694","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the prison service of prison officers working longer before retirement.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33235","33235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506695","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how prison officers were informed of changes to their pensions following the transfer from Classic to the Alpha Scheme; and how those changes affected the employment contracts of such prison officers.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33239","33239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506696","2016-04-12","Cabinet Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department took to inform prison officers in Scotland of the transfer of Civil Service Employee Pensions from the Classic to the Alpha Scheme.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33236","33236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506697","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of efficiency savings made from use of video link technology in criminal cases.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33140","33140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506698","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what further plans he has to extend the scope for police officers to give evidence via video link during trials.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33154","33154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506699","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the availability of category C prison spaces in the South East.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33153","33153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506700","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions his Department has had with Chief Crown Prosecutors on the decision not to prosecute any individuals for suspected electoral and financial fraud committed in Tower Hamlets during the mayoral election there in 2014.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33188","33188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506701","2016-04-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 March 2016 to Question 31430, on Anti-Semitism, which legal changes form part of the Government's position on boycott, divestment and sanctions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33083","33083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506702","2016-04-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the report of the review of the South Yorkshire Community Rehabilitation Company that took place in November 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33118","33118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506703","2016-04-12","Prime Minister","2016-04-08","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to require all Ministers to publish their annual tax return.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33189","33189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506704","2016-04-12","Prime Minister","2016-04-08","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will make it his policy to revise the Ministerial Code to include an obligation on members of the Government not to use offshore tax arrangements.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32901","32901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506705","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding has been allocated to improve local transport infrastructure in Easington constituency in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32863","32863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506706","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving test examiners have (a) left and (b) been recruited by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency in the last (i) one, (ii) two and (iii) five years.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32898","32898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506707","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent on improving the road network in the Easington constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32862","32862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506708","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times Southern Trains has cancelled a scheduled stop at Plumpton Station in East Sussex in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32847","32847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506709","2016-04-13","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to respond to the Office of Rail and Road's recommendations following Which?'s super-complaint regarding train companies and the compensation process for passengers affected by train delays.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32910","32910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506710","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Network Rail has paid to Southeastern trains in compensation in the last (a) 12 months, (b) three years and (d) five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32915","32915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506711","2016-04-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on the number and severity of incidents involving trains carrying nuclear material on the rail network.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32913","32913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506712","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the development of a new railway station at Horden; and when that development is expected to be completed.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32876","32876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506713","2016-04-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on the number and severity of incidents involving vehicles transporting nuclear material on the strategic road network.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32914","32914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506714","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve journey times and train frequencies between Easington constituency and local rail hubs at Sunderland and Newcastle.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32865","32865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506715","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans are in place to upgrade trains and services on the Sunderland to Nunthorpe line.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32866","32866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506716","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve transport connectivity between Easington constituency and the six principal city regions as part of the Northern Transport Strategy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32864","32864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506717","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the publication by HS2 Ltd, Broad options for upgraded and high speed railways to the North of England and Scotland, published in March 2016, whether the Government is planning to extend High Speed 2 beyond Manchester and Leeds.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32807","32807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506718","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many incidents of laser pen attacks were recorded on ships in UK waters in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32784","32784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506719","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the likelihood of private hire operators straddling licensing authorities in order to avoid more thorough licensing requirements under the Deregulation Act 2015.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32785","32785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506720","2016-04-13","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to present the new Buses Bill to Parliament.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32814","32814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506721","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department issues guidance to bus operators on air pollution control and leaving bus engines running idle while at a bus stand.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32801","32801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506722","2016-04-13","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2015 to Question HL248, when  Network Rail is expected to complete the impact assessment of the European Rail Traffic Management System.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32821","32821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506723","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to limit the effect that engineering works on rail lines have on travel over long bank holidays.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32672","32672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506724","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost to Highways England was of its contract with Amey for services in Area 7; and which other companies bid for that contract.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32681","32681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506725","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what arrangements Highways England have agreed with Amey to provide services for Area 7 of the network on (a) reporting to Highways England, (b) monitoring fulfilment of that contract and (c) options for early termination.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32682","32682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506726","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of electrifying the railway line from (a) Crewe to Chester and (b) Chester to Holyhead.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32747","32747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506727","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average cost per mile of electrification of a railway line in the UK.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32748","32748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506728","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of upgrading the M56 to a smart motorway between junctions 12 and 14.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32749","32749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506729","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average cost per mile to upgrade a motorway to a smart motorway.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32750","32750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506730","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether an impact assessment has been carried out on the Maritime and Coastguard Agency's Survey and Inspection Transformation Programme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32741","32741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506731","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether an impact assessment has been carried out on the Maritime and Coastguard Agency's proposals to reduce the number of marine offices in the UK.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32742","32742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506732","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what dates the marine offices in (a) Brixham, (b) Leith and (c) Newlyn were closed; and how many Maritime and Coastguard Agency staff were (i) made redundant or (ii) transferred to other marine offices as a result of those closures.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32743","32743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506733","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff currently work at the marine offices in (a) Tyne, (b) Plymouth, (c) Beverley, (d) Orpington, (e) Harwich and (f) Norwich; and how many unfilled vacancies exist at each such location.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32744","32744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506734","2016-04-13","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the proposed new flightpaths before a decision is taken on a third runway at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32725","32725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506735","2016-04-13","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, at what stage in the decision making process regarding a third runway at Heathrow Airport he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on that matter.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32726","32726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506736","2016-04-13","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of a third runway at Heathrow Airport on compliance with EU Air Quality limits.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32727","32727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506737","2016-04-13","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Highways Agency on litter clearance on roads.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32709","32709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506738","2016-04-13","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who is responsible for litter clearance on the A1.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32710","32710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506739","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what contracts (a) have been agreed and (b) are still to be awarded by Highways England for (i) routine highway services and (ii) specialist goods and services.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32693","32693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506740","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what routine responsibilities are required of Amey by Highways England in its maintenance and response contract for the East Midlands.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32694","32694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506741","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) serious injuries and (b) fatalities in road traffic accidents were been reported to the police in (i) Dartford and (b) Kent in each year between 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33152","33152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506742","2016-04-13","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much subsidy was paid to the operators of the Northern rail franchise in each financial year between December 2004 and April 2016.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33082","33082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506743","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the capacity and the availability of seating for passengers on peak services on High Speed 1 trains between Ebbsfleet and London St Pancras.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33216","33216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506744","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether an impact assessment has been undertaken of the proposal in Question 35 of his Department's consultation on the extension of charging overseas visitors and migrants using the NHS in England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33157","33157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506745","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department has allocated to Kent County Council for local road maintenance for (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33158","33158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506746","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for (a) seafarer welfare and (b) compliance with the Maritime Labour Convention Regulation 4.1 on medical care onboard ship and ashore of the proposal in Question 35 of the Department of Health consultation on the extension of charging overseas visitors and migrants using the NHS in England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33000","33000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506747","2016-04-12","Department of Health","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential cost to industry of the proposal in Question 35 of the Department for Health consultation on the extension of charging overseas visitors and migrants using the NHS in England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32999","32999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506748","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of seafarers that would be affected by the proposal in Question 35 of the Department for Health consultation on the extension of charging overseas visitors and migrants using the NHS in England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32998","32998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506749","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what sanctions are in place to prevent the practice of nationality-based pay discrimination against EEA seafarers employed on (a) UK and (b) non-UK registered vessels working from UK ports.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32997","32997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506750","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what total revenue has been generated from foreign-registered freight lorries under the Dart Charge scheme since that scheme's inception.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32986","32986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506751","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many penalty charge notices have been (a) issued to motorists and (b) subsequently withdrawn or successfully appealed since the inception of the Dart Charge scheme.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32985","32985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506752","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has held discussions with academics and charities in receipt of grants from his Department on the potential effect of the anti-lobbying clause on their work.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32926","32926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506753","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how his Department plans to monitor and assess the effect of the revised anti-lobbying clause beyond 1 May 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32927","32927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506754","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential economic benefits of extending Crossrail to (a) Dartford and (b) Ebbsfleet stations.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32978","32978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506755","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what provisions his Department has put in place as part of the rail franchise package for the Calder Valley rail line to improve rolling stock on that line.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33207","33207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506756","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has for the future role of the merchant navy.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33210","33210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506757","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential economic benefits to the Calder Valley of a high speed rail link between Leeds and Manchester.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33208","33208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506758","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Maritime and Coastguard Agency is taking to encourage people to join the merchant navy.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33211","33211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506759","2016-04-12","Department for Transport","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential economic benefits to the Calder Valley of accelerating the upgrade of the M62 to a four-lane smart motorway between junctions 20 and 25.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33209","33209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506760","2016-04-12","Women and Equalities","2016-04-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the enforcement of age discrimination legislation in respect of people seeking employment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33177","33177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506761","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Lifetime ISA will be included in assessments of savings under universal credit.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33179","33179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506762","2016-04-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of the National Living Wage on the level of child poverty in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33224","33224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506763","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2016 to Question 31791, on employment and support allowance: inflammatory bowel disease, how many of those claimants started receiving employment and support allowance before 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33135","33135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506764","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that medical assessors and people considering appeals have sufficient knowledge of muscular dystrophy, neuromuscular conditions and other rare and progressive conditions.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33045","33045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506765","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department make available to people whose mandatory reconsideration and appeal takes longer than seven weeks to resolve.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33044","33044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506766","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many stroke survivors are currently in receipt of the personal independence payment.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33027","33027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506767","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many stroke survivors are in (a) receipt of employment and support allowance and (b) the work-related activity group.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33028","33028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506768","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate (a) the number of employers who have passed the full increase in national insurance contributions associated with the Pensions Act 2014 on to their employees, (b) the number of employees who have been affected by those changes, (c) the change in real terms to the take-home pay of such staff as a result of those changes and (d) the number of employers who are making profits to a sufficient level that there is no need to use the override facility incorporated within that Act.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33090","33090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506769","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to amend the aids and appliances descriptors, or the points awarded to them, for personal independence payments assessments.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33055","33055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506770","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to introduce lifetime awards for people assessed as requiring the upper personal independence payment allowance mobility component who have been diagnosed with muscle degenerative diseases or conditions.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32963","32963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506771","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many days it took his Department to answer hon. Members' correspondence on average in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32952","32952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506772","2016-04-12","Cabinet Office","2016-04-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many disabled people joined the workforce in each sector in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32935","32935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506773","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many allegations of fraudulent benefit claims have been reported by members of the public in each year since 2010; and by what means such allegations were reported.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32920","32920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506774","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many allegations of fraudulent benefit claims made by members of the public led to (a) benefits being stopped and (b) prosecutions in each of the  last five years.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32921","32921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506775","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his oral contribution of 21 March 2016, Official Report, column 1268, on welfare, whether he plans to implement his Department's proposal to cap housing benefit paid to social tenants at the level of local housing allowance.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32947","32947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506776","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who had their entitlement to the personal independent payment enhanced mobility rate removed and then reinstated on appeal were required to return a mobility vehicle or aid before that reinstatement in 2014-15.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33037","33037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506777","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in England are currently registered disabled as a result of having a stroke.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33022","33022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506778","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what contractual standards have been set for Maximus Health and Human Services Ltd for the number of completed work capability assessments.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33014","33014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506779","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work capability assessments have been (a) completed and (b) cancelled by Maximus Health and Human Services Ltd in (i) total and (ii) each local authority area.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33013","33013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506780","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons appointments were cancelled by Maximus Health and Human Services Ltd in each local authority area in each month of that organisation's contract with his Department.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33015","33015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506781","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to gather the views of and comments from claimants regarding their experiences with Maximus Health and Human Services Ltd.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33016","33016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506782","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many nationals from other EU member states have been in receipt of jobseeker's allowance for (a) less than one month, (b) more than one month, (c) between one and three months, (d) between three and six months, (e) between six and 12 months and (f) more than 12 months.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32729","32729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506783","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of EU migrants who will be eligible to receive benefits in each of the next five years and (b) cost of paying those benefits to the public purse.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32730","32730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506784","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many nationals from other EU member states have received jobseeker's allowance in each of the last 10 years; and what the total cost of such expenditure was to the public purse.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32731","32731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506785","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many care leavers as identified through the self-identified marker used by his Department between the ages of 18 and 25 had their (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance sanctioned in 2013-14 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32751","32751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506786","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with motor neurone disease are currently in receipt of the (a) lower and (b) higher rate of Attendance Allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32735","32735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506787","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department issues to jobcentre staff on the delivery of the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32736","32736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506788","2016-04-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will consider extending the exemptions that exist in the sea fishing industry to self-employed workers seeking Skills Funding Agency support for apprenticeships in the construction industry.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32770","32770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506789","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in Scotland who reach state pension age in 2016-17 will receive less than the full flat rate of the new state pension.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32838","32838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506790","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of men in Scotland who reach state pension age in 2016-17 will receive the full flat rate of the new state pension.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32839","32839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506791","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of women in Scotland who reach state pension age in 2016-17 will receive the full flat rate of the new state pension.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32840","32840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506792","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in Scotland who reach state pension age in 2016-17 will receive the full flat rate of the new state pension.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32841","32841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506793","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) average and (b) maximum time taken for contractors to return assessments to his Department was for Scottish claimants of (i) employment and support allowance and (ii) personal independence payments in each of the last four quarters for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32903","32903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506794","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) longest and (b) average journey time to attend a medical assessment was for Scottish claimants of (i) employment and support allowance and (ii) personal independence payments in each of the last four quarters for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32842","32842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506795","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many outstanding (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment assessments for Scottish claimants there were in each of the last four quarters for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32843","32843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506796","2016-04-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of claim decisions for Scottish claimants of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payments were upheld at appeal in each of the last four quarters for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32904","32904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506797","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of assessment reports conducted by contractors for Scottish claimants of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payments were carried out by a qualified doctor in each of the last four quarters for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32844","32844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506798","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of Scottish claimants of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payments were successful in each of the last four quarters for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32845","32845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506799","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of assessment reports conducted by contractors for Scottish claimants of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payments were returned by his Department as not being of a sufficient standard to enable a decision to be made in each of the last four quarters for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32846","32846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506800","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of women who are entitled to a state pension based on married women's reduced rate national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32827","32827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506801","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2016 to Question 31790, what categories of information his Department holds on people that apply for employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32826","32826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506802","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 23980, on employment plans: mental illness, whether he plans to introduce new measures of support for people with mental health problems before the end of the three year period of voluntary trials.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32812","32812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506803","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the potential effect on the cost of health and criminal justice services of the proposed housing benefit cap for people living in supported accommodation.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32868","32868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506804","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the Supported Accommodation review to be completed.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32869","32869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506805","2016-04-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Supported Accommodation review on the commissioning of services for vulnerable people.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32870","32870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506806","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to advise HM Revenue and Customs when an individual is moved from the employment and support allowance work related activity group into the support group.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32875","32875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506807","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to change (a) the points awarded to individual descriptors under the personal independent payments (PIP) and (b) other elements of the PIP assessment process system.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32912","32912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506808","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of assessment reports conducted by contractors for Scottish claimants of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payments did not meet the contractual standard required in each of the last four quarters for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32905","32905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506809","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether transitional protection where entitlement is lower will begin as soon as tax credit recipients start migrating to universal credit.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33185","33185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506810","2016-04-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the total expenditure on disability, incapacity, industrial injuries and carer's benefits in each year from 2015 to 2020 in real terms.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33186","33186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506811","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which of the Directors in his Department has responsibility for the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33250","33250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/506812","2016-04-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2016 to Question 30330, if he will publish examples of the feedback received on the placing of work coaches in foodbanks.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 33196","33196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486931","2016-04-11","Attorney General","2016-03-24","To ask the Attorney General, if he will place in the Library data gathered by Crown Prosecution Service Business Area of prosecutions and convictions for (a) rape-flagged offences, (b) domestic violence, (c) child abuse and (d) human trafficking for each year since 2013.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32531","32531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486932","2016-04-11","Attorney General","2016-03-24","To ask the Attorney General, if he will place in the Library the number of cases of (a) rape, (b) domestic violence, (c) child abuse and (d) human trafficking referred by each police force in England and Wales to each regional division of the Crown Prosecution Service in (i) 2014 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32532","32532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486933","2016-04-11","Attorney General","2016-03-24","To ask the Attorney General, how many directors of companies were disqualified as a result of a criminal investigation by the Serious Fraud Office in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32533","32533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486934","2016-04-11","Attorney General","2016-03-24","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of all defendants charged with (a) rape, (b) sexual offences other than rape and (c) domestic violence were aged (i) 14 to 17, (ii) 18 to 24, (iii) 25 to 34, (iv) 35 to 44, (v) 45 to 54, (vi) 55 to 64 and (vii) over 65 in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32550","32550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486935","2016-04-11","Attorney General","2016-03-24","To ask the Attorney General, how many tip-offs were made to the Serious Fraud Office tip-off line in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32551","32551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486936","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the quality of information and data used to inform his Department's investment prioritisation process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32537","32537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486937","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will conduct an assessment of UK science infrastructure to inform departmental decision-making on spending priorities.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32538","32538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486938","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the number of UK firms based in the East Midlands that trade with other EU member states; and how many people are employed by each such firm.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32610","32610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486939","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the number of UK firms based in Yorkshire and the Humber that trade with other EU member states; and how many people are employed by each such firm.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32611","32611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486940","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the number of UK firms based in the North West of England that trade with other EU member states; and how many people are employed by each such firm.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32612","32612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486941","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the number of UK firms based in the East of England that trade with other EU member states; and how many people are employed by each such firm.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32613","32613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486942","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what applications for arms export licences were rejected by his Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32495","32495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486944","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the productivity of small and medium-sized businesses of the planned withdrawal of HM Revenue and Customs' evaluation check services.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32464","32464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486945","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to promote the take-up of employee ownership schemes by small and medium-sized businesses in each nation of the UK.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32474","32474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486946","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, to which location he plans to relocate his Department's functions out of London.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32477","32477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486947","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the rent review will take place on 1 Victoria Street; and what plans he has to publish the results of that review.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32478","32478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486948","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with staff at his Department's office at 2 St Paul's Place, Sheffield, since the announcement of the proposed closure of that office.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32479","32479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486949","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on upgrading IT systems at 2 St Paul's Place, Sheffield in 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32480","32480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486950","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on upgrading its IT systems in 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32481","32481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486951","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2016 to Question 29835, and with reference to the Answer of 10 June 2013 to Question 158962, for what reasons information on the number of national minimum wage inquiries made to the Pay and Work Rights and Acas helplines relating to the domiciliary care and residential care sectors is not being collected at the previously available level of disaggregation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32490","32490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486954","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange a meeting between the Photo Marketing Association and the Passport Office to discuss ensuring that future digitally-supplied ID photographs meet International Civil Aviation Organisation compliance standards and are supplied by photographic professionals.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32622","32622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486955","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to ensure all legislation available on the legislation.gov.uk website is (a) accessible and (b) up to date.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32555","32555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486956","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.59 of the Summer Budget 2015, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of restricting finance cost relief for landlords on the ability of private individuals who operate buy-to-let businesses with large private buy-to-let companies.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32542","32542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486957","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Table 2.1 of the March Budget 2013, what his most recent estimate is of the effect of employee shareholder status income tax measures in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32569","32569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486958","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether revenue raised from the planned soft drink industry levy will be hypothecated for the public health budget.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32605","32605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486959","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.19 of the report, Overview of Tax Legislation and Rates, published on 16 March 2016, which technologies his Department is considering (a) adding and (b) removing from the list of qualifying technologies for the first-year allowance scheme for energy-saving and environmentally-beneficial technologies.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32618","32618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486960","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.19 of the report, Overview of Tax Legislation and Rates, published on 16 March 2016, what consultation with industry his Department undertook when considering which technologies will be added or removed from the list of qualifying technologies for the first-year allowance scheme for energy-saving and environmentally-beneficial technologies.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32619","32619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486961","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 30272, what account he has made of the effect on economic growth of the recent reduction in fuel duty.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32588","32588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486963","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 34 of the report, Overview of Tax Legislation and Rates, published on 16 March 2016, which producers will be exempt from the soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32620","32620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486964","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to consult with local businesses in Cumbernauld on the proposed closure of HM Revenue and Customs Cumbernauld office.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32600","32600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486965","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to conduct an impact assessment on the local economy of Cumbernauld of the proposed closure of HM Revenue and Customs Cumbernauld office.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32601","32601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486966","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to consult with (a) employees and (b) PCS representatives at HM Revenue and Customs Cumbernauld office on the proposed relocation of staff.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32602","32602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486967","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.19 of the Treasury report entitled, Overview of Tax Legislation and Rates, published on 16 March 2016, what impact assessment has been undertaken on which technologies will be added or removed from the list of qualifying technologies for the first-year allowance scheme for energy-saving and environmentally-beneficial technologies.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32572","32572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486968","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.134 of Budget 2016, when HM Revenue and Customs plans to publish the technical note clarifying the interpretation of existing legislation on tax reliefs for decommissioning expenditure.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32573","32573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486970","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to hold a public consultation on the proposed closures of HM Revenue and Customs offices in Scotland.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32597","32597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486971","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to consult with people in Cumbernauld on the proposed closure of HM Revenue and Customs Cumbernauld office.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32598","32598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486973","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.133 of Budget 2016, whether the adjustments to Investment Allowances for oil and gas production in the UK will extend to investment in pipelines.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32584","32584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486976","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the proposed 36 month stamp duty grace period for people transitioning from one property to another will apply retrospectively.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32467","32467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486977","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential costs and benefits of introducing an import tax on coal and gas imported from outside the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32468","32468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486978","2016-04-12","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that consumers have adequate advice and information about the benefits and risks of investing in a lifetime ISA.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32504","32504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486980","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2016 to Question 30533, for what reasons a separate breakdown for revenue accrued from financial spread betting and other general betting duties is not available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32503","32503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486981","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what lessons were learned from the universal credit scheme pilot; and what changes have been put in place as a result of those lessons.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32516","32516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486982","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing a national deposit return scheme as part of the Government's litter strategy.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32465","32465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486983","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the number of new private rented homes that will be needed to meet demand in the next five years.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32466","32466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486985","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to undertake the review of shared ownership announced in the report, Proposals to streamline the resale of shared ownership properties, Consultation: summary of responses, published in March 2015.","Biography information for Lucy Frazer","Lucy Frazer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32617","32617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486987","2016-04-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to commemorate the First World War in 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32471","32471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486988","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2016 to Question 25292, to which countries RAF Reaper or Watchkeeper drones have been deployed on intelligence, surveillance and reconnaissance sorties since 5 February 2016.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32492","32492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486989","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the last three exercises were carried out under the Five Powers Defence Arrangements; and how many armed forces (a) personnel and (b) assets were used in each of those exercises.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32484","32484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486990","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what modifications are required to HMS Prince of Wales to make it suitable for use as an amphibious assault platform.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32494","32494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486991","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what sites are under consideration for the shore-based testing facilities for the power and propulsion systems for the T26 Global Combat Ship.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32496","32496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486992","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to publish an updated timetable for commencing the building of the first T26 Global Combat Ship.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32497","32497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486993","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of the time taken in Block 3F testing of the F-35B Lightning II mission systems software on the planned commencement of formal initial operational test and evaluation development of that aircraft.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32558","32558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486994","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy for the House to be informed after his Department's cyber strike capability has been used in cases where urgent action has been required such that it has not been possible to inform the House in advance.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32570","32570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486995","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy for the House to be given an opportunity to debate in advance any decision to use his Department's cyber strike capability.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32571","32571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486996","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to improve the stability of radar sensors in the F-35B Lightning II Fighter.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32559","32559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486998","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the suitability of the Honeywell TCAS II collision warning system for use in Typhoon fighter aircraft.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32557","32557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/486999","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to fit airborne collision avoidance systems to Puma helicopters.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32552","32552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487000","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to fit airborne collision avoidance systems to Lynx helicopters.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32553","32553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487001","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions his Department's cyber strike capability was used in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32530","32530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487002","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to ring-fence special educational needs funding as part of her Department's new national funding formula.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32563","32563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487004","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2016 to Question 30139, what steps she plans to take to expand grant funding projects to other local authorities to support young carers under the age of 16, similar to that provided by Suffolk family carers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32587","32587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487006","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department issues guidance to schools on how to identify and manage incidences of parental alienation.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32604","32604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487008","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2016 to Question 30801, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to amend section 136 of the Education and Inspections Act 2006 to introduce a requirement on local authorities to ensure that home-schooled children are being educated to the same standard as schooled children.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32518","32518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487010","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on (a) the tax treatment of foster carers who claim tax benefit and (b) the qualification of such people for other benefits.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32520","32520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487011","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of her Department's reform of AS and A-level qualifications on the number of hours of study students are undertaking in post-16 education.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32493","32493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487012","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2016 to Question 29811, on further education, how many meetings have been held for area reviews in (a) Birmingham and Solihull, (b) Greater Manchester, (c) Sheffield City Region, (d) Tees Valley, (e) Sussex, (f) Solent and (g) West Yorkshire in each of the last nine months.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32491","32491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487013","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2016 to Question 29811, on further education, if she will publish the minutes of each of those meetings.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32475","32475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487015","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many tonnes of air pollution control residues were recovered into end-of-waste products in 2015; into what types of products those residues were returned back into the environment; how those products can be traced in case of recall; and what estimate she has made of the number of tonnes of air pollution control residues that will be recovered into end-of-waste products in 2016.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32513","32513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487016","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, upon what criteria she plans to decide whether to remove the derogation in the Waste Framework Directive which currently allows air pollution control residues, which have been recovered from municipal waste to energy incineration facilities, to be treated and disposed to hazardous landfill sites.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32514","32514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487018","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will launch a consultation on proposals for a deposit return system for single use drinks containers.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32517","32517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487020","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the preparedness is of the Animal and Plant Health Agency to react to and control a potential future animal health outbreak similar in scale to the foot and mouth outbreak of 2001.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32500","32500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487021","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will estimate the costs to local authorities of (a) mixing a tonne of air pollution control residues into concrete blocks and (b) disposing of a tonne of air pollution control residues to secure hazardous waste landfill.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32609","32609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487022","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish the (a) most recent environmental risk assessment for bound use of air pollution control residues in concrete blocks, (b) exposure levels of dioxins and heavy metals in the air when the blocks were cut, drilled or crushed in buildings and (c) scientific methodology used for measuring these levels.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32621","32621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487023","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing a deposit return scheme for single use drinks containers to reduce litter.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32607","32607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487024","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps she is taking to ensure that farmers receive fair pricing for their dairy produce.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32564","32564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487025","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many tonnes of air pollution control residues were captured at municipal energy from waste incineration facilities in 2015; and what estimate she has made of the total tonnes of air pollution control residues that will be generated by municipal energy from waste incineration facilities in 2016.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32515","32515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487026","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Liberia.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32535","32535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487027","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress on implementation of the recommendations of the Truth and Reconciliation Commission of Liberia.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32536","32536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487028","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress made at the recent UN peace talks in Geneva on Syria.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32556","32556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487029","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of human rights workers being (a) summoned for questioning, (b) banned from travelling and (c) subject to attempts to freeze their personal funds and family assets by the Egyptian authorities.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32547","32547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487030","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of injured children trying to leave Syria being turned away at the Jordanian border.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32548","32548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487032","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of elections due to take place in November 2016 on political stability in Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32549","32549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487034","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent violence in Israel and the West Bank on relations in that region.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32581","32581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487035","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of Hamas fighters joining ISIS in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32582","32582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487036","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the influence of ISIS in Gaza.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32583","32583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487037","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what investigatory methods his Department uses for reports of potential breaches of international humanitarian law by UK allies in Yemen.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32498","32498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487038","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he expects the UK-China human rights dialogue to take place.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32521","32521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487039","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which cases of human rights violations against Tibetans he or ministerial colleagues have taken up with their Chinese counterparts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32522","32522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487040","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to end arms exports to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32476","32476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487041","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of UK relations with Pakistan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32470","32470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487042","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to (a) review and (b) improve the autism self-assessment framework.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32469","32469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487045","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many diabetes specialist nurses there are in (a) Leicester General Hospital, (b) Leicester Royal Infirmary, (c) Glenfield Hospital and (d) Leicestershire.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32483","32483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487047","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what scientific testing Spirit Healthcare's Empower type 2 diabetes education programme underwent for the outcomes it produces.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32507","32507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487049","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times Spirit Healthcare has been commissioned to deliver type 2 diabetes education to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32508","32508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487050","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts with the NHS for diabetes education Spirit Healthcare holds.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32509","32509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487058","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what responsibility NHS England has to fund HIV prevention programmes.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32575","32575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487059","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to support recommendation 17 of the Mental Health Taskforce report of February 2016, on 24/7 access to mental health services by 2020-21.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32576","32576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487060","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on treating people with inflammatory bowel disease in (a) the last 12 months and (b) each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32577","32577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487061","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that every patient with inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) is recorded on (a) a local searchable database and (b) the UK registry for IBD patients.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32578","32578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487063","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to use the inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) registry to get an accurate number of people living with IBD.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32579","32579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487064","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effects on healthcare of the introduction of a registry of patients with inflammatory bowel disease in England; and what support his Department has provided for that registry.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32580","32580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487066","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to encourage the use of faecal calprotectin in primary care to facilitate prompt and appropriate referral of people with suspected inflammation of the bowel.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32585","32585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487068","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue guidance to NHS trusts on ensuring future reductions in frontline staff numbers are not made for the purpose of reducing trusts' deficits.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32599","32599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487069","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2016 to Question 22159, on mental illness and A&E departments, if he will publish that data for each month of 2015 and 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32627","32627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487071","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will meet with NICE, NHS England and Vertex to discuss the provision on the NHS of the drug Orkambi to treat cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32606","32606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487072","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason NHS England decided not to proceed with the Truvada commissioning process; and what plans the Government has to make that drug available on the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32608","32608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487074","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on implementing recommendation 10 in the executive summary of Public Health England's March 2015 report entitled, Public mental health leadership and workforce development framework, on building the capacity of the National Mental Health Intelligence Network.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32628","32628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487076","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS funding was provided to GP surgeries in each of the last five years","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32591","32591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487078","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many colleges and universities have had (a) sponsorship licences revoked and (b) faced other restrictions related to allegations of English Language Test fraud; and what steps she plans to take to reconsider those revocations and restrictions.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32586","32586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487079","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will estimate the number of people affected by the decision of 23 March 2016 of the Upper Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum Chamber) in the case Qadir v Secretary of State; and what steps she plans to take to (a) notify those people affected and (b) support appeals of previous immigration decisions by those people affected.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32574","32574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487080","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what process Tier 2 intra-company transfer visas for IT undergo when they reach her Department.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32562","32562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487081","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what powers she has to shorten the term of a Police and Crime Commissioner elected in May 2016 in order that the role is subsumed by a Metro-Mayor.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32560","32560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487083","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she is permitted to consider a bid from a Combined Authority for a Police and Crime Commissioner elected in May 2016 to be subsumed by a Metro-Mayor.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32561","32561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487085","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 31078, on immigration officers, whether (a) her Department, (b) the Interception of Communications Commissioner and (c) any other body has reviewed the use of the power of immigration officers to carry out property interference since 2013.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32566","32566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487087","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 31078, on immigration officers, what policy, guidance or code of practice is provided to immigration officers carrying out equipment interference.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32567","32567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487090","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 30648, what details of family members her Department records in respect of refugees who are granted asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32506","32506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487091","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 30649, when she plans to publish the outcomes of the review of the process of dealing with family reunion applications.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32505","32505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487092","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to how many appeal hearings her Department did not send a representative at (a) First-tier Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum) and (b) Upper Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum) in (i) 2012-13 (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32528","32528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487093","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has for future provision of the collective passport service.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32485","32485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487094","2016-04-11","House of Commons Commission","2016-03-24","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what the annual catering bill is for the House of Commons.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32589","32589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487095","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost is per patient attending at GPs' surgeries nationally.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32590","32590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487096","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the UK aid budget will be allocated as (a) grants and (b) loans in 2016-17.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32603","32603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487098","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received on the use of aid disbursed to the Palestinian Authority for purposes related to terrorist activity.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32482","32482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487099","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made in its programme to increase the use of Long Lasting Insecticide Treated Nets among children under five years of age and pregnant women in Uganda.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32526","32526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487100","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the outcomes have been of her Department's programme of post-conflict development in Northern Uganda.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32524","32524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487101","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of her Department's programmes in the eight districts of the Central Region of Uganda in preventing the spread of malaria.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32525","32525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487102","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the outcome has been of its programme to improve the effect of public expenditure on the quality of service delivery and poverty reduction in Uganda.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32523","32523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487103","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on steps to remove foreign national offenders from UK prisons to their home countries.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32511","32511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487104","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to improve prisons' engagement with employers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32512","32512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487105","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many former civil servants who worked on JSi projects have now left his Department.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32529","32529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487106","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the additional cost to his Department in the last year of appeal hearings at the First Tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support) which were adjourned because the Department of Work and Pensions did not send a representative in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32527","32527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487107","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeal hearings at the First-tier Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum) were (a) withdrawn and (b) adjourned because the Home Office did not send a representative in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32540","32540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487108","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners at each establishment have risk indicators which have been identified after completion of a cell sharing risk assessment.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32541","32541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487109","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on whether Passenger Service Performance by the TSGN has exceeded the Default Performance Level for any benchmark for any (a) three consecutive reporting periods, (b) four reporting periods within a period of 13 consecutive reporting periods or (c) any five reporting periods within a period of 26 consecutive reporting periods except in relation to any reporting periods falling within a no breach reporting period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32502","32502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487110","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what provisions his Department has put in place to improve rolling stock as part of the rail franchise package for the North West.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32510","32510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487111","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take in response to the rejection by the European Parliament of the competitive market exemption condition agreed by the Council of Ministers in 2014 as part of the Council's General Approach to the Ports Regulation to ensure that the UK ports industry is fully protected from the effects of that regulation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32519","32519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487112","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the top five reasons were for imposing sanctions on jobseeker's allowance claimants in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32501","32501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487113","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provisions his Department has in place to ensure that sufferers of multiple sclerosis do not experience a decrease in benefit payments as a result of experiencing a temporary period of remission in their condition.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32499","32499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487114","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for reconsideration or appeal of a sanction decision were submitted in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32534","32534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487115","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many care leavers aged 18 to 25 have had sanctions overturned or reduced on reconsideration or appeal in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32472","32472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487116","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications from care leavers between the age of 18 and 25 were made for reconsideration or appeal of a sanction decision in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32473","32473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487117","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance were processed within (i) 10 days and (ii) 16 days in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32486","32486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487118","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new universal credit claims were processed within one month in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32487","32487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487119","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of applications for short term benefit advance were successful in the most recent 12 months for which data is available; and what reasons were given to those people who made unsuccessful applications in that period.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32488","32488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487120","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people from other EU member states receive support through the Work Programme.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32489","32489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487121","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people from other EU member states were in receipt of housing benefit in each of the last 10 years; and what the total cost to the public purse was of those people claiming that benefit in each of those years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32543","32543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487122","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis claiming benefits whose claim (a) partly and (b) solely relates to that condition have had their benefits payments (i) reduced and (ii) ceased after medical reassessment undertaken on behalf of the Department due to that person being in remission from that condition.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32539","32539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487123","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2016 to Question 27517, how many foreign nationals living in the UK have been prosecuted for a fraudulent child benefit claim for a child living in the EU.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32554","32554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487124","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2016 to Question 31496, how many appeals were (a) withdrawn and (b) adjourned at the First-Tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support) due to his Department not sending a representative in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32568","32568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487125","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March to Questions 30367, on vocational guidance, whether he plans that Jobcentre Plus or the Careers and Enterprise company will contact those schools.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32565","32565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487126","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people from other EU member states were in receipt of universal credit in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what the cost to the public purse was of those payments of that credit.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32545","32545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487127","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value was of (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance sanctions imposed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32546","32546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487128","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people from other EU member states have received each type (a) of working aged and (b) in-work benefit in each of the last 10 years; and what the total cost to the public purse was of those people claiming each of those benefits in each of those years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32544","32544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487129","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will discuss with vehicle manufacturers improvements to in-vehicle technology to prevent vehicle hacking.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32614","32614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487130","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to improve trade with (a) Hong Kong and (b) China as a whole.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32624","32624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487131","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2016 to Question 21634, when he plans to deposit in the Library information on the end of year budget surplus or deficit for each further education college in London in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32658","32658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487132","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to Answer Question 26990, tabled on 11 February 2016 by the hon. Member for Glasgow South West.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32641","32641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487133","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Government plans to publish its response to Lawrence Tomlinson's report on the lending practices of banks to small businesses.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32662","32662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487134","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with officials of the Home Office and the police on proposals to allow members of the public to take their own ID photos for official documents on their own digital devices and the potential effect of this on ID fraud and quality of images.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32646","32646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487135","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency (DVLA) has had with the professional photographic sector since June 2015; and if he will request that the DVLA meets representatives of the Photo Marketing Association to discuss the future provision of digital ID photographs.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32647","32647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487136","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contribution his Department is making to Government steps to reduce the incidence of serious youth violence.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32648","32648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487137","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of child benefit payments to non-UK citizens.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32664","32664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487138","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Housing Statistical Release Right to Buy Sales October to December 2015, published on 24 March 2016, what the average length of time was from a start on site to occupancy.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32644","32644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487139","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether housing association tenants who part-buy their properties under shared ownership will be able to use Right To Buy to purchase either a share or all of that property.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32632","32632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487140","2016-04-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what contribution his Department is making to Government steps to reduce the incidence of serious youth violence.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32650","32650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487141","2016-04-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to commemorate the life of Bobby Moore and to mark the 60th anniversary of his captaincy of the 1966 England FIFA World Cup winning team.","Biography information for Damian Collins","Damian Collins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32657","32657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487142","2016-04-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to maximise engagement of children and young people in the arts.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32663","32663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487143","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the Government has to extend the period of time separating spouses of service personnel have to vacate his Department's accommodation.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32655","32655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487144","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether spending on the upkeep of the defence estate counts towards the Government's pledge to spend at least two per cent of GDP on defence, as defined by NATO.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32645","32645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487145","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution of cadet forces to reducing the incidence of serious youth violence.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32594","32594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487146","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in how many towns there is no choice of secondary education provision.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32593","32593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487147","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what contribution her Department is making to Government steps to reduce the incidence of serious youth violence.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32651","32651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487148","2016-04-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 26458, how much investment in energy efficiency measures (a) was made during the last Parliament and (b) will be made during this Parliament.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32639","32639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487149","2016-04-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department holds data on the amount of heat a tonne of biomass gives off when burned compared to a tonne of coal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32625","32625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487150","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 31488, how many British officials who have provided advice to Saudi Arabia's internal investigation into the breaking of international humanitarian law in Yemen have visited Yemen as part of this investigation; and where each of those officials was based.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32640","32640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487151","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the prospects for the Middle East peace process.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32661","32661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487152","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on the number of civilians (a) killed and (b) injured in the Yemen conflict to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32643","32643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487153","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP appointments were available in Enfield North constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32654","32654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487154","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure all frontline NHS staff are trained in suicide prevention; and whether such training will be compulsory.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32656","32656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487155","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs were working in (a) Enfield North constituency, (b) Enfield and (c) London (i) in total and (ii) per head of population in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32652","32652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487156","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which (a) ministers and (b) officials of his Department will be present at the International Aids Conference in Durban in July 2016.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32616","32616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487157","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce variations in mental health spending and services between clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32626","32626"
