"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999609","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions the Government has had with steel companies on the construction of electric arc furnaces on Teesside.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187065","187065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999610","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's report entitled Understanding organised crime 2015-16, published in November 2018, what assessment he has made of the reasons behind the £9.3 billion rise in the social and economic cost of drugs to society; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187083","187083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999611","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the change in real-terms funding made available to regional organised crime units from their inception to the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187084","187084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999612","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department made of trends in the level of reported ethnic and linguistic tensions in Cameroon in the last three years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187055","187055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999613","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to review its policy on the tethering of horses, donkeys, ponies and their hybrids; and what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of (a) making guidance on tethering enforceable by Environmental Officers, (b) introducing a time-limit on tethering and (c) making it an offence to tether an animal in a location that poses a danger to the animal or the public.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187056","187056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999614","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Serious and Organised Crime Strategy, published on 1 November 2018, when he plans to bring forward proposals for a new funding model to tackle serious organised crime.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187085","187085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999615","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number of staff hours it will take to process applications for settled status by non-UK EU citizens living in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187057","187057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999616","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what specific projects his Department is leading on to (a) support complex families with children at risk of involvement in crime and (b) build safer communities with a greater resilience to serious and organised crime.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187086","187086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999617","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what specific projects his Department is leading on to divert young people from becoming involved in serious and organised crime.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187087","187087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999618","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what changes there have been in the social background of children in secondary level education in the bottom quartile for educational attainment from 2007 to 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186976","186976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999619","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of welfare and benefits fraud committed by serious and organised criminals in the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187088","187088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999620","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Serious and Organised Crime Strategy, published on 1 November 2018, whether he plans to publish the key performance indicators for that strategy.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187089","187089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999621","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many disruptions as a result of ROCU operations were achieved in each year from their inception to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187090","187090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999622","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of levels of performance in processing and paying VAT refunds.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187134","187134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999623","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the new online service for VAT refunds on the time it takes to process and pay VAT refunds.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187135","187135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999624","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many biometric residence permits have been issued in the last three months; and what the average time taken has been for issuing such permits in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186985","186985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999625","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 176098, how his Department plans to contact people with existing leave to remain in the UK on applying for a biometric residence permit.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186986","186986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999626","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Integrated Care Provider contracts on improving (a) quality of care and (b) value for money.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187144","187144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999627","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that Integrated Care Provider contracts do not divert resources away from acute services operated by the same provider.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187145","187145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999628","2018-11-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2018 to Question 183928 on Influenza: Vaccination, and with reference to the guidance, Flu Vaccination Programme Delivery Guidance 2018-19 published by NHS England, what assessment he has made of appropriateness of delivering aTIV to healthcare providers by mid-November.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187015","187015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999629","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taking to invest in infrastructure in the Clacton region.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187158","187158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999630","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department's arrangement with Citizens Advice to provide universal credit support to claimants will operate in (a) constituencies and (b) local authority areas that do not have a Citizens Advice bureau.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187046","187046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999631","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many meetings his Department has held with big society capital in (a) each year since 2012 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187034","187034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999632","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many meetings his Department has held with social enterprises in (a) each year since 2012 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187035","187035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999633","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) progress and (b) fairness of appeals against the dismissal by public sector employees in Turkey since July 2016.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186987","186987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999634","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Turkish counterpart on (a) the removal from office of directly-elected mayors in that country and (b) the recent statement by President Erdogan suggesting that successful mayoral candidates in Kurdish-majority areas may also be removed following local elections.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186988","186988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999635","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the trade dispute between the Governments of the United States and China on the implementation by China of UN sanctions against North Korea.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186989","186989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999636","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) China and (b) North Korea on the talks held between the leaders of those countries in Beijing on 18 June 2018; and what information his Department holds on the outcomes of those talks.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186990","186990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999637","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in North Korea on recent imports of crude oil to that country in excess of the maximum levels permitted by UN Security Council Resolution 2375.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186991","186991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999638","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Civil Society Strategy, when he plans to publish information on the regular forum for social enterprises to coordinate relations with Government; and whether that forum will have an independent chair.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187036","187036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999639","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many official in his Department are working on projects related to social impact bonds.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187037","187037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999640","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to close the autism employment gap.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187154","187154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999641","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Health and Work Programme for autistic people.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187155","187155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999642","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department have taken to record the employment outcomes of the Health and Work Programme for autistic people.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187156","187156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999643","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking (a) to measure the employment rate among autistic people and (b) to record autism in the Labour Force Survey.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187157","187157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999644","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has undertaken an impact assessment of his Department's decision to delay the implementation of a maximum stake on fixed odds betting terminals from April 2019 to October 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187130","187130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999645","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans her Department has to consult on proposals for mandatory participation in pensions dashboards by pension providers.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187095","187095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999646","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2018 to Question 176435, whether support for funding will include costs incurred as a result of requests for mutual aid following the Salisbury incident and its aftermath.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187091","187091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999647","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long people have waited on average to receive the elements of universal credit that are paid on the basis of health conditions or disabilities by condition in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what comparative assessment she has made of that waiting time with the average waiting time for standard allowance.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187124","187124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999648","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what preconditions his Department has set for the UK to recognise the State of Palestine.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186926","186926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999649","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on facilitating visits to Gaza for hon. Members.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186927","186927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999650","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of universal credit have a (a) health condition (b) disability) and (c) a diagnosis of cancer.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187125","187125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999651","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the (a) progress, (b) independence and (c) transparency of investigations into (i) the use of live fire and (ii) related deaths on the Gaza border in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186928","186928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999652","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to encourage all parties to engage with the UN Human Rights Council commission of inquiry on the 2018 protests in the Occupied Palestinian Territory.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186929","186929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999653","2018-11-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of his Department's projected spend on PFI contracts in 2028.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186961","186961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999654","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time is for a claimant of universal credit to receive a UC50 form as part of their work capability assessment as a result of a (a) health condition and (b) disability for each of those conditions and disabilities.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187126","187126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999655","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Egyptian counterpart on the proposal for the  Palestinian reconciliation process to be overseen by the Egyptian Government.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186930","186930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999656","2018-11-05","Department for International Development","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to introduce a new economic development package in Gaza to (a) increase trade (b) support job creation and (c) enhance the supply of electricity and clean water.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186931","186931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999657","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the resumption of substantive negotiations between Israel and the Palestinians.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186932","186932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999658","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b)what proportion of her Department's Answers to Written Parliamentary Questions on universal credit stated that the requested information was (a) not collected and (b) not collected centrally in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186962","186962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999659","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of measures related to universal credit announced in Budget 2018 on disabled people who are (a) in work and (b) out of work.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187026","187026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999660","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she had made of the levels of spending on social security for disabled people as a result of the provisions of Budget 2018.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187027","187027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999661","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of changes to universal credit announced in Budget 2018 on self-employed people.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187028","187028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999662","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of international involvement in Israeli investigations on the use of live fire and related deaths on the Gaza border in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186933","186933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999663","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of apprenticeship levy funds were spent by non-levy payers in 2017-18.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186952","186952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999664","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with relevant organisations and bodies on how they plan to (a) respond to and (b) implement the recommendations set out in the Meningococcal Working Group report.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186984","186984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999665","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the decision was taken to stop the support provided to claimants of existing benefits and tax credits for between three and five weeks when they are migrated to universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186921","186921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999666","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's policy is on decision-making by NHS Trusts in the event that recommendations from (a) Getting it Right First Time and (b) NICE are contradictory.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187004","187004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999667","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184391 on Department for Work and Pensions: Contracts, how many contracts her Department has issued with any such clauses in each of the past three years; what proportion of those contracts have been breached; and what sanctions her Department has in place in the event that the clause is breached.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186963","186963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999668","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what relative priority he attaches to non-trial evidence compared to evidence from randomised clinical trials to inform NICE and NHS commissioning guidance.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187005","187005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999670","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) pheasants and (b) partridges were kept in raised laying cages for the breeding of game birds for sporting purposes in England and Wales in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186942","186942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999671","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of (i) pheasants and (ii) partridges kept in raised laying cages by the Bettws Hall Game Farm for the breeding of game birds for sporting purposes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186943","186943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999672","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Federation of British Herpetologists on the implications for shops and businesses selling reptiles and related species of the new animal activities licence.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186953","186953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999673","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the administration of the new animal activities licence on shops and businesses holding or selling reptiles and related species.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186954","186954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999674","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidelines he and his officials have given to local authorities as to the nature and reasonable costs of inspection and licence renewal for shops and businesses holding or selling reptiles and related species under the provisions of the new animal activities licence.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186955","186955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999675","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8915 on Hospitals: Hygiene, when he plans to publish the data on hospital hand hygiene compliance.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187024","187024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999676","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of extending the transition timetable for the new animal activities licence for shops selling reptiles and related species beyond 31 December 2018.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186956","186956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999677","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of (a) self harm, (b) violence against prisoners and (c) violence against prison staff per 100 prisoners there were in each prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186964","186964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999678","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 183354, how many of the 23,712 international GCSE entries in EBACC subjects in 2018 were taken in (a) independent schools and (b) independent special schools.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187032","187032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999679","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of rough sleepers in (a) towns and cities with a population above 150,000 and (b) towns and cities with a population of under 150,000 in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186965","186965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999680","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful (a) fines and (b) prosecutions have been made as a result of evidence obtained from ANPR cameras in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186966","186966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999681","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 5.21 of Budget 2018 Red Book whether the £400 million for School Equipment and Maintenance Uplift applies to (a) specialist schools and (b) alternative provision.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187038","187038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999682","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2018 to Question 182759 on Universal Credit: Wolverhampton North East, what estimate he has made of the cost of recording the postcode of applicants for universal credit advance payments (a) by telephone, (b) in person and (c) online.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186967","186967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999683","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many veterans that joined the armed forces aged (a) 18 or under and (b) 19 or older have registered at Jobcentres in each region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187100","187100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999684","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the additional tax revenue that will accrue to the public purse from fixed odds betting terminals as a result of the delay in the introduction of the maximum stake from April 2019 to October 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187131","187131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999685","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many medical appointments by type of appointment were made by Junior Soldiers at AFC Harrogate medical facilities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187101","187101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999686","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) veterans and (b) serving armed forces personnel that enlisted aged 18 or under have sought mental health support in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187102","187102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999687","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many veterans that joined the armed forces aged (a) 18 or under and (b) 19 or older have applied for Jobseeker’s Allowance in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187103","187103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999688","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many veterans that joined the armed forces aged (a) 18 or under and (b) 19 or older have applied for Enhanced Learning Credits in each region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187104","187104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999689","2018-11-05","Church Commissioners","2018-11-01","To ask the Right Honourable Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, how women in ministry are being supported with eldercare and parental care.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187075","187075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999690","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has undertaken a review of the disciplinary policy at AFC Harrogate.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187105","187105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999691","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has sought the views of (a) current junior soldiers and (b) former junior soldiers on the disciplinary policy at AFC Harrogate in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187106","187106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999692","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department has received from (a) current junior soldiers and (b) former junior soldiers on the disciplinary policy at AFC Harrogate in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187107","187107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999693","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Junior Soldiers have been subject to the disciplinary procedure at AFC Harrogate in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187108","187108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999694","2018-11-05","Church Commissioners","2018-11-01","To ask the Right Honourable Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether women in ministry with caring responsibilities are in receipt of their full stipend.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187076","187076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999695","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many junior soldiers have appealed against a decision of the disciplinary procedure at AFC Harrogate in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187109","187109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999696","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department provides for junior soldiers at AFC Harrogate with mental health problems.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187110","187110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999697","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether AFC Harrogate has internal mental health support workers for junior soldiers.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187111","187111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999698","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the full combination of EBACC entries in (a) independent and (b) state-funded schools were wholly (i) IGCSEs and (ii) GCSEs entries.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187033","187033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999699","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 5.16 of Budget 2018, what proportion of the £410 million for adult and children social care is for children's social care.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187039","187039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999700","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 5.16 of Budget 2018, how the £410 million for adult and children social care will be distributed among local councils.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187040","187040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999701","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the disciplinary policy of AFC Harrogate.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187112","187112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999702","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 5.17 of Budget 2018, what proportion of the £55 million of the Disabled Facilities Grant will be allocated to programmes targeted at children.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187041","187041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999703","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the funding allocated to Belfast after the bank buildings fire will be distributed and administered to local businesses and residents.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187132","187132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999704","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Indonesian Government on increasing child immunisation rates for diseases such as measles in West Papua.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187146","187146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999705","2018-11-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) adults (b) children with learning disabilities or autism have been admitted to assessment and treatment units in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187013","187013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999706","2018-11-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,with reference to the report, Building the Right Support, published in 2015, what progress his Department is to reduce the number of people with (a) learning disabilities and (b) autism being held on Assessment and Treatment Units by March 2019.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187014","187014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999707","2018-11-06","Scotland Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the Glasgow city region deal to date.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187133","187133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999708","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will provide guidance on the Government buying standards for food and catering services on sourcing game meat.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187051","187051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999709","2018-11-06","Department for International Development","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of people enrolled on training courses provided by the Punjab skills development fund are (a) from minority communities and (b) on nursing courses.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187066","187066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999710","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many junior soldiers were (a) arrested by civilian police and (b) charged with a criminal offence during their time at AFC Harrogate in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187113","187113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999711","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of serving soldiers that trained at (a) AFC Harrogate, (b) ITC Catterick, and (c) ATC Pirbright were arrested by the civilian police during each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187114","187114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999712","2018-11-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 01 November 2018 to Question 185122 on In Vitro Fertilisation, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of making mandatory National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines on the assessment and treatment of people with fertility problems.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187136","187136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999713","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to convene a summit of European and Arab foreign ministers with the US Administration to discuss the red lines for that country’s Middle East peace plan.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186992","186992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999714","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Israeli government on the proposed implementation of Military Order 1797 to (a) accelerate the process of demolitions within the Occupied Palestinian Territories and (b) prevent third-party legal challenges against those demolitions.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186993","186993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999715","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the timeframe for the publication of the final report of  the Office for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons into the reported chemical weapons attack on Douma in April 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186994","186994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999716","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support on cyber-threats the Government is providing to the government of Ukraine in advance of that countries elections in 2019.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186995","186995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999717","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Tunisia on the implementation by that country of the recommendations of its Commission on Liberties and Equality.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186996","186996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999718","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Tunisia on the threat posed by the return of Tunisian Daesh fighters to that country; and what plans he has to support that Government in tackling that threat.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186997","186997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999719","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason human rights abuses in Cameroon’s Anglophone regions was not on the agenda during the UK presidency of the United Nations Security Council in August 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186998","186998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999720","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Sri Lankan counterpart on the implementation of the transitional justice mechanisms set out in UN Human Rights Council Resolution 30/1.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186999","186999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999721","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the statutory basis for any obligation on (a) parents and (b) guardians to allow a child to take an assessment test before that child has reached the compulsory school age is.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187120","187120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999722","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) leukaemia, (b) myeloma, (c) Hodgkin’s lymphoma and (d) non-Hodgkin’s lymphoma are in receipt of personal independence payment.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187016","187016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999723","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it the Government's policy that the current average council tax across Christchurch, Poole and Bournemouth be used as the base for setting the 2019-20 council tax across the new unitary authority.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186923","186923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999724","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) leukaemia, (b) myeloma, (c) Hodgkin's lymphoma and (d) non-Hodgkin's lymphoma have successfully appealed against a decision not to award personal independence payment.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187017","187017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999725","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) leukaemia, (b) myeloma, (c) Hodgkin's lymphoma and (d) non-Hodgkin's lymphoma have (i) been reassessed from disability living allowance to personal independence payment and (ii) received reduced rates of award.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187018","187018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999726","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports issued by his Department were reported lost in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186922","186922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999727","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications for a tax-free childcare account have been started but not completed.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187121","187121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999728","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of unqualified teachers working in schools in (a) Dulwich and West Norwood, (b) London and (c) England.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187097","187097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999729","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of unqualified teaching staff working in (a) maintained state schools, (b) academies and (c) free schools.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187098","187098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999730","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October to Question 183461, if he will publish the higher education institutions that are participating in the Teachers Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187045","187045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999731","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of students in London schools taught by unqualified teachers in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187099","187099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999732","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy that the current average council tax across Christchurch, Poole and Bournemouth be used as the base for setting the 2019-20 council tax across the new unitary authority.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186924","186924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999733","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations has he made to his Yemeni counterpart on incitement against members of the Baha'i community in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186957","186957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999734","2018-11-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what employee benefits there are for new recruits to the armed forces who are not eligible to join the armed forces childcare vouchers scheme.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187122","187122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999735","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on five year sentences for animal cruelty.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186983","186983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999736","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Budget 2018, paragraph 1.60, if he will publish a breakdown of the £4.7 billion of extra DEL allocated to the reserves to cover additional costs arising from the reduction in the discount rate for employer contributions to public sector pension schemes.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187161","187161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999737","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to encourage businesses to relocate their manufacturing functions to the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187160","187160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999738","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department takes to incorporate big society or civic society considerations into its policy formulation process.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186968","186968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999739","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to incorporate (a) big society and (b) civic society considerations into its policy formulation process.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186969","186969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999740","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the Get it Right First Time report.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186913","186913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/998517","2018-10-31","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-31","When the next meeting of the British-Irish Intergovernmental Conference will take place.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907331","907331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/998518","2018-10-31","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-31","What discussions her Department has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on preparations for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907332","907332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/998560","2018-11-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to protect heritage buildings.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907393","907393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/998563","2018-11-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of his Department's ability to meet the universal service obligation for superfast broadband coverage in Hampshire.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907406","907406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999115","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of court closures in (a) Bury St Edmunds and (b) Lowestoft on access to justice in Suffolk.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186295","186295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999116","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations he has received on protecting the bittern under phase one of the 2016 Special Protection Area Review; and what steps he is taking to implement the recommendations of that review.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186211","186211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999117","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) leukaemia, (b) myeloma ,(c) hodgkin’s lymphoma and (d) non-hodgkin’s lymphoma are in receipt of personal independence payments.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186331","186331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999118","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) leukaemia, (b) myeloma, (c) hodgkin’s lymphoma and (d) non-hodgkin’s lymphoma have successfully appealed against a decision not to award personal independence payment.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186332","186332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999119","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) leukaemia, (b) myeloma, (c) hodgkin’s lymphoma and (d) non-hodgkin’s lymphoma have (i) been reassessed from disability living allowance to personal independence payments and (ii) received a reduced rate of award.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186333","186333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999120","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the health condition of fatigue is assessed by the personal independence payments assessment.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186334","186334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999121","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children and care leavers went on to key stage 5 in 2016-17.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186405","186405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999122","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will support the recommendation in the Greater Manchester clean air plan to replace all buses that are not compliant with clean air standards; and if he will make a statement","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186443","186443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999123","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps in conjunction with local authorities to ensure standards of air quality are adhered to in vehicle and technology manufacturing and distribution.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186444","186444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999124","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the level of risk of landlords bypassing rules licensing houses in multiple occupation by (a) acquiring bed and breakfast accommodation and (b) using outbuildings to house tenants.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186181","186181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999125","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of privately owned tower blocks which have dangerous cladding.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186182","186182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999126","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the time taken for decisions to be made on asylum seekers claims before being eligible to find employment.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186296","186296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999127","2018-11-05","Department for International Development","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has taken to ensure that (a) food, (b) fuel and (c) medical supplies reach hard to access parts of Yemen.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186297","186297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999128","2018-10-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has a policy of zero tolerance of bullying, harassment and discrimination.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186306","186306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999129","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for reducing the mean average gender pay gap in his Department to (a) 10 per cent and (b) zero.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186307","186307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999130","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received from local authorities on the funding of adult social care in England.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186445","186445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999131","2018-11-05","Attorney General","2018-10-31","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 23rd July 2018 to Question 165033 on the National Fund, whether he has received a hearing date from the High Court on his application to release the money held by the National Fund.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186228","186228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999132","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have participated in his Department's Desistance and Disengagement programme during (a) the trial period of that programme and (b) since that programme has been fully rolled out; and how many of those participants in each such period were mandated to take part in that programme.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186294","186294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999133","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many 999 hoax phone calls have been made in each of the last ten years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186229","186229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999134","2018-11-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings (a) he, (b) Ministers and (c) officials of his Department have had with Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland in the past twelve months on cross border security arrangements after 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186230","186230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999135","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 134595 on Railways: Electrification, what the expected timetable is for introduction of new electric powered trains.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186231","186231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999136","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2018 to Question 182250 on Revenue and Customs: Cumbernauld, what the (a) maximum and (b) minimum duration of any such extension to lease on the HMRC office in Cumbernauld is under the terms of that lease.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186338","186338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999137","2018-11-05","Department for International Trade","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the article entitled UK has rolled over only 14 of 236 EU International Treaties published by the Financial Times on 29 October 2018, how many of the EU free trade agreements the Government has secured agreement to replicate.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186277","186277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999138","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 176432 on Offences against Children, whether any funding requests from police forces for investigations into child sexual exploitation have been rejected by the Government in the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186384","186384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999139","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officers in (a) the Metropolitan Police and (b) other police forces are in teams working solely on preparing for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186385","186385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999140","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he made an assessment of the potential merits of reducing the standard for accreditation for police forensics laboratories; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186386","186386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999141","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the proportion of police laboratories that have achieved accreditation for forensics.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186387","186387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999142","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2018 Question 177666 on Occupational Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure members of the public are aware of the IORP2 Directive on occupational retirement savings.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186293","186293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999143","2018-11-05","Cabinet Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Crown Commercial Service's Transparency data, CCS prompt payment data 2018-19, whether the aggregated totals figure of 196.88 per cent for the percentage of invoices paid within five days is correct; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186191","186191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999144","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether data processed by the Secure Information Exchange Network Application system is owned by Europol.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186388","186388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999145","2018-11-05","Cabinet Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's press release of 10 April 2018, New changes to encourage small businesses to apply for government contracts, what progress he is making on excluding suppliers from major Government procurements if they cannot demonstrate fair and effective payment practices with subcontractors.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186192","186192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999146","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department has collected as part of the Rough Sleeping Initiative.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186183","186183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999147","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK can participate in Europol operational projects after the UK leaves the EU without an adequacy agreement for data sharing.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186389","186389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999148","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of universal credit on the funding available to providers of accommodation through the Severe Weather Emergency Protocol.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186446","186446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999149","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164474 on the Mineworkers’ Pension Scheme, what discussions his Department has had with the trustees of that scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186447","186447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999150","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political and security situation in Cameroon; and what representations his Department is making to the Cameroon Government on those matters.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186347","186347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999151","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to (a) launch and (b) respond to the proposed consultation on the pensions dashboard.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186448","186448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999152","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the factors effecting the UK's position in the G7 growth table.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186449","186449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999153","2018-11-05","Scotland Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in November 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186425","186425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999154","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations she has received from claimants with muscular dystrophy on their personal independence payment assessment; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186178","186178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999155","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on life insurance policies for people suffering from (a) long term medical conditions and (b) muscular dystrophy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186179","186179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999156","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the supply of Nutricia Nutrini Energy Multi Fibre for people requiring percutaneous endoscopic gastrostomy feeding after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186357","186357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999157","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the supply of Nutricia Nutrini Energy Multi Fibre and similar products for those requiring percutaneous endoscopic gastrostomy feeding in the event the the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186358","186358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999158","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Crown Estate on responsibility for (a) land and (b) property held in escheat; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186180","186180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999159","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to support the availability of bleed control kits for police response units.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186335","186335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999160","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the new business rates relief announced in Budget 2018 on local authority finances.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186407","186407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999161","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether local authorities that see a reduction in funding as a result of the change to business rates will receive additional funding from central Government.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186408","186408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999162","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, where the new University Enterprise Zones announced in Budget 2018 will be; and by what process that decision was reached.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186409","186409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999163","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been refused personal independence payments as a result of the past presence rule on residency (a) since 2013 and (b) in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186406","186406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999164","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial support further education and sixth form colleges receive for students who entered the UK via the Syrian Children's Resettlement Scheme.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186410","186410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999165","2018-11-05","Department for International Trade","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to his Department's press release entitled International visits pay off for British business, published on 8 June 2018, what estimate he has made of size of the revenue stream for the public treasury of the Government of Cameroon that is forecast to as a result of the natural gas deal between New Age (African Global Energy) Ltd and the Cameroonian Government announced in that press release.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186257","186257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999166","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in (a) the misuse of public funds and (b) other corrupt practices undertaken by the Government of Cameroon.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186258","186258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999167","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made on identifying a set of metrics to measure the quality of work as recommended by the Matthew Taylor Review of Modern Working Practices.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186253","186253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999168","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to respond to its consultations on (a) employment status, (b) increasing transparency in the labour market, (c) agency workers recommendations and (d) enforcement of employment rights.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186254","186254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999169","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff were employed by the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186255","186255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999170","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to pages 62 to 65 of the February 2018 of the Government response to the Taylor Review of Modern Working Practices, what steps the Government has taken to improve support for self-employed people.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186256","186256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999171","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the gender balance percentage is of full-time permanent contract staff in his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186361","186361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999172","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the gender balance percentage is of temporary contract staff in his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186362","186362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999173","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women were employed in his Department in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186363","186363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999174","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many projects funded by his Department are focused on gender equality programmes.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186364","186364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999175","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the gender balance percentage is of full-time permanent contract staff in his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186365","186365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999176","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2018 to Question 179180 on Saudi Arabia: Conferences, whether representatives of the UK Government attended the future investment initiative conference in Riyadh.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186303","186303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999177","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the gender balance percentage is of temporary contract staff in his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186366","186366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999178","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many women were employed by his Department in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186367","186367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999179","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many projects funded his Department are focused on gender equality programmes.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186368","186368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999180","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to support the imposition of trade sanctions on the state of Myanmar as a result of alleged war crimes being committed by its military on the Rohingya people.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186369","186369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999181","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will draft a resolution at the UN Security Council granting the ICC leave to investigate and prosecute alleged war crimes in Myanmar.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186370","186370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999182","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government is seeking cooperation and coordination with the (a)EU and (b)other multilateral actors on its civilian-military humanitarian and peacekeeping missions in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186371","186371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999183","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has for continued cooperation with the EU in Mali.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186372","186372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999184","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has for continued cooperation with the EU in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186373","186373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999185","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to help rebuild the Libyan economy following that country’s civil war.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186374","186374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999186","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reinstating the Migration Impact Fund.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186421","186421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999187","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise the findings and recommendations of the UN Human Rights Council Group of Eminent Experts Report on Yemen with his counterparts in (a) Saudi Arabia, (b) the United Arab Emirates and (c) the Yemeni Government.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186375","186375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999188","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on the actions agreed at the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting 2018.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186274","186274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999189","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the accident figures on the M20 motorway between Junctions 8 and 9 for September and October (a) 2018 and (b) 2017 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186152","186152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999190","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the progress of road works on the M20 between Junctions 3 and 6; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186153","186153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999191","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with UN Special Envoy Martin Griffiths on a new UN resolution calling for a ceasefire in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186177","186177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999192","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the steps taken by his Department to help veterans suffering from post-traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186223","186223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999193","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2018 to Question 182229 on Children: Maintenance, if she will publish those same figures for Inverclyde constituency.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186382","186382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999194","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Government press release entitled PM pledges action on suicide to mark World Mental Health Day, published on 9 October 2018, what assessment he has made of the benefits throughout the UK of the extra money announced for the Samaritans charity over the next four years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186224","186224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999195","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has has made of the effect of the implementation of the general data protection regulation on administrative operations within the NHS.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186225","186225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999196","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list the recipients of LIBOR funding since the inception of the grant scheme in 2012 by (a) country of the UK and (b) sector.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186226","186226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999197","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation, of 17 May 2018, Official Report, column 241WH, what information his Department holds on the (a) number of speaking events blocked by a university or students’ union, (b) books removed from university libraries and (c) changes to courses due to changes in equalities guidance.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186352","186352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999198","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost was of support to asylum seekers whose case has taken more than 52 weeks to resolve in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186353","186353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999199","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Afghan counterpart on human rights and religious freedom in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186227","186227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999200","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made HMRC's readiness for the UK to leave the EU without a Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186354","186354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999201","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the consultation on the Shared Prosperity Fund has not yet been launched; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186355","186355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999202","2018-11-05","Wales Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what specific and technical guidance has been provided to (a) charities, (b) local authorities and (c) the Welsh Government on how to apply for money under the funding guarantee for ERDF programmes in the event no deal being reached with the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186356","186356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999203","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) holdings were tested for bovine tuberculosis, (b) animals were tested in each of those holdings and (c) of those animals tested positive using the interferon gamma test in each county of England in 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186168","186168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999204","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce an obligatory tenancy deposit scheme for commercial premises with a rateable value of £51,000 or less.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186170","186170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999205","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on people affected by the 2019 Loan Charge.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186275","186275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999206","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of the use of pilot programmes to demonstrate the value of rapid diagnostics in tackling antimicrobial resistance.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186348","186348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999207","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ask NHS England to make tackling healthcare acquired infections a priority in the upcoming long term plan.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186349","186349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999208","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what additional (a) security and (b) other staff are planned to be recruited to deliver the zero tolerance approach towards violence against NHS employees.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186330","186330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999209","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the number of locum (a) doctors and (b) nurses are affected by the 2019 Loan Charge.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186276","186276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999210","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a nationally mandated optimal blood cultures pathway.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186350","186350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999211","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department has allocated to (a) support and (b) treat people who indicate they are addicted to gambling or have suffered gambling related harm in (i) 2018-19 and (ii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186383","186383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999212","2018-11-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has held with representatives of the (a) EU and (b) Governments of EU Member States on the potential consequences of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on visa-free travel between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186171","186171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999213","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued to housing associations on the proximity of vulnerable people in nearby accommodation when placing known problem tenants.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186172","186172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999214","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government recognises (a) Ranil Wickramasinghe and his Cabinet or (b) Mahinda Rajapaksa and his Cabinet as the Prime Minister and Government of Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186259","186259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999215","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's consultation on powers for dealing with unauthorised development and encampments, which closed on 15 June 2018, when his Department plans to respond to that consultation.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186273","186273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999216","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any funds allocated to Sri Lanka between 2016 and 2019 through the Conflict Stability and Security Fund have been withdrawn because of human rights concerns.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186260","186260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999217","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his UN counterpart on accelerating the work of the investigative team on the enslavement of Yazidi women and girls by Daesh.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186261","186261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999218","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many experts recruited under the prevention of sexual violence initiative are deployed to the Rohingya refugee camps in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186262","186262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999219","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the Democratic Republic of Congo on (a) changes in the level of documented cases of sexual violence in that country in 2017 and (b) the number of those cases attributed to the Congolese armed forces and police.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186263","186263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999220","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason the UK does not contribute to the UN trust fund for victims of sexual violence; and whether he plans to review that decision.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186264","186264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999221","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to widen access to university for children who have been in care.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186173","186173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999222","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Chinese government on that government's decision to legalise the use of products derived from (a) tigers and (b) rhinoceros horn in medical centres.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186265","186265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999223","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is his policy to support the governments of (a) Germany and (b) France on the potential merits of a coordinated European position on arms sales to Saudi Arabia for use in the Yemen conflict.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186266","186266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999224","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the size of Tahrir al-Sham in Idlib; and what proportion of the overall Syrian rebel strength that groups represents in that area.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186267","186267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999225","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is his policy to support the inclusion of Mongolia in the six-party talks on the denuclearisation of the Korean peninsula.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186268","186268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999226","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Mongolia on (a) the protection of human rights and (b) the reduction in the level of poverty in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186269","186269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999227","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent progress he has made on the restoration of the Prisoner Transfer Agreement with Pakistan.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186270","186270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999228","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to ensure the implementation of NICE guidance on antenatal care for (a) twin and (b) triplet pregnancies in maternity units in England.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186351","186351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999229","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the accessibility of consular support for UK citizens that are victims of forced marriage in Pakistan.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186271","186271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999230","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the US administration has supplied his Department with the United States’ Middle East peace plan.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186272","186272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999231","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there is a prescribed test for determining whether an application is deemed to be complex and therefore falls outside Home Office service standards.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186166","186166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999232","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the annual surpluses to Government from the Mineworkers Pension Fund in each year since 1994.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186222","186222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999233","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with representatives of automotive companies on the effect of the rise in diesel tax rates introduced in April 2018 on (a) automotive sales and (b) the sustainability of the automotive industry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186174","186174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999234","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding his Department allocated to Hull to prepare for its status as 2017 City of Culture; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186175","186175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999235","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2017 to Question 120798 on Speed Limits, when he plans to publish the final Atkins report on 20mph limit (signed only) zones; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186325","186325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999236","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the Atkins report on the effectiveness of 20mph speed limit (signed only) schemes has not yet been published.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186326","186326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999237","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will introduce legislative proposals to make it an offence to (a) own and (b) supply GPS jammers.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186176","186176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999238","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had since 2014 with (a) Atkins, (b) Aecom and (c) Professor Mike Maher on the research it commissioned on the effectiveness of 20mph speed limit (signed only) schemes.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186327","186327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999239","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2018 to Question 169109 on Drugs, on what date during the financial planning process for 2019-20 the level of funding will be determined.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186290","186290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999240","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2018 to Question 169109 on drugs, what level of funding NHS England has proposed for the financial planning process for products undergoing review by the prioritisation process in 2019-20.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186291","186291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999241","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2018 to Question 142774 on Clinical Priorities Advisory Group, what progress has been made by NHS England on the development of the new pilot assurance process to assess whether new treatments are being equitably provided to patients across England.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186292","186292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999242","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the £2 million allocated in Budget 2018 for the city centre in Belfast following the fire at Bank Buildings in August 2018 will be distributed.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186359","186359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999243","2018-11-05","Scotland Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what representations he has made to the Chancellor of the Exchequer on (a) financial and (b) other support for fire-hit businesses in the Sauchiehall Street area of Glasgow.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186360","186360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999244","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times aircraft were intercepted by Quick Reaction Alert flights in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018 to 31 October.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186336","186336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999245","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK citizens renounced their citizenship in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186337","186337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999246","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the tax gap between tax owed and tax paid by private landlords.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186184","186184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999247","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has received a request from Greater Manchester for mayoral precept powers to fund bus franchising.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186412","186412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999248","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that guidance given to NHS and social care commissioners on how to commission children’s palliative care reflects National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidance and quality standards.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186396","186396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999249","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow East of 26 September 2018, reference DL1987.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186426","186426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999250","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to allocate unused money from the Integrated Activity Fund.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186434","186434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999251","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many additional people with mental health conditions he expects will be in work by 2023-24 as a result of decisions taken in Budget 2018.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186278","186278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999252","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of the change in the employment rate between 2017-18 and 2023-24 for people with (a) schizophrenia, (b) bipolar disorder, (c) depression and (d) mental health conditions as a whole.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186279","186279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999253","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many additional schools he estimates will have mental health support teams and specialist crisis teams in (a) Windsor, (b) the South East and (c) the UK by 2023-24.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186280","186280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999254","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many additional people he estimates will retain employment as a result of the individual placement support programme in (a) Windsor and (b) the South East by 2023-24.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186281","186281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999255","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much additional funding there will be for children and young people’s mental health crisis teams in (a) Windsor and (b) the South East by 2023-24.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186282","186282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999256","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the additional mental health specialist ambulances that will be in service by in (a) Windsor and (b) the South East and (c) the UK by 2023-24.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186283","186283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999257","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 5.10 of Budget 2018, how many A&Es in the Windsor constituency have been identified as major centres which will receive funding for comprehensive mental health support.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186284","186284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999258","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of how many additional crisis cafes will be in service in (a) Windsor, (b) the South East and (c) the UK by 2023-24.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186285","186285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999259","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of how many schools-based mental health support teams and specialist crisis teams for young people there will be in (a) Windsor and (b) the South East and (c) the UK by 2023-24.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186286","186286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999260","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the process for enabling young people to transition to adult mental health services at the age of 18; whether he plans to put in place a developmental approach to such transition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186169","186169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999261","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Budget 2018 paragraph 5.10 on mental health funding, what estimate he has made of the savings that will accrue to the public purse as a result of pressure being taken off (a) accident and emergency, (b) police, (c) probation and (d) social services by 2023-24.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186287","186287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999262","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to announce which projects will be run by DLT Field Labs to test the potential of distributed ledger technologies.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186288","186288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999263","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Budget 2018 paragraph 4.26 on Cryptoassets Taskforce, if he will list those actions that will allow innovators to thrive in the cryptoasset sector.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186289","186289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999264","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Special Investigation Unit in Bahrain receives training from organisations funded by the UK Government.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186435","186435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999265","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the case of Bahraini death row inmate and torture victim Maher Al-Khabbaz has been recorded in line with his Department's torture and mistreatment reporting guidance.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186436","186436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999266","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to promote cultural diplomacy.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186440","186440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999267","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his oral contribution of 29 October 2018, Official Report column 665, whether Glasgow qualifies for similar new support as a result of the two large fires that disrupted economic activity in that city centre.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186429","186429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999268","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Government held its most recent discussions with the Government of Myanmar on the Rohingya crisis and status of refugees in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186413","186413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999269","2018-11-05","Cabinet Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2018 to Question 183994 on Electronic Government: Proof of Identity, for what reason that Answer did not provide an average cost per user to verify identity across those private sector identity providers.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186439","186439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999270","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October to Question 183290 on Rehabilitation, when the review of community performance reporting was commissioned; who is undertaking that review; and what the (a) terms of reference and (b) time frame are for that review.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186241","186241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999271","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what research the Government has (a) undertaken and (b) commissioned on fracking and subsidence in former coal mining areas.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186390","186390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999272","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when her Department plans to respond to the letter of 26 July 2018 from the rt. hon. Member for Birkenhead to the Minister of State for Disabled People on the Government’s response to the Work and Pensions Committee report on employment support for carers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186218","186218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999273","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his oral contribution of 29 October 2018, Official Report, column 658, whether the donation of £10 million to the Armed Forces Covenant Fund Trust raises the Government commitment in perpetuity to £20 million per annum in support of the Covenant.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186240","186240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999274","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled, Understanding the performance and potential of specialist hospitals,  published by the Innovation Agency and UCLPartners Academic Health Science Partnership in October 2018 , whether he has plans to encourage a closer working relationship between academic health science networks and specialist hospitals to improve performance in the NHS.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186379","186379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999275","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people accessed eye movement desensitisation and reprocessing therapy on the NHS in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186380","186380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999276","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the blind person's allowance, what the criteria for for people register with (a) central government and (b) local authorities as severely sight-impaired.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186219","186219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999277","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of youth unemployment was in (a) May 2010 and (b) May 2018.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186298","186298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999278","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what training his Department provides to NHS doctors on (a) eye movement desensitisation and (b) reprocessing treatment for cases of post traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186381","186381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999279","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of unemployment was in (a) May 2010 and (b) May 2018.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186299","186299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999280","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he has made an assessment of the implications for his Department’s policies of the recommendations contained in the Independent Monitoring Board's Charter Flights Annual Report of (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186411","186411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999281","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of youth unemployment was in Suffolk in (a) May 2010 and (b) May 2018.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186300","186300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999282","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of unemployment was in Suffolk in (a) May 2010 and (b) May 2018.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186301","186301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999283","2018-11-05","Department for International Development","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the Rohingya community is party to negotiations on the repatriation of that community.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186422","186422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999284","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to table 2.1 of Budget 2018, what estimate he has made of the cost of the public purse of (a) increasing the personal allowance to £12,500 and (b) increasing the higher rate threshold to £50,000, in each year of the forecast period.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186423","186423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999285","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what definition of vulnerability her Department plans to use for claimants that will be transfer to universal credit under managed migration.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186316","186316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999286","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what procedures her Department has put in place to identify people that are classified as (a) vulnerable and (b) having complex needs in relation to the managed migration of claimants onto universal credit.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186317","186317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999287","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students in (a) state funded schools and (b) independent schools studied (i) art and design, (ii) design and technology, (iii) drama, (iv) media, film and TV studies, (v) music and (vi) performing and expressive arts subjects to GCSE level in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186431","186431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999288","2018-11-05","Cabinet Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many communications specialists are employed at the National Cyber Security Centre; and what the total salary cost of those specialists is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186193","186193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999289","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to Homes England's Strategic Plan, what targets have been set for Homes England in relation to affordable housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186185","186185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999290","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184429 on Public Sector: Pensions, whether the effect on budges of the previously envisaged cost was communicated to police forces in advance of the Written Statement of 6 September 2018 on quadrennial valuations of the public service pension schemes.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186391","186391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999291","2018-11-05","Cabinet Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Question 61 of oral evidence given on 25 June 2018 to the Joint Committee on the National Security Strategy by Mr  Ciaran Martin, what the specific campaigns are that form the duties of communications specialists in the National Cyber Security Centre.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186194","186194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999292","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for each available year, under the Child Maintenance Service, how many claims from a non-resident parent for a recalculation of maintenance as a result of a change in the income of that parent were (a) received; and (b) successful in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186376","186376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999293","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will bring forward legislative proposals to require TV broadcasters to provide Audio Description Access.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186377","186377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999294","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment has his Department made of the effect of commercial fishing regulations on the tourism fishing sector.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186424","186424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999295","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the granting of asylum to Asia Bibi following her acquital of the charge of blasphemy.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186154","186154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999296","2018-11-05","Cabinet Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the (a) birth and (b) infant mortality rate in (i) England, (ii) London and (iii) the London Borough of Lewisham for each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186401","186401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999297","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of health visitors in (a) England, (b) London and (c) the London Borough of Lewisham in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186402","186402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999298","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 146 of the Office for Budget Responsibility's Economic and Fiscal Outlook 2018, published in 29 October 2018, if she will make an assessment of the contribution of (a) the cost of administering universal credit, (b) policy changes affecting the level payable under universal credit and (c) any other factors to universal credit becoming more expensive than the legacy system would have been from 2019-20 to 2022-23.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186220","186220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999299","2018-11-05","Attorney General","2018-10-31","To ask the Attorney General, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186195","186195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999300","2018-11-05","Cabinet Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186196","186196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999301","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the capacity of broadcasters to meet their access service obligations of their being permitted to spend only a maximum of one per cent of their turnover on doing so.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186378","186378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999302","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186197","186197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999303","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186198","186198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999304","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186199","186199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999305","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186200","186200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999306","2018-11-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186201","186201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999307","2018-11-05","Department for International Development","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186202","186202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999308","2018-11-05","Department for International Trade","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186203","186203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999309","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186204","186204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999310","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186205","186205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999311","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186206","186206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999312","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186207","186207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999313","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186208","186208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999314","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186209","186209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999315","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a list of the bids the Government has received from local authorities under the scheme announced in Budget 2017 to increase housing revenue account borrowing headroom.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186186","186186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999316","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees relating to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186210","186210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999317","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department is lead department on the Festival of Britain funding.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186397","186397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999318","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how money allocated to the Festival of Britain is planned to be distributed; and whether those funds will be distributed to agencies throughout the UK.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186398","186398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999319","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Independent Review of Building Regulations and Fire Safety: Final Report, published by his Department in May 2018, when he plans to publish a full response to that review.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186187","186187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999320","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the announced Festival of Britain is not money re-allocated from existing budgets.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186399","186399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999321","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it Government policy to enable employers to make (a) the required Settled Status payments directly to his Department on behalf of employees and (b) ensure that such support is not treated as a benefit in kind.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186400","186400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999322","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to table A.1 on page 231 of the Office for Budget Responsibility's Economic and fiscal outlook: October 2018 publication, what estimate he has made of the loss to the public purse of revenue arising from the sale of student loans in each year of the forecast period.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186328","186328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999323","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of using the kWh/m2/year rating as the principle energy efficiency rating for future energy efficiency regulations.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186430","186430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999324","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the scheme announced in Budget 2017 to increase housing revenue account borrowing headroom, if he will publish (a) the additional borrowing headroom and (b) any additional linked grant funding applied for by councils under that scheme, by local authority.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186188","186188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999325","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many delay repay claims have been made by rail passengers since that scheme was introduced.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186394","186394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999326","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of computers available to claimants in Jobcentre Plus have in-built access to assistive technology.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186221","186221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999327","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding her Department has allocated to organisations that provide support to deaf people in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186395","186395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999328","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure thta the Tuberous Sclerosis Association is able to submit evidence on behalf of (a) patients and (b) families to NHS England’s specialised commissioning relative prioritisation process assessment of everolimus for refractory epilepsy related to tuberous sclerosis complex.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186344","186344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999329","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what processes are in place to ensure that NHS England’s clinical priorities advisory group receives the views of (a) patients and (b) patient families as part of the specialised commissioning relative prioritisation process.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186345","186345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999330","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what status NHS England’s clinical priorities advisory group confers on evidence that has (a) not been published in an academic journal, (b) been presented at an academic conference and (c) resulted from clinical trials during the specialised commissioning relative prioritisation process.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186346","186346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999331","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the figures in the table entitled Exchequer Impact (£m) on page 5 of his Department's document, Budget 2018: policy costings, published on 29 October 2018, if he will publish a separate figure for the Exchequer impact of the increase in the personal allowance to £12,500 for each of those financial years.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186304","186304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999332","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the figures in the table entitled Exchequer Impact (£m) on page 5 of his Department's document, Budget 2018: policy costings, published on 29 October 2018, if he will publish a separate figure for the Exchequer effect of the increase in the higher rate threshold to £50,000 for each of those financial years.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186305","186305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999333","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals after the UK has left the EU on graphic warnings on firework packaging on the health dangers from the misuse of pyrotechnics.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186165","186165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999334","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the extension of permitted development rights on the amount of funding made available for local areas through planning obligations.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186189","186189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999335","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Government's proposals to extend permitted development rights to include upwards extensions to free standing blocks of flats over five storeys, what assessment he has made of the (a) consistency of those proposals with the recommendations of the Hackitt Review of Building Regulations and Fire Safety and (b) effect of those proposals on fire safety in high rise blocks.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186190","186190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999336","2018-11-05","Department for International Development","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the accuracy of recent reports by the International Rescue Committee of atrocities in South Cameroon and the displacement of 250,000 people in that region.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186312","186312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999337","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of access for disabled and partially sighted people at Wolverhampton Railway Station.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186313","186313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999338","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding the Government makes available to (a) install step free access and (b) otherwise improve disabled access at train stations in England.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186314","186314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999339","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many stations in England (a) do and (b) do not have step free access; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186315","186315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999340","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 78 of the Red Book and page 11 of the policy costings for Budget 2018, what the schedule is for the start and end of (a) the pilot for the managed migration of people claiming legacy claimants to universal credit and (b) the managed migration as a whole.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186339","186339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999341","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, at what level work allowances are planned to be set at from April 2019 as a result of the change to work allowances announced in Budget 2018 for (a) lone parents (i) with and (ii) without housing costs, (b) couples with children (A) with and (B) without housing costs, (c) single people without children (1) with and (2) without housing costs, (d) couples without children people (i) with and (ii) without housing costs and (e) people with limited capability for work (A) with and (B) without housing costs.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186340","186340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999342","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to deliver the funding promised to South Yorkshire to improve journey times along the Hope Valley Line.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186321","186321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999343","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department’s press release entitled Government announces new housing measures, published 1 October 2018, how many houses of the 300,000 houses are planned to be built in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186322","186322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999344","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will take steps to establish a network of wildflower paths to help reverse the decline in the UK bee population.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186323","186323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999345","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference paragraph 5.38 on page 78 of the Budget 2018 Red Book, what estimate she has made of the effect on the public purse of the delay until April 2020 of the reduction of the level of earnings to be disregarded under the surplus earnings rule from £2,500 to £300.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186341","186341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999346","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 65 of the Budget 2018 Red Book, what proportion of the £430 million to be allocated to road maintenance including potholes is planned to be spent in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186324","186324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999347","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer given on 25 July 2018 to Question 164527 on Buildings: Insulation, whether the Government has made an estimate of the number of (a) schools, (b) care homes, (c) hospitals and (c) other high-risk buildings that might have combustible cladding or insulation.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186414","186414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999348","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the level of fire risk posed in cases of combustible cladding is used on (a) schools, (b) hospitals and (c) care homes.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186415","186415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999349","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in England and Wales of any height are estimated to have combustible (a) cladding and (b) insulation.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186416","186416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999350","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164527 on Buildings: Insulation, what estimate he has made of the number of hospitals in England and Wales of any height that have combustible (a) cladding and (b) insulation.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186417","186417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999351","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer given on 25 July 2018 to Question 164527, what estimate he has made of the number of care homes in England and Wales of any height that have combustible (a) cladding and (b) insulation.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186418","186418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999352","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the causes of radicalisation of lone-actors in relation to extreme right-wing terrorism in the UK.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186392","186392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999353","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164527 on Buildings: Insulation, whether the Government plans to ban the use of combustible materials on (a) schools, (b) hospitals and (c) care homes.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186419","186419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999354","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made on the potential economic cost to businesses who transfer data across borders in Europe in the event of the UK Government not reaching an adequacy decision with the EU before 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186250","186250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999355","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of UK businesses that engage in data transfers with nations within the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186251","186251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999356","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the potential timeframe for the UK to reach a data adequacy agreement with the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186252","186252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999357","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the appointment process was for the chief executive of the Student Loans Company.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186213","186213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999358","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the appropriateness of the Student Loans Company gathering evidence from applicants' social media as part of its loan approval process.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186214","186214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999359","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions his Department has had with the Student Loans Company on the parameters of that company's gathering of evidence from applicants' social media as part of its loan approval process.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186215","186215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999360","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164527 on Buildings: Insulation, whether the Government has made an estimate of the number of (a) schools, (b) care homes and (c) hospitals that are partially clad in combustible material such as ACM cladding.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186420","186420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999361","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions his Department has had with the Office for Students on the effect on student protections of the Student Loans Company gathering evidence from applicants' social media as part of its loan approval process.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186216","186216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999362","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the number of pieces of violent extremist content aligned to the extreme right that were taken down from social media platforms in the latest year for which data is available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186393","186393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999363","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what responsibility clinical commissioning groups have for funding family history clinics for people with a family history of breast cancer.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186437","186437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999364","2018-11-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when UK citizens living in the EU will have certainty about their rights after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186441","186441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999365","2018-11-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether UK citizens living in the EU will have their rights guaranteed in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186442","186442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999366","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the accessibility of family history clinics for people with a family history of breast cancer across England.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186438","186438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999367","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his oral contribution of 29 October 2018, Official Report, column 664, Financial Statement, which aspects of the Belfast Region City Deal will require a functioning Northern Ireland Executive for their implementation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186233","186233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999368","2018-11-05","Prime Minister","2018-10-31","To ask the Prime Minister, what plans she has to visit Northern Ireland before Christmas 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186234","186234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999369","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made in assessing the business case submitted by the Police Service of Northern Ireland for additional resources required for preparations for the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement on the timescale for his Department making a final decision on that matter.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186235","186235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999370","2018-11-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to visit the land border between Northern Ireland and Ireland before Christmas 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186236","186236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999371","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that hospices throughout the UK will be zero rated from VAT after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186237","186237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999372","2018-11-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much has been paid in salaries to Members of the Legislative Assembly since its collapse in January 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186238","186238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999373","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2018 to Question 180694 on Alcoholic Drinks: Rehabilitation, how many in-patient beds are commissioned for the treatment of substance misuse in (a) England, (b) London and (c) Suffolk.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186302","186302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999374","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of claimants of legacy benefits who will migrate to universal credit without transitional protection.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186342","186342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999375","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to help energy suppliers improve gas storage to minimise the risk of a National Grid gas deficit warning this winter.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186427","186427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999377","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made on securing compensation from the Libyan authorities for the victims of Gaddafi-sponsored IRA terrorism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186239","186239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999378","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to line 15 of table 2.1 on page 36 of the Budget 2018 Red Book, for what reasons he estimates that the revised implementation schedule for universal credit will result in increased revenue for the Exchequer between 2020-21 and 2023-24.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186343","186343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999379","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) rheumatology healthcare professionals in the NHS and (b) the provision of treatment for people with rheumatology of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186432","186432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999381","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the new prisons planned to be built at (a) Glen Parva and (b) Wellingborough will be (a) operated and (b) managed by a private company.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186403","186403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999382","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 31 October 2018, Official Report, what the evidential basis is for the Prime Minister's statement that £1.4 billion of additional funding was committed to schools in this financial year.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186329","186329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999383","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance he has issued to employers on how to check the entitlement to work of EU citizens in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186212","186212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999384","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the £475 million for schools capital funding in his 2018 Autumn Budget to FE Colleges.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186217","186217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999385","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Intellectual Property Office in helping to keep new drug prices at affordable levels; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186161","186161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999386","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to row 15 of table 2.1 of Budget 2018, what methodology his Department used to calculate the cost savings arising from the revised implementation schedule for universal credit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186155","186155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999387","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if she will publish the top 10 drugs by purchased by his Department in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186162","186162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999388","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason the ministerial responsibilities of Edward Argar are not listed on the relevant Ministry of Justice web page.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186404","186404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999389","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the cost to the NHS of Harvoni; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186163","186163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999390","2018-11-05","Department for International Trade","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what preparations have been made for the level of representation the UK will require at the World Trade Organisation after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186242","186242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999391","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of levels of racism on modern slavery and human trafficking in the African Great Lakes Region.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186243","186243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999392","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of patients recommended the drug Harvoni by medical practitioners who have been denied access to the drug on grounds of affordability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186164","186164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999393","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his South African counterpart on the provision of justice as a result of the attacks on South African farmers.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186244","186244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999394","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress her Department has made on implementing the recommendations of the report, Thriving at Work: a review of mental health and employers, published by her Department in October 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186308","186308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999395","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department plans to make a decision on whether to grant right of abode to former British-Hong Kong servicemen.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186245","186245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999396","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to enable Christians to remain in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186246","186246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999397","2018-11-06","Department for International Development","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the description on 30 June 2018 by Mahmoud Al-Habbash, an advisor to the  PA President, of Israelis and Jews as the culture of Satan.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186156","186156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999398","2018-11-06","Department for International Development","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the assertion on 5 October 2018 on official PA TV, that Jews dance and live on the body parts of others, and on the blood of others.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186157","186157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999399","2018-11-05","Department for International Development","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the assertion reported on 19 October 2018 on official PA TV, that Jews didn't learn from what Hitler did to them.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186158","186158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999400","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many businesses have adopted the core standards set out in the report, Thriving at Work: a review of mental health and employers, published by her Department in October 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186309","186309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999401","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many large businesses have adopted the enhanced standards set out in the report, Thriving at Work: a review of mental health and employers, published by her Department in October 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186310","186310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999402","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Tanzanian counterpart on reducing poaching activity in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186247","186247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999403","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date a Minister in his Department last visited the Republic of Burundi; and what issues were discussed during that visit.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186248","186248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999404","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the visits he has undertaken to (a) adult mental health services and (b) children and young people's mental health services since he took office.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186311","186311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999405","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184345 on Serious Violence Taskforce: Social Media, what assessment he has made of the suitability of the content hosted by (a) Kik Messenger, (b) Snapchat, (c) Telegram, (d) Viber, (e) Wickr and (f) Whatsapp on their encrypted messaging apps in relation to county lines activity.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186159","186159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999406","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date a Minister in his Department last visited the Republic of Tanzania; and what issues were discussed during that visit.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186249","186249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999407","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2018 to Question 183520 on Ukraine: aviation, when he last communicated with the families of the victims of flight MH17; and if he will ensure that those families are updated on the progress of that investigation.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186318","186318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999408","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2018 to Question 183881 on chronic obstructive pulmonary disease, what steps he is taking to tackle the increase in the number of people diagnosed with that disease.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186232","186232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999409","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184345 on Serious Violence Taskforce: Social Media, how he plans to develop engagement with (a) Kik Messenger, (b) Snapchat, (c) Telegram, (d) Viber, (e) Wickr and (f) WhatsApp in relation to the use of encrypted messaging apps for county lines activity.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186160","186160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999410","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2018 to Question 182193 on Research and Development Expenditure Credit, how the performance of the Research and Development Allowance is assessed; why the data on the amount of relief claimed cannot be identified; and if there are any plans to improve the technical specification of the system for capturing data on that allowance.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186319","186319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999411","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-31","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184368 on Public Sector Exit Payments, whether the affirmative regulations referred to are the same as the necessary regulations which were reported in the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 1447 on Public Sector: Redundancy Pay, as being currently in the process of drafting; and whether the regulations have now been drafted.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186167","186167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999412","2018-11-05","Cabinet Office","2018-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2018 to Question 182765 on Harvey Weinstein, for what reasons the Forfeiture Committee is unlikely to take action to remove the honorary CBE awarded to Harvey Weinstein until the end of legal proceedings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186320","186320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999413","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on extending the scope of his consultation on cycling offences; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186149","186149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999414","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 7193, what progress he has made on the review of the maximum penalties for driving offences resulting in death and or serious injury.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186150","186150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999415","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will include the Association of Residential Managing Agents in his working group on leasehold reform and the regulation of managing agents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186151","186151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997486","2018-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","Whether he plans to support sanctions on the leaders of the Myanmar armed forces and Government as a result of alleged recent war crimes in that country.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907359","907359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997487","2018-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","What discussions he has had with his Ukrainian counterpart on the political and security situation in eastern Ukraine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907360","907360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997488","2018-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","What recent progress has been made in securing support for a marine protected area in the Weddell Sea.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907361","907361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997489","2018-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","What recent discussions he has had with his Tunisian counterpart on that country’s diplomatic and economic relationship with the UK.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907362","907362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997490","2018-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","What recent representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on communities threatened by demolition and forcible transfer in the West Bank.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907363","907363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997491","2018-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","What diplomatic support his Department provides to the English-speaking community in Cameroon.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907364","907364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997492","2018-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","What recent steps he has taken to promote human rights in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907365","907365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997493","2018-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","Whether he has made a recent assessment of the effectiveness of the processes for enabling member states to leave the EU.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907366","907366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997494","2018-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","What recent assessment he has made of the political and security situation in Myanmar.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907367","907367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997543","2018-11-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department takes to (a) support fertility treatment in the NHS and (b) ensure NHS England and Clinical Commissioning Groups deliver fertility treatments in line with NICE guidelines.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185587","185587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997544","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the decision by G4S to refuse to recognise the PCS Union on the terms and conditions of employment of those employed by G4S in the justice sector.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185673","185673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997545","2018-11-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the (a) Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) Coventry City Council on the future funding for free music festivals in Coventry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185491","185491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997546","2018-11-01","Department for Education","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has received representations on the exclusion of Christianity from the religious studies syllabus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185597","185597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997547","2018-11-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Healthy Homes and Buildings all party parliament group green paper Building our Future: Laying the Foundations for Healthy Homes and Buildings; and what steps the Government is taking to improve the overall standard of new and existing homes to ensure that people live in comfortable, warm, dry, well-lit and well designed homes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185598","185598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997548","2018-11-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will hold discussions with the all-party group on Healthy Homes and Buildings on the (a) extent of the problems caused by poor quality homes and buildings and (b) steps that are being taken to incentivise home providers and builders to build and retrofit homes to the highest standards.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185599","185599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997549","2018-11-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will (a) work with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government and (b) establish a cross-departmental committee on health and buildings.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185600","185600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997550","2018-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times his Department has (a) received a request for and (b) suggested the voluntary downgrading of an employee; when that request or suggestion took place and for what reason; for what reason voluntary downgrading was (i) applied and (ii) rejected; and whether his Department (A) applied and (B) declined pay protection in the three years prior to 3 July 2017.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185601","185601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997551","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the German government on broadening access for other Europeans to its thalidomide fund.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185531","185531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997552","2018-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost of not taking into account jointly-owned homes when assessing the eligibility of victims of domestic violence for legal aid.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185674","185674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997553","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the cost per prison place of a prison built with (a) with private finance and (b) funds from the public purse.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185675","185675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997554","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of his Department's contracts which are open for tender have been subject to bids from companies that are under Serious Fraud Office investigation for overcharging his Department.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185676","185676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997555","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2018 to Question 173561, what other agreements have been made under the Scotland Act 1998 (Agency Arrangements) (Specification) Order 2018; and whether the Scottish Government has advised it will ask for further agreements.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185566","185566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997556","2018-11-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of planning laws to protect wildlife habitats.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185552","185552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997557","2018-11-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect of increasing the transition period after the UK leaves the EU on the UK's ability to negotiate preferential trade agreements with third countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185602","185602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997558","2018-11-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will ensure that in further negotiations with the EU that the UK will not accept a border down the Irish Sea which will separate Northern Ireland from the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185603","185603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997559","2018-11-05","Prime Minister","2018-10-30","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to the reported comments of Syed Kamall MEP, on 24 October 2018, what representations she has made to her counterpart in the European Parliament on this matter.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185805","185805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997560","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of reports that Uighur Muslims in China have been detained for unwanted blood, tissue and DNA tests.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185636","185636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997561","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the legal framework governing the sale of nitrous oxide for the protection of public health and safety.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185736","185736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997562","2018-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with large clothing companies based in the EU who have stores in the UK on their future relationship with the UK after the UK leaves the European Union.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185560","185560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997563","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how he plans to assess the effectiveness of his Department's implementation of the recommendations that are forthcoming from the Committee on Climate Change in their response to the IPCC report on global warming of 1.5 degrees.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185489","185489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997564","2018-11-05","Attorney General","2018-10-30","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to support the pro bono work of lawyers.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185735","185735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997565","2018-11-01","Department for Transport","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the cost of CCTV in taxis and private hire vehicles on the vehicle owners.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185618","185618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997566","2018-11-01","Treasury","2018-10-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the funding allocated by the EU to underwrite successful bids by UK organisations to competitive EU grant programmes, including Horizon2020, will be funded from (a) UKRI’s annual budget allocation or (b) additional funding  allocated by his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185619","185619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997567","2018-11-01","Treasury","2018-10-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to make any payments to the European Union and its institutions after 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185665","185665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997568","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 139 of the Office for Budget Responsibility’s report entitled Economic and Fiscal Outlook October 2018, published in October 2018, CM9713, what proportion of the £1.5 billion allocated to the Brexit funding pot will be spent in 2018-19.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185719","185719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997569","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of building the new prison at Glen Parva.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185677","185677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997570","2018-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the public purse of legal aid for bereaved families for inquests under the exceptional case funding scheme in the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185678","185678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997572","2018-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse was for legal aid funding for inquests under the exceptional case funding scheme in the last five years was; and how many applications for that funding were (a) made, (b) granted and (c) denied broken down by reason for refusal in the same period.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185679","185679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997573","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of applications for exceptional case funding for legal aid for inquests that have been refused and subsequently granted following an appeal.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185680","185680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997574","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time between an application for legal aid for inquests under the exceptional case funding scheme and a decision made was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185681","185681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997575","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the annual spend by state bodies for their own legal representation at article two inquests in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185682","185682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997576","2018-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of his Department's annual spend on legal representation for prisons and probation staff at inquests on deaths in prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185683","185683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997577","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release of 19 July 2018, New relationships and health education in schools, what progress his Department is making on implementing compulsory health education in schools by September 2020.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185582","185582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997578","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to ensure that Ofsted school inspections include an assessment of pupil wellbeing and mental health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185583","185583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997579","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Prime Minister’s announcement of 10 October 2018 during the Downing Street reception to mark World Mental Health Day that the Government will provide schools with an approved framework which can help them with measuring all aspects of their students’ health, including mental wellbeing, what progress his Department is making on developing that framework; and when he plans to publish that framework.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185584","185584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997580","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training will be provided for new and existing teachers to ensure that they can deliver the new relationships and health education in schools announced in July 2018; and whether he plans to allocate extra resources for that training.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185585","185585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997581","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training and resources will be provided for senior leadership teams in schools to ensure (a) priority for and (b) a whole school approach to the new relationships and health education in schools announced in July 2018.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185586","185586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997582","2018-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that progress is made on implementing the recommendations made to the UK in 2017 under the Universal Periodic Review process on children's rights and the elimination of child poverty.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185684","185684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997583","2018-11-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, in the continued absence of a functioning Northern Ireland Government, if she will meet with the Permanent Secretaries of the Northern Ireland Executive to discuss the implementation of the recommendations of the Hart Report of 20 January 2017 on compensation for victims and survivors of historical institutional abuse in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185541","185541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997584","2018-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 178349 on Prisons: Private Sector and with reference to paragraph 5.28 of the Budget 2018 setting out the allocation of Government funding for the building of HMP Glen Parva, how the construction of that prison will be funded.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185685","185685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997585","2018-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 1.51 of the Budget 2018, whether his Department plans to build new prisons using private finance.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185686","185686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997586","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to line 40, urban tree planting, of Table 2.1 and paragraph 4.71 of the Budget 2018, how the Government will fund the additional £50 million of carbon credits for qualifying tree planting under the Woodland Carbon Guarantee scheme.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185620","185620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997587","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference paragraph 1.40 and Table 2.1 line 1 of the Budget 2018, how much has been allocated to the NHS in each of the next five fiscal years to provide for the adjustment in NHS pension costs as a result of the SCAPE rate change.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185731","185731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997588","2018-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of households using the childcare element of universal credit who have entered arrears on childcare costs.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185732","185732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997589","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons the warm home discount scheme is only eligible for use with some electricity suppliers; and whether he plans to extend that list of suppliers for the scheme.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185479","185479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997590","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether all GP practices in the (a) Stroud constituency and (b) England have sufficient supplies of the FluMist flu vaccine to vaccinate all vulnerable groups including those eligible through age.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185480","185480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997591","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the funding allocated to the upgrade of the A303 and the Lower Thames Crossing will include private finance.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185590","185590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997592","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-10-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding his Department plans to allocate to the construction of Glen Parva Prison as a result of the abolition of  PF2 projects.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185591","185591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997593","2018-11-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Arc21 Residual Waste Infrastructure Procurement project will be financed as a PF2 project.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185592","185592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997594","2018-11-01","Department for Transport","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps (a) his Department and (b) agencies of his Department have taken to support the National Pollinator Strategy on (i) roads (ii) railway lines.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185806","185806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997595","2018-11-01","Department for International Trade","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase the level of foreign direct investment into the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185807","185807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997596","2018-11-01","Department for International Development","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the asbestos industry in India on incidences of mesothelioma in people (a) living near and (b) working in the industry.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185727","185727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997597","2018-11-01","Department for International Development","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to support programmes to ensure the safe disposal of asbestos waste in countries in the Global South.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185728","185728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997598","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many PFI contracts he or his predecessors signed between 14 October 2011 and 15 July 2014.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185733","185733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997599","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many PPP contracts he or his predecessors signed between 14 October 2011 and 15 July 2014.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185734","185734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997600","2018-11-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to Article 127 of the 1994 European Economic Area (EEA) Agreement, whether the Government has given the twelve months’ written notice to the other Contracting Parties of its intention to withdraw from that Agreement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185596","185596"
