"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713504","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how information on the safe removal of ticks is publicised.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69012","69012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713505","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the level of NHS card and support available to people who have been diagnosed with encephalitis.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69011","69011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713506","2017-03-28","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) proportion and (b) amount of grant paid by his Department to Action on Smoking and Health has been spent on staff salaries; and what the job titles were of each such staff.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68965","68965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713507","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice his Department gives to pregnant women on dieting.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68972","68972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713508","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with trigeminal neuralgia in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68973","68973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713509","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has had discussions with the British Medical Association on its consultation on proposals to amend the law on abortion.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68974","68974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713510","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the proposed £20 million budget impact threshold will apply to treatments still being appraised by NICE at the proposed implementation date of 1 April 2017.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68985","68985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713511","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of breast cancer treatments potentially affected by the proposed £20 million budget impact test.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68975","68975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713512","2017-03-28","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to correct the TTP SystmOne clinical IT software error present since 2009 and affecting around 26 million patients.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68916","68916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713513","2017-03-28","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the planned annual expenditure on the NHS is for the years ending 31 March (a) 2017, (b) 2018, (c) 2019 and (d) 2020.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68913","68913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713514","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with HELLP syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68919","68919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713515","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with anorexia when aged (a) between 12 to 20, (b) between 21 to 30, (c) between 31 to 50 and (d) over 51 years of age in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68920","68920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713516","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the Government has made of trends in the number of routine annual health checks undertaken in the last five years; and what estimate has been made of the effect on the NHS budget of such trends.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68921","68921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713517","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has had recent discussions with clinical bodies on the potential benefit of (a) the Mediterranean diet and (b) other diets in reducing the incidence of cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68922","68922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713518","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there are plans to make intramedullary high tibial osteotomy available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68923","68923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713519","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has had discussions with clinical bodies on the possible connection between hormone replacement therapy and reduced risk of heart disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68924","68924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713520","2017-03-28","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2017 to Question 68208, on NHS: buildings, for how long those properties have been vacant; when the most recent valuation of those properties was undertaken; and what the current valuation is of each of those properties.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68939","68939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713521","2017-03-28","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what operational liaisons are under development among air ambulances and the Association of Air Ambulances across the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68909","68909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713522","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number of new treatments that will reach or exceed the new budget impact test that NICE plans to introduce on 1 April 2017, (b) number of patients in England that will be delayed in accessing those treatments and (c) potential effect on the health outcomes of those patients delayed in accessing those treatments.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68859","68859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713523","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will provide a summary of the submissions made to NICE and NHS England consultation on changing arrangements for evaluating and funding drugs and other health technologies appraised through NICE's technology appraisal and highly specialised technologies programmes.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68860","68860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713524","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions officials of his Department have had with stakeholders in developing the new budget impact test that NICE plans to introduce on 1 April 2017.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68861","68861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713525","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the potential (a) medium and (b) long-term cost savings to the NHS of the use of genetic cascade testing to identify and treat familial hypercholesterolaemia.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68839","68839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713526","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the 100,000 Genome Project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68840","68840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713527","2017-03-27","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to give the independent communications data authorising body statutory underpinning.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68847","68847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713528","2017-03-27","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what budget has been set aside to establish and maintain the independent communications data authorising body referred to in the IP Act Implementation, Programme Layer advert published on gov.uk on 17 March 2017.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68857","68857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713529","2017-03-28","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether staff for the independent communications data authorising body will be drawn from among existing officers working on data requests.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68876","68876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713530","2017-03-28","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to report to Parliament on the functioning of the independent communications data authorising body.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68877","68877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713531","2017-03-27","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many firearms have been imported into the UK by registered importers from other countries within the EU in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68900","68900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713532","2017-03-27","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides to universities and colleges on the requirement for comprehensive sickness insurance for EU citizens from outside the UK.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68896","68896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713533","2017-03-27","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides for insurance providers and non-UK EU citizens who plan to be resident in the UK on what qualifies as comprehensive sickness insurance.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68897","68897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713534","2017-03-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will consider increasing the penalties for dog attacks on livestock; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68893","68893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713535","2017-03-28","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether reforms to the UK's immigration rules will be within the scope of negotiations on the UK's future relationship with the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68873","68873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713536","2017-03-28","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the budget for the independent communications data authorising body will be drawn from existing police budgets.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68917","68917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713537","2017-03-27","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has had discussions with police forces on the retention of horses for use in crowd control.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68952","68952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713538","2017-03-28","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her most recent assessment is of the potential consequences of implementation and enforcement of Northern Ireland legislation on prostitution for the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68962","68962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713539","2017-03-27","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents involving alleged offences by hunt saboteurs have been reported in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68949","68949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713540","2017-03-28","Home Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what approaches the Government is piloting for identifying and supporting victims of forced prostitution; and what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of such approaches.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68963","68963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713541","2017-03-27","Cabinet Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of assaults carried out by people using knives in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68951","68951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713542","2017-03-27","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the development of decentralised renewable energies in developing countries.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68984","68984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713543","2017-03-27","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will increase funding for the eradication of fuel poverty in developing countries.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68983","68983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713544","2017-03-28","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance the Government is giving to people in Nigeria who have begun to return to their home villages after the retreat of Boko Haram.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68912","68912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713545","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2017 to Question 67423, what criteria his Department uses when deciding whether to raise an issue of incitement with the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68889","68889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713546","2017-03-27","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2017 to Question 63106, in which countries her Department is strengthening nutrition outcomes of its water, sanitation and hygiene programmes.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68846","68846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713547","2017-03-27","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on increasing the level of UK aid to Eastern Europe; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68844","68844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713548","2017-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) children under 18 and (b) young people aged 18 to 24-years of age (i) applied for legal aid through the Exceptional Case Funding Scheme (ECF) and (ii) were granted ECF in immigration cases in (A) 2013-14, (B) 2014-15 and (C) 2015-16.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68894","68894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713549","2017-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) children under 18 and (b) young people aged 18 to 24-years of age received legal aid funding in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68895","68895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713550","2017-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) children under 18- years of age and (b) young people aged 18 to 24-years old received legal aid funding for immigration cases in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68866","68866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713551","2017-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions have been brought and (b) convictions have been secured against (i) people overseas and (ii) people in (A) England and (B) Wales under (1) section 2 of the Obscene Publications Act 1959, (2) section 1 of the Protection of Children Act 1978, (3) section 63 of the Criminal Justice and Immigration Act 2008 and (4) section 62 of the Coroners and Justice Act 2009.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68914","68914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713552","2017-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance her Department has issued on what prisoner to staff ratio in prisons is safe.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68927","68927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713553","2017-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what mechanisms exist for prison officers and their representatives to raise health and safety concerns in prisons.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68928","68928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713554","2017-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Serious Further Offence reviews have been carried out in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69001","69001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713555","2017-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were prosecuted for television licence offences in the last five years for which data is available; and how many of those people prosecuted were sentenced to prison.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68994","68994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713556","2017-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what her Department's definition is of a Serious Further Offence.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68992","68992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713557","2017-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was accrued to the public purse from prosecutions for television licence offences in the last five years for which data is available; and what the cost to HM Courts and Tribunals Service was of those prosecutions.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68993","68993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713558","2017-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Serious Further Offence reviews involving (a) the National Probation Service and (b) Community Rehabilitation companies in England and Wales were conducted in each of the five years up to February 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69048","69048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713559","2017-03-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his response was to the possibility of siting the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre at (a) Potters Field by City Hall, (b) Millbank near the Tate Britain  and (c) the Imperial War Museum.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68934","68934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713560","2017-03-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the legal status is of the National Holocaust Memorial Foundation.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68926","68926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713561","2017-03-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, who has made presentations on what duty to whom in his Office on the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68935","68935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713562","2017-03-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what was calculated to be the distance from Downing Street to the three initial sites considered for the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68936","68936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713563","2017-03-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which Department holds the capital for the proposed National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68937","68937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713564","2017-03-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how the (a) running and (b) legacy costs for the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre will be funded.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68938","68938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713565","2017-03-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether all proposals for the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre have been made available to the public.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68925","68925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713566","2017-03-28","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will direct the DVLA to ensure that opticians are required to report drivers whose eye test has revealed that their eyesight, even with glasses or lenses, is below the standards needed to drive safely.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68915","68915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713567","2017-03-27","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what measures he is taking to improve passenger rail journeys in southern England.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68931","68931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713568","2017-03-27","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to provide  support for a new fleet of rolling stock serving the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68933","68933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713569","2017-03-27","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the long-term investment of the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68943","68943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713570","2017-03-27","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much per capita funding was spent on transport infrastructure in (a) the North East and (b) London in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68944","68944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713571","2017-03-27","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to invest in new road infrastructure in the South West; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68864","68864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713572","2017-03-28","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons no HS2 Ltd board meeting minutes have been published on the gov.uk website since 3 March 2016; and if he will publish those minutes.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68882","68882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713573","2017-03-27","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether plans to dual the A303 and upgrade the A358 will change in response to the recommendations in the recently published National Audit Office report, Progress with the Road Investment Strategy.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68871","68871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713574","2017-03-27","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to support plans to introduce four trains an hour through New Barnet and Oakleigh Park on the Great Northern Line when the December 2018 timetable is introduced following the completion of the Thameslink programme.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69034","69034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713575","2017-03-27","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 65186, on High Speed 2, how much has been paid to each of the contractors listed in Annex A in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68976","68976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713576","2017-03-27","Department for Transport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passenger journeys have (a) started and (b) ended at British Steel Redcar Railway Station in the last five years.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68968","68968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713577","2017-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken under Access to Work for disabled people to receive the support packages they require; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68818","68818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713578","2017-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people Jobcentre Plus has assisted in finding employment in (a) Kettering and (b) England since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68827","68827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713579","2017-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the universal credit minimum income floor on the agricultural sector workers whose income is seasonal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68887","68887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713580","2017-03-28","HM Treasury","2017-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2017 to Question 68122, what estimate he has made of the amount of fines due to be payable as a result of those people who missed the 31 January 2017 deadline for their tax returns.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68911","68911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713581","2017-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people with multiple sclerosis on (a) income-based employment and support allowance and (b) the limited capability for the work element of universal credit have received sanctions in the latest year for which data is available.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68898","68898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713582","2017-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria a person would have to meet to receive a sanction equal to the financial support they receive from the limited capability for the work element of universal credit (a) now and (b) from April 2017 following the change in the rate at which that element is paid.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68901","68901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713583","2017-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people with mental health conditions who will be affected by the changes to personal independence payments in the Social Security (Personal Independence Payment) (Amendment) Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68940","68940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713584","2017-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have been awarded the highest rate of personal independence payment solely on the basis of a mental health condition will be affected by the changes to that payment in the Social Security (Personal Independence Payment) (Amendment) Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68941","68941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713585","2017-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what set of circumstances a person would receive a sanction equal to the financial support they receive from universal credit.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68957","68957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713586","2017-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2017 to Question 66566, if he will set out each case in the current Parliamentary session for which an equalities impact assessment has been produced but not published; and in each of those cases the reason for non-publication.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69020","69020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713587","2017-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many eligible disability living allowance (DLA) claimants have been invited to apply for personal independence payments since April 2016; and of those claimants invited to apply, how many have not applied within the time allowed and have had their DLA terminated as a result.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69022","69022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713588","2017-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the efficacy of the use of cassette audio recording equipment during personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69041","69041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713589","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, following the independent self-employment review of February 2016, whether he plans to introduce a legal definition of self-employment.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69019","69019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713590","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, following the independent self-employment review of February 2016, what steps he is taking to introduce a new adoption allowance for self-employed people.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69018","69018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713591","2017-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, following the independent self-employment review of February 2016, what steps he is taking to enhance the level of maternity allowance for self-employed people.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69017","69017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713593","2017-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of applying equivalent maternity rights for women in permanent employment to women in casual, fixed-term or zero-hours employment contracts.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68999","68999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713594","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed changes to EU copyright law on UK firms engaged in the digital economy.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68990","68990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713595","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which gas-fired power stations have been built since 2010; and what the generation capacity was of each of those stations.","Biography information for Amanda Milling","Amanda Milling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68977","68977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713596","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what contribution he has made to EU negotiations to reform EU copyright law.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68986","68986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713597","2017-03-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what contribution she has made to EU negotiations to reform the EU Electronic Communications Framework.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68987","68987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713598","2017-03-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect on UK firms engaged in the digital economy of proposed changes to the EU Electronic Communications Framework.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68988","68988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713599","2017-03-27","HM Treasury","2017-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what contribution he has made to EU negotiations to reform VAT arrangements for the EU Digital Single Market.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68989","68989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713600","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many megawatts of power generation capacity has been provided to the National Grid from gas powered stations in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Amanda Milling","Amanda Milling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68960","68960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713601","2017-03-27","HM Treasury","2017-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with sectoral representatives on steps to increase levels of bank lending to small businesses.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68959","68959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713602","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether Matthew Taylor's independent review into modern employment practices will consider whether those moving from employee positions to self-employment are being driven by positive choice or through market forces.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68953","68953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713603","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether Matthew Taylor's independent review into modern employment practices will consider whether the recent growth in the self-employed workforce represents a genuine wave of entrepreneurship and a desire for flexible working or a tool for businesses to hold down pay and restrict workers' rights.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68954","68954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713604","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether Matthew Taylor's independent review into modern employment practices will consider whether people in self-employment should share the same characteristics of workers and should therefore be entitled to sick pay, annual leave and the national living wage.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68955","68955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713605","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2017 to Question 66792, on climate change: snow and ice, whether there are declines of snow and ice, other than of Arctic Sea ice extent, that are inconsistent with reasonably expected national variability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68956","68956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713606","2017-03-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans for Ofcom to continue to participate in the Body of European Regulators for Electronic Communications after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68942","68942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713607","2017-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will require people to use their full legal name when setting up a limited company.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68872","68872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713608","2017-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether new fuel poverty and home energy efficiency policies will be included in his Department's forthcoming Clean Growth Plan.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68890","68890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713609","2017-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66594, on energy: meters, whether SMETS2s installed by one energy provider may be operated by any other existing or new provider if the consumer decides to switch provider.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68878","68878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713610","2017-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66594, on energy: meters, whether SMETS1s installed by one energy provider may be operated by any other existing or new provider if the consumer decides to switch provider.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68879","68879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713611","2017-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66594, on energy: meters, how much has been spent on installing SMETS1 meters; and how many such meters have been installed.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68880","68880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713612","2017-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to extend shared parental leave and pay to self-employed workers.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68875","68875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713613","2017-03-28","Department for Education","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many international students attended (a) Sheffield Hallam and (b) Sheffield University in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68884","68884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713614","2017-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66594, on energy: meters, how much has been spent on installing SMETS2 meters; and what is the target for the number of such installations.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68881","68881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713615","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the differences in (a) future carbon and capture and storage projections detailed in his Department's publications, Energy and emissions projections 2015 and (b) Energy and emissions projections 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68858","68858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713616","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what evaluation his Department has made of the overall efficiency of a combined heat and power plant.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68843","68843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713617","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to continue support for the production of steam from renewable energy sources used for industrial applications.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68837","68837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713618","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the combined heat and power tariff from 10 to 20 per cent efficiency on the (a) use and (b) price of energy generated by Organic Rankine Cycle turbines.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68838","68838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713620","2017-03-28","HM Treasury","2017-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations the Government made to other G20 members on including financing action on climate change in the G20 trade statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68835","68835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713621","2017-03-28","Department for International Trade","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to page 54 of the Government White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the 40 per cent growth in UK exports of goods and services to Liechtenstein between 2005 and 2014.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 69047","69047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713622","2017-03-27","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for International Development on increasing the level of UK aid to Eastern Europe.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68851","68851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714849","2017-03-29","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to projects facilitating peaceful co-existence between Palestinians and Israelis.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909549","909549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714850","2017-03-29","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to promote economic development in developing countries.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909548","909548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714851","2017-03-29","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to promote economic development in developing countries.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909553","909553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714852","2017-03-29","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to the UN's Step It Up for Gender Equality initiative.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909554","909554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714853","2017-03-29","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle child exploitation in developing countries.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909552","909552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714854","2017-03-29","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what proportion of the Official Development Assistance budget will be spent by her Department in 2017.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909555","909555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714855","2017-03-29","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure value for money of UK aid through strengthened monitoring.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909547","909547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714856","2017-03-29","Department for International Development","2017-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help developing countries raise more tax revenue.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909546","909546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714366","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Trade on UK arms sales to countries that are part of the Saudi-led coalition operating in Yemen.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909525","909525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714367","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role his Department has in the protection of endangered species abroad.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909524","909524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714368","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the implications for his policies are of the interim report and recommendations of the Advisory Commission on Rakhine State, published on 16 March 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909531","909531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714369","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assist east African nations affected by drought.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909526","909526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714370","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he next plans to meet his EU counterparts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909532","909532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714371","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on harassment of schoolchildren and expulsion of university students from the Baha'i community in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909527","909527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714372","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political and security situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909523","909523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714373","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his priorities have been during the UK's Presidency of the UN Security Council in March 2017.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909529","909529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/714374","2017-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to promote greater freedom of movement for civilians entering and leaving Gaza.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909530","909530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712868","2017-03-23","Attorney General","2017-03-21","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions the Law Officers' Departments took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68662","68662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712869","2017-03-23","Cabinet Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68663","68663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712870","2017-03-23","Cabinet Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths in the Pendle area were (a) alcohol and (b) drug-related in each of the last five years; and how many of those deaths were of people aged (i) under 18, (ii) 18 to 24, (iii) 25 to 40 and (iv) over 40 years old.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68642","68642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712871","2017-03-24","Cabinet Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the budget the Government has for advertising in newspapers for each government department in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68736","68736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712872","2017-03-24","Cabinet Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Government spent on advertising in the Evening Standard newspaper in the last financial year for which information is available.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68738","68738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712873","2017-03-24","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what budget his Department has for advertising in newspapers in the (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68737","68737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712874","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has allocated for marriage allowance in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) the next three years.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68718","68718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712875","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on marriage allowance in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68711","68711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712876","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the income decile profile is of claimants of (a) marriage allowance and (b) married couple's allowance.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68712","68712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712877","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in receipt of universal credit (a) are eligible for and (b) claim the marriage allowance.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68713","68713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712878","2017-03-24","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the Landlord Licensing Scheme introduced by the London Borough of Newham on supporting HM Revenue and Customs identify underpayment of tax by landlords.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68741","68741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712879","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he made an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the diversion rate for the Landfill Communities Fund prior to the introduction of the Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68646","68646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712880","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68674","68674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712882","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.29 of Spring Budget 2017, if he will make it his policy to engage with non-industry representatives, including non-governmental organisations with expertise in environmental, energy and consumer rights issues when consulting on the formation of future North Sea oil and gas policy.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68797","68797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712883","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.29 of Spring Budget 2017, when he plans to publish the formal discussion paper on the allowing of transfers of tax history between buyers and sellers of North Sea oil and gas assets.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68799","68799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712884","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.29 of Spring Budget 2017, by what criteria members will be appointed to the new advisory panel on oil and gas tax policy; and when he plans for that new advisory panel to be established.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68798","68798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712885","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on corporation tax receipts of UK companies creating headquarter subsidiaries in EU countries after the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68781","68781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712886","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to stop providing Government support through the Help to Buy scheme for new houses sold on a leasehold basis.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68793","68793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712887","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that ancient woods and veteran trees are protected from development in planning policy.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68801","68801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712888","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68664","68664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712889","2017-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, who will be eligible for funding from the Housing Infrastructure Fund.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68745","68745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712890","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to (a) promote responsible letting and (b) deal with rogue landlords.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68702","68702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712891","2017-03-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2017 to Question 68114, on public libraries: complaints, what the total number of correspondence received by her Department from all local authorities complaining about library services changes since 2010 is.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68689","68689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712892","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications for his policies are of the data from the Office for National Statistics on the disproportionately high rate of suicide among women in the culture, media and sport sectors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68627","68627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712893","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many premises authorising the sale or supply of alcohol by means of a (a) premises licence or (b) club premises certificate there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68789","68789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712894","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel from the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) RAF have received training as part of the Preventing Sexual Violence in Conflict initiative.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68804","68804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712895","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel currently deployed as part of UN missions have received training as part of the Preventing Sexual Violence in Conflict initiative.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68805","68805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712896","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel due to be deployed to South Sudan have received training as part of the Preventing Sexual Violence in Conflict initiative.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68806","68806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712897","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many fully trained personnel qualified for Guided Multiple Launch Rocket System roles there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68802","68802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712898","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army reservists are currently qualified to operate the 105 mm light gun.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68803","68803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712899","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the installation of a tactical data link on board the fleet of Leonardo Wildcat helicopters.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68787","68787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712900","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost is of applying thermal metal coating on the landing areas of HMS Queen Elizabeth.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68788","68788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712901","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what modifications will be required for the Queen Elizabeth-class carriers to provide battlefield helicopter operations.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68785","68785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712902","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) pilots, (b) maintenance engineers, (c) software programmers and (d) logistics and support staff from his Department are currently training with the US Marine Corps on the F35B Lightning II programme.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68786","68786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712903","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which platforms he is considering to provide for a Maritime intra-theatre list solution for carrier strike groups.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68780","68780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712904","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which units will be disbanded under Army 2020 Refine in order to free up personnel.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68812","68812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712905","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans to make changes to the Royal Artillery as part of the development of the Army's new warfighting concepts.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68813","68813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712906","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which units and elements of units are currently attached to 3rd (UK) Division.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68814","68814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712907","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which infantry units have been identified for an increase in strength as part of Army 2020 Refine.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68811","68811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712908","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many battalion-sized regular units will be moved from their home bases as part of Army 2020 Refine.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68810","68810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712909","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel posts he expects to be re-assigned to new units as part of Army 2020 Refine.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68808","68808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712910","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which units will be reduced in strength as part of Army 2020 Refine; and by how many personnel.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68809","68809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712911","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what advice his Department gives to military personnel on alcohol intake and good health.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68632","68632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712912","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68665","68665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712913","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 3.11, page 41 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, how many of his Department's personnel (a) are and (b) have been seconded to the US-based Joint Program Office for the Lightning II programme since that programme began.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68693","68693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712914","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 1.8, page 16 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, whether the task group supporting the carriers is likely to represent around 27 per cent of the Navy's fleet by tonnage and 20 per cent of the personnel needed to crew the fleet, depending on how the carriers are deployed.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68694","68694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712915","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 2.6, page 23 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, how many UK F-35B Lightning II fighters will be left in the US after 2018; and for how long those fighters will remain in the country.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68696","68696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712916","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 1.9, page 16 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, what plans his Department has to ensure that the number of Merlin helicopters is sufficient to provide for the needs of the carrier task group.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68695","68695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712917","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to figure 9, page 33 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, whether that figure accurately depicts departmental estimates of the expected number of Lightning II jets in the UK fleet.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68697","68697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712918","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the financial decisions detailed in figure 11, page 36 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, for (a) additional equipment and training to allow US F-35B jets to fly from UK carriers and vice versa, (b) sufficient weapons stockpiles for CEPP platforms, (c) tactical datalinks for intra-task group operations and (d) further development of the F-35B Lightning II computer system.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68698","68698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712919","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the UK-specific software programming is for the F-35B Lightning II programme, as detailed in paragraph 3.4, page 38 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68699","68699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712920","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilians are employed directly by his Department; and what progress is being made towards the target of employing no more than 41,000 civilians in that Department by 2020-21.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68709","68709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712921","2017-03-24","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2016 to Question 45976 on Education Funding Agency: buildings, what progress her Department has made on determining the future use of the former East Ham police station.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68740","68740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712922","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average pupil to teacher ratio was in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (i) the UK, (ii) Greater London and (iii) the London Borough of Newham in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68733","68733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712923","2017-03-24","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of provision in primary schools of teaching for children on how to stay safe online.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68743","68743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712924","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in Pendle were eligible for free school meals on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68703","68703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712925","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage small and medium-sized enterprises to employ apprentices.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68700","68700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712926","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions her Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68666","68666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712927","2017-03-24","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department has (a) allocated and (b) spent on encouraging BME people to take apprenticeships in construction, IT and engineering.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68656","68656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712928","2017-03-24","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that the Education Funding Authority receives value for money when purchasing sites for new schools.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68657","68657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712929","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will provide additional funding to schools to support students with dyslexia.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68647","68647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712930","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what specialist training is provided to teachers in (a) initial teacher training and (b) ongoing personal development to support children with special needs.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68648","68648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712931","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will consider extending to maintained schools exemptions similar to those which exist for small academies from the Apprenticeship Levy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68634","68634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712932","2017-03-24","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to tackle the under-representation of women in senior positions in universities, including in the position of Vice Chancellor.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68651","68651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712933","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will commission a nationwide study to report on the prevalence of girls missing school because they cannot afford to buy sanitary protection; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68644","68644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712934","2017-03-24","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to hold a consultation on proposals to extend free transport to students studying at selective schools.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68654","68654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712935","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2016 to Question 42492, on Trade in Animals and Related Products Regulations 2011, when her Department will begin the five-year review of those regulations.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68633","68633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712936","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the implications for her policies on protecting endangered species in the UK are of the State of Nature 2016 report, published by the RSPB on 14 September 2016; and whether she is taking steps to protect such species.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68630","68630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712937","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to introduce legislative proposals on the use of wild animals in circuses in the next session of Parliament.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68649","68649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712938","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on how many occasions her Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68667","68667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712939","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps her Department has taken to assist the farming industry to become more competitive.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68705","68705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712940","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding her Department has provided for research into the dairy farming sector in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68706","68706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712941","2017-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2017 to Question 68033, on agriculture, when her Department plans to make a decision on how the commitment to maintain agricultural sector funding at equivalent Pillar 1 levels under the CAP from when the UK leaves the EU until 2020 will be managed and delivered; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68754","68754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712942","2017-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research and information her Department holds on the prevalence of bovine TB in areas surrounding the pilot culls for each year of those pilot culls.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68756","68756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712943","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's Environmental Impact Assessment - Joint Technical Consultation, published on 14 December 2016, how many responses her Department received (a) in support of and (b) in opposition to, proposals to increase the Forestry Environmental Impact Assessment threshold in England; and when her Department plans to respond to that consultation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68778","68778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712944","2017-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2017 to Question 66627, on bovine tuberculosis: disease control, how many of the 421 carcasses of badgers culled by controlled shooting underwent post-mortem examination in each year; and how many of those carcasses were found to have evidence of more than one hit in each year.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68800","68800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712945","2017-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many members of his Department's staff employed in overseas roles were based in the Russian and Eastern Europe region in each year since 2010; and how many such staff were in roles requiring the ability to speak a local language.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68753","68753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712946","2017-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government (a) has raised or (b) plans to raise with the Government of Israel the issue of deportations from Israel of activists who support a boycott of illegally occupied Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68766","68766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712947","2017-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to commit new research funding to the UK National Action Plan on Women, Peace and Security to support the Government's commitment to the Preventing Sexual Violence in Conflict initiative.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68807","68807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712948","2017-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding Women's security-related projects in (a) Afghanistan, (b) Bosnia, (c) Kosovo, (d) the Democratic Republic of Congo, (e) Somalia and (f) South Sudan received from the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund in each year between 2008 and 2015.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68724","68724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712949","2017-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Women, Peace and Security-related projects in (a) Afghanistan, (b) Bosnia, (c) Kosovo, (d) the Democratic Republic of Congo, (e) Somalia and (f) South Sudan have received funding from the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68723","68723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712950","2017-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding Women, Peace and Security-related projects in (a) Afghanistan, (b) Bosnia, (c) Kosovo, (d) the Democratic Republic of Congo, (e) Somalia and (f) South Sudan received from the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund in (i) 2015-16 and (ii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68722","68722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712951","2017-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the merits of negotiating Andy Tsege's return to the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68719","68719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712952","2017-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Arabian counterpart on the cases of Ali Mohammed al-Nimr, Dawood al-Marhoon and Abdullah al-Zaher.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68731","68731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712953","2017-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of his Department's staff passed a language examination at (a) Extensive, (b) Operational, (c) Functional and (d) Confidence levels in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68749","68749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712954","2017-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many members of staff his Department employs overseas in roles requiring an ability to speak the local language; in which countries such staff are based; and in which languages such staff are required to be proficient.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68750","68750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712955","2017-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many members of staff his Department employs overseas in roles based in the Middle East and North Africa region in each year since 2010; and how many such staff were in roles requiring an ability to speak a local language.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68751","68751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712956","2017-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many and what proportion of staff employed by his Department overseas in roles requiring an ability to speak a local language are at the Target Level Attainment for that language.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68752","68752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712957","2017-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68669","68669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712958","2017-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of whether the Burmese Government's domestic process for investigating claims of sexual violence by Burmese security forces against Rohingya Muslim women is consistent with the standards set out in the International Protocol on the Documentation and Investigation of Sexual Violence in Conflict.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68645","68645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712959","2017-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to host another Global Summit to End Sexual Violence in Conflict; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68650","68650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712960","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who within his Department is responsible for monitoring and enforcing the Access to Health Records Act 1990.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68628","68628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712961","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances there have been where (a) an individual and (b) a family have put in a request to access the health records of individuals to whom they are related in accordance with the Health Records Act 1990; and how many of those requests were rejected in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68629","68629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712962","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on investigating historical allegations of abuse at Aston Hall, Derbyshire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68635","68635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712963","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Vetrex and NHS England on the drug Orkambi's availability to people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68636","68636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712964","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of making the drug Orkambi availabile to people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68637","68637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712965","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) nurses and (b) midwives from other EU member states were registered with the Nursing and Midwifery Council in each month in the last five years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68652","68652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712966","2017-03-27","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spends each year on treatment of meningococcal B disease.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68640","68640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712967","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government plans to establish an independent taskforce on lung health.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68687","68687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712968","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the additional funding for social care announced in the Spring Budget 2017 will be divided between the NHS and local councils.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68744","68744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712969","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using intelligent conveyancing systems to assist ambulance services in taking patients to the most appropriate hospital; and which ambulance services in England do not operate such systems.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68710","68710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712970","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what cost-benefit analysis his Department has carried out on the NHS (a) Quality and Outcomes Framework and (b) Quality, Innovation, productivity and Prevention programme; and if he will place a copy of all such analysis in the Library.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68716","68716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712971","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a Freedom of Information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68717","68717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712972","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of injuries and mortalities caused by falls over child stair gates in the home in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68692","68692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712973","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will require all ambulance trusts to report and publish data on all the tail breaches for which it is responsible.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68690","68690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712974","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish ambulance trust performance figures relating to green graded calls.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68691","68691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712975","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which sustainability and transformation plans contain no mechanism for engaging schools and colleges as active stakeholders.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68688","68688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712976","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to encourage (a) understanding and (b) effective treatment of people with chronic pain conditions within the NHS.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68678","68678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712977","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of making sanitary products available on prescription.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68639","68639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712978","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to (a) secure appointments and (b) provide additional support in other ways to the 111 patients in Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS Trust areas whose referrals were missed off waiting lists in 2016.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68721","68721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712979","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason NHS England does not refer patients to Navigo's specialist eating disorder unit Rharian Fields in Great Grimsby.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68725","68725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712980","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to launch the Daily Mile nationwide in England.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68767","68767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712981","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent GPs were working in (a) Warrington, (b) the North West and (c) England per head of population on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68758","68758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712983","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of enabling physician associates to prescribe medicines.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68759","68759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712984","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an estimate of (a) how many and (b) what proportion of consultant cellular pathologists will retire in the next five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68762","68762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712985","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the funding that the Care Quality Commission will receive in 2017-18 after the commencement of its new fees scheme in April 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68763","68763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712986","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of staffing levels in cellular pathology.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68764","68764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712987","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost of employing locum doctors in the NHS in (a) Gloucestershire, (b) the South West and (c) England has been for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68765","68765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712988","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency plans the Government has made in the event of an anti-microbial resistance pandemic; and if he will place a copy of those plans in the Library.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68795","68795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712989","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of ambulance staff are employed by G4S.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68796","68796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712990","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Neurosciences centres fulfil the NHS England service specification for neurological care.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68782","68782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712991","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what Government policy is on the maintenance of border control arrangements between France and the UK for (a) rail, (b) ferry and (c) flight passengers after the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68783","68783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712992","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions officials in her Department supported local authorities in assessing children's needs in families who are seeking Section 17 of the Children Act 1989 in 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68779","68779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712993","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information the Government has provided to citizens from other EU countries residing in the UK as self-sufficient persons or students of the requirement to have comprehensive sickness insurance.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68794","68794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712994","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Scottish Government on the assignment of designated competent bodies in Scotland for Tier 1 (Exceptional Talent) visas.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68776","68776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712995","2017-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted under the terms of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997 have also been made the subject of a restraining order.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68755","68755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712996","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people with dependants who have been granted leave to remain in the UK had a no recourse to public funds condition attached to their leave in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68768","68768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712997","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2017 to Question 67025, which support groups are engaged by the Home Office to support asylum applicants who are deaf and hard of hearing.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68748","68748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712998","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests were made to her Department for a change of conditions of leave lifting the condition of no recourse to public funds in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68770","68770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712999","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of staff time for casework within her Department to review applications for a change of conditions of leave granted on the basis of family or private life.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68771","68771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713000","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests were made to her Department for a change of conditions of leave were approved in lifting the no recourse to public funds condition to the applicants conditions of leave in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68769","68769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713001","2017-03-24","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff her Department seconded to local authorities to support in the assessment of needs of children in families who are seeking section 17 of the Children Act 1989 in 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68772","68772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713002","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers were convicted of a criminal offence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68708","68708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713003","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2017 to Question 67099, on deportation: children in care, whether her Department holds information on which countries those young children that have left care were deported to.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68739","68739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713004","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which organisations she consulted prior to the decision to end automatic settlement of refugees after completion of five years leave to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68734","68734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713005","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the costs of introducing safe return reviews for refugees who have completed five years leave to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68735","68735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713006","2017-03-24","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many young people who left care in the last five years were subsequently deported to (a) Somalia, (b) Afghanistan, (c) Democratic Republic of Congo, (d) Central African Republic and (e) Albania.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68746","68746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713007","2017-03-23","Cabinet Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many nationals from other EU countries residing in the UK have been (a) self-sufficient and (b) students for a period during that residence.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68727","68727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713008","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for permanent residency from nationals from other EU countries who have been in the UK for a continuous period of five years have been rejected due to the applicant being (a) self-sufficient or (b) a student  for a period during that residency without a comprehensive sickness insurance policy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68728","68728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713009","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to improve police training and cross-border co-operation in cases of cyberstalking; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68643","68643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713010","2017-03-23","Department for International Development","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much has been spent on the Global Learning Programme in schools in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68714","68714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713011","2017-03-23","Department for International Development","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment has been carried out of the effectiveness of the Global Learning Programme initiative in schools across Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68715","68715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713012","2017-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2017 to Question 68249, on drugs: sentencing, how many people serving a custodial sentence for drug offences are serving that sentence for personal possession.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68747","68747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713013","2017-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) charged and (b) convicted under section (i) 2, (ii) 2a, (iii) 4 and (iv) 4a of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997 during 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68726","68726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713014","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of sentence handed down to a person convicted of rape was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68707","68707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713015","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions she has had with Ministerial colleagues on drug addiction services in prisons.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68704","68704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713016","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions her Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68671","68671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713017","2017-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who appealed to a tribunal against a decision not to award the enhanced rate mobility component of personal independence payments were awarded (a) the standard rate, (b) the enhanced rate and (c) nothing in each quarter of 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68658","68658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713018","2017-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who appealed to a tribunal against a decision not to award the standard rate mobility component of personal independence payments were awarded (a) the standard rate, (b) the enhanced rate and (c) nothing in each quarter of 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68659","68659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713019","2017-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the decline in the number of drink-driving convictions between 2004 and 2014.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68660","68660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713020","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps she has taken to improve drug treatment facilities in prisons.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68791","68791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713021","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 78 of the concluding observations of the UK's report to the Committee on the Rights of the Child, published in June 2016, whether the recommendations will be applied to minors in detention in the armed forces.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68784","68784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713022","2017-03-23","Cabinet Office","2017-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions 10 Downing Street took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68672","68672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713023","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68673","68673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713024","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government monitors the extent of fuel price differentials between motorway and non-motorway service stations.","Biography information for Victoria Atkins","Victoria Atkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68685","68685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713025","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the average price differential of fuel per litre in cost and percentage terms between motorway and non-motorway service stations.","Biography information for Victoria Atkins","Victoria Atkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68686","68686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713026","2017-03-24","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on improving access to affordable transport for 16 to 18 year old further education students.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68655","68655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713027","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the effect of diesel car emissions on public health.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68631","68631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713028","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of staged car accidents in the latest period for which figures are available and (b) effects of such accidents on (i) car insurance premiums and (ii) other costs to motorists.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68701","68701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713029","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to reform airspace policy.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68729","68729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713030","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that assistance dog owners are able to access taxis and minicabs.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68730","68730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713031","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what account his Department has taken of the volume of air passengers from London Luton Airport in its work to define the scope of the forthcoming East Midlands rail franchise consultation; and what assessment he has made of the potential (a) economic, (b) social and (c) environmental benefits to that airport from improved rail services related to that franchise.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68732","68732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713032","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings have taken place between Ministers of his Department and Volkswagen's UK representative since December 2016 to discuss Volkswagen's manipulation of emissions tests; and how many cars affected by that scandal had been rectified at the date of each of those meetings.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68777","68777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713033","2017-03-24","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many flights were undertaken by HS2 Ltd personnel at a cost to (a) that company and (b) the public purse during the last six months; what the cost was of those flights; and what the reasons for those flights were.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68773","68773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713034","2017-03-24","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reasons are for the time taken to sign the contracts with CH2M for the HS2 Phase B development partnership.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68775","68775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713035","2017-03-24","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many flights were undertaken by his Department's officials at a cost to the public purse during the last six months; what the cost of those flights was; and what the reasons for those flights were.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68774","68774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713036","2017-03-24","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the communications provided by tour companies and airlines to UK nationals in places affected by the new US restrictions on electronic devices on flights is consistent and comprehensive.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68815","68815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713037","2017-03-24","Department for Transport","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions UK representatives have had with (a) US authorities, (b) authorities in affected countries, (c) airlines and (d) other national or international bodies on the recent US announcement restricting electronic devices on flights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68816","68816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713038","2017-03-24","Women and Equalities","2017-03-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2017 to Question 67623, whether she plans to make representations to the Equality and Human Rights Commission on the dismissal of those 10 employees or take any other steps in relation to those dismissals.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68757","68757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713039","2017-03-24","Department for Education","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will work with the Department for Education to draw up and enact an action plan to recruit and retain more male teachers in primary schools.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68626","68626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713040","2017-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the success rate for appeals against decisions on (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment entitlement in Leeds has been in the most recent 12 month period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68653","68653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713041","2017-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to assist people in Pendle who are in receipt of jobseeker's allowance to enter employment.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68641","68641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713042","2017-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help people who wish to move from part-time to full-time employment.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68792","68792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713043","2017-03-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to increase employment in the manufacturing sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68790","68790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713044","2017-03-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department or its predecessors have conducted an assessment of the effectiveness of training standards developed by the Global Wind Organisation for employees in the UK offshore wind industry.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68760","68760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713045","2017-03-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to promote the transfer of employment and skills between different sectors of the offshore energy industry.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68761","68761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713046","2017-03-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68661","68661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713047","2017-03-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the total number of homes to be insulated through the Energy Company Obligations scheme in each of the next three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68638","68638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713048","2017-03-24","Department for International Trade","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which the three non-EU countries are with which the UK does not have a free trade agreement and with which the UK trades most by value.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68625","68625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713049","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the potential effect on the Welsh agricultural sector of the UK reverting to World Trade Organisation rules when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68675","68675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713050","2017-03-23","Department for International Trade","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68670","68670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713051","2017-03-24","Department for International Trade","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many companies in (a) Greater London and (b) the London Borough of Newham exported goods or services to (i) other EU countries and (ii) non-EU countries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68742","68742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713052","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on the level of milk exports to the Republic of Ireland when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68679","68679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713053","2017-03-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on the Welsh aerospace sector of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68676","68676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713054","2017-03-23","Department for International Trade","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on the Welsh automotive sector when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68677","68677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713055","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the potential effect on the level of poultry meat imports when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68680","68680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713056","2017-03-23","Department for International Trade","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on direct foreign trade investment from (a) Japan and (b) Korea when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68681","68681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713057","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the potential effect on the level of bacon and ham imports when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68682","68682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713058","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the potential effect on the level of beef imports from the Republic of Ireland when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68683","68683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713059","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on levels of Welsh lamb and mutton (a) exports and (b) imports when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68684","68684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713060","2017-03-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of tariff increases on the viability of the UK agriculture industry sector in the event that the UK leaves the single market.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68720","68720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713061","2017-03-23","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, on how many occasions his Department took longer than 30 working days to respond to a freedom of information request in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68668","68668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713592","2017-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations the Government has received on the applicability of the national minimum wage and the national living wage to staff who are asleep during a sleep-in shift at work.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909497","909497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713957","2017-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to encourage more women to enrol in pensions at a younger age.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909494","909494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713958","2017-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the policy implications for his Department of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909481","909481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/713959","2017-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the financial effect on women of recent changes in the pension age","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909488","909488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712361","2017-03-22","Cabinet Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when each department plans to publish updated Single Departmental Plans.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68504","68504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712362","2017-03-23","Cabinet Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether future meetings between Ministers and the right hon. Member for Tatton will be required to be published in the Departments' transparency data concerning meetings with proprietors, editors and media executives after his appointment as editor of the London Evening Standard; and whether any such meetings will be exempt from declaration in such transparency data.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68588","68588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712363","2017-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 4.5 of the Spring Budget 2017, what estimate the Government has made of the number of public houses that will be eligible for the £1,000 business rate discount in (a) Bedford and (b) Bedfordshire.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68565","68565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712364","2017-03-22","HM Treasury","2017-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the number of jobs sustained by cryptocurrency trading and related services.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68563","68563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712365","2017-03-22","HM Treasury","2017-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much VAT was recovered by UK businesses from other EU member states under Articles 170 and 171 of Council Directive 2006/112/EC in each local authority area since 2010.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68571","68571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712366","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to regulate distributed ledger technology and cryptocurrencies in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68581","68581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712367","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much VAT was recovered by EU member state businesses from the UK exchequer under Articles 170 and 171 of Council Directive 2006/112/EC in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68584","68584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712368","2017-03-22","HM Treasury","2017-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on advertising with the Evening Standard newspaper in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68589","68589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712369","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what her Department's rationale was for introducing a sliding scale of probate fees based on the worth of an estate.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68494","68494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712370","2017-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the planned business rates rise on the nursery sector.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68508","68508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712371","2017-03-22","HM Treasury","2017-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 65651, on Treasury: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within his Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68530","68530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712372","2017-03-23","HM Treasury","2017-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on advertising with the Evening Standard in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68448","68448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712373","2017-03-23","Church Commissioners","2017-03-20","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what guidance is issued to churches on allowing church premises to be used for yoga classes.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68543","68543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712374","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2017 to Question 67412, on licensed premises: non-domestic rates, when he plans to publish the consultation on the eligibility criteria for the discount for eligible pubs.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68550","68550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712375","2017-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 65636, on Department for Communities and Local Government: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within his Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68533","68533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712376","2017-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will publish a definition of the term social lettings agencies as used in the white paper, Fixing our broken housing market, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68432","68432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712377","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of permitting the construction of 15 new garden city-style developments of 100,000 homes.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68582","68582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712378","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will devolve additional fiscal powers to local councils to fund social care.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68580","68580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712379","2017-03-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to tackle doping in amateur competitive sports.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68575","68575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712380","2017-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to promote mountain biking as a sport.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68586","68586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712381","2017-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the UK Digital Strategy 2017, published on 1 March 2017 by her Department, if she will publish the evidential basis for the statement that superfast broadband is on track to reach 95 per cent of UK premises by December 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68607","68607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712382","2017-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish the correspondence between her Department and the Welsh Government on the issue of the appointment of a Welsh member to the BBC Board.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68445","68445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712383","2017-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to increase the number of (a) children and (b) adults who swim regularly in (i) Greater London and (ii) the London Borough of Newham.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68462","68462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712384","2017-03-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Civil Society plans to amend section 10 of the Charities Act 2011 to define ecclesiastical corporations as charities.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68476","68476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712385","2017-03-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to review the restrictions paced on digital locks under the EU Copyright Directive as a result of Britain's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68480","68480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712386","2017-03-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 65637, non Department for Culture, Media and Sport: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within her Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68518","68518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712387","2017-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2017 to Question 68114, on public libraries: complaints, which 15 local authorities have been investigated since 2010; and what the outcomes were of those investigations.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68553","68553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712388","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy personnel are currently training alongside the US military to maintain aircraft carrier skills.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68487","68487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712389","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 65638, on Ministry of Defence: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within his Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68523","68523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712390","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to retain Royal Navy and RAF pilots.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68488","68488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712391","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date the inaugural sailing of the first Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carrier is planned to take place.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68489","68489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712392","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to tackle the shortage of engineers needed to support Royal Navy carrier strike capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68490","68490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712393","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of his Department's personnel have visited LEYAL Ship Recycling Ltd in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68546","68546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712394","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff of LEYAL Ship Recycling Ltd are working on secondment at his Department.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68544","68544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712395","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what fees his Department has received from LEYAL Ship Recycling Ltd in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68545","68545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712396","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans that HMS Queen Elizabeth will achieve carrier strike capability.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68481","68481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712397","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what date has been set for the inaugural sailing of the HMS Queen Elizabeth.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68482","68482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712398","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 22, page 13 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, what steps his Department is taking to set out arrangements for long-term leadership and oversight of Carrier Enabled Power Projection capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68470","68470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712399","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 22, page 13 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of that report's recommendation.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68472","68472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712400","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 19, page 12 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, what steps he is taking to address the long-standing skills gaps in his Department's contract management teams.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68473","68473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712401","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 1.9, page 16 of the National Audit Office report, Delivering Carrier Strike, published on 16 March 2017, whether he plans to procure additional helicopters to increase the number of Crownsnest radar-enabled aircraft available.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68474","68474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712402","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy senior personnel are working with the US Navy to develop a UK-specific Carrier Enabled Power Projection doctrine and assessing interoperability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68463","68463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712403","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel are deployed to an operationally deployed US Navy carrier strike group.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68464","68464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712404","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel are deployed with (a) US Fleet Forces Command, (b) US Pacific Fleet, (c) US Naval Forces Europe - Naval Forces Africa, (d) US Naval Forces Central Command, (e) US Naval Forces Southern Command, (f) US Naval Special Warfare Command, (g) US Navy Operational Test and Evaluation Force, (h) US Navy Naval Warfare Command, (i) Military Sealift Command and (j) US Navy Naval Reserve Forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68465","68465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712405","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many US Navy personnel are working at his Department's Development, Concept and Doctrine Centre in support of developing a UK-specific Carrier Enabled Power Projection doctrine.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68466","68466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712406","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether plans exist to increase the number of Royal Navy and Royal Air Force F-35 pilots trained in the US above the numbers already planned.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68436","68436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712407","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to minimise cost increases to the Carrier Strike programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68458","68458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712408","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency provision his Department has made for changes in the cost to the UK of Lightning II jets as a result of changes in the number of orders for such aircraft worldwide.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68430","68430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712409","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on each Substitute Service (a) Family and (b) Single Accommodation in each year from 2010 to 2017.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68440","68440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712410","2017-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the capacity is of (a) Service Family Accommodation and (b) Single Living  Accommodation; and where such accommodation by type is located.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68441","68441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712411","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made a recent estimate of the number of UK-flagged escorts required to support Carrier-Enabled Power Projection capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68434","68434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712412","2017-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will prioritise UK suppliers during contracting negotiations on complex support arrangements for Carrier-Enabled Power Projection capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68435","68435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712413","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the allocation for extended rights to free home-to-school travel will be published for each fiscal year from 2017-18 to 2019-20.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68442","68442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712414","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the accuracy of information provided by (a) schools, (b) local authorities and (c) academy trusts in response to freedom of information requests related to asbestos exposure.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68450","68450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712415","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been allocated in PE and Sport Premium funds to schools in (a) Greater London and (b) the London Borough of Newham in each year since they were introduced.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68461","68461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712416","2017-03-23","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the announcement made by the Chancellor of the Exchequer in the Budget Statement, 16 March 2016, Official Report, column 963, on a fair national funding formula, how £500 million of funding has been allocated to date; and how much is allocated for future spending.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68547","68547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712417","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the inclusion of citizenship education in Key Stages 3 and 4 of the National Curriculum on understanding of democracy, government and how laws are made and upheld.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68492","68492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712418","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in (A) York local authority and (B) Yorkshire and the Humber in (1) cash terms and (2) at 2014 prices in 2005-06 and in each year since.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68497","68497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712419","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how her Department plans to allocate the additional Sport Premium funding announced in Budget 2016.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68493","68493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712420","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure regional funding equality in the provision of education for children who are in hospital and requiring statutory entitlement to education.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68495","68495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712421","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average pupil to teacher ratio was in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in York in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68496","68496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712422","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that students taking reformed A-Level courses have access to resources and revision material to prepare for exams.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68555","68555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712423","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received on the availability of resources and revision materials to students taking reformed A-Level courses.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68556","68556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712424","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2017 to Question 65639, on Department for Education: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within her Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68522","68522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712425","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department has made available to schools, colleges and universities to provide access to mental health services to students (a) throughout the academic year and (b) at exam times.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68596","68596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712426","2017-03-22","HM Treasury","2017-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding each NUTS 1 region will receive from the Government's policy to top-up the apprenticeship levy in 2017-18.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68618","68618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712427","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many large businesses have registered to access funds under the apprenticeship levy in each NUTS 1 region; and what proportion of apprenticeships does this represent in each region.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68619","68619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712428","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships in each NUTS 1 region her Department envisages will be created as a result of the apprenticeship levy in 2017-18.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68620","68620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712429","2017-03-22","Department for Education","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to (a) raise the aspirations of and (b) address the educational attainment gap for working class boys.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68564","68564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712430","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to reduce fly tipping; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68587","68587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712431","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the Green Paper on the future of the UK agricultural industry.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68579","68579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712432","2017-03-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department last made an assessment of the case for revising the levels of grants for (a) solar panels, (b) domestic biomass heating and (c) other household renewable energy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68574","68574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712433","2017-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress the UK is making towards Aichi 2020 and the 2030 Agenda for Sustainable Development.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68622","68622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712434","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking in response to the TB outbreak within Kimblewick Hunt's foxhounds to ensure that other hunts are free of TB.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68539","68539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712435","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research her Department has commissioned to date into the spread of TB from hunting hounds to cattle.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68540","68540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712436","2017-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to include measures applying to (a) England and (b) all nations of the UK in the forthcoming 25 year plan for food and farming.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68505","68505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712437","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to cancel all hunting activities until foxhound packs across the UK are certified to be free of TB.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68538","68538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712438","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to investigate the source of the bovine TB outbreak within Kimblewick Hunt's foxhound packs.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68536","68536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712439","2017-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2017 to Question 67006 on bovine tuberculosis: dogs, whether her Department has carried out any research on diseases in packs of hunting dogs.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68511","68511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712440","2017-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy for TB in hunt packs operating in close proximity to cattle to be a notifiable disease.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68537","68537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712441","2017-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the EU REACH process identification of four synthetic chemicals, DEHIP, DIBP, DBP and BBP, as endocrine-disrupting chemicals for human health; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68459","68459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712442","2017-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many and what proportion of serving HM Ambassadors and High Commissioners are not career diplomats.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68433","68433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712443","2017-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department and the Ministry of Defence plan to hold the next two plus two meeting with the foreign and defence ministers of Japan.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68491","68491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712444","2017-03-22","Department for International Trade","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will take steps to ensure that human rights have equal or higher protection in UK free trade agreements as in EU free trade agreements after the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68503","68503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712445","2017-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his contribution on 13 March 2017, to the debate on Budget Resolutions (HC Deb, col 84), whether he has had discussions with the private sector on the construction or commissioning of a new royal yacht.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68552","68552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712446","2017-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his contribution on 13 March 2017, to the debate on Budget Resolutions (HC Deb, col 84) and pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2016 to Question 47643, whether he has held discussions with the Department for International Trade on the effect of a privately-funded royal yacht on securing trade deals.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68551","68551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712447","2017-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in Israel to reverse demolition orders relating to the village of Khan Al Ahmar in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68542","68542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712448","2017-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 65641, on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within his Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68531","68531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712449","2017-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the legality of Andy Tsege's (a) trial, (b) arrest and rendition and (c) detention.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68600","68600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712450","2017-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to North Korea on recent nuclear missile tests in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68573","68573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712451","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent NHS (a) consultants, (b) junior hospital doctors, (c) nurses and midwives, (d) other clinical staff and (e) staff in total were employed at York hospitals, excluding mental health units in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68576","68576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712452","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of patients referred to York Hospital for (a) elective surgery and (b) outpatient appointments waited longer than 18 weeks from referral to treatment in each year since 2009-10; and what the average waiting time was in each of those years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68513","68513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712453","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of patients referred for elective surgery to York Hospital waited longer than six months from referral to treatment in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68514","68514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712454","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a second, junior tier of qualified nursing staff in order to increase the general supply of nursing staff in public hospitals.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68559","68559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712455","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of reforming the General Medical Council's licensing rules to increase the general supply of doctors in public hospitals.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68560","68560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712456","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent NHS (a) consultants, (b) junior doctors, (c) nurses, (d) other clinical staff and (e) staff in total were employed at NHS mental health units in the 2012 City of York council area in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68572","68572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712457","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the supply of nurses in public hospitals.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68554","68554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712458","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on advertising with the Evening Standard newspaper in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68591","68591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712459","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Information Commissioner on the breach of the IT system SystmOne.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68594","68594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712460","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of medical records at risk of being unlawfully accessed through the SystmOne IT system managed by the company TPP.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68595","68595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712461","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has received a request for funding from the group Action on Smoking and Health in respect of the next financial year; and if he will ensure that all grants awarded for such work are assessed on a competitive basis.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68614","68614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712462","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to improve the regulation of dermal fillers used in non-surgical cosmetic interventions and not classified as medical devices.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68608","68608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712463","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of carrying out the GP Patient Survey in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68506","68506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712464","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of GPs have left the UK to work abroad within (a) one, (b) two and (c) three years of completing their training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68485","68485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712465","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding was allocated by NHS England to the learning disability GP annual health check scheme in 2015-16.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68449","68449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712466","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average annual cost to the public purse of supporting a person with challenging behaviour and learning disabilities, autism or both within an assessment and treatment unit.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68446","68446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712467","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished consultant episodes there were at York Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68455","68455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712468","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to make continuous glucose monitors available on the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68467","68467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712469","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 15 March 2017, Official Report, column 144WH, if the proposed creation of super-hubs in rural areas means the closure of local practice buildings to be replaced with new larger buildings.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68468","68468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712470","2017-03-23","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on advertising with the Evening Standard newspaper in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68444","68444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712471","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, by what process (a) Serco, (b) G4S and (c) Clearel procure accommodation under the provisions of the Compass system.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68477","68477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712472","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many sub-contractors supply accommodation under the provision of the Compass system in each region.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68478","68478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712473","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is the responsibility of (a) the contractor or (b) the landlord to cover the cost of landlord insurance under the Compass system.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68479","68479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712474","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to reduce the number of acid attacks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68460","68460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712475","2017-03-22","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who passed through the National Referral Mechanism as victims of modern slavery or of human trafficking with positive conclusive grounds status were granted discretionary leave to remain in the UK in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 1 April to 31 December 2016.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68451","68451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712476","2017-03-22","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on use of dogs to patrol (a) immigration detention centres and (b) Dungavel immigration removal centre.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68452","68452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712477","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on advertising with the Evening Standard in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68447","68447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712478","2017-03-22","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on whether EEA citizens will be removed from or refused re-entry to the UK on the basis that they do not have comprehensive sickness insurance; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68486","68486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712479","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is her Department's policy to recognise the threat of female genital mutilation as grounds for an asylum claim in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68534","68534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712480","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many acid attacks there were in (a) the UK, (b) Greater London and (c) the London Borough of Newham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68535","68535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712481","2017-03-23","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on advertising with the Evening Standard newspaper in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68597","68597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712482","2017-03-22","Department of Health","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of attacks on ambulance workers in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Lancashire.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68566","68566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712483","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of sentence was for people convicted of attacks on ambulance workers in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68567","68567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712484","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted of attacking ambulance workers in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68568","68568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712485","2017-03-23","Department for International Development","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will take steps to provide humanitarian assistance to Palestinians displaced by the expected demolition of Khan Al Ahmar in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68541","68541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712486","2017-03-22","Department for International Development","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 65645, on Department for International Development: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within her Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68520","68520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712487","2017-03-22","Department for International Development","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to use some of the UK's aid budget to support the creation of processing plants to allow start-to-finish manufacture of chocolate and coffee in countries that provide the base products for fair-trade food items.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68475","68475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712488","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to reduce violence against prison staff.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68471","68471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712489","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what consideration was given to including punishment as a purpose of prisons in clause 1(2) of the Prisons and Courts Bill.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68469","68469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712490","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of changes to the discount rate for motor insurance on the take-up of such insurance.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68438","68438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712491","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of changes to the discount rate for motor insurance on the average cost of such insurance.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68439","68439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712492","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to answer Question 62919, tabled on 2 February 2017 by the hon. Member for Coventry South on prisoners.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68549","68549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712493","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 65647, on Ministry of Justice: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within her Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68524","68524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712494","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to ensure that Prison Service staff undertaking the same work receive the same level of remuneration.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68502","68502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712495","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to answer Question 64822, tabled on 21 February 2017 by the hon. Member for Coventry South on prison service: pay.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68548","68548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712496","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of turnover of prison staff; and what steps she is taking to support retention and recruitment of such staff.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68484","68484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712497","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the level of morale in the prison service.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68498","68498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712498","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effect of raising the retirement age of prison officers to 68 years old on safety in prisons.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68501","68501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712499","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support she has made available to prison offices experiencing mental health issues as a result of their employment.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68499","68499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712500","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will bring forward proposals to reduce the retirement age of prison officers to bring it in line with the retirement age for police officers.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68500","68500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712501","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of prisoner-on-prisoner violence have been recorded in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68592","68592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712502","2017-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2017 to Question 67198, on prisons: electronic equipment, what proportion of the total cost of the issued 19,000 television sets is expected to be recovered.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68612","68612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712503","2017-03-22","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU nationals were detained in prison under immigration powers in each quarter of (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68623","68623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712504","2017-03-22","Home Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of detaining EU nationals in immigration removal centres in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68624","68624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712505","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to announce a date for the publication of the Farmer Review.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68621","68621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712506","2017-03-22","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 65648, on Northern Ireland Office: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within his Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68525","68525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712507","2017-03-23","Cabinet Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to prevent the right hon. Member for Tatton from accessing copies of Government, Cabinet or Cabinet Committee papers relating to the period when he was in the Government while he is the Editor of the London Evening Standard.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68598","68598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712508","2017-03-23","Leader of the House","2017-03-20","To ask the Leader of the House, whether the right hon. Member for Tatton will continue to (a) have access to Privy Council papers, (b) attend full meetings of the Privy Council and (c) receive sensitive information on Privy Counsellor terms after his appointment as Editor of the London Evening Standard.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68599","68599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712509","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when and how the decision was made that the Victoria Tower Gardens should be considered as a suitable site and preferable to the alternatives for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68603","68603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712510","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by whom and under what criteria the decision was made for Victoria Palace Gardens to become preferred to alternatives for the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68604","68604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712511","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Government has made of how many people will on average visit the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre each week in its first year of opening.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68605","68605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712512","2017-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how he plans for objections to Victoria Tower Gardens as a possible location for the National Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre to be taken into account before a final decision is made.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68606","68606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712513","2017-03-22","Scotland Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 65649, on Scotland Office: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within his Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68526","68526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712514","2017-03-22","Department for Transport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 65650, on Department for Transport: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within his Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68532","68532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712515","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on advertising with the Evening Standard newspaper in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68443","68443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712516","2017-03-22","Department for Transport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) financial and (b) accessibility implications for disabled drivers of the process of applying for a reduced rate of vehicle tax.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68453","68453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712517","2017-03-22","Department for Transport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward proposals to accept applications for a reduced rate of vehicle tax online and at Post Office branches.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68454","68454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712518","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the reduction in the rail freight grant on the volume of freight that will be carried by (a) rail and (b) road.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68611","68611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712519","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria were used to set the £535,000 per annum base salary of the new chief executive officer of HS2.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68601","68601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712520","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64112, if he will publish details of Mark Thurston's previous experience, which was used to inform the decision to appoint him to the role of Chief Executive Officer of HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68602","68602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712521","2017-03-22","Department for Transport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish the response to its consultation on the future of the Severn Bridges which closed on 10 March 2017.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68569","68569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712522","2017-03-22","Department for Transport","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on advertising with the Evening Standard newspaper in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68590","68590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712523","2017-03-23","Wales Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he plans to announce his decision on the Swansea Bay City Deal to the House before any other public forum.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68437","68437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712524","2017-03-22","Wales Office","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 65652, on Wales Office: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within his Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68527","68527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712525","2017-03-22","Women and Equalities","2017-03-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2017 to Question 65642, on Government Equalities Office: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within her Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68528","68528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712526","2017-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 65653, on Department for Work and Pensions: Brexit, what (a) EU agencies and other organisations are within his Department's remit, (b) staff time was spent on engagement with those bodies and (c) financial resources were spent on engagement with those bodies in 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68529","68529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712527","2017-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of fees in the Child Maintenance Service on collection rates of child maintenance.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68507","68507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712528","2017-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on behalf of DEC, Compaq and Hewlett Packard pensioners with pre-1997 pension contributions in resolving their case.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68483","68483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712529","2017-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on legal fees in all stages of legal proceedings related to Pandemrix.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68578","68578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712530","2017-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals have there been in (a) the UK, (b) the North East and (c) Easington constituency against personal independence payments decisions in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68615","68615"
