"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29414","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what Child Support Agency (CSA) cases will come within Segment 2 of his Department's proposed order for CSA case closure; and what period of nil compliance with child maintenance will be necessary for a case to be included in Segment 2.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180365","180365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29415","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many local authorities are currently developing or implementing programmes to increase the prevalence of audio-visual systems on buses in their area compared to the same time last year.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180337","180337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29416","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on marginal airline route services of transferring responsibility for aviation security from his Department to the Civil Aviation Authority from 1 April 2014.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180387","180387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29417","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, further to the Answer of 6 September 2013, Official Report, column 579W, on excise duties: tobacco, whether he has completed his assessment of the implications of Article 4 of Council Decision 2010/12/EU; and what plans HM Revenue and Customs and the UK Border Force have to enforce compliance with its provisions by travellers.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180368","180368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29418","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the success of his Department's attempts to encourage bus and coach providers to increase the proportion of their staff who have received training in disability matters.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180338","180338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29419","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department made of the performance of IT systems in hospitals in England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180377","180377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29420","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who provides the IT services to each hospital in NHS England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180378","180378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29421","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that any new charges to the aviation industry as a result of transferring responsibility for aviation security from his Department to the Civil Aviation Authority are phased in to mitigate the potential negative effects on marginal airline route services.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180388","180388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29422","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the cost of administering the Renewable Heat Incentive in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Scotland and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180369","180369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29423","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that, following the planned process of Child Support Agency (CSA) arrears validation that will accompany the case closure programme, the Child Maintenance Service will give the same priority to the active recovery of any CSA arrears which a parent with care of a dependent child wishes to have collected, regardless of whether a £20 application fee has been paid to the Child Maintenance Service in respect of continuing maintenance for the child.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180366","180366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29424","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the IT systems in use in hospitals in England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180379","180379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29425","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether guidance given to train operators on designing Disabled People's Protection Policies promotes the need to educate staff on interchange to other modes of transport for disabled people.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180339","180339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29426","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of his Department's impact assessments in the field of aviation reform.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180389","180389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29427","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether police officers are required to be members of the Police Federation.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180381","180381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29428","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people declared fit for work have subsequently reapplied and been classed as unfit for work within a three month period.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180340","180340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29429","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Police Federation is funded by her Department.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180382","180382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29430","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) general accuracy of impact assessments prepared by his Department and submitted to Parliament prior to enactment of the Civil Aviation Act 2012 and (b) estimated annual costs in the form of new charges to be met by the aviation industry when responsibility for regulating aviation security transfers from his Department to the Civil Aviation Authority from 1 April 2014.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180390","180390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29431","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the cost of decommissioning existing nuclear power stations in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Wales and (d) Scotland.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180370","180370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29432","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the National College of Teaching and Leadership has allocated more teacher education places than estimated need in 2014-15 for secondary subject and primary phase.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180392","180392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29433","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether police officers acting as an officer of the Police Federation are given paid time off to undertake their duties as Federation officers.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180383","180383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29434","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what study trips to America (a) his Department and (b) the NHS undertook in 2008; which senior staff in (i) his Department and (ii) NHS London took part in each such trip; and what the cost to the public purse was of each such trip.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180371","180371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29435","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance will be given to Child Maintenance Service officials in respect of Child Support Agency cases closed within Segment 2 of his Department's case closure programme because of nil compliance, where a parent with care who applies to use the new Child Maintenance Service asks to use the statutory collection service straight away, on the grounds that the non-resident parent's nil payment record means they are unlikely to pay the new maintenance liability in accordance with the calculation if left to do so via a voluntary Direct Pay arrangement.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180367","180367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29436","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what external consultancy contracts were procured by NHS London in each year since 2005; what the value of each such contract was; and what the date of each such contract was.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180384","180384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29437","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the total amount paid out in the form of constraint payments to wind installations in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Scotland, (d) Northern Ireland and (e) Wales in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180372","180372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29438","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 2, on Interpol, what the length of time between issue and withdrawal or revocation was of each of the eight Interpol Red Notices which were withdrawn or revoked by the UK.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180398","180398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29439","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, to how many firms the Serious Fraud Office has out sourced investigative work in the last three years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180393","180393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29440","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect of marginal fuel allowances on investment in North Sea resource extraction since their introduction.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180373","180373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29441","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to encourage all UK banks to allow their current account customers access at post offices.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180410","180410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29442","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts NHS England awarded to Carnall Farrar LLP in the last five years; and what the (a) value and (b) date was of each such contract.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180385","180385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29443","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, if he will review the Serious Fraud Office's out sourcing controls and procedures following the prosecution of Victor Dahdaleh.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180394","180394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29444","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the hunger strike of Bhai Gurbakhash Singh in India.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180374","180374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29445","2013-12-17","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to improve road safety for cyclists in Greater London.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180386","180386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29446","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on Sikh prisoners in India remaining in prison despite having completed their sentences.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180375","180375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29447","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, when the Serious Fraud Office (SFO) engaged the services of Akin Gump during its investigation of Victor Dahdaleh; and how much was paid by the SFO for any services Akin Gump provided.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180395","180395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29448","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he received the evidence review commissioned by the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the landscape of food aid provision and access in the United Kingdom; and when he expects to comment to that Department.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180399","180399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29449","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what basis the contract for the Post Office card account will be tendered if a new contract is continued into 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180411","180411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29450","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what savings the Government has achieved by reducing fraud against the public sector since May 2010; and what proportion of total fraud against the public sector do those savings represent.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180376","180376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29451","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to provide full access to credit union services through the national post office network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180412","180412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29452","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teacher education places the National College of Teaching and Leadership has estimated are required by secondary subject and primary phase in each English region in 2014-15.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180391","180391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29453","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 142W, on Afzal Amin, whether Afzal Amin is employed in any other capacity by his Department.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180401","180401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29454","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, what the cost to the public purse was of the Serious Fraud Office's investigation and prosecution of Victor Dahdaleh.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180396","180396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29455","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the implementation of Article 21.1 of EU Directive 2011/24 regarding cross border access to health care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180413","180413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29456","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many EU member states have transposed into national law EU Directive 2011/24, on the application of patients' rights in cross-border healthcare; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180414","180414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29457","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 383W, on overseas trade: females, what guidance his Department offers to UK Trade and Investment on promoting women in trade delegations and exporting.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180402","180402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29458","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the decision of the trial judge to direct the jury to acquit Victor Dahdaleh on grounds that included the delegation by the Serious Fraud Office of parts of the investigation to a law firm that was suing the defendant; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180397","180397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29459","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost of fraud to the public sector; and what steps have been taken since May 2010 to tackle such fraud.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180403","180403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29460","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what 24 hour GP services operate in (a) England, (b) Greater London and (c) the London Borough of Southwark.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180405","180405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29461","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to Final investment decision enabling for renewables, update 3: contract award process, published by his Department on 4 December 2013, how many of the applications for final investment decision enabling contracts for renewables phase 2 have received planning consent.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180415","180415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29462","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans his Department has to support the creation of jobs in Greater London.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180290","180290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29463","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are currently being housed with foster parents in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180416","180416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29464","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that its Departments and agencies are able to share confirmed fraud data both with other bodies in the (a) public and (b) private sector.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180404","180404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29465","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children who are being cyber-bullied in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180417","180417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29466","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks posed to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of insufficient attention and support from his Department due to other demands.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180291","180291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29467","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2013, Official Report, column 154W, on universal credit, who is providing jobcentre plus advisors with training; and at what cost.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180406","180406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29468","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks posed to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme by the scale and speed of the programme making it unachievable or achievable only superficially.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180292","180292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29469","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to prevent forces fighting in the Central African Republic from profiting from illegal trade in diamonds, uranium or petroleum.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180407","180407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29470","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks posed to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of a failure of poorly designed operational processes.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180293","180293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29471","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he was first informed that the phasing out of new claims to existing benefits and credits would be delayed until after April 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180408","180408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29472","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks posed to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of a failure of poor engagement with trusts and failure to take on board their views.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180294","180294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29473","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks posed to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of insufficient testing of operational design.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180295","180295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29474","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the total receipts from Air Passenger Duty was attributable to (a) band C and (b) band D in (i) 2009, (ii) 2010, (iii) 2011, (iv) 2012 and (v) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180409","180409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29475","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, how many Serious Fraud Office investigations are under way relating to each of the (a) banking, (b) pharmaceuticals and (c) energy sectors.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180297","180297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29476","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks posed to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of a failure due to a lack of resources and preparation.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180296","180296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29477","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on how many occasions Mr Lawrence Tomlinson has met officials from the Insolvency Service in relation to his report on RBS; and on which dates such meetings took place.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180419","180419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29478","2013-12-18","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that local authorities are consulting with people with autism, their families and community-based charities as they develop local plans to implement the Adult Autism Strategy.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180400","180400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29479","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether officials from the Insolvency Service were consulted ahead of the publication of Mr Lawrence Tomlinson's report on RBS; and whether the report was approved by the Insolvency Service.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180420","180420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29480","2013-12-19","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of progress of redress arrangements for businesses subject to interest rate swap mis-selling.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180424","180424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29481","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether investigations are being carried out by the Insolvency Service into the findings of Mr Lawrence Tomlinson's report on RBS.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180421","180421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29482","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings have taken place between (a) Ministers and (b) officials at his Department and staff at the Insolvency Service in relation to Mr Lawrence Tomlinson's report on RBS.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180422","180422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29483","2013-12-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-12-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the turnout was in the most recent (a) general and (b) local elections in (i) Ribble Valley constituency, (ii) Lancashire and (iii) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180418","180418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29484","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the accounts of the Police Federation from 2003 to 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180380","180380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29886","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has for the future of HM Courts and Tribunals Service.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901670","901670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/30118","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to tackle rogue PPI claim companies and nuisance calling by those companies.","Biography information for Steve Brine","Steve Brine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901661","901661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28885","2013-12-12","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-12-10","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, if he will publish any briefing notes given to the media in (a) advance of and (b) response to enquiries about the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority's decision on hon. Members' future salaries.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179909","179909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28886","2013-12-12","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-12-10","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, when the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority Board made the decision on hon. Members' future salaries.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179910","179910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28887","2013-12-12","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-12-10","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, which media (a) were contacted by the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority (IPSA) and (b) contacted IPSA in the week commencing Monday 2 November on IPSA's decision on hon. Members' future salaries.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179911","179911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28888","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what length of delays on the rail network were attributable to Network Rail maintenance failures in the last year for which data are available.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179912","179912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28889","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the National Offender Management Service has been of monitoring the use of social media by its employees.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179913","179913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28890","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff within the National Offender Management Service (NOMS) monitor NOMS employees' use of social media.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179914","179914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28891","2013-12-12","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-12-10","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, if the Chairman and Chief Executive will prepare a briefing note for hon. Members explaining the decision of the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority Board on hon. Members' future salaries.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179915","179915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28892","2013-12-12","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-12-10","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, if the Chief Executive of the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority  (IPSA) will write personally to all members of the public who communicate with hon. Members on IPSA's recent decision on hon. Members' salaries; and if he will issue an invitation to all hon. Members to forward all such communications to him.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179916","179916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28893","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who is permitted to lay a wreath at the Remembrance Sunday service at the Cenotaph; and on whose behalf such people lay wreaths.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179917","179917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28894","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who currently lays wreaths on behalf of (a) the Crown Dependencies and (b) the British Overseas Territories at the Remembrance Sunday service at the Cenotaph.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179918","179918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28895","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what process is used when the decision is made as to who is permitted to lay a wreath at the Remembrance Sunday service at the Cenotaph.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179919","179919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28896","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his policy to advise the Royal Household that each of the (a) British Overseas Territories and (b) Crown Dependencies should be allowed to lay a wreath of their own at the Remembrance Sunday service at the Cenotaph.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179920","179920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28897","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what sustainability assessment he has carried out on announcements contained in the Autumn Financial Statement, Cm 8747.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179921","179921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28898","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to increase the flow of capital to small and medium-sized businesses through crowdfunding and similar platforms.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179922","179922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28899","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to extend the Business Finance Partnership.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179923","179923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28900","2013-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to his Answer to the hon. Member for Brighton Pavilion, of 18 November 2013, Official Report, column 714W, on bovine tuberculosis. for what reasons tests for tuberculosis were not carried out as part of all post-mortem examination of badgers shot during culls; what the results were of the few tests carried out at the specific request of landowners; and if he will consider carrying out TB tests in culled badgers as a matter of course.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179924","179924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28901","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students were in higher education in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179925","179925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28902","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received from people in Thirsk and Malton constituency on the rural fuel duty rebate pilot scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179926","179926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28903","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what applications he received for the extension to the rural fuel rebate pilot scheme; and what the timetable is for applications to be considered.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179927","179927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28904","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he is making in receiving state aid approval from the EU Commission for the rural fuel rebate pilot scheme.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179928","179928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28905","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what returns will be made to insurance company investments under the National Infrastructure Plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179761","179761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28906","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire were in apprenticeships in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179762","179762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28907","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which foreign governments have complained to the UK (a) before 2013 and (b) in 2013 about the treatment of their citizens in family court proceedings.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179792","179792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28908","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on the use of greenfield sites for new home building.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179802","179802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28909","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much blood has been donated in each NHS blood and transplant local area, in each month of the last two years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179803","179803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28910","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many businesses in (a) Worcester and (b) Worcestershire will qualify for the full £1,000 business rates discount announced in the Autumn Statement of 5 December 2013.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179812","179812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28911","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many donor sessions for each NHS blood and transplant local area, ran in each month of the last two years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179804","179804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28912","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time staff are employed in each NHS blood and transplant local area.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179805","179805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28913","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what safeguards her Department has put in place to ensure that Azure Payment Cards issued to those receiving support under Section 4 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 are used only in accordance with her Department's rules for the card; and what steps she takes to monitor compliance.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179813","179813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28914","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that requirements on those in receipt of jobseeker's allowance and employment and support allowance respect the religious adherence of individuals.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179771","179771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28915","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the provision of insulin pumps for (a) adults and (b) children in each of the Clinical Commissioning Group areas in England in the last 12 months.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179806","179806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28916","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will conduct an audit of insulin pump provision.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179807","179807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28917","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will estimate the value to organisations certified for receiving payment with Azure Payment Cards of receiving payments made through that scheme; and if he will take steps to increase the number of retailers participating in the scheme.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179814","179814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28918","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many businesses in (a) Worcester and (b) Worcestershire are in receipt of 100 per cent small business rate relief.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179808","179808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28919","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many donors in each NHS blood and transplant local area, have given blood (a) six or more times a year, (b) between four and six times a year, (c) between two and four times a year and (d) once a year in each of the last two years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179809","179809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28920","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what criteria or conditions under contractual terms his Department will use to decide whether or not to withhold discretionary bonuses for banks and advisors involved in the Royal Mail privatisation.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179772","179772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28921","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered donors there are in each NHS blood and transplant local area.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179810","179810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28922","2013-12-16","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to refer the alleged breaches of the Ministerial Code by the right hon. Member for Chipping Barnet contained within the hon. Member for St Albans' letter of 10 September 2013 to the Independent Adviser on the Ministerial Code.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179815","179815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28923","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much blood was donated in each NHS blood and transplant local area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179811","179811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28924","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) South Lanarkshire successfully appealed against a work capability assessment decision in 2013.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179773","179773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28925","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sex offenders are held at HM Prison Oakwood; and how many places on sex offender treatment programmes are available at that prison.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179774","179774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28926","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to his Department's budget has been of its work on the enhanced online service for universal credit to date; from which budget heading it has been met; and how much further spending he plans on this project from his Department's budget.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179816","179816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28927","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidences of (a) suicide, (b) attempted suicide and (c) self-harm there were in (i) HM Prison Oakwood and (ii) on average in all adult prisons in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179775","179775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28928","2013-12-16","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the Cabinet Secretary is conducting an investigation into the hon. Member for St Albans' letter of 10 September 2013 alleging breaches of the Ministerial Code by the right hon. Member for Chipping Barnet.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179817","179817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28929","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults on (a) prisoners and (b) prison staff there were (i) in HM Prison Oakwood and (ii) on average in all adult prisons in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179776","179776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28930","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the cost to his Department of appeals against the work capability assessment in 2013.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179777","179777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28931","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether any Minister in his Department has received verbal or written representations from the right hon. Member for Chipping Barnet regarding the Radlett Rail Freight Terminal.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179818","179818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28932","2013-12-16","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, when the Cabinet Secretary will reply to the hon. Member for St Albans' letter of 10 September 2013 alleging breaches of the Ministerial Code by the right hon. Member for Chipping Barnet.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179819","179819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28933","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff were employed by Atos Healthcare as part of the Medical Services Agreement in each month since 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179778","179778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28934","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the cost to his Department of appeals against the work capability assessment in 2013.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179779","179779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28935","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail on increasing capacity east of Broadbottom on the Manchester to Glossop rail line.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179831","179831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28936","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what work his Department has undertaken on assessing any link between energy prices and excess winter deaths.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179780","179780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28937","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what grants have been issued in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire under the New Homes Bonus scheme since that scheme's introduction.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179763","179763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28938","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what monthly targets he has set for those leaving prison and rolling onto the Work Programme.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179781","179781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28939","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on Palestinian membership of the International Olive Council.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179782","179782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28940","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2013, Official Report, columns  289-90W, on children: day care, how many (a) basic, (b) higher and (c) additional rate tax payers were in receipt of employer supported childcare vouchers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179832","179832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28941","2013-12-12","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the UK's national action plan on business and human rights was referred to by officials and businesses during his recent visit to China.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179764","179764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28942","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners Oakwood prison is contracted to hold; and whether its operator receives any payment for holding prisoners above its certified normal accommodation.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179783","179783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28943","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in how many different prisons individuals who are detained solely under immigration powers are currently detained.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179793","179793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28944","2013-12-12","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with President Xi Jinping of China on the issue of Tibet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179765","179765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28945","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-foreign national offenders have been detained in prison solely under immigration powers in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179794","179794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28946","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what controls her Department has put in place to intercept the delivery of substances controlled by the Misuse of Drugs Act at (a) postal sorting offices and (b) distribution centres in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179784","179784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28947","2013-12-12","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, whether following his recent visit to China any trade deals were signed involving companies doing business in Tibetan areas of China.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179766","179766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28948","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether HS2 Ltd will be able to recover VAT on its spending; and what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on this matter.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179785","179785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28949","2013-12-12","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with President Xi Jinping of China on political prisoners in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179767","179767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28950","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on a new Worcestershire Parkway station.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179768","179768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28951","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on steps to decrease train times on the North Cotswold line.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179769","179769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28952","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people given (a) prohibited activity and (b) exclusion requirements in each probation trust area were electronically monitored, in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179786","179786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28953","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the rate of progress of creation of alternative fuels infrastructure for the recharging of electric vehicles in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179820","179820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28954","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 55.10.1 of her Department's Enforcement Instructions and Guidance, what information is used in decisions on transfers from the prison estate to immigration removal centres for time-served foreign national offenders based on the length of time an individual has been held in prison solely under immigration powers.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179795","179795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28955","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on doubling the A4440 Southern Link Road.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179770","179770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28956","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many businesses in (a) Worcester and (b) Worcestershire are currently in receipt of small business rate relief.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179821","179821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28957","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, in respect of which objects a decision on a licence application under the Export of Objects of Cultural Interest scheme was originally deferred, but a licence for permanent export was later granted in 2011-12 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179796","179796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28958","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he last had discussions on the future of Warrington and Halton NHS Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179797","179797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28959","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) on the potential effect of new crowdfunding regulations set out in the FCA's consultation paper 13/13, published in October 2013, on SME finance.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179822","179822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28960","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on implementing the Government's commitment to require sustainable palm oil provided under public procurement contracts for food and catering.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179787","179787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28961","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the number of people in the Philippines who are in need of relief but are yet to receive any official aid.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179798","179798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28962","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, to which enterprise zones superfast broadband has been provided to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179933","179933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28963","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with social media sites on protecting children online.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179823","179823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28964","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to those rice farmers in the Philippines who require seeds and tools following Typhoon Haiyan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179799","179799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28965","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children under 16 years of age are part of a sport or exercise club in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179934","179934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28966","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the spread of water-borne diseases in the Philippines following Typhoon Haiyan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179800","179800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28967","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with NHS England on changes to the funding formula for clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179788","179788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28968","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her international counterparts on donations to the UN appeal following the Bohol earthquake.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179801","179801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28969","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what safeguarding measures are in place to prevent British nationals from being arrested on the basis of a politically-motivated or otherwise abusive Interpol Red Notice; and whether additional measures are in place for such warrants received from countries with a poor record of human rights.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179935","179935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28970","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with leading social media sites on protecting children online.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179824","179824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28971","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Border Force staff were made redundant and what the cost to the public purse was in (a) 2010-11 and (b) 2011-12.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179789","179789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28972","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many jobs have been created to date at each enterprise zone; and how many jobs are currently based at each enterprise zone.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179936","179936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28973","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the independent investigation by the Medical Research Council into vivisection practices at Imperial College, London; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179825","179825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28974","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from small and medium-sized enterprises on banks in which the Government has a stake unnecessarily recalling business loans.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179833","179833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28975","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have to visit the HM Revenue and Customs' office in Newry to assess the (i) effectiveness of the service provided and (ii) specialist tax avoidance and tax evasion work undertaken in respect of the construction industry scheme.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179790","179790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28976","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with banks in which the Government has a stake on ensuring that business loans to small and medium-sized enterprises are not unnecessarily recalled.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179834","179834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28977","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of value of the specialist tax avoidance and tax evasion work undertaken by Newry HM Revenue and Customs office in respect of the construction industry scheme.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179791","179791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28978","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent meetings he has held with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on best practice in care homes throughout the UK.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179835","179835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28979","2013-12-12","Northern Ireland Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many dissident republicans have been (a) arrested and (b) convicted for terrorist acts in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179836","179836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28980","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to promote science skills, research and understanding in Africa.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179826","179826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28981","2013-12-12","Northern Ireland Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many acts of terrorism linked to Irish republican groups have been reported in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179837","179837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28982","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what requirements there are on energy companies to offer the same range of energy tariffs throughout the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179827","179827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28983","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many firms are currently based at each enterprise zone; and how many firms have begun occupying premises at each enterprise zone since each zone began operation.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179937","179937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28984","2013-12-12","Northern Ireland Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what representations she has made to the government of the Irish Republic on the publication of the Smithwick Report.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179838","179838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28985","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how any gap in per pupil funding between the highest and the lowest funded authorities has changed in the last 15 years.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179929","179929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28986","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what digital assistance is available for people in Newcastle required to claim benefits online; and where any such assistance can be found.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179828","179828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28987","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent meetings he has held with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on obesity problems throughout the UK.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179839","179839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28988","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the continued use of the pound between each remaining constituent part of the UK, the Crown Dependencies and an independent Scotland; and whether he has considered any plans for a new currency in the remaining constituent parts of the UK.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179938","179938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28989","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors and (b) nurses worked in NHS accident and emergency departments in (i) Portsmouth South constituency and (ii) Hampshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179930","179930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28990","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of right-to-buy leaseholders who regret their purchase because of the need to implement costly repairs.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179829","179829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28991","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate HM Revenue and Customs has made of loss of revenue as a result of fuel laundering in Northern Ireland in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179840","179840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28992","2013-12-12","Cabinet Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the proportion of young people who have been unemployed for more than 12 months in Portsmouth South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179931","179931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28993","2013-12-16","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what weight is given to sustainability and the inclusion of cycling schemes when assessing bids made under the local growth fund.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179939","179939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28994","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate HM Revenue and Customs has made of loss of revenue as a result of cigarette smuggling into Northern Ireland in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179841","179841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28995","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals have resulted in local authority decisions being overturned by the planning inspector in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179932","179932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28996","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department offers right-to-buy leaseholders on steps to take to be informed of ongoing costs associated with their property.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179830","179830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28997","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on business prospects in the different regions of the UK.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179842","179842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28998","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs staff are employed in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179843","179843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28999","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time in accident and emergency was (a) in Barking, Bexley, Havering and Redbridge University Hospitals NHS Trust, (b) across London and (c) in England in each of the last four (i) quarters and (ii) years.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179940","179940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29000","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients visited accident and emergency departments in (a) Barking, Havering and Redbridge University Hospitals NHS Trust, (b) each London NHS Trust and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179941","179941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29001","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to visit Londonderry during its year as UK City of Culture 2013.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179844","179844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29002","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients waited longer than the admission target to accident and emergency in (a) Barking, Havering and Redbridge University Hospitals NHS Trust, (b) each NHS trust in London and (c) England in each month in 2012-13.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179942","179942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29003","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote science skills, research and understanding in Africa.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179944","179944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29004","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many medical posts in accident and emergency departments were left vacant in (a) Barking, Havering and Redbridge University Hospitals NHS Trust, (b) each NHS trust in London and (c) England in each year in 2009-10.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179943","179943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29005","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK Border Agency intends to publish a service protocol on its website giving information on (a) what visa applicants might expect for their administration fee and (b) who applicants can contact for updates on the progress of their visa application.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179945","179945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29006","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which school in England receives the (a) lowest and (b) highest amount of funding per pupil.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179946","179946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29007","2013-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Bangladeshi government not to proceed with the execution of Abdul Qader Mollah.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179947","179947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29008","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's plans are for the Nursery Milk Scheme.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179948","179948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29009","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support UK Green Manufacturing.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179949","179949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29010","2013-12-12","Attorney General","2013-12-10","To ask the Attorney General, if he will make an assessment of whether the General Treaty for Renunciation of War as an Instrument of National Policy remains binding on the UK.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179950","179950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29011","2013-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which food banks each Minister in his Department has visited since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179951","179951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29012","2013-12-12","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, which food banks he has visited since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179952","179952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29013","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the reasons for changes in the number of jobseeker's allowance claimants being sanctioned.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179955","179955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29014","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding his Department allocated to development agencies in the (a) North West, (b) North East and (c) Yorkshire in (i) 2007-08, (ii) 2008-09 and (iii) 2009-10.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179953","179953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29015","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the findings of the National Diabetes Audit on the number of sufferers with type 1 diabetes who are offered a place on a structured education course in the last year.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179956","179956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29016","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the total amount of capital invested or loaned to small and medium-sized businesses through crowdfunding platforms to date; and what assessment he has made of changes in the amounts of such lending.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179954","179954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29017","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to change the sanctions applied to benefits claimants following the recent Supreme Court judgement R v Secretary of State for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179957","179957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29018","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will review the criteria for building on greenfield sites.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179958","179958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29019","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been detained following detection by sniffer dogs on more than one occasion at the ports of (a) Calais, (b) Dunkirk and (c) Channel Tunnel in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179980","179980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29020","2013-12-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the potential amount of investment arising from implementation of the the provisions in the Energy Bill.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179959","179959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29021","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on extending the regional growth programme beyond September 2014.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179960","179960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29022","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether any Minister in his Department has received verbal or written representations from any hon. Members who are or have been Ministers in the Treasury since May 2010 regarding the Radlett Rail Freight Terminal.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179981","179981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29023","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools in England with at least 100 pupils received the (a) lowest and (b) highest amount of funding per pupil in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179961","179961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29024","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding assistance he will put in place to assist regional growth after September 2014.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179962","179962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29025","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on the response of UK authorities when they encounter a person subject to an Interpol Red Notice.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179982","179982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29026","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the amount of police time spent implementing Interpol Red Notices in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179983","179983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29027","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the policy of (a) the UK and (b) other EU member states is on deleting information received from Interpol once a Red Notice has been removed from Interpol's systems.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179984","179984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29028","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the London School of Economics report, Costs and benefits of an EU-USA Investment Protection Treaty, commissioned by his Department and published in April 2013, what assessment he has made of the value of inserting a provision for an investor-state dispute settlement mechanism in the proposed Translantic Trade and Investment Partnership; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179963","179963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29029","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of which EU member states and US states have a legal system that does not guarantee adequate protection for foreign investors.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179964","179964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29030","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for how long does he intend that staff in his Department will be engaged on developing the enhanced online digital service for universal credit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179985","179985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29031","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of job seeker's allowance claimants waited longer than (a) one week, (b) two weeks, (c) three weeks and (d) one month to have their benefit claim processed in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179986","179986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29032","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average processing times of jobseeker's allowance claims were for each quarter since January 2006.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179987","179987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29033","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS trusts and foundation trusts provide places in a specialist mother and baby unit where the mother may be treated for perinatal mental illness without being separated from her baby.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179965","179965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29034","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the enhanced online digital service for universal credit whose development has been started by the Government Digital Services will relate to the universal credit system whose development has been led by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179988","179988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29035","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which external consultants are used by his Department regarding the formulation of its policy on reforming defence procurement; and what the cost to the public purse has been for each such consultant.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179989","179989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29036","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the sufficiency of the number of midwives trained to offer perinatal mental health support within the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179966","179966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29037","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to line (ii) of Table 2.5 of the Autumn Statement, whether his Department has decided to sell parts of the pre-2012 income contingent repayment student loan book.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180000","180000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29038","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and which NHS trusts and foundation trusts have sufficient levels of midwives trained to support women dealing with perinatal mental illness.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179967","179967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29039","2013-12-16","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what business deals involving conducting business in Tibetan areas were signed during his recent visit to China.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180001","180001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29040","2013-12-16","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he raised specific political prisoners' cases with the Chinese government in his recent visit to that country.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180002","180002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29041","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's plans are to support employment and support allowance (ESA) claimants whose work capability assessments are being reconsidered, but who are unable to claim ESA during the reconsideration or appeal period.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179968","179968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29042","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2013, Official Report, column 696W, on armed forces: young people, when he expects the terms of reference of that review to be finalised; and if he will publish those terms of reference before publication of the initial report.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179978","179978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29043","2013-12-16","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, which charitable organisations and non-governmental organisations campaigning on human rights issues he met during his recent visit to China.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180003","180003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29044","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's plans are to support employment and support allowance (ESA) claimants whose work capability assessments are being reconsidered, but who are ineligible to claim either ESA or jobseeker's allowance during the reconsideration or appeal period.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179969","179969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29045","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to commemorate the achievements of Mediterranean Command in World War Two.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179979","179979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29046","2013-12-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which food banks each Minister in his Department has visited since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180013","180013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29047","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what veto powers the Welsh Government has in respect of which territorial entities are able to use sterling.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179970","179970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29048","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what timetable his Department has set for improvements to the A27 corridor between Worthing and Shoreham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180005","180005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29049","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2013, Official Report, column 787W, on sexual offences: victim support schemes, what support is available to male perpetrators of sexual violence or abuse whose offending behaviour is related to their own past experience as a victim of sexual abuse or violence.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180010","180010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29050","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she expects to make the announcement on digital radio infrastructure.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179971","179971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29051","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse has been of the (a) salary, (b) hotel costs, (c) air fares, (d) rail fares, (e) taxi fares, (f) use of official car and driver and (g) any other benefits-in-kind accrued by the Chief of Defence Materiel since his appointment on 4 January 2011.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179990","179990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29052","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time for a Capita-run health assessment for those seeking to claim Personal Independence Payment is; what procedure Capita uses to notify claimants of cancelled assessments; and what telephone number Capita uses for the Personal Independence Payment claimaint helpline.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180011","180011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29053","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 824W, on students: fees and charges, what recent estimate of non-repayment of loans he has made.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180006","180006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29054","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the details were of each official overseas trip undertaken by the Chief of Defence Materiel since his appointment on 4 January 2011; and what the cost of each such trip was.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179991","179991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29055","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the value of increasing the coverage of local radio stations on DAB transmission frequency.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179972","179972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29056","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when (a) Ministers, (b) special advisers and (c) officials in his Department have met with Mr Lawrence Tomlinson since May 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180007","180007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29057","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to increase the number of DAB transmitters.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179973","179973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29058","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when her Department will publish the action plan on nuisance calls.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180012","180012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29059","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Mr Lawrence Tomlinson's report on RBS was (a) seen, (b) amended and (c) approved by (i) Ministers, (ii) special advisers and (iii) officials in his Department before its publication on 25 November 2013.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180008","180008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29060","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that the switchover to DAB only happens when the majority of consumer radio listening is conducted through digital signals.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179974","179974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29061","2013-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which food banks each Minister in his Department has visited since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180014","180014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29062","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to increase investment on improving local DAB coverage.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179975","179975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29063","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 824W, on students: fees and charges, what the structural problems in the forecasting model were.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180009","180009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29064","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which food banks each Minister in his Department has visited since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180015","180015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29065","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which food banks each of the Ministers in his Department has visited since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180016","180016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29066","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what food banks each of the Ministers in his Department has visited since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180017","180017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29067","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the sale of alcohol at Government-controlled motorway service areas.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180041","180041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29068","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations she has received on the DAB switchover.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179976","179976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29069","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the proportion of accident and emergency departments which have at least one alcohol liaison nurse.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180042","180042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29070","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to  ensure that digital infrastructure can be used by local and national radio stations.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179977","179977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29071","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the annual exposure of children to alcohol advertisements on (a) television, (b) billboards, (c) cinema screens and (d) the internet.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180043","180043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29072","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the safe maximum level of exposure children should have to alcohol advertising on (a) television, (b) billboards, (c) cinema screens and (d) the internet.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180044","180044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29073","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when consultations between (a) him, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department and trades unions regarding the implementation of the Defence Equipment and Support plus proposals are planned to take place.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180018","180018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29074","2013-12-16","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, for what reasons Gordon Johncox, Managing Director of Aston Manor Brewery, was invited to join his recent delegation to China; and what role he played during the visit.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180045","180045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29075","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2013, Official Report, column 677W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what supporting activities are provided by his Department to any civil unmanned system developers or operators when those applications may have some defence outcome.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180028","180028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29076","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK were admitted to their first choice university in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180046","180046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29077","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 70W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, which remotely piloted in-service aircraft systems are known to have flown in the UK outside danger areas or segregated airspace.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180029","180029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29078","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 70W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what information his Department records or collates on the trialling or other use of unmanned aerial systems by MOD state bodies in UK air space.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180030","180030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29079","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have met their counterparts in the Cabinet Office and the Treasury on the liberalisation of pay and conditions as part of his Defence Equipment and Support plus proposals in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180019","180019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29080","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 70W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what testing and evaluation of unmanned aerial system capabilities is being conducted or is planned for 2014 by 56(R) Squadron at the Air Warfare Centre.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180031","180031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29081","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 70W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, which Government department or body records or collates information on the trialling or other use of unmanned aerial systems by state bodies in UK airspace.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180032","180032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29082","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to table 2.5 of the Autumn Statement 2013, what estimate his Department has made of (a) gross proceeds from sale of the student loan book, (b) surrendered repayment income and (c) net proceeds arising from the sale of the student loan book.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180047","180047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29083","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2013, Official Report, column 640W, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Information Exchange Agreement with the United States on unmanned aerial systems.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180033","180033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29084","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of clinical commissioning groups with a (a) specialist designed lead for perinatal mental health and (b) perinatal mental health strategy.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179992","179992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29085","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GPs (a) with training in dealing with perinatal mental illness and (b) who have received refresher training in the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179993","179993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29086","2013-12-19","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the number of pelican crossings, puffin crossings and countdown crossings in operation on national and on local authority roads.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180051","180051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29087","2013-12-19","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the circumstances in which a pelican crossing can have a superior safety record to that of a puffin crossing.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180052","180052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29088","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support the economy by reducing rates of high street shopping in towns.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180034","180034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29089","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what employment changes will apply to (a) existing Defence Equipment and Support (DE & S) personnel and (b) staff brought into DE and S under his DE & S plus model; and whether any such staff will receive remuneration higher than that of the Prime Minister under these proposals.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180020","180020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29090","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that every man has a health MOT with his GP between the ages of 40 and 50.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180035","180035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29091","2013-12-19","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the puffin pedestrian crossing accident study published by TRL in March 2011, for what reasons his Department permits local authorities to install new pelican crossings.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180053","180053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29092","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what work his Department will undertake on the development of the Defence Equipment and Support plus financial control and management systems.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180021","180021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29093","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been repossessed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180036","180036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29094","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much will be saved from his Department's annual budget as a result of the Defence Equipment and Support plus proposals.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180022","180022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29095","2013-12-19","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department needs to commission further research before mandating that local highway authorities discontinue installation or renewal of pelican crossings.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180054","180054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29096","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, under what criteria the new Chief Executive of Defence Equipment and Support was appointed.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180023","180023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29097","2013-12-19","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will issue guidance to local highway authorities on the dangers of pelican crossings on roads with multi-lane approaches.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180055","180055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29098","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Chief of Defence Materiel will become Chief Executive of Defence Equipment and Support plus; and whether his contract of employment has yet been signed.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180024","180024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29099","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will update his Department's current guidance on the responsibility of private landlords to install carbon monoxide detectors in residential properties.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180025","180025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29100","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many pensioners claimed the over-75 free television licence in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179994","179994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29101","2013-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Syrian counterpart on the mass graves discovered in Sadad in Syria.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180037","180037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29102","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the smoking prevalence rate is in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179995","179995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29103","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Brigg and Goole constituency are employed in the retail sector.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179996","179996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29104","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the number of new (a) pelican crossings and (b) puffin crossings installed on roads in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011 and (iii) 2012.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180048","180048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29105","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are studying politics at AS and A Level in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179997","179997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29106","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which local authorities installed new pelican crossings in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180049","180049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29107","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the expected length of contracts put out for tender under those areas of the Defence Equipment and Support plus model which require additional support from the private sector is; and when he expects any such tenders to be announced.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180026","180026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29108","2013-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) China, (b) Saudi Arabia and (c) Vietnam on protection of religious liberty in those countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180038","180038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29109","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list types of pedestrian crossing in order of their safety performance.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180050","180050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29110","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with medical professionals about recent innovations in surgery to treat kidney cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180039","180039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29111","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the introduction of a new human resources function within the Defence Equipment and Support plus model will include powers of hiring and firing beyond those currently used within the civil service.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180027","180027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29112","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children have been diagnosed with juvenile arthritis in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180040","180040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29113","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2013, Official Report, column 412W, on Army: Germany, what meetings he, Ministers and Officials in his Department have had with counterparts in (a) the Ministry of Defence and (b) the Department for Education on the effect of re-basing on the local authorities in which (i) Dalton Barracks, Abingdon, (ii) Kendrew Barracks, Cottesmore and (iii) Imjin Barracks, Gloucester are situated.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179998","179998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29114","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children have been living in poverty in Lancashire in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180056","180056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29115","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to encourage more young people to be involved with charity.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180057","180057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29116","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to encourage charities to appoint more young trustees.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180058","180058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29117","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2013, Official Report, column 700W, on cancer, what steps (a) his Department and (b) NHS England is taking to ensure that cancer survival rates in Britain match the level of the best in Europe.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180059","180059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29118","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the experience of older people with cancer.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180060","180060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29119","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the prevention and earlier diagnosis of (a) kidney, (b) stomach, (c) ovarian and (d) colorectal cancer.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180061","180061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29120","2013-12-12","Cabinet Office","2013-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons a quote from Jonathan Isaby, Political Director of the Taxpayer's Alliance, was included in his Department's press release, Government savings reach £5.4 billion at mid-year point, published on 7 November 2013.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179999","179999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29121","2013-12-16","Prime Minister","2013-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, whether Government officials and businesses who accompanied him on his recent visit to China used and referred to the UK's national action plan on business and human rights in their work on that visit.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180004","180004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28570","2013-12-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with social media sites on protecting children online.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179010","179010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28571","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the recorded average temperatures at Capel Curig, Gwynedd weather station, used for the calculation of cold weather payments in each week of the last three years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178924","178924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28572","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2013, Official Report, column 849W, on unmanned aerial and marine vehicles, what assessment he has made of the potential use of unmanned vehicles for maritime reconnaissance by the Air ISTAR Optimisation Study.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178925","178925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28573","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work capability assessment centres have induction loops for deaf and hard of hearing people.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178926","178926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28574","2013-12-11","Department for Transport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total value was of departmental underspend on rail maintenance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178927","178927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28575","2013-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many boarding establishments are licensed as quarantine kennels in (a) England and (b) Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178928","178928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28576","2013-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many kennel spaces there are in quarantine kennels in (a) England and (b) Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178929","178929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28577","2013-12-11","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons she has decided that Boko Haram was not a threat to the life of Mr Isa Muaza.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178930","178930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28578","2013-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the results were of the most recent assessment of the risk to people living in Nigeria of Boko Haram.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178931","178931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28579","2013-12-11","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what upper limit is set to the costs of deporting a single individual.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178932","178932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28580","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what responsibility the Commonwealth War Graves Commission has for Crimean War graves in (a) Turkey and (b) Ukraine.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178933","178933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28581","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what capital investment took place at Northwick Park Hospital, part of North West London Hospitals NHS Trust, between 1997 and 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178962","178962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28582","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what (a) legislative and (b) administrative changes are required for the Public Appointments Commissioner to undertake the task of appointing a recognition panel for the purposes of newspaper regulation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178963","178963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28583","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects refurbishment work at Northwick Park Accident and Emergency Department to be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178964","178964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28584","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many small businesses in Harrogate and Knaresborough constituency will benefit from the extension of the small business rate relief scheme to April 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178934","178934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28585","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he (a) has and (b) is aware of for further investment (i) in primary care services in Harrow, (ii) for extending opening hours GP surgeries and (iii) for expanding the opening hours of Alexandra Avenue polyclinic; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178965","178965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28586","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in the new Adaptive Force Brigade Headquarters in Yorkshire will transfer from 15 Brigade Headquarters, and how many from 4 Mechanised Brigade Headquarters; how many staff in the new Brigade Headquarters will work on (a) Firm Base functions hitherto undertaken by 15 Brigade and (b) Adaptive Force functions; and what assessment he has made of the feasibility of basing the Brigadier and his Firm Base staff in York and the Brigadier's Adaptive Force staff in Catterick.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178954","178954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28587","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that standard forms for disability living allowance applications capture an accurate portrayal of needs.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178935","178935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28588","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he (a) has made and (b) is aware of as to when the downgrading of emergency services at (i) West Middlesex, (ii) Hammersmith, (iii) Ealing, (iv) Charing Cross and (v) Central Middlesex will commence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178966","178966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28589","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers were injured in Phase 1 and Phase 2 training in each quarter of 2012 and 2013; and how many of those soldiers were using the Pay to Dine system.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178955","178955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28590","2013-12-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the reduction in consumer energy bills announced on 2 December 2013 will apply to off-grid gas consumers.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178936","178936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28591","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus employees work directly with external employers in order to source work for jobseekers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178967","178967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28592","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus offices contain staff who work directly with external employers in order to source work for jobseekers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178968","178968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28593","2013-12-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the future growth of the fracking industry in England will require the use of water from Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178937","178937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28594","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports he has received suggesting that a significant proportion of soldiers injured during training were undernourished as a result of the introduction of the Pay to Dine system.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178956","178956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28595","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage British businesses to ensure that supply chain businesses are free from slavery and the effects of human trafficking.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178969","178969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28596","2013-12-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people are enrolled in adult skills sessions in Cannock Chase constituency.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178957","178957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28597","2013-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of current political developments in Ukraine.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178970","178970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28598","2013-12-11","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the (a) take-up of places in and (b) performance of academies in Cannock Chase constituency.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178958","178958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28599","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last met her European counterparts to discuss the human rights situation of the Roma in the EU.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178971","178971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28600","2013-12-11","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many businesses in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire have been fined for employing illegal foreign national workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178959","178959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28601","2013-12-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals have resulted in local authority decisions being overturned by the planning inspector in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178960","178960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28602","2013-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the degree of over-leverage in water companies' finances; and what assessment he has made of the effect of such over-leverage for Government infrastructure guarantees.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178938","178938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28603","2013-12-11","Cabinet Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Government contracts and of what value have been awarded to companies or projects based in (a) Livingston constituency and (b) West Lothian local authority area since May 2007.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178944","178944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28604","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the efficiency of the Pensions Ombudsman.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178939","178939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28605","2013-12-11","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of crime in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178961","178961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28606","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken to process an application to the Pensions Ombudsman has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178940","178940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28607","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what consultation was undertaken prior to the design and introduction of the standard dropbox forms for disability living allowance applications.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178941","178941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28608","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department has (a) produced, (b) commissioned and (c) evaluated on the effectiveness of addressing drug-related offending by extending drug testing requirements from Class A to Class A and B drugs for those on licence and under the new supervision period.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178982","178982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28609","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many caseworkers have been employed by the Pensions Ombudsman in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178942","178942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28610","2013-12-11","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he intends to make a decision on the future of the thalidomide health grant.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178943","178943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28611","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the findings of the studies carried out in 2010 into moving the Headquarters of 15 Brigade from Imphal Barracks, York to (a) Bourlon Barracks, Catterick and (b) Queen Elizabeth Barracks, Strensall were on the (i) feasibility and (ii) cost of moving the Headquarters; what estimate he made of how many staff Catterick and Strensall could accommodate; for what reasons it was decided not to move the Headquarters; and if he will place a copy of these studies in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178945","178945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28612","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the costs arising from the extension of drug testing requirements for those on licence and under the new supervision period from Class A to Class A and B drugs; and what steps he is taking to ensure that adequate drug service provision to deal with the extended testing is available in all local areas.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178983","178983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28613","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has received from the Reserve Forces and Cadets Association for Yorkshire and the Humber on how the region can improve the recruitment of Reserve Forces Personnel.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178946","178946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28614","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the Reserve Forces are or were based in (a) York and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber (i) now and (ii) in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178947","178947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28615","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what targets he has set for increasing the number of Reserve Forces based in Yorkshire and the Humber as part of his overall plan to increase the number of reservists to 30,000.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178948","178948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28616","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has (a) produced, (b) commissioned, (c) evaluated any research suggesting a correlation between offending behaviour and cannabis use; and whether such research informed his decision to extend drug testing requirements from Class A to Class A and B drugs for those on licence and under the new supervision period.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178984","178984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28617","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the consequences for due diligence and the requirements for sponsorship of the delisting of Eurasian Natural Resources Corporation from the London Stock Exchange.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178972","178972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28618","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has undertaken an evaluation of (a) the effects on the probation system of the introduction of a payment by results model and (b) the effectiveness of similar systems operating in other countries.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178985","178985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28619","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff based at 15 Brigade Headquarters he expects (a) to move to Catterick and (b) to be made redundant as a result of the establishment of the new Adaptive Force Brigade Headquarters at Catterick; and what estimate was made of the removal expenses, travel and subsistence, redundancy payments, early retirement payments and other personnel costs associated with the move.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178949","178949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28620","2013-12-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has for future ownership of Channel 4.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179026","179026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28621","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when a judgement was made on the correct valuation of Royal Mail shares ahead of privatisation.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178973","178973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28622","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of providing IT systems for the new Adaptive Force Brigade Headquarters in Yorkshire of the Headquarters being based at (a) Imphal Barracks, York, (b) Queen Elizabeth Barracks, Strensall and (c) Bourlon Barracks, Catterick.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178950","178950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28623","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role the new Yorkshire-based Adaptive Force Brigade Headquarters will play in managing the recruitment of reservists.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178951","178951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28624","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of providing suitable premises for the new Adaptive Force Brigade Headquarters at (a) Imphal Barracks, York, (b) Strensall Barracks, York and (c) Catterick Garrison.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178952","178952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28625","2013-12-12","Department for Transport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any imports of float glass used in the construction of trains in the UK will be subject to independent testing in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178974","178974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28626","2013-12-12","Women and Equalities","2013-12-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress has been made in promoting the provision of breast feeding and baby care facilities in high streets.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179025","179025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28627","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many days of sick leave were taken by staff at (a) HM Prison Oakwood and (b) all adult prisons in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178975","178975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28628","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average daily cost is of a (a) Crown court trial and (b) magistrates' court trial.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178976","178976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28629","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the relationship between depression and musculoskeletal conditions; and how NHS England is working with primary care services to ensure that such multi-morbidities are addressed by GPs.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179027","179027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28630","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the staff turnover was at each adult prison in England and Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178977","178977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28631","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 19 November 2013, Official Report, column 43WS, on student support in England, how much funding the 23 alternative providers of Higher National Diplomas and Higher National Certificates received from his Department through the Higher Education Funding Council for England in 2012-13 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179015","179015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28632","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment Public Health England has made of (a) the effect of an aging population on prevalence of disease and (b) the consequent public health challenges.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179028","179028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28633","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the written statement of 5 December 2013, on universal credit, for how long he envisages developing two separate universal credit IT systems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178978","178978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28634","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 19 November 2013, Official Report, column 43WS, on student support in England, what estimate his Department has made of the savings resulting from the decision to instruct the 23 alternative providers to suspend recruitment of students for Higher National Certificates and Higher National Diplomas in the current academic year; and whether he plans to continue this policy in future years.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179016","179016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28635","2013-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the written ministerial statement of 5 December 2013 on universal credit, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of implementing each of the two separate IT systems currently being developed for universal credit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178979","178979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28636","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what responsibility 15 Brigade has for planning and co-ordinating resilience operations in response to floods, major weather events, major fires and other civil emergencies; and what assessment he has made on the future effectiveness of civil-military co-operation of the establishment of the Army's new Adaptive Force Brigade Headquarters in (a) Catterick and (b) York.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178953","178953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28637","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal entrants to the UK have been detected by sniffer dogs in the (a) port of Calais, (b) port of Dunkirk and (c) Channel Tunnel in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179017","179017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28638","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals were deported from (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178980","178980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28639","2013-12-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2013, Official report, columns 668-9W, on National Lottery: Olympic Games 2012, what estimate she has made of the receipts that will arise on completion of the Olympic Village in 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179029","179029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28640","2013-12-12","Cabinet Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of Roma currently residing in the UK.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179018","179018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28641","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints and on what subjects the Independent Monitoring Board of HM Prison Oakwood has received from prisoners in each year since that prison opened.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178981","178981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28642","2013-12-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether British patent attorneys who hold a British Patent Attorney Litigators Certificate will be issued with a certificate by the UK authorities confirming that they are lawyers for the purpose of rights before the Unified Patent Court.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178986","178986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28643","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors and (b) nurses worked in NHS accident and emergency departments in (i) Coventry, (ii) the West Midlands and (iii) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179019","179019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28644","2013-12-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that the number of people proceeded against under the offence of unauthorised copying of a registered design is monitored closely; and if he will review the effectiveness of that offence two years after it has come into force.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178987","178987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28645","2013-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of possible sanctions against Iran for a breach of the Iran nuclear agreement.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178988","178988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28646","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the banks and advisers involved in the Royal Mail privatisation have been paid.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179020","179020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28647","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the completion date of the Financial Conduct Authority redress scheme will be.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178989","178989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28648","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the banks about completion of the Financial Conduct Authority redress scheme.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178990","178990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28649","2013-12-11","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued to care homes on prevention of the spread of (a) norovirus and (b) other diseases.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179006","179006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28650","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assistance his Department is providing to deaf or hard of hearing people who wish to have their work capability assessment videoed.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178996","178996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28651","2013-12-11","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the links between stress and obesity.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179007","179007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28652","2013-12-12","Department for International Development","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what non-governmental organisations have been allocated official funds for the relief effort in the Philippines; and how much has been (a) allocated to them and (b) received by those organisations.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179021","179021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28653","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the evidence given by Dr Mark Carney to the Treasury Select Committee on 26 November 2013; and if he will instruct the Financial Conduct Authority to conduct an inquiry into RBS's treatment of small businesses.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178991","178991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28654","2013-12-11","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the expenditure by NHS England (a) in total and (b) per capita for each GP practice in England was in 2012-13.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178997","178997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28655","2013-12-12","Department for International Development","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in (a) France, (b) Italy, (c) Russia and (d) Brazil about those countries' donations to the UN Flash Appeal for aid to the Philippines.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179022","179022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28656","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to prepare a preliminary proposal for refuelling the Vanguard class submarines; what the timetable is for that work; and what budget has been set aside for that work.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179008","179008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28657","2013-12-11","Department for Transport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the recent announcement by the Welsh Assembly Executive of investment in the North Wales Coast Mainline, what discussions he has had with the Welsh Assembly Executive on the effect of such investment on the Conwy Valley railway line.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178992","178992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28658","2013-12-12","Department for International Development","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with the European Commission on aid donations to Belarus.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179023","179023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28659","2013-12-12","Department for International Development","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with the European Commission on aid donations to the Philippines disaster relief effort.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179024","179024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28660","2013-12-11","Department for Transport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with train operating companies about increasing services on the North Wales Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178993","178993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28661","2013-12-11","Department for Transport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Network Rail and (b) train operating companies on improvements to Llandudno Junction train station.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178994","178994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28662","2013-12-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects the Financial Conduct Authority and the Prudential Regulation Authority to respond to his Department's referral to them of the Tomlinson Report.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178998","178998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28663","2013-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evaluation he has made of the effectiveness of the Environmental Audit Committee in overseeing the implementation of sustainable development policy since the abolition of the Sustainable Development Commission; and what discussions he has had with the Chair of that committee on the resources available to it to undertake that task.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179009","179009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28664","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the proportion of the total discretionary housing budget that has been spent during the last six months of 2012-13.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178995","178995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28665","2013-12-11","Wales Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the performance of Wales in the recent PISA rankings.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178999","178999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28708","2013-12-11","Department for International Development","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will consider increasing funding to provide additional shelters for female victims of violence in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179038","179038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28709","2013-12-11","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were referred for speech therapy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179039","179039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28710","2013-12-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had on the future of the Trawsfynydd nuclear site.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179000","179000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28711","2013-12-11","Wales Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had on the future of the Trawsfynydd nuclear site.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179001","179001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28712","2013-12-11","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the national funding formula will reflect local authorities' decisions on funding of pupils for whom English is an additional language; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179011","179011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28713","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make the new enterprise allowance available to work programme participants.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179002","179002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28714","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are currently registered as having employee shareholder status.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179012","179012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28715","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the suitability of Clifford Chance to conduct the internal investigation at RBS following the report made by Lawrence Tomlinson.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179003","179003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28716","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the average annual tax relief to individuals benefiting from employee shareholder status.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179013","179013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28717","2013-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department will set out plans to support environmentally-friendly farming following reform of the Common Agricultural Policy.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179004","179004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28718","2013-12-11","Cabinet Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of jobseekers over the age of (a) 50 and (b) 60 in (i) Glasgow North West constituency, (ii) Glasgow, (iii) Scotland and (iv) the UK in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179048","179048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28719","2013-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support farm environment schemes.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179005","179005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28720","2013-12-11","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the long-term effects of cyber bullying on its victims.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179040","179040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28721","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on training for people over the age of 50 looking for new jobs in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179049","179049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28722","2013-12-11","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to school teachers to assist them when dealing with cyber bullying.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179041","179041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28723","2013-12-11","Department for International Development","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking in partnership with the government of Afghanistan to (a) ensure that violent crimes committed against women and girls do not go uninvestigated or unpunished and (b) safeguard women's rights following withdrawal of Coalition forces.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179014","179014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28724","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people over the age of 25 who have been offered an apprenticeship in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179050","179050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28725","2013-12-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on promoting Small Business Saturday in each region.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179042","179042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28726","2013-12-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase the number of young people with the skills required to work in the nuclear industry.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179051","179051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28727","2013-12-11","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote campaigns to tackle prostate cancer.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179043","179043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28728","2013-12-11","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidelines have been issued to schools for tackling childhood obesity.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179044","179044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28729","2013-12-11","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to respond to its consultation entitled, Making the Nursery Milk Scheme more cost-effective.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179052","179052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28730","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs has spent in preparation for the implementation of universal credit to date.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179045","179045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28731","2013-12-12","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has allocated to Cornwall from the fund to help create care environments for people with dementia.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179060","179060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28732","2013-12-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the timeframe for full completion of the national coastal footpath around England.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179053","179053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28733","2013-12-11","Cabinet Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the Big Society initiative; and whether he had discussions with Civil Exchange on its audit of the Big Society initiative.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179046","179046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28734","2013-12-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department has budgeted for the introduction of a national coastal footpath around England.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179054","179054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28735","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what services providing independent domestic violence advisers received Government funding in each year since 2010; and how much each service received (a) nationally and (b) in each region in each year.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179061","179061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28736","2013-12-11","Cabinet Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the life expectancy for (a) men and (b) women is in (i) Glasgow North West constituency, (ii) Glasgow, (iii) Scotland and (iv) the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179047","179047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28737","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what services have received Government funding for rape crisis centres and helplines (a) nationally and (b) in each region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179062","179062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28738","2013-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the French Ministry of Foreign Affairs about the conflict in the Central African Republic; and what representations he has made at the (a) EU Foreign Affairs Council and (b) UN Security Council on the issue of funding for the deployment of French troops to the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179055","179055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28739","2013-12-11","Department for International Development","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the threat presented by the conflict in the Central African Republic to humanitarian efforts in that country; and what aid the Government is providing to humanitarian organisations operating in that country.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179056","179056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28740","2013-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made on the threat presented by the conflict in the Central African Republic to stability in the wider region.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179057","179057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28741","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are employed by HM Revenue and Customs in the High Net Worth Unit.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179030","179030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28742","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) assets and (b) personnel have been provided to operations in the Central African Republic; and for how long they will be operating in that theatre.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179058","179058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28743","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been allocated to each English local authority for under three provisions for buildings funded by the Priority School Building Programme.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179063","179063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28744","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on the Government-owned contractor-operated tender process to date.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179059","179059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28745","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs employees are working on the delivery of Real Time Information.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179031","179031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28746","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are employed by HM Revenue and Customs to locate and capture the 30 most wanted tax fugitives.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179032","179032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28747","2013-12-12","Scotland Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he last met representatives of food bank operators in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179065","179065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28748","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what reviews have been carried out relating to child abuse involving employees or former employees of her Department.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179033","179033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28749","2013-12-12","Scotland Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the implications for Scotland of the study he has commissioned of evidence on the landscape of food aid provision and access in the UK.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179064","179064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28750","2013-12-12","Scotland Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make it his policy to record the number of people using food banks in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179066","179066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28751","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what reviews are ongoing within her Department relating to historic cases of child sexual exploitation; and when she expects to report the results of these reviews.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179034","179034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28752","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2013, Official Report, columns 449-50W, on Shannon Matthews, if he will publish the consent order of the High Court dated 19 June 2013 and the explanation of how his decision was arrived at.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179035","179035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28753","2013-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has had discussions with Cambridgeshire and Peterborough Fire and Rescue Authority on submitting auditable data to the Chartered Institute of Public Finance and Accountancy in a timely fashion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179067","179067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28754","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employees of HM Revenue and Customs are working on the implementation of universal credit.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179068","179068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28755","2013-12-12","Northern Ireland Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress she has made on establishing a Bill of Rights for Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179036","179036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28756","2013-12-12","Northern Ireland Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings she has held with the Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission since assuming office.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179037","179037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28757","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's consultation on keeping children safe in education guidance, what role he envisages local authorities having in monitoring, supporting and challenging child safeguarding practice in schools.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179069","179069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28758","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish his Department's response to its consultation on keeping children safe in education; and when he plans to bring forward proposals arising from that consultation.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179070","179070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28759","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether GEO has been approved for the purposes of competitive tendering for probation services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179882","179882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28760","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether Delta has been approved for the purposes of competitive tendering for probation services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179883","179883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28761","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether Stonham Home Housing Group has been approved for the purposes of competitive tendering for probation services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179884","179884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28762","2013-12-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he intends to respond to the recommendations of the Shakespeare review of public sector information.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179081","179081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28763","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children took part in the early education pilot for disadvantaged two year old children before September 2013; and how many of the two year olds taking up the free early education offer from September 2013 (a) were new to the scheme and (b) took part in that pilot.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179863","179863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28764","2013-12-11","Department for International Development","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to halt the informalisation of labour market opportunities for women in developing countries.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179071","179071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28765","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the differences in progress being achieved by LEPs across the UK.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179864","179864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28766","2013-12-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the recommendations of the Shakespeare review of public sector information, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of a National Data Strategy on data publishers in the private sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179082","179082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28767","2013-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department expects air quality standards in central London to comply with UK and EU legal requirements.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179072","179072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28768","2013-12-12","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies received tax relief for workplace nurseries in the last period for which figures are available; and what the average amount of such relief was.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179865","179865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28769","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what responsibility the Commonwealth War Graves Commission has for Baltic campaign war graves in the Baltic region.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179083","179083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28770","2013-12-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the (a) level of and (b) trend in emissions of particulates from diesel vehicles in (i) central and (ii) Greater London.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179073","179073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28771","2013-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officers cap badged to regiments of the Household Division are currently serving.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179853","179853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28772","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the number of two year olds accessing (a) 15, (b) fewer than 10 and (c) fewer than five hours of free early education.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179866","179866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28773","2013-12-12","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what arrangements are in place for overseas students with a visa to study in Northern Ireland who arrive in the Republic of Ireland before making onward travel to their academic institutions.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179854","179854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28774","2013-12-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance his Department is planning to give to support the building of memorials in Ukraine to commemorate the UK's casualties in the Crimean War.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179084","179084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28775","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what (a) assessment was made of the UK economy and (b) evidential basis was used in reaching the decision to maintain the fuel duty differential between road fuel gases other than LPG autogas and conventional fuels and narrowing the fuel differential between LPG autogas and conventional fuels.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179074","179074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28776","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders who breached their Community Order received a custodial sentence in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179867","179867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28777","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders who breached their Suspended Sentence Order received a custodial sentence in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179868","179868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28778","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer to the right hon Member for Edinburgh South West, of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 1118, on the Autumn Statement, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on its forecast for North Sea oil revenues in 2016.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179075","179075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28779","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer to the right hon Member for Edinburgh South West, of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 1118, on the Autumn Statement, what assessment he has made of the forecast for North Sea oil revenues made by the Scottish Government.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179076","179076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28780","2013-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Republic of Ireland on arrangements for overseas students with a valid visa to study in Northern Ireland who enter through the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179855","179855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28781","2013-12-11","HM Treasury","2013-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer to the right hon Member for Edinburgh South West, of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 1118, on the Autumn Statement, if he will publish the advice from the Office for Budget Responsibility regarding its forecast for North Sea oil revenues.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179077","179077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28782","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether Atos has been approved for the purposes of competitive tendering for the provision of probation services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179856","179856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28783","2013-12-11","Department for Transport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many schools had lollipop patrols in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179085","179085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28784","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many companies or consortia have been approved for the purposes of competitive tendering for the provision of probation services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179857","179857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28785","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders who received a custodial sentence have previously served (a) no, (b) between one and four, (c) between five and nine and (d) more than 10 community sentences in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179869","179869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28786","2013-12-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will take steps to build with other members of the Human Rights Council a broad coalition of support for the UN to establish an independent international investigation into alleged serious violations of international human rights and the international humanitarian law in Sri Lanka before the March 2014 session of that council.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179078","179078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28787","2013-12-11","Department of Health","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on campaigns alerting people to the symptoms of lung cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179086","179086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28788","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether Capita has been approved for the purposes of competitive tendering for the provision of probation services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179858","179858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28789","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the criteria are to trigger cold weather payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179079","179079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28790","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether G4S has been approved for the purposes of competitive tendering for the provision of probation services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179859","179859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28791","2013-12-11","Home Office","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with social media sites on protecting children online.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179087","179087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28792","2013-12-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which wards in each county borough in Wales received cold weather payments in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179080","179080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28793","2013-12-11","Women and Equalities","2013-12-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she has taken to support the Church of England's General Synod on the subject of women bishops.","Biography information for Guy Opperman","Guy Opperman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179088","179088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28794","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Funding and structures for local economic growth, published on 6 December 2013, what assessment he has made of the effect on local growth of the dip in funding from central Government at the time of the transition from regional development agencies to the new local growth landscape.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179860","179860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28795","2013-12-11","Department for Transport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total (a) value and (b) number of outstanding car parking fines was in (i) England, (ii) Wales, (iii) Scotland and (iv) Northern Ireland on the last date for which data is available.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179845","179845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28796","2013-12-12","Department for Education","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people applied to the early years apprenticeship bursary scheme between 5 September and 22 November 2013; how many people have applied to that scheme since 23 November 2013; how many childcare settings the National College of Teaching and Leadership has identified which are willing to take on an apprentice; and what funding has been committed to that scheme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179861","179861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28797","2013-12-11","Department for Transport","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many car parking fines were issued by local authorities in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland in (i) 2011, (ii) 2012 and (iii) 2013.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179846","179846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28798","2013-12-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 3.24 of the National Audit Office report, Funding and structures for local economic growth, published on 6 December 2013, for what reasons 40 Regional Growth Fund schemes achieved less than 25 per cent of their annual job targets.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179862","179862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28799","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the national completion rates for each of the community sentence requirements were in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179870","179870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28800","2013-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was between the requirements of a community sentence being set and those requirements commencing in each probation trust in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179871","179871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/28801","2013-12-11","Department for International Development","2013-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding the Government has allocated to recruit, retain and promote female police officers in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 179847","179847"
