"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101757","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of exploitation have been identified by the Gangmasters Licensing Authority in sectors other than the agriculture sector in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212649","212649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101758","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212617","212617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101759","2014-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to strengthen enforcement of regulatory safeguards for agency workers.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212650","212650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101760","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to promote the UK as a location of choice for life science investment in trade missions.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212638","212638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101761","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs in each region and constituent part of the UK which are supported by the life science industry.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212639","212639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101762","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the number of higher education students purchasing assignment writing services.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212580","212580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101763","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of the practice of retentions as a means of insurance in the construction industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212581","212581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101764","2014-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Education (Student Support) (Amendment) Regulations 2014, when Student Finance England will issue guidance for students intending to apply for financial support for 2015-16.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212588","212588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101765","2014-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what tonnage of imports of wood pellets there has been into the UK in the last three years.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212602","212602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101766","2014-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices in (a) England, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland were paid the apprentice rate of the national minimum wage in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212604","212604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101767","2014-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects to publish the 2014 Apprenticeship Pay Survey.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212605","212605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101768","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he agrees that responsible and sustainable investment practices are beneficial to businesses, the wider economy and society as a whole.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212534","212534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101769","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the UK has supported inclusion of the investor-state dispute settlement system in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212541","212541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101770","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that signatories of the Prompt Payment Code adhere to its regulations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212559","212559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101771","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote the Prompt Payment Code as a means of ensuring that small and medium-sized businesses do not suffer financial hardship as a result of late payments.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212560","212560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101772","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what measures are in place to enable the Prompt Payment Code is effective in preventing late payments.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212561","212561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101773","2014-11-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will carry out an international comparative assessment of the ease of registering for the new .uk domains as a UK business.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212645","212645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101774","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what comparative assessment he has made of the competitiveness of the (a) UK, (b) France, (c) Germany, (d) China and (e) US life science industry.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212635","212635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101775","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what structures his Department has in place to ensure that (a) the Life Sciences Organisation and (b) the Office for Life Sciences co-ordinate with the MHRA and National Institute of Health and Care Excellence.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212636","212636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101776","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to increase the level of access to credit to businesses in Fareham constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212666","212666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101777","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support small and medium-sized businesses in Fareham constituency.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212667","212667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101778","2014-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices under 19 were paid less than £90 per week in the last year for which data are available.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212725","212725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101779","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Department issues on the use of retentions as insurance in the construction industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212687","212687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101780","2014-11-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations he has received on Nominet's policy of first offering the new .uk domain names to the holder of the equivalent .co.uk domain.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212691","212691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101781","2014-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many grants were distributed to the video games industry under Innovate UK's Smart Programme in 2013-14; and what the value of such grants was.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212706","212706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101782","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what regulatory safeguards are in place to protect agency workers from trafficking; if she will review the effectiveness of those safeguards; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212708","212708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101783","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps Post Office Ltd is taking to encourage banks to expand availability of their services through the Post Office network.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212738","212738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101784","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, at what locations in the UK Post Office Ltd has installed applicant enrolment identification machines.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212739","212739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101785","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote the UK as a hub for global trade to foreign investors involved in the telecoms industry.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212747","212747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101786","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's proposed changes to Disabled Students' Allowances on access by disabled students to assistive technology.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212759","212759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101787","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's proposed changes to Disabled Students' Allowances on rates of entry by disabled people to further and higher education.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212760","212760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101788","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with (a) disability charities and organisations and (b) universities and colleges on the effects of his Department's proposed changes to Disabled Students' Allowance.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212761","212761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101789","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with specialist subcontractors in the construction industry on tackling late payment to small and medium-sized businesses.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212762","212762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101790","2014-11-03","Cabinet Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how often (a) pneumococcal disease and (b) pneumococcal community-acquired pneumonia was mentioned on death certificates in England and Wales in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212755","212755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101791","2014-11-03","Cabinet Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that government departments pay contractors on time and in full; and if he will take steps to ensure that all future payments to subcontractors who work on government projects are paid on time and in full.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212730","212730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101792","2014-11-04","Cabinet Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what income accrued to his Department from commercial activities at the former premises of the Civil Service College, Sunningdale, in each of the last four financial years; and if he will publish a list of users of those premises.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212713","212713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101793","2014-11-03","Cabinet Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to intriduce LED lighting throughout buildings and sites used by (a) the Cabinet Office, (b) the Deputy Prime Minister's Office and (c) 10 Downing Street; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in such sites which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212616","212616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101794","2014-11-04","Cabinet Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse was of the former Civil Service College at Sunningdale in each of the last four financial years; and what spending is planned on the college.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212592","212592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101795","2014-11-04","HM Treasury","2014-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria is used to establish whether a sector is high-risk in terms of non-compliance with the national minimum wage; and which sectors are so defined.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212652","212652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101796","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the merits of introducing fiscal incentives to more widespread use of LED lighting.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212613","212613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101797","2014-11-04","HM Treasury","2014-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what training is provided to national minimum wage inspectors to identify cases of trafficking.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212651","212651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101798","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses have (a) claimed and (b) been successfully awarded employment allowance in (i) Bury St Edmunds, (ii) Suffolk, (iii) the East of England and (iv) England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212563","212563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101799","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212632","212632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101800","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, to the hon. Member for Vale of Glamorgan, Official Report, column 26W, on Bitcoin, what his policy is on the regulation of Bitcoin derivatives and other securities paired to digital currencies.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212665","212665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101801","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his speech of 6 August 2014 on FinTech, what progress his Department has made on its programme of work exploring the potential of virtual currencies and digital money.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212668","212668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101802","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the ability of businesses using digital currencies to open a UK bank account.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212669","212669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101803","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what forecasts he has made of the long-term trends in house-building in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212748","212748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101804","2014-11-03","Cabinet Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that procurement regulations do not increase the administrative burden (a) on local authorities seeking to procure education services and (b) on providers seeking to tender for contracts for education services.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212539","212539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101805","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will issue guidance to (a) local authorities and (b) fire and rescue authorities that they should implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting in their buildings.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212615","212615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101806","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212619","212619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101807","2014-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will prepare and publish a new draft code for sustainable homes.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212607","212607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101808","2014-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to enable local authorities to promote sustainable house building.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212608","212608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101809","2014-11-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212620","212620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101810","2014-11-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to increase media coverage and commercial investment in women's sport; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212578","212578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101811","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to enable war widows who remarried between 1973 and 2005 to keep their pensions.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212562","212562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101812","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212621","212621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101813","2014-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will review his Department's policy on the Accumulated Campaign Service Medal.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212655","212655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101814","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military personnel and (b) UK personnel there will be in the NATO training, advice and assistance mission in Afghanistan in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212584","212584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101815","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) assets and (b) personnel are taking part in NATO Exercise Iron Sword.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212731","212731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101816","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what upgrades the Sentinel R1 aircraft is receiving; and what the (a) purpose, (b) cost to the public purse and (c) completion date of those upgrades is.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212732","212732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101817","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where Sentinel R1 aircraft will be based in their maritime surveillance role.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212733","212733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101818","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the upgrades to the Sentinel R1 aircraft will include the ability to collect and process (a) magnetic anomaly and (b) bathymetric data.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212734","212734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101819","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports he has received of a sonic boom over the outer-Hebrides on 29 October 2014; and what assessment he has made of the likely cause.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212735","212735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101820","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the terms of engagement are of the deployment to Sierra Leone to tackle Ebola.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212680","212680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101821","2014-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is with respect to the Accumulated Campaign Service Medal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212656","212656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101822","2014-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the extent of damage done to the wrecks of HMS Repulse and HMS Prince of Wales; what steps can be taken better to prevent the desecration of these designated war graves; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212659","212659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101823","2014-11-04","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-10-30","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the performance of local enterprise partnerships (LEPs); and which LEPs he has assessed as (a) highest and (b) lowest performing.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212693","212693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101824","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that children at secondary school are being efficiently grouped according to their academic ability.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212550","212550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101825","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many SENCO-accredited courses are being run in (a) colleges and (b) universities in 2013-14.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212540","212540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101826","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent progress she has made on improving financial education in schools.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212533","212533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101827","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout her Department's buildings and sites; if she will estimate the proportion of lighting in her Department which is LED; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212622","212622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101828","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will issue guidance to schools and sixth form colleges that they should implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting in their buildings.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212610","212610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101829","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that schools do not use charges for uniform, school trips and other activities as a means of selection.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212670","212670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101830","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Children's Commission on Poverty report, At What Cost? Exposing the impact of poverty on school life, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that poverty does not prevent children and young people taking full advantage of school life.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212664","212664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101831","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit schools from taking a commission on the sale of school uniform to parents.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212672","212672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101832","2014-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the social cost per tonne of emitted carbon his Department uses to judge the cost benefit of energy policies.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212727","212727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101833","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of hydraulic fracturing being adopted in the Welsh valleys on seismic activity in that area.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212766","212766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101834","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the use of water for hydraulic fracking on the general supply and cost of water.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212767","212767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101835","2014-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many onshore wind turbine applications in the UK were (a) approved and (b) rejected in the year to October 2014.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212714","212714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101836","2014-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many onshore wind turbine applications in Nottinghamshire were (a) approved and (b) rejected in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013 and (iii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212716","212716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101837","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his policy is on requiring companies to inform people about fracking under their home or land.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212774","212774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101838","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the ratio of energy used in extraction, including to energy produced, taking into account transportation costs and possible damage to infrastructure.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212772","212772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101839","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the potential effect the investor protection clause of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership will have on the number of legal challenges to the fracking industry.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212773","212773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101840","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to put in place a planning process for fracking which diverges from existing planning rules.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212775","212775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101841","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether he plans to make Government subsidies available to the fracking industry during exploration, gas extraction and land reclamation.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212776","212776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101842","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the mode of storage and containment of water that has been used for the hydraulic fracking permitted by the Government to date; and whether any sites have been designated for this purpose.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212768","212768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101843","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what contingency plans his Department has in place for clean-up after fracking activity in the event that small fracking companies go bankrupt or refuse to take responsibility for any necessary cleaning.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212769","212769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101844","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what courses of action are available for people to raise concerns about suspected contamination of water as a result of fracking.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212770","212770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101845","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will take steps to ensure that independent monitoring of drill sites and their effect on public health and local geology takes place.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212771","212771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101846","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212623","212623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101847","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many onshore wind turbine applications in Nottinghamshire were (a) approved and (b) rejected in 2010.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212587","212587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101848","2014-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of renewable electricity and renewable heat was supplied by biomass fuelled technologies in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212603","212603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101849","2014-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many onshore wind turbine applications in Nottingham were (a) approved and (b) rejected in 2011.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212589","212589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101850","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what chemical additives with a prospective use in hydraulic fracturing have been assessed for toxicological risk and other prospective health hazards by the Joint Agencies Groundwater Directive Advisory Group (JAGDAG); and if he will publish the URL where the minutes of JAGDAG meeting may be found.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212543","212543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101851","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to improve competition in the wholesale energy markets.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212544","212544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101852","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with power companies on their preparations for bad weather events in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212545","212545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101853","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she next plans to meet farming organisations in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212547","212547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101854","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on the Government review of the Forestry Commission's policy on grey squirrels.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212535","212535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101855","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on the use of warfarin in controlling grey squirrel numbers.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212536","212536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101856","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to check and certify the online selling of Chlorpyrifos.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212586","212586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101857","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout her Department's buildings and sites; if she will estimate the proportion of lighting in her Department which is LED; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212624","212624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101858","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of greening measures included in reform of the Common Agricultural Policy on UK farming.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212642","212642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101859","2014-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance she issues to farmers on the use of antibiotics in meat and dairy cattle; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212601","212601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101860","2014-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to paragraph 4.6.25 of the Consultation Document on UK Renewable Energy Strategy, published on 26 June 2008, what plans his Department has to consult on (a) an MOT-type scheme for biomass boilers and (b) other arrangements to maintain emission standards.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212726","212726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101861","2014-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2014 to Question 211199, for what reason a decision was taken not to routinely assess the social costs of air pollution; and if she will now assess the social costs of biomass heat.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212724","212724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101862","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much in Single Farm Payment was paid to farm businesses in each county of Northern Ireland in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212648","212648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101863","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212625","212625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101864","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Kenyan counterpart on the threat of Islamist militants in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212676","212676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101865","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) total Allied and (b) UK financial contribution to the Afghan National Security Forces will be in the current year; and how much is pledged for each contribution in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212689","212689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101866","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to end sexual violence against women in Somalia.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212678","212678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101867","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of human rights in Nepal.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212679","212679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101868","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether agreement has been reached with the President of Afghanistan on the role and status of (a) foreign and (b) UK military personnel in Afghanistan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212690","212690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101869","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the UK's financial share is of the EU's contribution to fighting the spread of Ebola.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212743","212743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101870","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on deforestation of uncontacted Indians' land in the Chaco region of Paraguay; and if he will make it his policy to liaise with other governments and international agencies to make representations to the government of Paraguay to halt that deforestation.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212736","212736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101871","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Iranian government on the imprisonment of (a) Ebrahim Firouzi, (b) Shahin Lahooti, (c) Suroush Saraie and (d) Mohammad Roghangir.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212637","212637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101872","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the draft religious conversion law proposed by the government of Burma.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212573","212573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101873","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Guinea-Bissau  on dealing with Ebola.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212548","212548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101874","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he is satisfied with the speed of border crossings between Spain and Gibraltar; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212549","212549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101875","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Burmese counterparts on ratification of the International Convention on Civil and Political Rights.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212572","212572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101876","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Sudanese government about lessons to be learnt from the case of Meriam Ibrahim.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212574","212574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101877","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much and what proportion of the public health budget in (a) Hackney local authority area, (b) London and (c) England is spent on mental health.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212579","212579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101878","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on RU486 in each year since January 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212552","212552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101879","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase spending on mental health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212577","212577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101880","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what studies have been commissioned by (a) his Department and (b) non-departmental public bodies which report to his Department on the potential health effects of radon concentrations found in shale gas obtained from hydraulic fracturing in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212542","212542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101881","2014-11-05","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many interpreters have been employed by or for the NHS in the last 12 months for which figures are available; and what the cost of such interpreters has been.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212606","212606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101882","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212626","212626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101883","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue guidance to all NHS organisations that they should implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting in all NHS premises.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212614","212614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101884","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to increase awareness and early diagnosis of prostate cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212583","212583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101885","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department will publish guidance on the timeline for a successor to the National Dementia Strategy for England and the Prime Minister's Challenge on Dementia.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212582","212582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101886","2014-11-04","Department for Education","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that all primary school children (a) learn to swim and (b) are knowledgeable about water safety.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212712","212712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101887","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of NHS trusts which do not have adequate buildings insurance.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212752","212752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101888","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) mean and (b) median length of hospital stay was for a person diagnosed with (i) pneumococcal disease and (ii) pneumococcal community-acquired pneumonia (A) in total, (B) for people aged 65 and over and (C) adults aged under the age of 65, as recorded by the hospital episodes statistics database in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212753","212753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101889","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged (a) 0 to five, (b) six to 15, (c) 16 to 64 and (d) 65 and over contracted pneumococcal community-acquired pneumonia in each (i) NHS England local area team area and (ii) clinical commissioning group area in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212758","212758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101890","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged (a) 0 to five, (b) six to 15, (c) 16 to 64 and (d) 65 and over contracted invasive pneumococcal disease in each (i) NHS England local area team area and (ii) clinical commissioning group area in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212757","212757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101891","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of (a) invasive pneumococcal disease and (b) pneumococcal community-acquired pneumonia were diagnosed in each (i) NHS England local area team area and (ii) clinical commissioning group area in the last 12 months; and how many such cases involved people aged (A) under and (B) over 65.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212756","212756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101892","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that women who have just given birth in hospital are not sent home between 11pm and 8am.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212737","212737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101893","2014-11-04","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the Children and Adolescent Mental Health Services prevalence survey.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212717","212717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101894","2014-11-04","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what elements in NHS England's Five Year Plan other than Children and Adolescent Mental Health Service impatient beds specifically relate to children.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212718","212718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101895","2014-11-04","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects that Sir Stuart Rose's report on NHS Leadership will be published.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212719","212719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101896","2014-11-04","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information on the Chief Medical Officer's physical activity guidelines is included in the curriculum for (a) trainee doctors, (b) trainee nurse, (c) trainee health visitors and (d) other medical students.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212709","212709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101897","2014-11-04","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to communicate the Chief Medical Officer's physical activity guidelines to frontline medical professionals.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212710","212710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101898","2014-11-04","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to monitor implementation of the Chief Medical Officer's physical activity guidelines to ensure that members of the public are reaching the recommended levels of physical activity.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212711","212711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101899","2014-11-04","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the new waiting time standards for adult Improving Access to Psychological Therapies (IAPT) apply to children and adolescents' IAPT.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212715","212715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101900","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Ministers in his Department have had with the insurance industry on cover for NHS buildings in the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212749","212749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101901","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS trusts do not have buildings insurance cover in excess of £5 million.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212750","212750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101902","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS trusts do not have buildings insurance cover in excess of £1 million.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212751","212751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101903","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the benefits to the NHS of a preventative public health approach to musculoskeletal conditions.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212742","212742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101904","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on the effectiveness of alcohol addiction treatment facilities.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212744","212744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101905","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many bed days were taken by people diagnosed with (a) pneumococcal disease and (b) pneumococcal community-acquired pneumonia (i) in total and (ii) in each age group, as recorded by the hospital episodes statistics database in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212754","212754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101906","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many abortions have been carried out on patients who are over 24 weeks pregnant since January 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212763","212763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101907","2014-11-05","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to introduce further measures at airports to prevent the spread of Ebola to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212791","212791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101908","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many deaths of people with a learning disability there have been in (a) assessment and treatment units and (b) other inpatient units in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212764","212764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101909","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the benefits of physical activity in reducing the prevalence of musculoskeletal conditions.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212765","212765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101910","2014-11-04","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in what circumstances Alternative Provider Medical Services contracts are used by NHS England; and how many such contracts were used in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212784","212784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101911","2014-11-04","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in what circumstances General Medical Services contracts are used by NHS England; and how many such contracts were used in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212785","212785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101912","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department expects to announce the timetable for developing a successor strategy to the National Dementia Strategy for England and the Prime Minister's Challenge on Dementia.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212685","212685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101913","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to prevent an upsurge in measles; and what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on that issue.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212677","212677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101914","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Northern Ireland Executive on a co-ordinated strategy to stem the increase in the number of overweight children.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212675","212675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101915","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what detailed assessments he has made of the effectiveness of the National Dementia Strategy; and if he will publish the full results of that assessment.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212686","212686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101916","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the National Clinical Director for Obesity and Diabetes in England has taken to promote local awareness of diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212660","212660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101917","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP Super-Practices he plans to set up by the end of 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212661","212661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101918","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the National Clinical Director for Obesity and Diabetes is taking to achieve the priorities in the NHS Five Year Forward View.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212662","212662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101919","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the amount (a) recoverable and (b) recovered by the UK through the European Health Insurance Card scheme was in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212684","212684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101920","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the amount (a) recoverable and (b) recovered for the cost of medical treatment of foreign visitors by the UK through its reciprocal arrangements with non-EU countries was in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212683","212683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101921","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking in response to the prioritisation of diabetes and obesity prevention in the NHS Five Year Forward View.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212663","212663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101922","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was to the NHS of providing treatment to visitors from (a) the European Economic Area and (b) other non-permanent residents in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212681","212681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101923","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether an official review of the National Dementia Strategy has taken place.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212671","212671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101924","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drivers were fined for speeding in each police force area in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212647","212647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101925","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training is being offered to local authorities on making referrals to the National Referral Mechanism for victims of human trafficking; and how many local authorities have undertaken such training to date.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212657","212657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101926","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of returning failed asylum seekers to Sri Lanka on the ability of the Office of the UN High Commission for Human Rights to investigate violations of human rights in that country; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212723","212723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101927","2014-11-03","Cabinet Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of young people between 16 and 25 years were not in work, training or education in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212682","212682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101928","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) British nationals and (b) other people have had their extradition from the UK under a European arrest warrant blocked under the proportionality test in section 21A of the Extradition Act 2003 since that Act came into force.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212692","212692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101929","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) British nationals and (b) other people have had their extradition from the UK under a European arrest warrant blocked under the provisions of section 12A of the Extradition Act 2003 since that section came into force.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212694","212694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101930","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps she has taken to tackle harassment on social media.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212688","212688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101931","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on (a) the Telegraph Modern Slavery in Britain site, (b) the Modern Slavery advertising campaign and (c) the website www.modernslavery.co.uk; and what assessment she has made of the effects of that expenditure on awareness-raising and prevention of modern slavery.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212702","212702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101932","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) British nationals and (b) other people have been extradited from the UK under a European arrest warrant since sections 156 and 157 of the Anti-Social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014 came into force.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212695","212695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101933","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the average time in each of the other EU Member States between a decision to try a British national who is wanted for extradition or has been extradited for the alleged offence that is the subject of that decision and the trial for that alleged offence (a) commencing and (b) concluding.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212696","212696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101934","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests each police force in England has made for European arrest warrants for the extradition of individuals elsewhere in the European Union for return to the UK since July 2014.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212698","212698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101935","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many European arrest warrant requests have been rejected since July 2014.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212699","212699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101936","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information is provided to trafficking victims on their rights to compensation; and how many victims of trafficking have had applications for compensation from the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority rejected in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212703","212703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101937","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many National Referral Mechanism decisions made by (a) the Human Trafficking Centre and (b) UK Visas and Immigration were subject to judicial review proceedings in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013; and how many such decisions were changed as a result of successful judicial review proceedings.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212704","212704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101938","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 September 2014 to Question 207075, on what legal basis Norway, Iceland, Switzerland and Liechtenstein have access to the False and Authentic Documents Online database through their participation in the Schengen acquis.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212697","212697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101939","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to address the increase in male victims of trafficking; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212705","212705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101940","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what forecast she has made of the proportion of extraditions of (a) British nationals and (b) other persons sought from the UK under a European Arrest Warrant in which a decision to charge or try the wanted person will require that person's presence in the country seeking their extradition after the Police and Criminal Justice Act.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212786","212786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101941","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to prevent agency workers becoming victims of trafficking for labour exploitation.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212787","212787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101942","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide details of the methodology used to develop the annual National Crime Agency Strategic Assessment of the Nature and Scale of Human Trafficking in the UK.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212788","212788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101943","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of co-operation between the devolved administrations and her Department in tackling animal cruelty crimes.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212746","212746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101944","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the level and effectiveness of the UK's co-operation with the Irish Republic in tackling cross-border organised crime.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212745","212745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101945","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what evidence her Department holds on extraditions of British nationals from the UK that took place over the period April 2009 to April 2014 under the European Arrest Warrant which led to the bringing into force of section 12A of the Extradition Act 2003.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212701","212701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101946","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons European arrest warrants have been rejected since July 2014.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212700","212700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101947","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people had their vehicle stopped and searched under section 44 of the Terrorism Act 2000 in each of the last five years; and how many of those were (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted of a (i) notifiable and (ii) terrorism-related offence in each police force area.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212565","212565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101948","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost in each budgetary category of national police recruitment campaigns was in each police force area in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212564","212564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101949","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2014 to Question 210766, what estimate she has made of the number of flights into private airfields which were not notified to UK Border Force in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212600","212600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101950","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Sri Lankan asylum seekers who claimed asylum in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012, (e) 2013 and (f) 2014, have been found to be victims of torture; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212654","212654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101951","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout her Department's buildings and sites; if she will estimate the proportion of lighting in her Department which is LED; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212627","212627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101952","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Sri Lankan asylum seekers who have been victims of torture have been removed to Sri Lanka in the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212653","212653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101953","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many European Arrest Warrant applications have been granted for extradition (a) from the UK and (b) to the UK for each type of offence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212641","212641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101954","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will issue guidance to operators of police forces that they should implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting in all police premises.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212612","212612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101955","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people attempting to enter the UK illegally who were intercepted at (a) Calais, (b) Zeebrugge and (c) Ostend in each of the last three years; and how much her Department has spent on measures to help prevent the entry of illegal immigrants to the UK through each such port in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212640","212640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101956","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that police officers are protected when handling dangerous calls alone.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212553","212553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101957","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to check whether applicants for British citizenship have criminal records.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212555","212555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101958","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to prevent people performing citizens' arrests being prosecuted.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212551","212551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101959","2014-11-04","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has consulted non-governmental organisations in the preparation of the Modern Slavery Action Plan; and when she will publish the Plan.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212789","212789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101960","2014-11-03","Department for International Development","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout her Department's buildings and sites; if she will estimate the proportion of lighting in her Department which is LED; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212628","212628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101961","2014-11-03","Department for International Development","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its programmes in West Africa do not create perverse incentives which prioritise short-term outcomes rather than longer-term strengthening strategies.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212576","212576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101962","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many on-the-spot fines have been issued in each police area to date.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212566","212566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101963","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) convictions and (b) fixed penalty notices there have been following arrests for speeding offences in England and Wales (i) in total and (ii) on (A) the A143 and (B) the A14 in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212569","212569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101964","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of each category of fixed penalty notices were (a) issued and (b) paid in each month since their introduction in (i) Bury St Edmunds, (ii) Suffolk, (iii) the East of England and (iv) England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212567","212567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101965","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drivers convicted of driving when under the influence of alcohol or drugs had previous convictions for the same offence in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk, (c) the East of England and (d) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212568","212568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101966","2014-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of officials in his Department have undergone specialist training on working with victims of sexual assault in a court environment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212599","212599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101967","2014-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of violent incidents in prisons linked to legal highs in the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212598","212598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101968","2014-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals against placement orders have been issued in family courts since 2010; and how many of those appeals have been allowed.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212596","212596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101969","2014-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many opposed applications for placement orders have been issued by local authorities in family courts since 2010; and how many of those applications have been ordered by the court.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212597","212597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101970","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisoners have been on the run since April 2004; what offence each such prisoner had committed; how long each prisoner's sentence was; and how long each prisoner had served before absconding.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212585","212585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101971","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will issue guidance to operators of (a) courts and (b) prisons that they should implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting in those buildings.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212611","212611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101972","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what services aimed at giving victims of crime practical and emotional support have been introduced since 1 October 2012.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212538","212538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101973","2014-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value was of fines (a) issued by the courts and (b) collected was in financial year 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212720","212720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101974","2014-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the announcement on 23 October 2014 by the Minister of State for Justice and Civil Liberties on more support for separating couples and parents, how much of the new £2 million package will be spent on improving the Government's Sorting Out Separation website.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212777","212777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101975","2014-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to integrate the new supporting separated parents in dispute helpline pilot to be run by the Children and Family Court Advisory and Support Service with the Sorting Out Separation Service and the Child Maintenance Options Service operated by the Department for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212778","212778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101976","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212629","212629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101977","2014-11-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will make it her policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout her Department's buildings and sites; if she will estimate the proportion of lighting in her Department which is LED; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212630","212630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101978","2014-11-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many drug-related arrests have been made in Northern Ireland since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212546","212546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101979","2014-11-03","Scotland Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212631","212631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101980","2014-11-03","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-10-30","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assistance is offered to households where residents may not have the capability or capacity to complete individual electoral registration forms.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212646","212646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101981","2014-11-04","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's Report, The Operation of Traffic Signals during Low Demand Periods, published in October 2012, what trials to turn off traffic lights during such periods proposed by local authorities have taken place; what the findings were of those trials; and whether his Department has issued any further guidance on this matter.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212722","212722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101982","2014-11-05","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the economic benefit of High Speed 3 to the North West.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212790","212790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101983","2014-11-04","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department spent on consultants on electrification in financial years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212721","212721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101984","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the announcement in HM Treasury's paper, Cm 8669, Investing in Britain's Future, page 13, that £15,145 million will be allocated to the Highways Agency between 2015-16 and 2020-21, to what schemes and use that funding has been allocated; and how that allocation is apportioned over time.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212729","212729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101985","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of acoustic fencing on reducing traffic noise levels.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212556","212556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101986","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of trees and vegetation in reducing traffic noise levels.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212557","212557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101987","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of different types of road surfaces on traffic noise levels.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212558","212558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101988","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the security regime in the Port of Belfast.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212575","212575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101989","2014-11-04","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the costs of administering each franchise of the Direct Awards programme are.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212594","212594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101990","2014-11-04","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what works will be required to overhead wiring south of Bedford as a result of the Midland Main Line electrification programme.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212593","212593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101991","2014-11-04","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what Directly Operated Railways' staff numbers and overall budget are projected to be in each year between 2013-14 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212595","212595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101992","2014-11-04","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what premises officials in his Department are working on High Speed (a) 2 and (b) 3; what the square footage is of each premises; and what the annual cost per square foot of each premises is.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212591","212591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101993","2014-11-04","Department for Transport","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff in each grade employed by (a) HS2 Ltd and (b) his Department are working on High Speed (i) 2 and (ii) 3; and what the average salary of each of those grades is.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212590","212590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101994","2014-11-03","Wales Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212633","212633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101995","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to implement a replacement programme to introduce LED lighting throughout his Department's buildings and sites; if he will estimate the proportion of lighting in his Department which is LED; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212634","212634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101996","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an estimate of the costs of Clause 3 of the Affordable Homes Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212658","212658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101997","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many housing benefit claimants there are in each constituency in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212673","212673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101998","2014-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases of (a) forced labour and (b) trafficking for labour exploitation were identified by the Health and Safety Executive in (i) 2011, (ii) 2012 and (iii) 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212707","212707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101999","2014-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many incapacity benefit claimants died during or after their work capability assessment in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212728","212728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102000","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants there are in each constituency in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212674","212674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102001","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the new Minister for Social Development in the Northern Ireland Executive on implementation of welfare reform.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212740","212740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102002","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department expects to announce its decision on the future of the Post Office card account.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212741","212741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102003","2014-11-04","Cabinet Office","2014-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many 18 to 21 year olds are claiming jobseeker's allowance in each English region; and what proportion of all 18 to 21 year olds in each region this represents.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212781","212781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102004","2014-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2014 to Question 211627, what assessment he has made of the likelihood of a link between the reduction in asbestos licence holders and changes in asbestos removal activity.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212782","212782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102005","2014-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects all new applications to be for universal credit instead of for existing benefits and credits.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212783","212783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102006","2014-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of applications for jobseeker's allowance used the rapid reclaim provisions in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212779","212779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102007","2014-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people aged between 18 and 21 claiming jobseeker's allowance who have skills levels below Level 2.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212780","212780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102008","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of benefit fraud committed in respect of each benefit which was attributable to identity fraud in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk, (c) the East of England and (d) England and Wales in the latest period for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212570","212570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102009","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individual cases of customer overpayment debt there have been in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk, (c) the East of England and (d) England and Wales in each of the last five years; and what the total monetary value was of customer overpayment debts in this period.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212571","212571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102010","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014 to Question 203682, whether the Government has met its expectation that no-one is waiting longer than 26 weeks for a personal independence payment assessment.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212537","212537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/102011","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many violent incidents have occurred in UK jobcentres in each year since January 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212554","212554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/106468","2014-11-05","Department for International Development","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what refugee relief work her Department is undertaking in Jordan.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905895","905895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/106469","2014-11-05","Department for International Development","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to encourage other developed nations to support efforts to tackle the Ebola virus in West Africa.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905898","905898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/106470","2014-11-05","Department for International Development","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to seek international consensus on post-2015 education goals and targets.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905901","905901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/106471","2014-11-05","Department for International Development","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help refugees from conflict in South Sudan.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905896","905896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/106472","2014-11-05","Department for International Development","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to put women and girls at the heart of the UK's development programmes.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905899","905899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/106473","2014-11-05","Department for International Development","2014-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the situation of refugees in Syria and Iraq.","Biography information for Mark Hunter","Mark Hunter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905900","905900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101519","2014-11-03","Attorney General","2014-10-29","To ask the Attorney General, what recent assessment he has made of the usefulness of the European Arrest Warrant as a prosecutorial tool.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212405","212405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101520","2014-11-03","Attorney General","2014-10-29","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with the Director of Public Prosecutions on the usefulness of the European Arrest Warrant as a prosecutorial tool.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212406","212406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101521","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the increased accuracy in weather forecasting arising from the new Met Office supercomputer.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212467","212467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101522","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the time taken for the general release of data from European Science Agency (ESA) projects; and if he will make future UK contributions to ESA projects conditional on full and immediate release of all data.","Biography information for Martin Caton","Martin Caton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212454","212454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101523","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many new apprenticeships were created in (a) Cumbria and (b) South Lakeland in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212460","212460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101524","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212492","212492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101525","2014-11-03","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-10-29","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the average cost to the public purse was of parliamentary by-elections since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212402","212402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101526","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will exempt charitably-funded rapid response vehicles from VAT.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212407","212407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101527","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of income inequality on national wellbeing.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212385","212385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101528","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the recommendation of the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Wellbeing Economics that stable and secure employment for all should be the primary objective of economic policy.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212387","212387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101529","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to monitor practices in the banking sector.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212470","212470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101530","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings the Exchequer Secretary has had with representatives of the tobacco industry since his appointment.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212455","212455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101531","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts about measures to reduce tax avoidance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212452","212452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101532","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his G7 counterparts about measures to reduce tax avoidance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212453","212453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101533","2014-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to promote environmental and sustainable housebuilding following the abolition of the Code for Sustainable Homes.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212394","212394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101534","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the planning system addresses (a) size and quality of housing, (b) opportunities for physical activity such as cycling and walking, (c) air and noise pollution, (d) access to green space, (e) isolation and loneliness and (f) other factors known to affect wellbeing.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212386","212386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101535","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on the level of street lighting they should have in place.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212384","212384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101536","2014-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to assist local authorities build more sustainable homes.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212393","212393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101537","2014-11-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made in improving 3G and 4G mobile telephone signals (a) nationally and (b) in Cumbria since 2011.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212408","212408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101538","2014-11-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what change there has been in the number of households in Northern Ireland holding a black and white television licence between 2003 and 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212404","212404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101539","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the direct military aid his Department provided to Kurdish forces in Iraq and Syria in 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212390","212390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101540","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will assess the merits of Army Technical Operations personnel in Northern Ireland being based closer to locations where the majority of explosive devices have been found in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212401","212401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101541","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many servicemen and women from Northern Ireland were injured in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212471","212471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101542","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what legacy the Armed Forces leave in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212475","212475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101543","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many claimants of the War Pensions Scheme in each age group receive (a) the Allowance for a Lowered Standard of Occupation and (b) the Unemployability Supplement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212425","212425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101544","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what cost his Department (a) has and (b) will incur for the (i) design and (ii) editing of the British Armed Forces Learning Resource 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212451","212451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101545","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to increase digital engagement by local education authorities.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212383","212383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101546","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will take steps to ensure that no child living in poverty grows up in a cold home.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212423","212423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101549","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's press release of 19 October 2014 entitled Subsidies for solar farms to be cut to help safeguard farmland, whether her Department holds evidence that shows that solar farms compromise the success of the UK agriculture industry.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212382","212382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101550","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, under what statutory instruments the Government can regulate historic landfill sites if it is suspected that they could be contaminated with poisonous gases or chemicals.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212427","212427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101551","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps alongside the food industry to institute a voluntary code for installing CCTVs in slaughter houses.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212424","212424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101552","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure MONUSCO peace-keepers are implementing their mandate.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212433","212433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101553","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to address the situation of religious minorities in India following the recent elections.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212429","212429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101554","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of the misselling of and corruption related to mortgages for properties for UK citizens buying in Cyprus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212434","212434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101555","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the reasons were for the time taken by his Department to reply to correspondence from the hon. Member for West Lancashire on Virunaga National Park.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212379","212379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101556","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contributions the Government made to the Mare Nostrum rescue program before the decision to no longer support it.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212389","212389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101557","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Iranian authorities on the imprisonment of Maryam Naghash Zargaran.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212410","212410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101558","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts about offering a Membership Action Plan for Montenegro; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212391","212391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101559","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Macedonian  counterpart about the possibility of the Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia joining NATO; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212392","212392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101560","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking in collaboration with Deputy Special Representative of MINUSCA, Diane Corner, to ensure that a comprehensive and inclusive disarmament, demobilisation and reintegration process is planned and prioritised in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212432","212432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101561","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with NATO counterparts about offering a Membership Action Plan for Georgia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212462","212462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101562","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what reports he has received from Health and Wellbeing Boards on improvements in raising diabetes awareness.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212457","212457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101563","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness and merits of (a) the recently announced New Medicines Fund in Scotland and (b) other funding models aimed at driving improved patient access to innovative medicines in the context of the payments made by the pharmaceutical industry under the current Pharmaceutical Pricing Regulation Scheme.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212458","212458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101564","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the active time of North West Ambulance Service ambulances stationed outside South Lakeland District is spent inside that District.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212422","212422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101565","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that payments made by the pharmaceutical industry under the current Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme are used to NHS England to achieve measurable and improved access to new medicines by NHS patients.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212418","212418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101566","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase his Department's budget for research and development.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212377","212377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101567","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency plans the Government is making for quarantine procedures for people entering the UK from countries where the Ebola virus is present in the event of a further spread of that virus.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212378","212378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101568","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support and screening facilities his Department has provided for health service volunteers assisting with the Ebola virus crisis in West Africa.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212400","212400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101569","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister for Health, Social Services and Public Safety in the Northern Ireland Executive on the 24 Hour Domestic and Sexual Violence Helpline in Northern Ireland; and what assessment he has made of the success of that service.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212463","212463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101570","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been removed from GPs' lists in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212464","212464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101571","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many radiologists are due to finish their training in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212380","212380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101572","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many increases to the annual salaries of Chairs of NHS Trusts that were over the limit set by him have been authorised by the NHS Trust Development Authority in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212381","212381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101573","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the active time of the North West Ambulance Service ambulances stationed in South Lakeland District is spent outside that district.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212421","212421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101574","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) obese patients and (b) smokers have been denied routine operations in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212466","212466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101575","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had on ensuring that the payments made by the pharmaceutical industry under the current Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme will be used to improve access to innovative medicines.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212417","212417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101576","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) process and (b) timelines followed by the NHS to determine a specialised clinical commissioning policy are; and what the roles and responsibilities are of the NHS committees involved.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212409","212409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101577","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for talking therapies in (a) Haltemprice and Howden constituency and (b) nationally.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212411","212411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101578","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP practices have not been able to replace doctors who have retired in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212465","212465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101579","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the payments made by the pharmaceutical industry under the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme will be apportioned to each of the devolved health administrations, whilst securing that the mechanism in place for determining apportionment ensures that patients in all four constituent parts of the UK receive benefits from the payments made throughout the duration of the scheme.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212420","212420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101580","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of mindfulness-based (a) cognitive therapy teachers and (b) stress reduction teachers in England.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212428","212428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101581","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include in the new NHS patient, visitor and staff car parking principles reduced fees for families of long-term hospital patients.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212468","212468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101582","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved administrations about the availability of free diabetes tests.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212469","212469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101583","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to use the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme to make the UK (a) a global leader in providing patients access to the most innovative appropriate medicines and (b) an attractive place for pharmaceutical companies to locate and invest.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212419","212419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101584","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2014 to question 209897, how many of the 88 minors who are non-UK nationals and were recorded as victims of sexual trafficking in the most recent figures still reside in the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212426","212426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101585","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2014 to Question 207807, whether a date has been set for commencement of section 65 of the Immigration Act 2014.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212456","212456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101586","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees have been settled in the UK during the last six months; and how many such refugees she expects to arrive in the next six months.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212431","212431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101587","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will carry out an inquiry into personal protection for the Prime Minister.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212474","212474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101588","2014-11-03","Department for International Development","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many British military and NHS personnel are in Sierra Leone to deal with Ebola; and what plans the Government has to increase their numbers.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212430","212430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101589","2014-11-03","Department for International Development","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she received of the use of UN humanitarian helicopters to transport military personnel in the eastern Democratic Republic of Congo; whether such transport is in accordance with the MONUSCO mandate; whether such transport is funded by her Department; and what assessment she has made of the effect of such transport on the (a) safety and (b) effectiveness of humanitarian personnel.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212416","212416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101590","2014-11-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will take steps to ensure that the Electoral Office for Northern Ireland holds additional registration clinics before March 2015 in areas remote from any electoral offices.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212403","212403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101591","2014-11-03","Prime Minister","2014-10-29","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will erect a memorial to honour the memory of the servicemen and women who lost their lives in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212472","212472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101592","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the short term objectives are of the Indian Diaspora Champion.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212444","212444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101593","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to appoint a diaspora champion for (a) Pakistan and (b) other countries.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212445","212445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101594","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Indian Diaspora Champion is taking to implement the Government's goal of stronger ties with India.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212446","212446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101595","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the purpose is of domestic visits by the Indian Diaspora Champion.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212447","212447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101596","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many candidates there were for the role of Indian Diaspora Champion; and how that Champion was selected.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212448","212448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101597","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many visits the Indian Diaspora Champion has made.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212449","212449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101598","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost is of the Indian Diaspora Champion.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212450","212450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101599","2014-11-03","Prime Minister","2014-10-29","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will bring forward proposals to enable an early date for the referendum on membership of the EU.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212473","212473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101600","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Indian Diaspora Champion is taking in response to the changes in numbers of Indian students enrolling in UK university courses.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212459","212459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101601","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what overseas visits the India Diaspora Champion has made; and what the cost of those visits was.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212461","212461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101604","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects to inform residential training colleges for disabled people whether their funding will be extended beyond August 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212413","212413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101605","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit applications can be processed on average manually by an adviser in a day.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212414","212414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101606","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funds the Government has provided to Motability in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212415","212415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101607","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects Jobcentre Plus to deploy an IT solution for the calculation of universal credit for those other than single people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212412","212412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101608","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's projected expenditure on (a) disablity living allowance and (b) personal independence payment is in each year up to 2017-18.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212399","212399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101609","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many front line job centre advisers will take part in user acceptance testing of the IT systems developed to facilitate the delivery of universal credit.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212398","212398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101610","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a conclusion has been reached on infringement proceedings generated by the European Commission against the Government of the United Kingdom, with regard to the application of the 'Past Presence' test for disability benefit purposes as it affects ex-patriate citizens of the United Kingdom now resident in other EU member states; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212388","212388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101611","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what metrics were used to determine whether the IT systems developed to facilitate the delivery of universal credit pathfinders were fit for purpose.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212395","212395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101612","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many front line job centre advisers took part in user acceptance testing of the IT systems developed to facilitate the delivery of universal credit pathfinders.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212396","212396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101613","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the programme management of universal credit made use of the Prince2 methodology.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212397","212397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101614","2014-11-03","Attorney General","2014-10-29","To ask the Attorney General, for which offences the Crown Prosecution Service routinely monitors the number and proportion of cases that fail because of victim issues.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212435","212435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101615","2014-11-03","Attorney General","2014-10-29","To ask the Attorney General, how many fraud prosecutions the Crown Prosecution Service has brought in Crown Courts in Wales in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212436","212436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101616","2014-11-03","Attorney General","2014-10-29","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions the Crown Prosecution Service has brought on breaches of immigration law arising from sham marriages in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212437","212437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101617","2014-11-03","Attorney General","2014-10-29","To ask the Attorney General, what reports he has received on whether the Serious Fraud Office will apply for additional funding from HM Treasury to finance its investigation into Tesco.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212438","212438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101618","2014-11-03","Attorney General","2014-10-29","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Law Officers' Departments spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212493","212493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101619","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many full-time equivalent officials of what grade in his Department have been assigned to assist UK Coal in the drafting of a state aid bid.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212484","212484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101620","2014-11-03","Cabinet Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much was spent by (a) 10 Downing Street, (b) the Deputy Prime Minister's Office, (c) the Office of the Leader of the House and (d) the Cabinet Office on (i) focus groups and (ii) surveys in (A) 2013 and (B) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212513","212513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101621","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his officials had with the Office for National Statistics between January and October 2014 on provision for backdating of payments of European contributions to accord with the European Statistics Agency reconciliation of the European Budget under ESA95.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212527","212527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101622","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the progress of arrangements to secure compliance with the requirements of ESA 2010 with respect to future calculation of the UK's European Budget contribution.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212528","212528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101623","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the accuracy of the European Statistics Agency's calculation of UK's contribution liability in respect of the European Budget under ESA 95 between 27 May and 13 October 2014.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212529","212529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101624","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212510","212510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101625","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212494","212494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101626","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding is allocated to the Local Government Ombudsman; how many staff the Ombudsman employs; and how many enquiries were received by the Ombudsman in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212525","212525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101627","2014-11-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212495","212495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101628","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212496","212496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101629","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much in total is paid to claimants of the War Pensions Scheme in each age group claiming (a) the Allowance for a Lowered Standard of Occupation and (b) the Unemployability Supplement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212520","212520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101630","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much on average is received each week by claimants of the War Pensions Scheme in each age group who claim (a) the Allowance for a Lowered Standard or Occupation and (b) the Unemployability Supplement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212521","212521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101631","2014-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) HM service personnel and (b) civilians have been seconded by the UK Government to (a) MINUSMA and (b) the EU Training Mission in Mali; and how many such personnel speak both English and French.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212440","212440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101632","2014-11-03","Cabinet Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Office spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212497","212497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101633","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212498","212498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101634","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212499","212499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101635","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many bids were received in the 14th licensing round for onshore oil and gas.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212485","212485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101636","2014-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he intends to announce the awarding of licences arising from the 14th Onshore Oil and Gas Licensing round.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212486","212486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101637","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212500","212500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101638","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212501","212501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101639","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on the conviction against Anwar Ibrahim, Leader of the Opposition of Malaysia; if he will raise his conviction for sodomy with his Malaysian counterpart; and if he will assess whether the charge and conviction of Anwar Ibrahim is a case of political persecution.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212489","212489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101640","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts on the possibility of offering a Membership Action Plan for Bosnia and Herzegovina; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212442","212442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101641","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts on the possibility of offering a Membership Action Plan for the Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212443","212443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101642","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Nigerian counterpart on alleged human rights abuses by the Nigerian military; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212481","212481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101643","2014-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with his international counterparts to co-ordinate the rescue of girls and women kidnapped by Boko Haram; what steps he is taking to help prevent further such abductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212480","212480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101644","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many consultant radiologist posts in NHS trusts are (a) vacant and (b) covered by locums.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212519","212519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101645","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of mindfulness-based interventions on NHS staff in terms of (a) wellbeing levels, (b) stress levels, (c) levels of care and compassion, (d) staff absence and (e) productivity.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212522","212522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101646","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there has been in the average age of the onset of depression in young people over the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212523","212523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101647","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of charging for NHS services required because of injuries caused by alcohol or drug misuse.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212524","212524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101648","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding NHS England makes available for promoting staff wellbeing.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212439","212439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101649","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his oral contribution of 23 October 2014, Official Report, columns 1044-5, on Five Year Forward View, if he will ensure that any Multispeciality Community Providers are NHS providers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212491","212491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101650","2014-11-03","Department of Health","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212502","212502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101651","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212503","212503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101652","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the last European Arrest Warrant was issued by the UK to the Republic of Ireland in relation to an offence or offences related to terrorism.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212487","212487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101653","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many European Arrest Warrants issued by the UK to the Republic of Ireland for terrorism-related offences remain outstanding.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212488","212488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101654","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students of have been deported from UK universities and colleges as a result of investigations into Educational Testing Service since February 2014.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212478","212478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101655","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many prosecutions have been brought against operators of unmanned aircraft in (a) England and Wales and (b) Northern Ireland in the last 12 months; how many such prosecutions were successful; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212518","212518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101656","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the country of origin was of each student deported as a result of the BBC Panorama investigation broadcast in February 2014; and to which country was each such student returned.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212477","212477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101657","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students of each institution have been deported from UK universities and colleges as a result of Educational Testing Service investigations in each month since February 2014.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212476","212476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101658","2014-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs have been put down in each of the last five years under section 1 orders of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 by each police authority in (a) England, (b) Scotland and (c) Wales.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212526","212526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101659","2014-11-03","Home Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has in place to assist non-UK minors who are trafficked into the UK for sex.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212441","212441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101660","2014-11-03","Department for International Development","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department has given to the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212530","212530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101661","2014-11-03","Department for International Development","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition on the effect of their policy on seed law on small farmers.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212531","212531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101662","2014-11-03","Department for International Development","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what practical support her Department has provided to help women who were kidnapped and subsequently escaped from or were released by Boko Haram to deal with psychosocial trauma; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212479","212479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101663","2014-11-03","Department for International Development","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212504","212504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101664","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212505","212505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101665","2014-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014 to Question 200960, when he plans to write to the hon. Member for Coventry South to provide the information he omitted to provide in that Answer.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212532","212532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101666","2014-11-03","Leader of the House","2014-10-29","To ask the Leader of the House, how much his Office spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212506","212506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101667","2014-11-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212507","212507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101668","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to tackle wrongful use of unmanned aircraft operating within the airspace over Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212517","212517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101669","2014-11-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will hold discussions with her ministerial colleagues on including parading rights in a Bill of Rights for Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212516","212516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101670","2014-11-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will take steps to secure funding for the Ulster Orchestra; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212515","212515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101671","2014-11-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will take steps to arrange a service of thanksgiving for people from Northern Ireland who served in Afghanistan and a commemoration for those members of the armed forces from Northern Ireland who died in that country on active service; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212514","212514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101672","2014-11-03","Scotland Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212508","212508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101673","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212509","212509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101674","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential saving to the public purse arising from placing collision protection beams at bridges which have a high incidence of strikes from lorries or other vehicles.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212483","212483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101675","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many collisions involving a vehicle hitting a bridge resulted in a delay to train services on the King's Cross to King's Lynn line in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212482","212482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101676","2014-11-03","Wales Office","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212511","212511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101677","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on (a) focus groups and (b) surveys in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212512","212512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101678","2014-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what metrics will be used to determine whether the IT systems that have been developed to facilitate the delivery of universal credit roll out from early 2015 are fit for purpose.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212490","212490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/105836","2014-11-04","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make a comparative assessment of the economic effect of (a) a target for a long-term current surplus and (b) an overall surplus target.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905856","905856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/105852","2014-11-04","HM Treasury","2014-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent fiscal steps he has taken to support small businesses.","Biography information for Julian Smith","Julian Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905857","905857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101296","2014-10-30","Attorney General","2014-10-28","To ask the Attorney General, whether the Serious Fraud Office has sought his assistance with securing evidence from the Ministry of Defence in relation to its investigation into GPT Special Project Management Ltd.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212318","212318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101297","2014-10-30","Attorney General","2014-10-28","To ask the Attorney General, whether any representations have been made to him or to the Director of the Serious Fraud Office (SFO) stating that the public interest would be served by entering into a Deferred Prosecution Agreement in relation to the SFO's investigation of GPT Special Project Management Ltd.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212320","212320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101298","2014-10-30","Attorney General","2014-10-28","To ask the Attorney General, how many meetings staff from the Serious Fraud Office have had with officials of the Ministry of Defence in relation to its investigation into GPT Special Project Management Ltd; and on what dates those meetings took place.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212319","212319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101299","2014-10-30","Attorney General","2014-10-28","To ask the Attorney General, whether he has conducted a public interest consultation exercise or sought ministerial representations on the public interest in relation to the Serious Fraud Office's investigation into GPT Special Project Management Ltd.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212325","212325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101300","2014-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what definition the Government uses of a green or low carbon job for the purposes of collating official statistics and announcements.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212324","212324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101301","2014-11-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the Government's estimate is of the proportion of video games sector employees who are women.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212360","212360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101302","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funds distributed by UK Trade and Investment were allocated to the video  games sector in each of the last three years; and what proportion of the total funding from UK Trade and Investment that represented in each such year.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212362","212362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101303","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2014 to Question 211397, what plans the Government has to increase the proportion of Technology Strategy Board funds allocated to the video games sector.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212346","212346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101304","2014-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many employers in (a) Hackney North and Stoke Newington constituency, (b) the London Borough of Hackney, (c) London and (d) England that have broken the national minimum wage law have been (i) prosecuted and (ii) named since the revision to the national minimum wage law came into effect on 1 October 2013.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212281","212281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101305","2014-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the new Met Office supercomputer will be better able to predict heavy storms such as the one in Castle Point on 20 July 2014; and whether that supercomputer will enable agencies listed as category one flood responders to obtain more accurate data about catastrophic weather events with more notice than they currently receive.","Biography information for Rebecca Harris","Rebecca Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212282","212282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101306","2014-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to take account of the omission of (a) some workers paid below the lower earnings limit and (b) unpaid travel time from the Annual Survey of Hours and Earnings when using that survey to estimate non-payment of the national minimum wage among homecare workers.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212198","212198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101307","2014-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many social enterprises there were in (a) Brighton and Hove, (b) East Sussex and (c) the South East in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212201","212201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101308","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in which publications the Insolvency Service has placed advertisements about Farepak unclaimed funds.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212231","212231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101309","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Insolvency Service has spent on advertising relating to Farepak unclaimed funds to date.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212232","212232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101310","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many advertisements the Insolvency Service has placed about Farepak unclaimed funds in (a) newspapers, (b) magazines, (c) television, (d) social media, (e) transport and (f) radio.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212233","212233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101311","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that mobile telephone operators and other companies display the total cost of consumer contracts over the contracts' lifetime, including predicted inflation rises at the point of sale.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212259","212259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101312","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many start-up loans have been granted in Brigg and Goole constituency  since that scheme's inception; and how much has been granted through such loans.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212263","212263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101313","2014-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage employer best practice in relation to employee wellbeing.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212278","212278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101314","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of potential relationships between employee wellbeing, productivity and levels of absenteeism.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212301","212301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101315","2014-11-03","Cabinet Office","2014-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many alcohol-related deaths there were in Brigg and Goole constituency in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212260","212260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101316","2014-11-03","Cabinet Office","2014-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has carried out a risk assessment of the threat posed to the UK by the Ebola epidemic.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212358","212358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101317","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of households claiming (a) tax credits and (b) child benefit are (i) in work and (ii) have dependent children.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212371","212371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101318","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what date (a) new and (b) existing claims to tax credits will end.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212374","212374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101319","2014-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy that people entitled to carer's allowance are included in the groups that qualify for the childcare costs earnings disregard for the purposes of calculating housing benefit.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212199","212199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101320","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials in his Department have had responsibility for monitoring gross national income accounting changes and their effect on the UK contribution to the EU in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212226","212226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101321","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department was first made aware of the EU Statistical Office revisions to the UK's gross national income and value added tax balances and subsequent calculation of an EU member state's contribution to the 2014 Amending Budget.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212227","212227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101322","2014-10-30","HM Treasury","2014-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the current size is of the Pool Re reserves.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212169","212169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101323","2014-11-03","HM Treasury","2014-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the research conducted by the Nevin Economic Research Institute in Ireland on the rate of VAT on tourism-related goods and services.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212224","212224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101324","2014-10-30","HM Treasury","2014-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Pool Reinsurance reserves in the event of a terrorist incident.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212253","212253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101325","2014-10-30","HM Treasury","2014-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses in North Ayrshire and Arran constituency receive employment allowance.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212254","212254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101326","2014-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many social housing homes in (a) Hackney North and Stoke Newington constituency, (b) the London Borough of Hackney, (c) London and (d) England have failed to meet the Decent Homes standard in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212243","212243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101327","2014-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the number of betting shops on high streets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212246","212246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101328","2014-11-03","Department for Transport","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to enable local authorities to retain information on sex offenders to inform the granting of licences to taxi drivers.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212298","212298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101329","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many council home tenants in Brigg and Goole constituency have bought their property under the right to buy scheme in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212262","212262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101330","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the declaration of interests requirements for people on parish councils on the number of people who serve on those councils; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212241","212241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101331","2014-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what records his Department keeps of the number of retaliatory evictions; what criteria he uses to define retaliatory eviction; and how many retaliatory evictions took place in the last (a) 12 months and (b) five years.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212213","212213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101332","2014-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many section 21 notices were served in each of the last (a) 12 months and (b) five years.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212214","212214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101333","2014-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the planning systems helps to promote physical activity, including cycling and walking; what assessment he has made of the wellbeing benefits of such measures; and what assessment he has made of the potential savings to the public purse from public health improvements arising from such measures.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212306","212306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101334","2014-10-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to permit the (a) Maritime Heritage Foundation and (b) Odyssey Marine Exploration, to sell material recovered from the wreck site of HMS Victory 1744.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212294","212294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101335","2014-10-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who has made representations to his Department on the future management of HMS Victory 1744; and what the content was of such representations.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212277","212277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101336","2014-10-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons his Department's Annual Report and Accounts for 2013-14 has not yet been published; and when that report is due to be published.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212257","212257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101337","2014-11-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with Ofcom on mobile telephones and mid-contract price increases.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212261","212261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101338","2014-10-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle homophobic abuse in football stadiums.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212242","212242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101339","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department's Annual Report and Accounts for 2013-14 has not yet been published; and when that report is due to be published.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212255","212255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101340","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any UK personnel deployed on Operation Telic have reported any ill effects due to exposure to legacy chemical weapons and made any claims for compensation due to exposure, whether real or perceived, to chemical weapons.","Biography information for Lord Hain","Mr Peter Hain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212182","212182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101341","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK personnel were involved in the destruction of Borak chemical rockets in 2006.","Biography information for Lord Hain","Mr Peter Hain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212183","212183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101342","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officers in the regular forces there have been at each rank between one star, NATO code OF-6, and five star, NATO code OF-10, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212165","212165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101343","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual operating cost is of RAF Northolt.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212250","212250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101344","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much annual revenue his Department generates from the commercial or civil use of RAF Northolt.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212251","212251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101345","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who has access to his Department's sports and social club; what the annual cost of running the club was in each of the last two years; what benefits members receive; and what the cost per person is of such benefits.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212238","212238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101346","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whom his Department consulted on its decision as part of the 2010 Strategic Defence and Security Review to disband the No 2 squadron of Tornado aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212237","212237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101347","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent meetings he has had with Bahraini human rights advocates.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212170","212170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101348","2014-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what arms the UK has sold to the government of Bahrain since 2010; what licence conditions were imposed on exporters; and what due diligence was undertaken to ensure those weapons would not be used on Bahraini citizens.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212305","212305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101349","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many single servicemen and servicewomen based at or near Catterick, North Yorkshire, are currently accommodated in (a) single living accommodation provided for his Department by a contractor and (b) other private rented accommodation; and what the average cost per month per person is to his Department for each such type of accommodation.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212285","212285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101350","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when Boulogne Barracks, Catterick, was last used as accommodation for single servicemen and women; what the maximum number of personnel who could be accommodated in that barracks was at that time; and if he will make an estimate of how much the cost was of renovating that barracks for use as single living accommodation.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212286","212286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101351","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether all items of cultural material from the HMS Victory 1744 wreck site will be acquired by the Maritime Heritage Foundation for deposition in one complete museum archive as required by the UNESCO Annex and Key Management Principles.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212334","212334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101352","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he had with Lord Lingfield, then Sir Robert Balchin, regarding the formation of a company or charity to take on management of the wreck of HMS Victory 1744.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212335","212335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101353","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether completion bonds or other financial arrangements will be put in place before granting the Maritime Heritage Foundation permission to recover at risk surface items from the wreck site of HMS Victory 1744; and what specific communications there have been between government departments on that matter.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212332","212332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101354","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which museum will be taking the accessioned collection of material from HMS Victory 1744.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212333","212333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101355","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reports from independent companies and subject experts in sea bed restoration and conservation the Maritime Heritage Foundation have been submitted to the Expert Panel and Advisory Group, in respect to the wreck site of HMS Victory 1744.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212336","212336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101356","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what sanctions are available to his Department if the Maritime Heritage Foundation or the Odyssey Marine Exploration attempt to sell any material of any kind from the wreck site of HMS Victory 1744 in contravention of the Deed of Gift, the UNESCO Annex and Government's Key Management Principles.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212338","212338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101357","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has been subject to any prospect of legal action by the Maritime Heritage Foundation or the Odyssey Marine Exploration, regarding the recovery of material from HMS Victory 1744.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212330","212330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101358","2014-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what arrangements his Department is making for direct, on board ship monitoring of the work on the HMS Victory wreck site by independent archaeologists.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212331","212331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101359","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children in England also have a sibling in care; and how many looked-after children in England are (a) living with at least one of their siblings and (b) not living with any of their siblings.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212283","212283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101360","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children in each local authority were in a foster care placement on 31 March (a) 2008, (b) 2010, (c) 2013 and (d) 2014; how many such children in each local authority were in a foster care placement with a relative or friend (i) inside and (ii) outside the authority boundary on each of those dates; how many such children in each local authority were under (A) an interim and (B) a full court order on each of those dates; and how many such children in each local authority area were looked after under a voluntary agreement under section 20 of the Children Act 1989 on each of those dates.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212293","212293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101361","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the requirement for secondary school places amongst religious denominations in the London Borough of Barnet in the next five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212160","212160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101362","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the requirement for secondary school places in the London Borough of Barnet over the next five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212161","212161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101363","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many black and minority ethnic teachers there are in state (a) primary and (b) secondary schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212173","212173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101364","2014-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to provide children in custody with better education; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212207","212207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101365","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academies provide boarding places for paying overseas students.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212302","212302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101366","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many overseas students are paying for boarding places in academies.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212303","212303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101367","2014-11-03","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people without a recognised teaching qualification are employed as teachers in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (i) the north west and (ii) Warrington.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212264","212264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101368","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons her Department's Annual Report and Accounts for 2013-14 has not yet been published; and when that report is due to be published.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212256","212256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101369","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers retired (a) due to age, (b) due to health problems and (c) prematurely from publicly-funded schools in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212177","212177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101370","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of how many additional teachers will be needed in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212178","212178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101371","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time teachers retired from publicly-funded schools in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212179","212179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101372","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers are no longer in service in the English publicly-funded schools sector and did not receive a pension in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212180","212180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101373","2014-10-30","Department for Education","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which free schools opened in September 2014; and how many children were enrolled at each such school at the time they opened.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212252","212252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101374","2014-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when all licensed import and distribution terminals will be fully post-Buncefield compliant.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212190","212190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101375","2014-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with Ofgem on the pricing structure of the energy industry.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212185","212185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/101376","2014-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many former refineries have been converted to import and distribution terminals.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 212181","212181"
