"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439356","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to conduct a revaluation of council tax bands in 2016.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20553","20553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439357","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to review the effectiveness of the general power of competence.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20554","20554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439358","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects to publish the outcomes of his Department's BBC Charter Review consultation.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20548","20548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439359","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects to publish the results of his consultation on the BBC Charter Review.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20546","20546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439360","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish the responses to his Department's consultation on the future of the BBC.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20594","20594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439361","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish the Government's response to the BBC Charter renewal consultation.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20585","20585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439362","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) his Department, (b) Ofcom, (c) Royal Parks, (d) Arts Council England, (e) Sport England, (f) UK sport, (g) Visit Britain, (h) Visit England and (i) the Equality and Human Rights Commission; and how many of those employees are paid more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those orqanisations in the most recent for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20617","20617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439363","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects to publish his Department's response to the BBC Charter Review consultation.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20638","20638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439364","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when responses from members of the public to the recent BBC Charter review consultation will be published.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20635","20635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439365","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the Government plans to publish the outcome of its consultation on the review of the BBC's Royal Charter which closed on 8 October 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20705","20705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439366","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he intends to answer the letter to him from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton, dated 9 November 2015 with regard to Mr S Hewitt.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20691","20691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439367","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many senior officers have attended at least one week of training at force development training centres.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20637","20637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439368","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) his Department, (b) the Defence Electronics and Components Agency, (c) the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory, (d) the UK Hydrographic Office, (e) the National Army Museum, (f) the National Museum of the Royal Navy, (g) the Royal Air Force Museum, (h) the Single Source Regulations Office and (i) the Oil and Pipelines Agency; how many of these employees earn more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those organisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20602","20602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439369","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral contribution of the Foreign Secretary of 16 December 2015, on Daesh: Syria/Iraq, if he will take steps to assess whether there have been civilian casualties as a result of UK airstrikes in Iraq and Syria through means other than receipt of reports.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20596","20596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439370","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have been killed as a result of UK airstrikes in Syria since 3 December 2015.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20597","20597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439371","2016-01-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether fact sheets have been prepared providing (a) supporting detail and (b) timetables for implementation of the proposals set out in the Strategic Defence and Security Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20598","20598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439372","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2015 to Question 19431, when in 2016 he expects the national shipbuilding strategy to be published.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20545","20545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439373","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether sixth form colleges that choose to become academies will be able to enter into contracts with the Skills Funding Agency.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20544","20544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439374","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 15125, when she plans to publish draft proposals on eligibility requirements for free school meals within universal credit; when the consultation on those proposals will be launched; and when she plans to make a final decision on eligibility.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20634","20634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439375","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) her Department, (b) Ofqual, (c) Ofsted, (d) the National College for Teaching and Leadership, (e) the Office of the Children's Commissioner and (f) the Equalities Office; how many of those employees earn more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those organisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20606","20606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439376","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) financial and (b) other support is available to help young adult carers who wish to continue on to higher education.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20664","20664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439377","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much parents and guardians have been fined for taking their children on term-time holidays in the academic year 2013-14.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20659","20659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439378","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will consider making young adult carers eligible for the vulnerable groups component of the bursary which provides financial support for 16 to 19 year olds.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20665","20665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439379","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of statutory PSHE education for the health of school pupils; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20676","20676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439380","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the Chief Medical Officer's recommendations that PSHE education be made a routine part of children's education.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20678","20678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439381","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects to be able to announce how carbon capture and storage research and deployment will be funded in future; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20679","20679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439382","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she intends to answer the letter to her from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton, dated 5 November 2015 with regard to Ms J Batsleer.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20692","20692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439383","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many press or public relations officers are employed by (a) Ofgem, (b) the Oil and Gas Authority, (c) the Civil Nuclear Police Authority, (d) the Coal Authority, (e) the Committee on Climate Change and (f) the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority; how many of those staff earn more that (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total cost is of running the press office in each of those organisations in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20626","20626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439384","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what electricity consumption in England was in (a) 2005, (b) 2010 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20611","20611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439385","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the total UK financial commitment to the Green Climate Fund until 2030.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20551","20551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439386","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department intends to expand the range of technologies available under the Renewable Heat Incentive as part of its process of reviewing the scheme.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20573","20573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439387","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has assessed the potential use of gas-driven heat pumps as part of its review of the Renewable Heat Incentive.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20571","20571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439388","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans the Government has to (a) provide financial support and (b) conclude and sign long-term contracts prior to construction in order to achieve the capital investment in energy storage technology necessary to reach the 27.4 gigawatts identified in the Technology Innovation Needs Assessment.","Biography information for John McNally","John Mc Nally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20541","20541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439389","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of (a) the efficacy of the third badger pilot cull in Somerset and (b) the humaneness of the badger pilot culls to date.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20581","20581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439390","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to extend badger culls into new areas.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20582","20582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439391","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish an analysis of the outcomes and costs of the third badger cull.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20583","20583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439392","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) guidelines, (b) regulations and (c) EU directives are in place which restrict the use of antibiotics for livestock.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20612","20612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439393","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the use of electric shock and prong collars for dogs before 2020.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20579","20579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439394","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the inspection regime is for ensuring that hens are housed in conditions compliant with relevant EU directives.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20694","20694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439395","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the dependency that hen welfare has on the frequency of human attention regardless of the position of the cages in which they are kept.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20695","20695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439396","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) the Forestry Commission, (b) the Water Services Regulation Authority, (c) the Animal and Plant Health Agency, (d) the Centre for Environment, Fisheries and Aquaculture Science, (e) the Rural Payments Agency, (f) the Veterinary Medicines Directorate, (g) the Agriculture and Horticulture Development Board, (h) the Board of Trustees of the Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew, (i) the Consumer Council for Water, (j) the Environment Agency, (k) the Joint Nature Conservation Committee, (l) the Marine Management Organisation, (m) the National Forest Company, (n) Natural England and (o) the Sea Fish Industry Authority; how many of those employees are paid more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those orqanisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20618","20618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439397","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, through what means his Department communicates with and receives communications from Christian communities in Syria; and how he assesses the quality of information received otherwise by his Department on the situation of such communities in that country.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20696","20696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439398","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on (a) travel, (b) first or business class flights for officials, (c) first or business class flights for Ministers, (c) first class train travel for officials and (d) first class train travel for Ministers in 2014-15.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20687","20687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439399","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) UK Trade and Investment, (b) FCO Services, (c) Wilton Park, (d) the British Council, (e) the Great Britain-China Centre, (f) the Marshall Aid Commemoration Commission and (g) the Westminster Foundation for Democracy, (h) Government Communications Headquarters and (i) the Secret Intelligence Service; how many of those employees earn more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those organisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20605","20605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439400","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of how many (a) children, (b) women and (c) men have been killed by Daesh/ISIL; and what his Department's estimate is of the number of women who have been raped by Daesh.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20660","20660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439401","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will issue a response to EDM 858, Violence in Galkayo, Somalia.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20572","20572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439402","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the case of Abdullah al-Zaher.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20567","20567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439403","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will issue a response to Early Day Motion 884, Arrests in Malawi of Cuthbert Kulemela and Kelving Gonani.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20552","20552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439404","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that records of the training history of the nurses convicted at Nursing and Midwifery Council hearings are kept on the same basis as such data in such cases by the General Medical Council.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20584","20584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439405","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the potential effect on the costs of elderly care of the introduction of the national living wage.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20575","20575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439406","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost is to the public purse of Deloittes' consultancy services on helping to develop commissioning policies for drugs to treat ultra-rare diseases.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20663","20663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439407","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Hepatitis C Improvement Framework will be published and whether that framework will contain guidance to commissioners on increasing patient access to new Direct Acting Antiviral treatments that have been approved by NICE.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20631","20631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439408","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people who were infected with hepatitis C due to contaminated blood products supplied by the NHS have attained sustained virological response following treatment for the infection.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20658","20658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439409","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the circumstances in which there should be an investigation into mental health outpatients who have an avoidable death.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20644","20644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439410","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of (a) GPs and (b) clinical commissioning groups have plans in place to identify unavoidable deaths.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20645","20645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439411","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Care Quality Commission on collection and publication of data on mortality rates of over 75s in mental health trusts.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20646","20646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439412","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many practising GPs there were in Northamptonshire in (a) 2005, (b) 2010 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20613","20613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439413","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 16 December 2015 to Question 19441 and 20 November 2015 to Question 16648, what the reason is for the apparent difference in the data collection policies on local clinical commissioning groups' spend with independent sector providers described in those Answers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20614","20614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439414","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will maintain patient access to technologies considered through commissioning through evaluation programmes during that evaluation.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20580","20580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439415","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's publication, Living Well for Longer: One year on, published in March 2015, when he plans to publish a hepatitis C Improvement Framework.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20586","20586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439416","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with hepatitis C have commenced treatment under the commissioning policy for the treatment of patients with cirrhosis since June 2015.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20600","20600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439417","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the hepatitis C Improvement Framework will include provisions on clinical commissioning groups and local authorities to engage with the Operational Delivery Networks jointly to commission services.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20601","20601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439418","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to answer the letter to his Department from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton, dated 16 November 2015 with regard to Mr M Bolton.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20689","20689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439419","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on the Chief Medical Officer's recommendations that PSHE education be made a routine part of children's education.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20677","20677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439420","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on average how many patients died in A&E on a (a) Monday, (b) Tuesday, (c) Wednesday, (d) Thursday, (e) Friday, (f) Saturday and (g) Sunday in the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20655","20655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439421","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on average, how many patients were admitted to A&E on a (a) Monday, (b) Tuesday, (c) Wednesday, (d) Thursday, (e) Friday, (f) Saturday and (g) Sunday in the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20656","20656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439422","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients have had miscarriages as a result of the amniocentesis test in the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20680","20680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439423","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients gave birth to children with Down's syndrome in each of the last three years; and how many such patients had had an amniocentesis test.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20681","20681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439424","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an estimate of the cost of introducing non-invasive prenatal testing for Down's syndrome to all NHS hospitals in the UK.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20682","20682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439425","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on elderly care providers of the introduction of the National Living Wage.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20686","20686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439426","2016-01-05","Department for International Development","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made on achieving the goals of the Global Polio Eradication Initiative.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20675","20675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439427","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with serious mental health issues are receiving appropriate physical health care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20643","20643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439428","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were barred from working with (a) children and (b) vulnerable adults in each of the last five years; and how many of those decisions were (i) automatic bars due to a criminal conviction which did not allow for representations, (ii) automatic bars due to a criminal conviction which did allow for representations and (iii) discretionary bars.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20698","20698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439429","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Harrow West, sent on 25 November 2015, about the immigration applications of Ms Raize Khan, Miss Radia Khan and Miss Aneela Khan; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20593","20593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439430","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) her Department, (b) the Disclosure and Barring Service, (c) the Gangmasters Licensing Authority, (d) the Independent Police Complaints Commission, (e) the National Crime Agency, (f) the Security Industry Authority, (g) UK Visas and Immigration and (h) HM Inspectorate of Constabulary; how many of those employees earn more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those organisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20610","20610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439431","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19916 on Temporary Exclusion Orders, when she expects that report to be published.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20627","20627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439432","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many properties have been bought by Serco for the purpose of housing asylum seekers in each parliamentary constituency in the Wigan local authority area; and how many asylum seekers have been housed in each such constituency.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20542","20542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439433","2016-01-05","Department for International Development","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department plans to take at the Global Fund to Fight AIDS, TB and Malaria's pre-replenishment meeting in Tokyo to encourage increased funding from other donors.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20566","20566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439434","2016-01-05","Department for International Development","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2015 to Question 19712, how much such funding her Department provided to (a) Jordan, (b) Iraq and (c) Israel in those years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20684","20684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439435","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason Community rehabilitation companies workforce information report: Q2 2015 to 2016 statistics were cancelled for release.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20674","20674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439436","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what educational provision there is for offenders who are unable to read or write.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20704","20704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439437","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reoffending rates are for (a) young people who do not complete an accredited qualification in prison, (b) young people who do complete an accredited qualification in prison, (c) all other offenders who complete an accredited qualification in prison, (d) all other offenders who do not complete an accredited qualification in prison and (e) offenders who leave prison unable to read and write.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20703","20703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439438","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been spent on the education of illiterate offenders in a prison setting in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20702","20702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439439","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many non-remand prisoners are classified a illiterate; and how many such prisoners there were in each prison in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20699","20699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439440","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding is available for illiterate prisoners to learn to read and write and to receive education while in prison.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20700","20700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439441","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of education on the probability of illiterate offenders reoffending.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20693","20693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439442","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding his Department has provided to the Gender Recognition Panel in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20560","20560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439443","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners took their own life in each month of (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015 to date.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20561","20561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439444","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many magistrates' courts opened in each local justice area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20562","20562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439445","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many magistrates' courts have been closed in each local justice area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20563","20563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439446","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of jury (a) intimidation and (b) tampering were recorded in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20564","20564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439447","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19495, what the (a) names, (b) job titles and (c) salary bands were of the staff who worked on Just Solutions International.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20629","20629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439448","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to consult the Justice Select Committee on introducing a new streamlined claims process for low cost medical negligence claims.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20595","20595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439449","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) the National Archives, (b) the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority, (c) HM Courts and Tribunal Service, (d) HM Prison Service, (e) the Legal Aid Agency, (f) the National Offender Management Service, (g) the Office of the Public Guardian, (h) Cafcass, (i) the Criminal Cases Review Commission, (j) the Judicial Appointments Commission, (k) the Legal Services board, (l) the Parole Board, (m) the Youth Justice Board for England and Wales, (n) the Law Commission, (o) HM Inspectorate of prisons, (p) HM Inspectorate of Prisons, (p) HM Inspectorate of Probation, (q) the Legal Ombudsman, (r) the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman, (s) the Victims' Commissioner; how many of those employees are paid more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those orqanisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20619","20619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439450","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff vacancies there are at the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency; and what assessment he has made of the effect of the level of those vacancies on (a) staff workloads, (b) staff morale and (c) relations between staff and management.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20565","20565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439451","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on international services stopping at Stratford International station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20555","20555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439452","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Eurostar on stopping services at Stratford International station.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20556","20556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439453","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects Deutsche Bahn to commence operating international services from London St Pancras; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20557","20557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439454","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his German counterpart on the future operation of Deutsche Bahn services between Stratford International and Germany.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20558","20558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439455","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers he estimates will be deployed in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18, (d) 2018-19 and (e) 2019-20.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20568","20568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439456","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to protect spending on the British Transport Police in real terms over the Spending Review period.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20569","20569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439457","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned expenditure is for the British Transport Police in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18, (d) 2018-19 and (e) 2019-20.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20570","20570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439458","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many miles of track Network Rail expects to electrify in Control Period 5.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20640","20640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439459","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Gospel Oak to Barking Line electrification programme includes electrification of that line's freight links.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20641","20641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439460","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 2.90 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what assessment he has made of the effect of phasing out the Transport for London (TfL) resource grant on TfL's funding of the British Transport Police.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20628","20628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439461","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on his Department's South East Flexible Ticketing programme.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20639","20639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439462","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) the office of Rail and Road, (b) the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency, (c) the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency, (d) the Maritime and Coastguard Agency, (e) the Vehicle Certification Agency, (f) the British Transport Police Authority, (g) Directly Operated Railways limited, (h) High Speed 2 Ltd; (i) Highways England, (j) Northern Lighthouse Board, (k) Transport Focus, (l) Trinity House, (m) Civil Aviation Authority and (n) the Airports Commission; how many of those employees are paid more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those organisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20616","20616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439463","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) directions or (b) guidance his Department issues to the British Transport Police or the British Transport Police Authority on cost savings in (i) 2015-16 and (ii) future financial years.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20607","20607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439464","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress has been made on the London and South Coast Rail Corridor Study covering the establishment of a Brighton Mainline 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20630","20630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439465","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what directions or guidance his Department has issued to (a) Network Rail, (b) train operating companies and (c) Transport for London regarding funding agreements with British Transport Police since the publication of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20636","20636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439466","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the British Transport Police budget was in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20670","20670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439467","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects Network Rail's review of the delivery programme of the Great Western Main Line electrification to be completed.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20701","20701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439468","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has requested the British Transport Police Authority to set out options for a reduction in the British Transport Police budget.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20671","20671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439469","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many police officers from the British Transport Police were deployed in (a) London and (b) the rest of the UK in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20672","20672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439470","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what financial contribution Transport for London made to the British Transport Police in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20673","20673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439471","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 19711, what the number of such claimants was in (a) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20685","20685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439472","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland who have been sanctioned found work within six months of that sanction being imposed.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20669","20669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439473","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland who have been sanctioned found work within three months of that sanction being imposed.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20668","20668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439474","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland who have been sanctioned found work within three months of that sanction being imposed.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20667","20667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439475","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseekers allowance claimants in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland who have been sanctioned found work within six months of that sanction being imposed.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20666","20666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439476","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to answer the letter to him from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton, dated 17 November 2015 with regard to Mr N Cooper.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20690","20690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439477","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many press and public relations are employed by (a) the Disabled People's Employment Corporation, (b) Health and Safety Executive, (c) National Employment Savings Trust Corporation, (d) Pensions Advisory Service, (e) Pensions Regulator, (f) Pension Protection Fund Ombudsman, (g) Pensions Ombudsman, (h) Pension Protection Fund; how many of those employees were paid more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total cost of running press office in each of those organisations was in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20608","20608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439478","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects to submit the full business case for universal credit to HM Treasury; and when he expects final approval of that case to be granted.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20625","20625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439479","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 20080, by what date his Department will review all reports which relate to the Welfare Reform and Work Bill; and whether his Department will publish a response to or make a statement on those reports after completing that review.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20662","20662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439480","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report entitled, Estimating the Early Labour Market Impacts of Universal Credit, published by his Department in December 2015, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of (a) the finding reported on page 27, that the additional work undertaken by participants in the study who were claiming universal credit is likely to consist of relatively few hours at relatively low wages and (b) the findings of the independent peer review, published in Annex B of the report, that the differences between the earnings of people in receipt of universal credit and people in the control group were not satisfactory significant.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20632","20632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439481","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 7 of the Government's response to the Fifth Report from the Work and Pensions Committee, on Benefit Sanctions: Beyond the Oakley Review, HC 557, when the Government plans to publish the results of its evaluation of the pilot programme of in-work sanctions.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20633","20633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439482","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of uprating the Minimum Income Floor for the self-employed on universal credit inline with the National Minimum Wage on the number of people moving into self-employment.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20657","20657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439483","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, under what circumstances a person within one of the universal credit north west pathfinder jobcentres, who meets the eligibility criteria for universal credit under the pathfinder programme, may start a claim for jobseeker's allowance instead of universal credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20615","20615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439484","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to answer Question 19086, tabled on 8 December 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20642","20642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439485","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to reform the (a) work allowances and (b) taper rate within universal credit during the current Parliament.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20620","20620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439486","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 2.50 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, to which claimants the announcement of an extension of job search conditionality relates.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20621","20621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439487","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each of the 11 pilot areas of universal support delivered locally (a) participated in that programme and (b) consented to have their information used for the purposes of evaluating that programme between September 2014 and September 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20622","20622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439488","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to evaluate the Universal Support Delivered Locally programme on completion of the pilot study.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20623","20623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439489","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he (a) submitted and (b) received a response to (i) the strategic outline business case and (ii) the outline business case for universal credit from HM Treasury.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20624","20624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439490","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people within each of the four Universal Credit North West Pathfinder jobcentres who meet the eligibility criteria for claiming universal credit under the Pathfinder programme have started a claim for jobseeker's allowance since the launch of universal credit in each of those jobcentres.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20647","20647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439491","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in which areas the digital service for universal credit is (a) in operation and (b) expected to be in operation by April 2016.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20648","20648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439492","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will undertake a distributional analysis of the effect of recent changes to the work allowances within universal credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20649","20649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439493","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the forecast number of people who will (a) move into work, (b) move out of poverty, (c) have increased income and (d) have increased of income of more than £25 a week following transition to universal credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20650","20650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439494","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the six pilot areas for Universal Support Delivered Locally were selected for an additional six months extension from September 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20651","20651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439495","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's report, Universal Credit Extended Gateway Evaluation, published on 6 December 2015, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the report's finding on page 39, that participants in the study who were claiming universal credit were more flexible regarding the type of work they would consider at the outset than people claiming jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20577","20577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439496","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's report, Universal Credit Extended Gateway Evaluation, published on 6 December 2015, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the report's finding on page 13, that 37 per cent of people claiming universal credit felt that their claimant commitment took account of their personal circumstances.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20578","20578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439497","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have been provided with advance payments of universal credit in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20559","20559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439498","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether (a) all and (b) vulnerable tenants who receive housing benefit are subject to additional protection from eviction by landlords.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20543","20543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442434","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the proposed council tax levy for social care will support integration of health and social care.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902877","902877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442435","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve one-year cancer survival rates over the next five years.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902878","902878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442436","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to achieve seven-day services in hospitals by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902873","902873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442437","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that implementation of European Professional Cards for doctors does not inhibit his Department's ability to perform background checks on doctors from other European countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902879","902879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442438","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission a review of portion sizes to inform the food industry and consumers about what constitutes a healthy portion.","Biography information for James Berry","James Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902876","902876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442439","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number of patients who went to A&E after being unable to make an appointment with their GP in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902882","902882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442440","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the frequency of use of police detention facilities for mental health patients who pose a risk to themselves or others when mental health facilities are full or unavailable.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902872","902872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442441","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve outcomes for people with rarer cancers.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902875","902875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442779","2016-01-06","Scotland Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the welfare measures announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 on the incidence of food poverty in Scotland.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902856","902856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442780","2016-01-06","Scotland Office","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) Ministers of the Scottish Government on the future of HM Revenue and Customs offices in Scotland.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902853","902853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443129","2016-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to support the development of additional new nuclear reactors.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902821","902821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443130","2016-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she has taken to ensure that the National Infrastructure Commission gives priority to energy efficiency programmes in its investment decisions.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902823","902823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443131","2016-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to increase parliamentary engagement in the implementation of Intended Nationally Determined Contributions.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902840","902840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443132","2016-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with energy suppliers on the effect of pre-payment meter tariffs on low-income households' energy costs.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902841","902841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443133","2016-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that the UK meets its EU renewable heat target for 2020.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902818","902818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443134","2016-01-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to reduce the level of fuel poverty.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902839","902839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438839","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on the ease with which the Student Loans Company can be contacted.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20407","20407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438840","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will set out the exemptions and compensation for the steel industry, and the dates from which each will apply, announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20439","20439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438841","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate he has made of the investment rate in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20442","20442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438842","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 11065, how many of the 2 million apprenticeships created in the last Parliament were in the (a) retail, (b) skilled labour and (c) construction sector.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20474","20474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438843","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value was of Government subsidies and financial incentives to retail companies to encourage the creation of apprenticeships in the retail sector since 2010.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20475","20475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438844","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Government subsidies and financial incentives to retail companies to encourage the creation of apprenticeships in the retail sector were given to companies known to use zero-hours or casual contract since 2010.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20476","20476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438845","2016-01-05","Cabinet Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the dates were of all meetings between July and November 2015 of the Cabinet Sub-committee on airports.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20399","20399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438846","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reduce the rate of VAT on tourism.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20409","20409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438847","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to use any of its statutory regulatory powers to ensure that there is the reduction in the cost of car insurance referred to in paragraph 1.143 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20373","20373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438848","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans that the three per cent additional stamp duty rate on the purchase of a second home will apply to people in the process of moving house who own two properties for a short period of time.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20402","20402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438849","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what mechanism any savings made by insurance companies as a result of a change to the small claims limit for soft tissue road traffic accident injuries will be passed on to policyholders.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20350","20350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438850","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received about the level of household debt.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20351","20351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438851","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effects on the economy of the level of (a) consumer borrowing and (b) personal loans.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20352","20352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438852","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential costs and benefits to business of changes to motor insurance proposed in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20348","20348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438853","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of HM Revenue and Customs office closures on the local economy in East Kilbride.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20362","20362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438854","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2014 to Question 211605, how many and what proportion of initial enquiries by HM Revenue and Customs, which sought confirmation that arrears had been paid to workers following enforcement action due to non-payment of the national minimum wage, were unable to confirm that the requisite arrears had been paid in full in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20432","20432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438855","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received about the work of Royal Bank of Scotland's Global Restructuring Group.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20452","20452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438856","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) UK Financial Investments and (b) Royal Bank of Scotland about the effects of decisions by the bank's Global Restructuring Group on (i) small businesses and (ii) the economy of the UK.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20453","20453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438857","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the contract between HM Revenue and Customs and Concentrix on compliance checks for tax credits includes payments by results.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20454","20454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438858","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the contract between HM Revenue and Customs and Concentrix on compliance checks for tax credits includes (a) the number of checks to be carried out, (b) the number of staff and (c) types of enforcement action.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20455","20455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438859","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information about applicants for tax credits is available to Concentrix under its contract with HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20456","20456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438861","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what grounds it was decided that compliance checks for tax credit applications would be outsourced to Concentrix.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20457","20457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438863","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the contract between HM Revenue and Customs and Concentrix was agreed.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20458","20458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438866","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what advice UKFI provided to his Department on when and how to complete a sale of Royal Bank of Scotland shares.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20481","20481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438868","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which organisations in addition to Rothschilds and the Governor of the Bank of England provided him with advice on whether the Government should sell its stake in the Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20482","20482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438870","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted for (i) off-shore tax evasion, (ii) in-shore tax evasion, (iii) tax credit fraud, (iv) VAT fraud, (v) smuggling and (vi) other tax-related offences in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20496","20496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438872","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities have received how many Syrian refugees.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20487","20487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438874","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will undertake an analysis of the benefits of owner-occupied retirement housing to residents of that housing; and if his Department will bring forward proposals to increase delivery of that housing.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20494","20494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438880","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much he expects local authorities to raise through the proposed social care precept arrangements; and what steps he is taking to ensure those funds are ring-fenced for care services.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20341","20341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438884","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letter of 11 October 2015 from the hon. Member for Bishop Auckland to the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which was passed to his Department.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20440","20440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438886","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2015 to Question 18920, how the local body contracts with BT have been funded.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20395","20395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438888","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2015 to Question 18159, if he will (a) collect information on the derivation of National Lottery Good Cause income by region and (b) request the National Lottery publish information on derivation of its income by region in accordance with Government open data guidelines.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20398","20398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438890","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with regulators and consumer groups on ensuring that nuisance telephone calls (a) in general and (b) to elderly citizens are eliminated.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20361","20361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438894","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much in horserace betting levy payments were received in (a) statutory and (b) voluntary payments from each betting operator in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20434","20434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438895","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many official animal mascots there are in the armed forces; and what the (a) rank, (b) rations, (c) species and (d) regiment is of such mascots.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20460","20460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438896","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what process his Department uses to estimate the number of civilians killed by the UK's bombing programme in Syria since 3 December 2015.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20490","20490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438897","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to Part 1 of the Education and Skills Act 2008, what assessment he has made of whether all armed forces personnel aged 16 and 17 are able to study for 280 guided learning hours per year towards accredited qualifications.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20347","20347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438898","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.47 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, what the timetable is for procurement of the three new logistic ships.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20374","20374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438899","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of the £2.1 billion Joint Security Fund allocation his Department will receive in each year up to 2020.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20375","20375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438900","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what programmes he plans to fund from the Joint Security Fund; and how much each such programme will receive in each year up to 2020.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20376","20376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438901","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the intelligence and surveillance technology components that will be retrofitted to Boeing P-8 Poseidon aircraft procured by his Department will be supplied by UK manufacturers.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20377","20377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438902","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many bids his Department received under its proposal to make the Defence Infrastructure Organisation government-owned contractor-operated.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20379","20379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438903","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what expenditure his Department was on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising on making the Defence Infrastructure Organisation government-owned in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13, (iii) 2013-14 and (iv) 2014-15.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20378","20378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438904","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what consideration he has given to the duties under the Natural Environment and Rural Communities Act 2006 to conserve biodiversity with regards to the sale of the former Royal School of Military Engineering training site at Lodge Hill in Medway.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20408","20408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438905","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, from which organisations his Department received bids under its proposal to make the Defence Infrastructure Organisation government-owned contractor-operated.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20380","20380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438906","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of making the Defence Infrastructure Organisation government-owned contractor-operated.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20381","20381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438907","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what risk assessment his Department made of making the Defence Infrastructure Organisation government-owned contractor-operated.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20382","20382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438908","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in his Department worked on proposals to make the Defence Infrastructure Organisation government-owned contractor-operated in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13, (c) 2013-14 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20383","20383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438909","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average amount received per pupil was in primary and secondary (a) academies, (b) free schools, (c) voluntary aided schools, (d) voluntary controlled schools and (e) community schools in England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20411","20411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438910","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which children's services departments have (a) been judged as inadequate by Ofsted and (b) had outside commissioners take over responsibility for those services from local authorities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20353","20353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438911","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which sponsors have expressed an interest forming trusts to take over the responsibilities of local authority children's services departments judged as inadequate.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20354","20354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438912","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which high performing children's services departments have provided assistance to other local authorities with such departments judged as inadequate since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20355","20355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438913","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many concurrent planning arrangements for children have been authorised in each of the last six years in each local authority.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20356","20356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438914","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Review of childcare costs: the analytical report, published by her Department on 25 November 2015, if she will publish the responses to her Department's call for evidence on childcare costs in full.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20512","20512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438915","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will change the funding for school children who receive their education outside of their own area, in order to enable the funding to follow the pupil.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20483","20483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438916","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to encourage unemployed teachers to seek work in England.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20467","20467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438917","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to consult the teaching profession before implementation of the English Baccalaureate.","Biography information for Peter Heaton-Jones","Peter Heaton-Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20534","20534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438918","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will bring forward proposals to regulate the energy market to allow residents to take their energy tariffs with them when they move property.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20527","20527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438919","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the total projected expenditure on (a) the feed-in-tariff scheme, (b) contracts for difference, (c) the Renewable Heat Incentive and (d) the capacity market mechanism in each year between 2016 and 2021 on her Department's current estimate of wholesale prices.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20492","20492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438920","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what wholesale price and carbon price forecast scenarios her Department uses when forecasting total projected expenditure of the Levy Control Framework.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20493","20493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438921","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households in (a) Birmingham, Northfield constituency, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK have prepayment meters; and what the change in the number of such meters has been in each of those areas over the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20386","20386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438922","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will apply for EU Solidarity Funding for the damage caused by recent flooding.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20403","20403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438923","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward amendments to regulations under the Pet Animals Act 1951 to include a ban on the sale of kittens in pet shops.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20415","20415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438924","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent on the Darwin Initiative in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20429","20429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438925","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many hectares of trees have been (a) felled and (b) replanted on Forestry Commission land in England in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20410","20410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438926","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of the application in the UK of elements of best practice in regulation of commercial cat breeding in other EU member states.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20413","20413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438927","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to introduce compulsory microchipping of owned cats.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20414","20414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438928","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what organisations provide Flood Defence Partnership Funding; and how much each such organisation has invested.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20495","20495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438929","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much Forestry Commission England spent on replanting in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20497","20497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438930","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has made to (a) Public Health England and (b) the Department of Health on the inclusion of (i) environmental criteria and (ii) the work of her Department's Green Food Project in the review of the Eat Well Plate.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20506","20506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438931","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on proposals for an EU ban on the prophylactic treatment of groups of animals where no disease has been diagnosed in any of the animals as part of the review of the EU Veterinary Medicinal Products legislation.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20502","20502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438932","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the process and timetable is for the European Food Safety Agency's review of its restrictions on the use of neonicotinoids; and what representations the UK has made on that review.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20503","20503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438933","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of levels of implementation of the greening requirements of the Basic Payment Scheme and its effectiveness in reducing carbon emissions and delivering improvements for pollinators and other wildlife in the farmed landscape.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20504","20504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438934","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's priorities are for the next round of negotiations on CAP.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20505","20505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438935","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the building of Israeli settlements on Palestinian land; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20539","20539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438936","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the government of Kyrgyzstan about human rights, and the Kyrgyz seat on the UN Human Rights Council from January 2016.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20531","20531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438937","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Kyrgyzstan about the role and future of international non-governmental organisations working on human rights; and whether he has raised with that government the ban on the head of the Human Rights Watch office in Bishkek.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20532","20532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438938","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government has provided to the Syrian Democratic Forces.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20533","20533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438939","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of allegations of electoral fraud in the recent legislative and presidential elections in Haiti.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20511","20511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438940","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made about the exclusion of Syrian Kurdish groups from peace talks in Riyadh.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20529","20529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438941","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the government of Turkey about (a) statements equating the PKK with ISIS and (b) negotiations between the government of Turkey and the PKK.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20530","20530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438942","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the creation of the Syrian Democratic Assembly in Northern Syria.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20528","20528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438943","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the governments of (a) Japan, (b) Norway and (c) Iceland on whaling.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20498","20498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438944","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the UK Mission to the UN is taking to address the recent findings by Haiti's National Electoral Office of contestations of irregularities to acts of fraud aimed at changing the results of the presidential elections in October 2015.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20473","20473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438945","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on the Darwin Initiative in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20431","20431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438946","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last discussed violence and insecurity in Burundi with (a) the Burundi Ambassador, (b) the Burundi government, (c) the UN and (d) the African Union.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20435","20435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438947","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation of (a) women, (b) journalists, (c) the LGBT community and (d) religious minorities in the Gambia.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20437","20437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438948","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed the declaration of an 'Islamic State' by the government of the Gambia with that government; and what assurances he has received from that government on the protection of religious freedoms in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20438","20438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438949","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Bahrain on the release of Dr Abduljalil Al-Singace in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20427","20427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438950","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Nigeria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20441","20441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438951","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Bahraini authorities about the release from prison of Mahdi Abu Dheeb, President of the Bahrain Teachers' Association.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20428","20428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438952","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) ECOWAS and (b) the African Union on ensuring free and fair elections in the Gambia in 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20436","20436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438953","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the situation in Eastern Ukraine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20400","20400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438954","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups have put in place plans for delayed discharges in co-operation with their local independent sector partners.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20397","20397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438955","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people were involved in the process of developing the care practitioner scheme which was being supported by the UK Commission for Employment and Skills; and what estimate his Department has made of how much that scheme would have cost to implement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20372","20372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438956","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has issued to clinical commissioning groups on cataloguing vacant beds within (a) the community, (b) respite care, (c) care homes and (d) nursing homes in order to cope with additional demand over the winter period.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20396","20396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438957","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's response of 16 December 2015, reference DE000001003266, to the Freedom of Information request made by the hon. Member for Lichfield on 18 November 2014 regarding that Member's meeting with the Minister for Public Health at the Department of Health at 2pm on 1 December 2014, for how long the notes taken by officials at that meeting were retained.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20387","20387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438958","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential effect of replacing student bursaries with loans on the number of British students entering nursing courses in each of the next five years; and what assessment his Department has made of whether there will be a need to increase international recruitment to the NHS as a consequence of that change.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20342","20342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438959","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on bus services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20363","20363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438960","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the average length of time that it will take for student nurses to pay off the cost of loans accrued under the proposed loans system for nurses.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20346","20346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438961","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have started treatment under NHS England's commissioning policy for the treatment of cirrhosis in adults with hepatitis C.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20470","20470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438962","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on NHS England's commissioning policy for the treatment of cirrhosis in adults with hepatitis C.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20471","20471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438963","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding is earmarked to support treatment for hepatitis C in 2016.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20472","20472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438964","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 19355, when specialist female genital mutilation mental health e-learning is planned to become available to NHS professionals.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20443","20443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438965","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 19044, which (a) voluntary sector organisations and (b) local areas Public Health England is working with to make sure there is effective distribution of the Help is at Hand publication.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20444","20444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438966","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 19043, what steps he is taking to address the increase in the number of people sectioned under the Mental Health Act 1983 since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20445","20445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438967","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 19359, what support his Department plans to provide under universal credit that is currently provided by the Severe Disability Premium.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20446","20446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438968","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) nurses and (b) healthcare assistants have undergone training for notifying parents that their baby has Down's syndrome.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20450","20450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438969","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidelines his Department issues on notifying parents of (a) Downs syndrome and (b) other chromosomal disorders.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20448","20448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438970","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training is given to healthcare practitioners for notifying parents that their baby has Down's syndrome.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20449","20449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438971","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of healthcare practitioners involved in notifying parents that their baby has Down's syndrome who have not received relevant specialist training.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20451","20451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438972","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the nutritional adequacy of food provided by private care homes.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20466","20466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438973","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2015 to Question 16660, what checks are made on locum social workers.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20513","20513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438974","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2015 to Question 16659, whether providers of locum social workers must be registered with the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20514","20514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438975","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has conducted on the number of private care homes with inadequate numbers of staff.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20515","20515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438976","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Clinical Director Specialised Commissioning for NHS England and the external assessments centres at Newcastle and York on the Commissioning through Evaluation programme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20516","20516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438977","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Care Quality Commission plans to introduce a public review system for care homes.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20517","20517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438978","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on the introduction of CCTV in private care homes.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20518","20518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438979","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to give the Care Quality Commission additional powers to sanction care providers which are persistently non-compliant with inspection regimes.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20519","20519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438980","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the Care Quality Commission has been the subject of legal action by care providers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20520","20520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438981","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will limit the costs that hospitals can charge for providing medical records to third parties or relatives of deceased persons.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20486","20486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438982","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will research the causes of systemic failure at private care homes run by the same provider.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20484","20484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438983","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department will take to enable union representation in private care homes.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20491","20491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438984","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate NHS England has made of how many patients will commence treatment for hepatitis C in 2016.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20469","20469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438985","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the proportion of the budgets European healthcare systems spent on (a) cancer and (b) other drug treatments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20508","20508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438986","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the NHS budget was spent on (a) generic and (b) branded cancer medicines for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20509","20509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438987","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the NHS budget was spent on (a) cancer drug treatments and (b) other treatments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20507","20507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438988","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect on patient access to medical technologies of NHS England's development of specialised commissioning policies in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20521","20521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438989","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has conducted on the effect on patient care of variable levels of staffing at private care homes at different times of the day.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20522","20522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438990","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the proportion of the budgets European healthcare systems spent on (a) generic and (b) branded cancer medicines for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20510","20510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438991","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that the level of mental health support available to victims of internal trafficking within the UK is equivalent to that available to victims of international human trafficking.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20447","20447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438992","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to coordinate investigations into lead thefts from places of worship (a) nationally and (b) regionally.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20406","20406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438993","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15775, on how many occasions since 2010 an authorisation under section 60AA of the Criminal Justice and Public Order Act 1994 has been granted in each police force area in England and Wales; and for what purpose each such authorisation was granted.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20345","20345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438994","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will direct HM Chief Inspector of Constabulary to investigate Kent Police's handling of a complaint of alleged corruption within the BBC in Tunbridge Wells made by a constituent of the hon. Member for North Norfolk.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20364","20364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438995","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have been employed in (a) the National Crime Agency's National Cyber Crime Unit and (b) each of the nine Regional Organised Crime Units for each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20365","20365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438996","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have been absent from work due to stress-related illnesses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20366","20366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438997","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse is of the Government's Cyberstreetwise programme for (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20367","20367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438998","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many National Crime Agency specials with particular expertise in cyber-crime there are; and how many such people have been recruited since January 2015.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20369","20369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438999","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cyber specials there are in police forces; and how many such people have been recruited since January 2015.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20370","20370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439000","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the responses to her letter of 24 November 2015 to all local council leaders on the Dispersal of Unaccompanied Asylum Seeking Children; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20412","20412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439001","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's fact sheet on the Syrian Resettlement Programme, what the evidential basis is for the Statement that Sudan is primarily a country of transit; what assessment her Department has made of the latest immigration statistics show that, in the year ending September 2015, Sudan was the country from which the second largest number of asylum applications originated; and if she will work more closely with the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs on this policy area.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20422","20422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439002","2016-01-05","Department for International Development","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on the Darwin Initiative in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20430","20430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439003","2016-01-05","Department for International Development","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what effect Sustainable Development Goal 3 has had on her Department's aid strategy for UK; and what account she plans to take of that goal in forming the new UK aid strategy.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20485","20485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439004","2016-01-05","Department for International Development","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 19180, how her Department calculates how to allocate refugee support funding to recipient countries; what information her Department holds on how the distribution of that funding is allocated by the recipient country; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20540","20540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439005","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 19570, if he will launch a public consultation on prison closures.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20525","20525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439006","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 1.143 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what steps his Department took to ensure accuracy of the £2 billion quoted as the cost to insurers of whiplash claims; and if his Department will conduct its own estimate of that cost.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20499","20499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439007","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 1.143 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what the evidential basis is of the statement that a claimant culture exists in England and Wales in relation to whiplash claims.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20500","20500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439008","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications by grandparents for permission to apply for a contact order to see their grandchildren were successful in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20477","20477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439009","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contact orders for grandparents to see their grandchildren were issued in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20478","20478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439010","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications by grandparents for rights of access to their grandchildren there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20479","20479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439011","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to reply to Question 15306, tabled by the hon. Member for Hammersmith on 16 November 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20461","20461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439012","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 18875, in which prisons each of those mobile telephones and sim cards were detected in each of those years; and what the number of such detections was per prisoner in each of those years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20343","20343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439013","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 18873, what proportion of his Department's staff were agency workers covering (a) cover operational uniformed staff, (b) uniformed operational staff and (c) clerical agency staff were represented in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20344","20344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439014","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents his Department has recorded of drones operating over prison estates in the last year for which figures are available; what steps his Department took following each such incident; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20357","20357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439015","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much (a) the National Offender Management Service and (b) his Department spent on external consultancy fees related to that service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20423","20423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439016","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations he has received on his Department's projections for prison (a) population and (b) capacity over the next 12 months.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20424","20424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439017","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support he has made available to enable people with learning disabilities to serve on juries in the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20425","20425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439018","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prison cells reckoned as (a) certified normal and (b) operational capacity accommodation in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20426","20426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439019","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the proportion of released prisoners subsequently convicted for offences committed in the first 18 days after release was in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20384","20384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439020","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for Contact Orders submitted by people to see their grandchildren were granted in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20385","20385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439021","2016-01-05","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many visits Ministers have made to the Northern Ireland Office in Brussels since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20465","20465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439022","2016-01-05","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many officials in her Department have been seconded from outside Northern Ireland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20462","20462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439023","2016-01-05","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Department of Agriculture in Northern Ireland in advance of the EU Fisheries Council in December 2015.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20463","20463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439024","2016-01-05","Cabinet Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times and in which locations the British Irish council has met since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20464","20464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439025","2016-01-05","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress was made at the recent tri-lateral cross-border ministerial meeting on the Stormont House agreement; and what topics were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20459","20459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439026","2016-01-05","Scotland Office","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 10602, on which dates he has held meetings with HM Treasury on the potential effects of a carbon price support exemption scheme in Scotland in the last year.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20538","20538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439027","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to enable smaller London airports to provide extra aviation capacity for the South East of England over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20501","20501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439028","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the organisations awarded funding from the Community Transport Minibus Fund in March 2015 have received (a) a vehicle and (b) that funding.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20358","20358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439029","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what winter weather resilience measures have been put in place for the West Coast mainline.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20359","20359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439030","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what contingency plans his Department has for the funding of the new Northern and TransPennine franchises in the event that projected passenger number increases are not achieved.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20368","20368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439031","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on proposals for an independent body to regulate the car insurance industry.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20349","20349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439032","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding the Rail Delivery Group received from the public purse in (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013, (d) 2014 and (v) 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20371","20371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439033","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on utilising existing airport capacity in the UK to 2030 in the last month.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20392","20392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439034","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will not make a decision on the choice of Thames Crossing options A and C until a decision is made on the proposed London Paramount theme park.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20416","20416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439035","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps are being taken to reduce congestion at the northbound entrance to the Dartford Tunnel caused by lorries carrying dangerous cargo being stopped and investigated.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20418","20418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439036","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 19589, what the budget for the BIS Automotive sector team has been in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20401","20401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439037","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to build an additional bridge at Dartford.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20419","20419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439038","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential arrangements for compensation required for people living in Thurrock and Dartford or Gravesend in the event of another river crossing being constructed at Dartford or to the east of Gravesend.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20421","20421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439039","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to help reduce traffic congestion on the northbound approaches to the Dartford Tunnel.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20420","20420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439040","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential effect on congestion at the Dartford Tunnel of increasing the number of Channel Tunnel freight trains that off-load north of the River Thames.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20417","20417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439041","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Health and Safety Executive is taking to ensure there is timely reduction in the backlog of safety-critical maintenance in the offshore oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20405","20405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439042","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether training is given to work capability assessors in the symptoms and effects of 22q11.2 deletion syndrome.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20393","20393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439043","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many welfare claimants were sanctioned between 21 and 27 December 2015; and how many such claimants were single parents.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20404","20404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439044","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the adequacy for people with support dogs of their rights physically to access businesses and services.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20394","20394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439045","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the amount his Department will save as a result of limiting the backdating of housing benefit to a maximum of one month in each of the next four years; and how that estimate was calculated.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20390","20390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439046","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 18835, what alternative options will be available to single people claiming housing benefit who are under the age of 35 and are not able to afford a social tenancy from April 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20391","20391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439047","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will exempt adults with disabilities whose partner is unable to share the same bedroom due to that disability from the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20388","20388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439048","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of housing benefit claims in respect of which a request for backdating was approved resulted in the payment of arrears for a period of (a) less than one month, (b) one month only, (b) between one and three months and (d) between three and six months in the most recent period for which figures are avilable.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20389","20389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439049","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people did not have a National Insurance number on 31 March 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20360","20360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439050","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect removing the family premium from new claims for housing benefit the ability of claimants affected to move outside their local authority area in order to take up better paid work.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20488","20488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439051","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the effect of limiting the backdating of housing benefit to a maximum of one month on (a) the ability of tenants to pay any rent arrears accrued after a delay in applying for housing benefit and (b) the willingness of landlords in the private rented sector to let properties to people claiming housing benefit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20489","20489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439052","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many women affected by state pension age equalisation live in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20468","20468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439053","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his estimate is of the notional average weekly change in benefit which working families currently claiming housing benefit would face as a result of removing the family premium from the calculation of their housing benefit entitlement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20480","20480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439054","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions work programme providers referred participants for a sanction between (a) June 2011 and November 2015 and (b) August 2015 and November 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20433","20433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439055","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of his Department's employees were paid (a) at the national minimum wage and (b) above the national minimum wage but below the voluntary living wage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20535","20535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439056","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance were made by (i) UK nationals and (ii) EU nationals from outside the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20536","20536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439057","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of (a) UK nationals and (b) EU nationals from outside the UK are (i) in work, (ii) in receipt of jobseeker's allowance and (iii) in receipt of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20537","20537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439058","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times participants in the work programme were sanctioned between (a) June 2011 and November 2015 and (b) August 2015 and November 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20526","20526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439059","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much and what proportion of his Department's budget for employment support has been allocated to the Work and Health Programme for each of the next four years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20523","20523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/439060","2016-01-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people, excluding people participating in the Work Programme, who were claiming employment and support allowance and were previously in receipt of incapacity benefit, ended their claim for employment and support allowance after moving into work during the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20524","20524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438558","2015-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of medical students in England and Wales are white men from a working class background.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20195","20195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438559","2015-12-17","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether employers that have offshored their company payroll will be required to pay the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20177","20177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438560","2015-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the value of the contract of tender for the employers' digital apprenticeship account; and when he plans to put that contract out to tender.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20179","20179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438561","2015-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was spent by the Government on apprenticeships in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20180","20180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438562","2015-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made in negotiations with Lloyd's Bank plc about business banking services being offered through the Post Office.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20207","20207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438563","2015-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made in negotiations with Barclays Bank plc about business banking services being offered through the Post Office.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20208","20208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438564","2015-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the number of postmasters who have been penalised as a result of the Post Office Horizon computer system.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20231","20231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438565","2015-12-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to widen access to the digital economy for young people.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20308","20308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438566","2015-12-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to help young people engage with the digital economy.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20309","20309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438567","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to respond to Question 18667, tabled on 3 December 2015.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20324","20324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438568","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2015 to Question 19258, if he will estimate the reduction in pounds in the amount of tax collected from the manufacturing sector as a consequence of reductions in the corporate tax rate.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20327","20327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438569","2015-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the budget for the Trade Show Access Programme will be in financial year (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18 and (c) 2018-19; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20266","20266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438570","2015-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which trades unions will be represented in the proposed Institute for Apprenticeships.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20275","20275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438571","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which external organisations have contributed to his Department's review on business rates.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20250","20250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438572","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings he has had on his Department's proposed review of business rates.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20249","20249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438573","2015-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the likely value of increased trade between the UK and Canada as a result of the EU Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership; and what steps he plans to take to encourage trade in (a) Alberta, (b) British Columbia and (c) the rest of Canada.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20279","20279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438574","2015-12-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what cross-departmental initiatives there are to tackle cyberbullying and protect young people from abuse online.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20310","20310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438575","2015-12-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to increase the level of home ownership relative to other EU countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20117","20117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438576","2015-12-17","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2015 to Question 15349, if HM Revenue and Customs will expand the tax exemption associated with the Cycle to Work scheme to provide employees with access to tax-free physical activity accessories and personalised activity plans for themselves and their families.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20264","20264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438577","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the reasons for increases in the trade deficit in UK goods and services in the three months to October 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20329","20329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438578","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department allocated to HM Revenue and Customs for the purpose of prosecuting employers who failed to pay the minimum wage in each financial year since 2005; and what the projected budget is for such activities in each financial year until 2020.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20326","20326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438579","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.122 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reducing the income rise disregard on the household income of a tax credit claimant family with one earner and two children whose income rose from £20,000 to £25,000 during the year.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20332","20332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438580","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2015 to Question 17980, if his Department will consider publishing details of meetings with insurance industry representatives before the next return.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20334","20334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438581","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2015 to Question 18028, with what representatives of claimants his Ministers or officials met when developing policy on the small claims limit.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20335","20335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438582","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to Answer of 9 December 2015 to Question 18558, how many families in receipt of tax credits in 2013-14 who benefited from the income rise disregard saw their income rise by over £2,500 but no more than £5,000 during the course of the year.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20258","20258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438583","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Northern Ireland currently in employment will not be paying Income Tax from April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20336","20336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438584","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which local authorities have returned childcare grant funding to the Exchequer in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20247","20247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438585","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the amount of direct private sector receipts from the EU was in 2014; and what the expected amount of direct private sector receipts from the EU is for 2015.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20284","20284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438586","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the number of businesses was that traded goods internationally through export or import in 2014.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20285","20285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438587","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a full list of each enterprise zone and the original date of its announcement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20248","20248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438588","2016-01-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the number of UK businesses is that (a) import services from, (b) export services to or (c) engage in services trade with (i) other EU countries and (ii) non-EU countries.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20286","20286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438589","2015-12-17","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Financial Conduct Authority will conclude its investigation into issues relating to the Connaught fund and allow those affected to submit claims to the Financial Services Compensation Scheme.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20232","20232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438590","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many full-time equivalent members of staff were employed by HM Revenue and Customs in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20241","20241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438591","2016-01-05","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on making the discounts to the Mersey Gateway Bridge toll available to residents of the Wirral.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20223","20223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438592","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria the Government is using to determine which people and residents of which areas will be eligible for discounts on tolls for the Mersey Gateway bridge.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20224","20224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438593","2015-12-17","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the number of communities of 5,000 people or more in England where there is no bank branch within a radius of three miles.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20209","20209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438594","2015-12-17","HM Treasury","2015-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the apprenticeship levy is expected to raise in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20178","20178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438595","2015-12-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to provide relief funding to allow local authorities to reduce business rates for businesses affected by flooding.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20182","20182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438596","2015-12-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on whether planning consent has been granted for a new traveller site situated in a conservation area within England since 2010.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20196","20196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438597","2015-12-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will ensure that affordable rent to buy housing is exempt from the Government's pay to stay proposals for higher income social tenants.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20181","20181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438598","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what UK projects received funding under the European Regional Development Fund 2007-2013; what the location of each such project was; and what the amount received in funding was for each such project.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20288","20288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438599","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how his Department plans to enable the sharing of best practice from current and completed devolution deals.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20262","20262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438600","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how his Department plans to monitor whether income from the proposed two per cent rise in council tax intended to contribute to the social care levy is being spent on social care.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20263","20263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438601","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of (a) the level of funding required to cover local authority spending on social care in the period to 2020 and (b) how much the proposed two per cent increase in council tax intended for the social care levy will have raised in funding by 2020 if every authority implements that proposal to the full.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20291","20291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438602","2016-01-05","Department for Transport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the level of local authority preparedness and funding for winter road maintenance.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20292","20292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438603","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Housing and Planning of 14 December 2015, Official Report, column 1278, if he will call in for his determination the application by Dorset County Council to grant itself planning permission for a new school on land in the green belt adjoining Marsh Lane, Christchurch, on grounds of its departing from the recently approved Local Development Plan.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20257","20257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438604","2015-12-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what special support his Department is providing to rough sleepers over the Christmas period.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20273","20273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438605","2015-12-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what special measures he has taken to provide assistance to rough sleepers in areas affected by floods in Lancashire and Cumbria.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20274","20274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438606","2016-01-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken in response to the recommendations and key findings of the National Audit Office's report, Financial sustainability by local authorities 2014, published in November 2014; and what work his Department has carried out on improving its understanding of the financial stability of local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20323","20323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438607","2015-12-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to increase the representation of Muslims on elected bodies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20118","20118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438608","2015-12-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy that affordable rent to buy housing is included as an option for developers in the Housing and Planning Bill's general duty on all planning authorities in order to promote the supply of starter homes.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20175","20175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438609","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 12142, if his Department will publish any expert advice it has received to inform its policy on the safety of safe-standing facilities at higher tier sports stadia.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20201","20201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438610","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many homes in Northern Ireland do not have broadband coverage.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20213","20213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438611","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how public investment infrastructure in superfast broadband is calculated by his Department.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20216","20216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438612","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the contribution of the horseracing industry to the economy in Scotland.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20222","20222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438613","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 12762, on broadband, whether the sum to be paid to local authorities and devolved administrations from the funding returned by BT will be linked to the take-up of broadband within that authority or administration's area.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20218","20218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438614","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 12762, on broadband, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of repaying a proportion of the returned funds to the BBC which made an initial contribution to the project.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20219","20219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438615","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 12762, on broadband, how the £129 million to be repaid to local authorities and the devolved administrations will be divided between those bodies; and how the allocation of that funding will be calculated.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20220","20220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438616","2016-01-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the timetable for and potential effects of the introduction of a Horserace Betting Right.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20221","20221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438617","2015-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 2 July 2014, Official Report, column 676W on AWE, what his most recent estimate is of the (a) anticipated out-turn cost and (b) projected in-service date of each of the new build projects in the Atomic Weapons Establishment Site Development Context Plan.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20228","20228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438618","2015-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department has not conducted economic impact assessments on proposed by-law changes (a) in general and (b) regarding the Raasay ranges.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20225","20225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438619","2015-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding has been received by organisations in Northern Ireland from the Community Covenant Grant Scheme.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20307","20307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438620","2016-01-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 19454, how many mental health specialists were employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20200","20200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438621","2015-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many dangerous occurrences were reported by his Department to the Health and Safety Executive in each of the last five years; and how many of those incidents involved the unplanned or faulty discharge of a weapon.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20157","20157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438622","2015-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many health and safety near misses were reported by his Department in each of the last five years; and how many of those near misses involved the unplanned or faulty discharge of a weapon.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20158","20158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438623","2015-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which weapons were identified in health and safety dangerous occurrences reported by his Department involving an unplanned or faulty discharge in each of the last five years; and how many such incidents there were for each of those weapons in each of those years.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20159","20159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438624","2015-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which weapons were identified in health and safety near misses reported by his Department involving an unplanned or faulty discharge in each of the last five years; and how many such near misses there were for each of those weapons in each of the those years.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20160","20160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438625","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have received young carer assessments under the Children and Families Act 2014 since its implementation; and what proportion of young carers received services from the local authority to meet their needs following such an assessment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20193","20193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438626","2015-12-17","Department for Education","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with internet service providers on preventing sexual abuse, cyber bullying and social media abuse of young people on the internet; and whether that industry adheres to a code of good practice on such matters.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20313","20313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438627","2015-12-17","Department for Education","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has issued to (a) schools and (b) further education colleges on educating young people about cyber bullying and social media abuse.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20314","20314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438628","2015-12-17","Department for Education","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funds her Department makes available to educational establishments to tackle cyber bullying and social media abuse by young people.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20315","20315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438629","2015-12-17","Department for Education","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to tackle (a) cyberbullying, (b) sexting and (c) other forms of peer-to-peer social media abuse by young people.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20316","20316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438630","2015-12-17","Department for Education","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of any shortfall in the number of qualified mathematics teachers in each English region.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20302","20302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438631","2015-12-17","Department for Education","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school academies do not follow the national curriculum.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20305","20305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438632","2016-01-05","Department for Education","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the need for special education facilities to educate young people coming to the UK as a result of the conflict in Syria; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20294","20294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438633","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her policy is on the development of Compressed Air Energy Storage as a means of cost effectively delivering large-scale electricity storage.","Biography information for John McNally","John Mc Nally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20296","20296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438634","2016-01-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the total (a) number and (b) payments made from feed-in tariff schemes in each year since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20246","20246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438635","2015-12-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she has reviewed the fitness-for-purpose of the UK Nuclear Industry Malicious Capability Planning Assessment to deal with attacks similar to those carried out recently in Paris and San Bernadino.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20270","20270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438636","2015-12-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which form of transport she used to travel to the COP21 climate change conference in Paris; and for what reasons she travelled by that mode of transport.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20271","20271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438637","2015-12-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what resources were committed by the UK at the COP21 climate conference in Paris to help developing countries pay for repairing damage from extreme weather events caused by climate change.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20127","20127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438638","2015-12-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions her Department has had with the Arctic Methane Emergency Group on ways to mitigate methane emissions from disruption of methane hydrates caused by climate change in the Arctic.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20128","20128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438639","2015-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made in making it lawful to reuse graves.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20166","20166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438640","2015-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for its policies of the report from the All-Party Parliamentary Group for Animal Welfare, The Urgent Need for an Effective, Enforceable and Enforced Equine Identification System, published in February 2014; and if she will bring forward proposals for such a system to be in place before the end of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20317","20317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438641","2015-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to make the certification process for the Basic Payment Scheme more efficient for farmers; and if she will include further accountability bodies who are able to certify active farmer status to improve efficiency of that scheme.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20276","20276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438642","2015-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with UK Border on the effectiveness of the implementation of the pet travel scheme.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20283","20283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438644","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received on enforcement of the Animal Welfare Act in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20239","20239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438645","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many greyhounds were euthanised at the end of their racing career in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20240","20240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438646","2016-01-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which bodies are responsible for enforcement of the Animal Welfare Act 2006.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20295","20295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438647","2015-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the threat to human health and safety from poor canine welfare at breeding establishments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20210","20210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438648","2015-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will call on his Ethiopian counterpart to allow peaceful protest in the Oromia region and withdraw paramilitary forces.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20229","20229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438649","2015-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will instruct HM Ambassador to Ethiopia to investigate allegations that paramilitary and security forces have killed more than 60 people in the Oromia region of that country following protests about enforced evictions of indigenous people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20230","20230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438650","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statement by Baroness Anelay of St John's of 28 October 2014, HCWA 149, what progress has been made arranging a return visit with the delegation who compiled the Children in Military Custody report.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20242","20242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438651","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statement of 1 December 2014, HC Deb, 46W, what assessment he has made of the performance of the pilot scheme allowing individuals to be summoned rather than arrests being made at night.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20243","20243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438652","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has had recent discussions with the Tunisian government on the safety of UK citizens who plan to travel to that country during 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20290","20290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438653","2015-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will make representations to the Israeli government about the proposed demolition of the Israeli Arab village of Umm-al-hiran.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20319","20319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438654","2015-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any Special Intelligence Service officers have been posted at Bagram airbase in Afghanistan since October 2001.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20268","20268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438655","2016-01-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on bilateral relations of recent decisions by China to construct new islands on coral reefs in disputed waters.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20331","20331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438656","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Local Transformation Plan local areas' plans in improving support for young carers and young adult carers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20189","20189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438657","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to publish statistics on the number of (a) young carers accessing children and adolescence mental health services (CAMHS) and (b) children provided with young carers assessments following contact with CAMHS.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20190","20190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438658","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will reopen his Department's consultation on the proposed NHS mandate.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20187","20187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438659","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the consultation on payment of compensation out of the his Department's contingency fund for those who have suffered from the contaminated bloods issue will report.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20198","20198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438660","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which years are included in his Department's consultation on the annual registration fee that local health trusts pay to the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20191","20191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438661","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of putting health warnings on cigarette packaging in different languages as well as English.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20184","20184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438662","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 19004, what steps he has taken to communicate with people affected by contaminated blood products on the timing of the consultation.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20185","20185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438663","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for NHS diagnosis and treatment services of the findings of research indicating that women who have severe pre-menstrual tension are significantly more likely to develop high blood pressure.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20124","20124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438664","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with clinical bodies on the approach in the NHS to prescribing Ritalin for children with ADHD.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20125","20125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438665","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce and treat irregular heartbeats in infants that can lead to premature death.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20126","20126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438666","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Scottish Government on strategies to prevent premature births.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20119","20119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438667","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the adult population had raised cholesterol in each of the last five years; and what steps his Department is taking to (a) raise awareness of cholesterol and (b) reduce the number of people with high cholesterol.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20120","20120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438668","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to develop a shared strategy across the UK for tackling sexually transmitted diseases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20121","20121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438669","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with organisations representing people with TB on support for people with that disease who are unable to work as a result.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20131","20131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438670","2015-12-17","Department for International Development","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to incentivise the development of new drugs to treat TB.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20132","20132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438671","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people with both TB and HIV receive joined-up care.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20133","20133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438672","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to develop a strategy for tackling and treating TB throughout the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20136","20136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438673","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England will publish the findings of the Mazars review into the deaths of people with mental health problems and learning disabilities at Southern Health NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20267","20267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438674","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of meningococcal disease there have been in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) England since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20320","20320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438675","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with clinical commissioning groups on the implementation of recommendations contained in NHS England's Nutrition and Hydration Commissioning Guidance.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20321","20321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438676","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on implementing the plan for community pharmacists to access Summary Care Records; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20322","20322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438677","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 27 February 2015 to Question 225126, what steps he is taking to ensure growth in investment to increase endoscopy unit capacity in line with the recommendations of Professor Sir Mike Richards, Gateway Reference 16973, of 8 December 2011; and what assessment he has made of progress with planning for 10 to 15 per cent year-on-year increase in lower gastro intestinal endoscopy actively in reducing waiting times and ensuring high quality care.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20340","20340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438678","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department is encouraging the use of medical nutrition as a integral part of healthcare where there is an identified clinical need; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20278","20278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438679","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to make a cheaper, more effective vaccine against pneumococcal meningitis available on the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20277","20277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438680","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve protection from meningococcal disease; and what steps he plans to take to protect people with low immunity from contracting meningococcal disease.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20280","20280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438681","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of womb cancer.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20226","20226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438682","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) St Albans, (b) Hertfordshire, (c) East of England and (d) the UK have Lyme disease; and what steps is he taking to better treat such people.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20227","20227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438683","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents there were of (a) self-harm, (b) attempted self-inflicted death and (c) self-inflicted death by prisoners on remand in each year since 2010; and what proportion of all prisoners on remand such incidents represented in each of those years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20192","20192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438684","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of medication given to patients with 22q11 syndrome; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20206","20206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438685","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what account he has made of the reason for the failure to meet ambulance response time targets for Red 1 999 emergencies between June 2015 and September 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20188","20188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438686","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) investment, (b) infrastructure and (c) measurement of implantation will be put in place to enforce (i) the recent NHS England Commissioning Guidance entitled Commissioning excellent nutrition and hydration and (ii) the existing NICE quality standards on nutrition.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20237","20237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438687","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will encourage clinical commissioning groups to prevent inequalities through adequate HCP outsourcing and training on medical nutrition.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20238","20238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438688","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to mandate that nutrition is written into all national care pathways for long-term conditions.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20299","20299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438689","2015-12-17","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in what ways his Department recognises and supports innovation on medical nutrition.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20300","20300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438690","2016-01-05","Department of Health","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from NHS trusts in England and Wales on the adequacy of midwife recruitment in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20245","20245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438691","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many removals from the UK under the Dublin Regulation there were in each year since 2005; and what information the Government holds on the number of such removals from other EU countries in each of those years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20287","20287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438692","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many training courses on cyber-crime are provided for police officers.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20293","20293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438693","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children seeking asylum have been referred by her Department to the Refugee Council Children's Section for advice in the last two years.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20212","20212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438694","2015-12-17","Home Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average response time was for a 101 call in each year since that service's launch; and what the average response time was for 101 calls made to the Humberside Police from (a) North Lincolnshire and (b) East Yorkshire in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20281","20281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438695","2015-12-17","Home Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average response time was for a 999 call in each of the last 10 years; and what the average response time was for 999 calls made to the Humberside Police from (a) across the force area, (b) North Lincolnshire and (c) East Yorkshire in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20282","20282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438696","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children have been age assessed while in detention in each of the last 12 months; and how such assessments were carried out by immigration officers.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20255","20255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438697","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of age assessments for unaccompanied asylum-seeking children have been completed within the new timetable for upon local authorities in each month since March 2015.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20253","20253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438698","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many National Crime Agency officers have completed the digital awareness e-learning course, The internet and you.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20251","20251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438699","2016-01-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions for domestic violence have been recorded in (a) Wrexham, (b) North Wales and (c) Wales in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 20252","20252"
