"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620895","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse has been of the National Teaching Service pilot in the North West; and how much funding has been allocated to that pilot.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50086","50086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620896","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 10 of her Department's consultation, Schools that work for everyone, whether the suggestion that the 50 per cent cap on faith-based schools admissions does not achieve inclusivity defines inclusivity by (a) income background and (b) ethnic background.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50098","50098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620897","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools are in temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50206","50206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620898","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the non-availability of History of Art AS and A Levels on disadvantaged young people with an interest in art who wish to pursue that course of study at university.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50115","50115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620899","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students in (a) London and (b) England and Wales studied History of Art at AS and A levels at state schools in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013, (v) 2014, (vi) 2015 and (vii) 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50118","50118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620900","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of exempting local authorities from statutory duties to children in social care on the wellbeing of children under the supervision of social workers and children living in care homes or foster homes.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50119","50119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620901","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with local authorities on the provision in the Children and Social Work Bill [Lords] to give Ministers the power to exempt local authorities from statutory duties to children under the supervision of social workers and children living in care homes or foster homes.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50120","50120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620902","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of outsourcing children's social care services and the running of care homes to private companies on the wellbeing of children under the supervision of social workers and children living in care homes or foster homes.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50121","50121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620903","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with private companies on (a) the outsourcing of children's social care services and the running of care homes and (b) other different ways of working in social care.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50122","50122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620904","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment she has made of how far pupils travel to attend (a) existing grammar schools and (b) non-selective secondary schools (i) on average and (ii) for those 10 per cent of pupils travelling the furthest to attend grammar schools.","Biography information for Chris Philp","Chris Philp","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50186","50186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620905","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many planning areas in England are in need of additional secondary school places by September 2017; how many such areas have (a) never had an application to open a secondary or all-through mainstream free school and (b) no open secondary or all-through mainstream free schools.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50184","50184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620906","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many planning areas in England are in need of additional primary school places by September 2017; how many such areas have (a) never had an application to open a primary or all-through mainstream free school and (b) no open primary or all-through mainstream free schools.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50183","50183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620907","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that all staff in schools, including teachers, teaching assistants, and kitchen assistants, have basic training in young people's mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50215","50215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620908","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49488, what estimate she has made of the number of full-time departmental employees who will work in plant health services after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50182","50182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620909","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many grievance complaints by staff of the Environment Agency against team leaders and managers in the Environment Agency have been received since January 2012.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50135","50135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620910","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many grievances against Environment Agency team leaders and managers have been upheld since January 2012.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50157","50157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620911","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the funds available to the Environment Agency to carry out routine riverbank maintenance work.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50259","50259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620912","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department makes of the appropriateness of the relative priority given to major flood defences and routine riverbank maintenance measures by the Environment Agency.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50257","50257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620913","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding is allocated internally by the Environment Agency to the (a) capital funding stream and (b) revenue funding stream for flood protection measures.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50258","50258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620914","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what provisions are in place in the Environment Agency to protect employees working in the field of criminal investigation from the baseless use of disciplinary proceedings by managers.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50136","50136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620915","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations she has received on closing the UK domestic ivory trade.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50095","50095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620916","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps her Department has taken to address the increase in food waste.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50108","50108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620917","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to promote the export of cheese.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50055","50055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620918","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps she has taken to promote the planting of trees.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50056","50056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620919","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what advice his Department provides to people going on holiday abroad on travel insurance.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50053","50053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620920","2016-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with UN member counterparts on the potential introduction of a no-fly zone over Syria.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50107","50107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620921","2016-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Venezuela.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50132","50132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620922","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what opportunities the Government will provide to Parliament to scrutinise the implementation of article 11 of the 1967 Exchange of Notes number 8737 between the UK and the US on the British Indian Ocean territory.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50169","50169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620923","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the provisions of part two of the Constitutional Reform and Governance Act 2010 will apply to the extension of the agreement between the US and the UK outlined in article 11 of the 1967 Exchange of Notes number 8737 on the availability for defence purposes of the British Indian Ocean Territory.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50170","50170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620924","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has raised with his Israeli counterpart access to essential medical treatment for people living in Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50165","50165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620925","2016-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department has undertaken a recent assessment of the welfare and treatment of Mr Andargachew Tsege; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50279","50279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620926","2016-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has been advised by the Ethiopian authorities that Mr Andargachew Tsege has been visited or contacted by family members.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50280","50280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620927","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on whether the 1967 exchange of notes between the UK and US concerning the British Indian Ocean territory is, or has the effect of, a treaty between the US and UK.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50198","50198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620928","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2016 to Question 49267, (a) when and (b) with which providers the 65 specialist mental health beds were commissioned; where those beds are situated in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50211","50211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620929","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 2.2 of the Government response to the Review on Antimicrobial resistance, published in September 2016, what plans he has to tackle the failure of market incentives to deliver public health need with regard to (a) cancer, (b) hepatitis C and (c) other conditions on account of high prices; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50227","50227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620930","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on NHS waiting lists for kidney transplants.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50234","50234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620931","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of arthritis and other musculoskeletal conditions to the NHS in each of the next 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50285","50285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620932","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State of 25 October 2016, Official Report, column 129, on undertaking to make inquiries of the Care Quality Commission (CQC) on the regulation of patient transport services commissioned by the High Weald Havens Clinical Commissioning Group, what the (a) names and (b) dates of operation of the providers about which he will undertake inquiries of the CQC are; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50155","50155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620933","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 48818, if he will ascertain the value of invoices sent to the High Weald Havens Clinical Commissioning Group from each trust which has incurred private ambulances costs arising from performance problems with Patient Transport Services provided by Coperforma and arms length driver operatives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50156","50156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620934","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 18 October 2016 to Questions 49268 and 49269, when the review of provision of specialised beds began; with whom NHS England is consulting on that review; when that review is expected to be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50212","50212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620935","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 18 October 2016 to Questions 49268 and 49269, for what reasons the introduction of a moratorium on the commissioning of new specialised mental health services was introduced in 2013; whether that moratorium is still in place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50213","50213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620936","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent general practice clinical staff there were in (a) Houghton and Sunderland South constituency, (b) the north east of England and (c) England in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50288","50288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620937","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many general practice (a) full and (b) part-time clinical staff (i) left and (ii) began employment in Houghton and Sunderland South constituency in (A) 2013-14, (B) 2014-15 and (C) 2015-16.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50289","50289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620938","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many student midwives (a) began and (b) successfully completed their training in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50172","50172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620939","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of student midwives who started their training (a) completed their studies and (b) went on to work as midwives in the NHS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50171","50171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620940","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for mental health nursing were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50236","50236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620941","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department intends to ensure that (a) no community in England will be left without a pharmacy and (b) that access to pharmacies will improve following funding changes to pharmacies.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50166","50166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620942","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cataract operations were performed in NHS hospitals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50237","50237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620943","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the optimum length of contracts for the provision of GP services by clinical commissioning groups in terms of (a) raising health levels at a primary care level, (b) ensuring value for money for the taxpayer and (c) determining that investment in primary care services is ensured; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50267","50267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620944","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of nutrition labelling in reducing obesity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50283","50283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620945","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) email, (b) meetings, (c) letters and (d) other contact he has had with the organisation Action on Smoking and Health on the Refresh Smoking Strategy in the last six months.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50265","50265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620946","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will undertake an independent review of the cumulative effect of tobacco control measures introduced by his Department in the last decade before moving forward with a refresh smoking strategy.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50266","50266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620947","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make representations to Gilead to ensure the lowest possible price for Truvada is offered to NHS England in the next Clinical Priorities Advisory Group prioritisation round.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50263","50263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620948","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will suffer from arthritis and other musculoskeletal conditions in each of the next 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50284","50284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620949","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS Private Finance Initiative schemes have been signed since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50235","50235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620950","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for diagnostic radiographers were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50238","50238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620951","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for learning disability nursing were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50240","50240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620952","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for midwifery were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50241","50241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620953","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for general practice were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50242","50242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620954","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average cost to the NHS of employing one (a) nurse, (b) midwife, (c) doctor and (d) GP.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50243","50243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620955","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made for the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of the Care Quality Commission report, The state of health care and adult social care in England in 2015/16; and what steps he is taking to ensure that this sector has sufficient funding.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50168","50168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620956","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make additional funds available to NHS England to ensure as many specialised treatments as possible are offered in the next Clinical Priorities Advisory Group prioritisation round.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50244","50244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620957","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for therapeutic radiographers were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50239","50239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620958","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will implement a process through which clinical commissioning groups are held to account on decisions relating to the restrictive prescribing of medical nutrition and its effect on health outcomes in (a) the first six months of recovery, (b) over the next three years and (c) over the course of long-term conditions.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50246","50246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620959","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the five-a-day scheme to alter eating habits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50255","50255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620960","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of Type (a) 1 and (b) 2 diabetes among the population of Hartlepool constituency; and what steps he is taking to (i) manage and (ii) reduce such conditions.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50256","50256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620961","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that effective treatments in bands three, four and five of the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group prioritisation list are not defunded as a result of additional financial pressures added since the last prioritisation round.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50247","50247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620962","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to ensure that clinical commissioning groups safeguard access to medical nutrition for all patients in their area for whom it is recommended as part of NICE guidelines.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50245","50245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620963","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for district nursing were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50249","50249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620964","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Private Finance Initiative contracts have been signed by his Department since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50262","50262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620965","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to introduce further provisions to ensure that people using the NHS from outside (a) the UK and (b) the EU pay for their treatment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50114","50114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620966","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September to Question 46210, who will represent his Department at the World Health Organisation Framework Convention on Tobacco Control in India in November 2016.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50133","50133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620967","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS (a) standalone midwife-led units, (b) midwife-led units situated alongside consultant-led maternity units and (c) consultant-led maternity units there are in each region of England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50207","50207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620968","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September to Question 46141, what his Department's priorities are for the 7th Conference of the Parties to the World Health Organisation Framework Convention on Tobacco Control to be held in November 2016.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50134","50134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620969","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to refresh its guidance on the link between (a) stress, (b) diet, (c) lack of exercise and (d) other elements of an unhealthy lifestyle with cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50113","50113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620970","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the average travel distance to GP services for patients in (a) England, (b) the North East, (c) Redcar and Cleveland, (d) Middlesbrough and (e) Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland constituency.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50090","50090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620971","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS-supplied (a) crutches, (b) wheelchairs and (c) other such mobility aids that have been broken are repaired rather than disposed of.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50057","50057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620972","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to ensure that vacant posts in breast radiology are filled over the next five years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Sir Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50058","50058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620973","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 18698, on midwives: training, whether any revisions have been made to the figures for midwife training between 2010-11 and 2014-15; and what the equivalent figure for such training is for 2015-16.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50052","50052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620974","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on research on rare and childhood cancers.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50081","50081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620975","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the compatibility of deporting children provided with sanctuary in the UK when those children reach adulthood with the Dublin regulations and with the European Convention on Human Rights.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50045","50045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620976","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to which countries her Department has not been able to return people through the assisted voluntary return programme in 2016 because their country of origin automatically removes citizenship from people who have had prolonged residence in another country.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50072","50072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620977","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have applied for leave to remain in the UK as a stateless person since 2013; and how many such applications have been successful.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50073","50073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620978","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received on the number of student visas issued to international students studying on UK higher education courses who lack proficiency in English.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50079","50079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620979","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many deportation decisions were made against non-EEA nationals from July 2012 to July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50069","50069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620980","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to which countries her Department has not been able to return people through the assisted voluntary return programme in 2016 due to their country of origin not facilitating or issuing the necessary documentation for that return.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50076","50076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620981","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to which countries her Department has not been able to return people through the assisted voluntary return programme in 2016 due to there being no viable route of return available.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50071","50071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620982","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who have applied for leave to remain as a stateless person in the UK have claimed asylum in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50074","50074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620983","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many appeals were lodged from July 2012 to July 2014 on Article 8 grounds against deportation decisions for non-EEA nationals.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50068","50068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620984","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many section 94B decisions were made against non-EEA nationals from July 2014 to July 2016.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50065","50065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620985","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on her Department's policies of Dame Louise Casey's review into opportunity and integration in some of the UK's most isolated communities; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50061","50061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620986","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with her French counterpart on tackling acts of violence at the refugee camp in Calais.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50054","50054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620987","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) male and (b) female child refugees and asylum seekers of each age have arrived in the UK since 1 September 2016.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50106","50106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620988","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to submit any new police funding formula for England and Wales to a public consultation.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50145","50145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620989","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of attacks reported against Jewish people in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50110","50110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620990","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have successfully applied for leave to remain in the UK as a stateless person in each of the last five years because their country of origin will not readmit them on the grounds of that country (a) refusing to issue the necessary documentation and (b) taking away their citizenship after prolonged residence in another country.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50075","50075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620991","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consideration her Department gives to (a) tourism and (b) mental health statistics in assessing funding for policing.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50148","50148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620992","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress has been made towards a review of the Police Core Grant Distribution Formula for England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50149","50149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620993","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures of rural deprivation are used by her Department when calculating police funding formulas.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50147","50147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620994","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the value of using alternative measures of the policing needs of the night-time economy rather than the volume and density of bars.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50146","50146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620995","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals for her Department to take responsibility for the care and accommodation of trafficked children.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50178","50178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620996","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will set out what steps she is taking to monitor whether victims of sexual violence are being detained at Yarlswood Detention Centre.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50187","50187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620997","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women resident in Yarlswood Detention Centre in the last 12 months have disclosed prior history of sexual violence; and  how many such women remain in detention.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50188","50188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620998","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether officials of her Department accept reports from dental consultants as evidence of age in cases where there is a dispute over the age of asylum seekers.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50229","50229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620999","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applicants have been issued with the IS.97M form in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50230","50230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621000","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of training for the police on how to support people in custody who are experiencing mental health problems.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50214","50214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621001","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have submitted reports from dental consultants to support age claims in each  of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50232","50232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621002","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many child asylum applicants have been refused accommodation by a local authority in each  of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50233","50233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621003","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applicants have been given an estimated date of birth by her Department which differs from the date claimed by those applicants in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50231","50231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621004","2016-10-27","House of Commons Commission","2016-10-25","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, whether the Commission plans to review the travel subsidy available for schools visiting the House.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50059","50059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621005","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance for medical care the Government provides for people living in Palestine.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50208","50208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621006","2016-10-27","Department for International Trade","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK Steel industry of granting China market economy status.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50158","50158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621007","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the outcome of the EU referendum and the consequent renegotiation of international trade deals, whether her Department plans to continue to support other countries' use of TRIPS flexibilities to ensure access to affordable quality medicine; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50228","50228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621008","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much direct financial assistance the Government plans to give to the Palestinian Authority in financial years (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50221","50221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621009","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which programmes administered by her Department provide financial assistance to the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50220","50220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621010","2016-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that her Department includes an extension to Northern Ireland of a pardon for gay and bisexual men convicted under now abolished offences and seeks a Legislative Consent Motion on this matter from the Northern Ireland Assembly.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50268","50268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621011","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the quality of assessments of prisoners diagnosed with psychosis before they are released.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50109","50109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621012","2016-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the extent to which Crown Courts operate at their full capacity.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50050","50050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621013","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many appeals lodged in cases where section 94B decisions were made for non-EEA nationals were allowed by the Tribunal from July 2014 to July 2016.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50064","50064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621014","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many appeals in cases where section 94B decisions were made for non-EEA nationals were lodged from outside the UK from July 2014 to July 2016.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50066","50066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621015","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many appeals lodged between July 2014 and July 2016 on Article 8 grounds against deportation decisions for non-EEA nationals were allowed by the Tribunal under Article 8 of the European Convention on Human Rights.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50067","50067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621016","2016-10-28","Prime Minister","2016-10-25","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will introduce legislative proposals to allow the Leader of the House to be elected by the House; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50180","50180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621017","2016-10-27","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much of the 500 million designated to shared education and housing from the Fresh Start deal has been spent to date.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50261","50261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621018","2016-10-27","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the current level of personnel in the PSNI; and what response he has made to the recent representations by the Police Federation for staffing levels to be increased.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50141","50141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621019","2016-10-28","Prime Minister","2016-10-25","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2016 to Question 48659, if she will make it her policy to include minutes of meetings with external agencies and members of the press as part of the transparency data which is released on a quarterly basis.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50210","50210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621020","2016-10-28","Prime Minister","2016-10-25","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will update the publication of the quarterly statistics of meetings held by the Prime Minister to cover the period since March 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50199","50199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621021","2016-10-28","Scotland Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many members of the public have contacted his Department on the implementation of the Pensions Act 1995, the Pension Act 2011 and the campaign to equalise state pensions for women in 2016; and what proportion of those people have received a response from his Department.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50222","50222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621022","2016-10-28","Scotland Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his Department has set a target time in which to respond to correspondence from members of the public; and what the average response time for such responses is.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50219","50219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621023","2016-10-27","Scotland Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether a recent assessment has been undertaken of the extent of the sale of counterfeit electrical goods in Scotland which includes the (a) cost to the economy of such sales, (b) amounts of such goods being imported and (c) extent of the sale of such goods.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50277","50277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621024","2016-10-27","Scotland Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the effectiveness of the Plugs and Sockets etc. (Safety) Regulations 1994 in preventing counterfeit electrical goods being sold and imported by online retailers in Scotland.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50281","50281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621025","2016-10-27","Scotland Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on provisions in the Digital Economy Bill to protect Scottish consumers from counterfeit electrical goods being sold online.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50143","50143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621026","2016-10-27","Scotland Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on government campaigns to raise awareness on the dangers of Scottish consumers buying counterfeit electrical goods.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50144","50144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621027","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the recommendations made to the Government by the Competition and Markets Authority regarding the Bus Services Bill, published on 29 June 2016, what assessment he has made of the powers of the Competition and Markets Authority to block bus franchising schemes.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50099","50099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621028","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to provide funding for the expansion of the Manchester Metrolink after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50089","50089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621029","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will put in place a legal ban on the construction of a fourth runway at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50204","50204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621030","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which body will finance changes to the M25 resulting from the decision to expand Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50201","50201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621031","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the proposed six and a half hour ban on night flights to and from Heathrow Airport will be given legal force.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50202","50202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621032","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much financial support the Government will contribute towards the cost of surface access to Heathrow Airport in the event that a new third runway goes ahead.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50203","50203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621033","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October to Question 46630, if his Department will amend train franchising contracts to regulate train operating companies charging taxi drivers to pick up passengers at train stations.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50128","50128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621034","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State, House of Lords Official Report, 12 October 2016, column 1897, what the format is of the review the Government is undertaking of the bus service operators' grant system; and when the priorities and objectives for that funding will be set out.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50129","50129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621035","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49572, how often the Joint Air Quality Unit working group has (a) met to date and (b) will meet routinely.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50278","50278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621036","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage changes from diesel to electric vehicles.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50270","50270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621037","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether officials in his Department plan to meet their counterparts in Northern Ireland to discuss steps to tackle drink driving.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50294","50294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621038","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what mechanisms the Government will use to guarantee that an expanded Heathrow Airport reserves a set percentage of its slots for flights to other UK airports.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50200","50200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621039","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2016 to Question 47481, when he plans to make an announcement on the provision of additional rolling stock to Southeastern.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50159","50159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621040","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to monitor the effect of changes to the drink-driving limit in Northern Ireland due to come into force in 2017.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50226","50226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621041","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a levy on second and subsequent journeys taken by air passengers in a single year.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50286","50286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621042","2016-10-28","Women and Equalities","2016-10-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) gender equality, (b) the rights of disabled people and (b) the rights of lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50177","50177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621044","2016-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Ministers and (b) officials of the Department for Work and Pensions on plans to exempt women who have a third or subsequent child as a result of rape from the Government's plan to limit tax credits to two children per family.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50087","50087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621045","2016-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of disabled people who will lose access to specialist help to find work as a result of changes in the level of funding for the Government's work programme.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50116","50116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621046","2016-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department plans to take to provide support for disabled people who will lose access to specialist help to find work as a result of changes in the level of funding for the Government's work programme.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50117","50117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621047","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is by the Benefit Director in his Department to reply to hon. Members' correspondence.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50104","50104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621048","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what procedure is in place for the Benefits Director in his Department to send written replies to letters from hon. Members writing on behalf of constituents.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50105","50105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621049","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 48471, if he will make it his policy to collect shift pattern data for (a) mining and (b) other potentially dangerous industries.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50173","50173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621050","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with the scheme administrator of the levy-funded Energy Company Obligation on monitoring requirements for households to make capital contributions towards the cost of any energy efficiency work from April (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50250","50250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621051","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the total value of client contributions that could be sought by obligated suppliers under the levy-funded Energy Company Obligation from April 2017 to April 2018.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50251","50251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621052","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential importance of a North/South Interconnector on the island of Ireland to the UK electricity supply.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50260","50260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621053","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Committee on Fuel Poverty on providing additional funds for energy efficiency from National Infrastructure funds to meet (a) the 2030 fuel energy efficiency target and (b) the interim milestones in England; and if he will publish details of such discussions.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50252","50252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621054","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the Committee on Fuel Poverty on meeting (a) the 2030 fuel energy efficiency target and (b) the interim milestones in England; and if he will publish details of such discussions.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50253","50253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621055","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who the UK delegation to the 2017 UN climate negotiations in Marrakech, Morocco will be.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50254","50254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621056","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2016 to Question 47961, how much of the 981,514 in arrears identified by HM Revenue and Customs between 1 April 2014 and 31 March 2016 was subsequently paid to the social care workers affected.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50160","50160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621057","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she plans to take to ensure progress on international climate change agreements relating to loss and damage at the upcoming COP22 UN Climate Change Summit.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50192","50192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621058","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 9 September 2016 on Companies House, reference ZA5077.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50209","50209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621059","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she plans to take to build resilience to climate change in developing countries through weather-indexed insurance at the Marrakech climate conference in November.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50191","50191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621060","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to increase binding commitments to protect the world's poorest from climate-related natural disasters and extreme weather at the Marrakech Climate Conference in November.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50195","50195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621061","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what financial commitments to support global climate mitigation and adaption the Government plans to make as part of the 2017 UN climate negotiations.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50287","50287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621062","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will increase climate risk insurance programmes to address loss and damage associated with the adverse effects of climate change on developing countries.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50190","50190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621063","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to include tidal power lagoons in the forthcoming industrial strategy.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50096","50096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621064","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students in Cambridge have completed courses funded by advanced learner loans in the last five years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50124","50124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621065","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage (a) further education institutions to apply for an advanced learner loans facility agreement with the Skills Funding Agency and (b) further education institutions to accept students funded by advanced learner loans.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50125","50125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621066","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of further education institutions in England offer courses funded by advanced learner loans.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50126","50126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621067","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many further education institutions in Cambridge are in receipt of an advanced learner loans facility agreement with the Skills Funding Agency.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50127","50127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621068","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 44431, which businesses related to the space sector his Department has had discussions with since the vote to leave the EU; what the outcome of those discussions has been; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50130","50130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621069","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential effect on the communication sector of the use of advertising as a proxy for payment.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50078","50078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621070","2016-10-27","Department for International Trade","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on the UK economy in the event that the EU-Canada free trade agreement is not concluded.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50049","50049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621071","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the provision of state aid in the event of the UK reverting to World Trade Organisation terms after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50097","50097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621072","2016-10-28","Department for International Trade","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that experts in trade from all countries of the UK are engaged in work on new trade agreements so that they reflect the interests of the country as a whole.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50218","50218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621073","2016-10-28","Department for International Trade","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase demand for British services and manufactured goods in non-EU unsaturated markets abroad.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50217","50217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621074","2016-10-28","Department for International Trade","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many civil servants working in his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50225","50225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621075","2016-10-28","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 49427, whether EU students will be eligible for student loans and grants in academic years after 2017-18; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50174","50174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621076","2016-10-27","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department plans to employ staff (a) directly or (b) on secondment with experience in defence policy to inform its negotiations on the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50274","50274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621077","2016-10-28","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 49489, if he will make it his policy to collect information on the number of civil servants working in his Department who have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50175","50175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621078","2016-10-27","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the Department of Health on the UK's relationship with the European Medicines Agency since the vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50123","50123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621079","2016-10-28","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government plans to share with Parliament the analysis presented to Ministers on the options for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50082","50082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621080","2016-10-28","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government plans to publish a White Paper or a Green Paper including proposals for the negotiations for the leaving the EU before Article 50 is triggered.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50083","50083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621081","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what safeguards her Department has put in place to ensure that academic staff from other EU countries working on multi-year research projects and based in the UK and funded from EU sources will retain the ability to remain in the UK after the UK leaves the EU while those projects remain ongoing; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50051","50051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622093","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the risk of Stuxnet cyber-attacks on the UK's civil nuclear power programme.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906893","906893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625101","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has plans to establish a public inquiry into events at Orgreave on 18 June 1984.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906899","906899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625102","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures she has put in place to ensure that providers inform local authorities in advance of their plans to place asylum seekers in accommodation within those local authority areas.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906895","906895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625103","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will issue updated country guidance for Eritrea as a result of the recent decision of the Upper Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum) on asylum seekers from that country.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906898","906898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625104","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of changes in the level of funding on the resilience of the fire and rescue service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906891","906891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625105","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children who are entitled to be resettled in the UK under the Dublin III arrangements have had their applications for take charge requests denied or rejected by the Home Office in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906892","906892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619048","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the net contribution made by international students to the UK economy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49818","49818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619049","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that funding is provided for the replacement and upgrade of fishing vessels.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49823","49823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619050","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress she has made on resolving Basic Payment Scheme claims which include common land.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49824","49824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619051","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff working for the Barking, Havering and Redbridge NHS Trust are (a) non-UK EU citizens and (b) citizens of countries outside the EU.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49820","49820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619052","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the new Carers Strategy.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49821","49821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619053","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how he plans to fund the new Carers Strategy.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49822","49822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619054","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of student visas that have been obtained fraudulently in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49819","49819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619055","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is her Department's policy not to employ people who have recently resided at an address covered by the British Forces Post Office.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49817","49817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619056","2016-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is her Department's policy not to employ people who have recently resided at an address covered by the British Forces Post Office.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49816","49816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619057","2016-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to attend interviews with claimants conducted by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49825","49825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619819","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many apprenticeships have been created in each Government department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many of those apprentices subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49829","49829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619820","2016-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many organisations have recertified (a) Cyber Essentials and (b) Cyber Essentials Plus in each year since each scheme's creation.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49949","49949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619822","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what underspend the Office of Cyber Security and Information Assurance has had in each year since its establishment.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49950","49950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619823","2016-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) FTSE 100 and (b) FTSE 350 companies have used the 10 Steps to Cyber Security guidance to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49966","49966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619824","2016-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many start-up businesses have participated in the Early Stage Accelerator programme since it began.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49954","49954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619825","2016-10-26","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Queen's Constitutional prerogative, the legal prerogatives or prerogative executive powers will be used when triggering Article 50 of the Treaty on the Functions of the EU.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49982","49982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619827","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the five most common causes of death among (a) women and (b) men in each age group in Greater Manchester were in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49961","49961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619828","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in each age group in (a) Leigh constituency and (b) Greater Manchester are employed on a zero-hours contract.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49962","49962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619829","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in each age group in (a) Leigh constituency and (b) Greater Manchester are paid less than the living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49963","49963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619830","2016-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many organisations held (a) Cyber Essentials and (b) Cyber Essentials Plus certification in each calendar year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49957","49957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619831","2016-10-26","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether a decision to use the Royal Prerogative to trigger Article 50 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the EU will be subject to judicial review.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50009","50009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619833","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy that executive agencies collect data on funding allocated to people who have protected characteristics as listed in the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50003","50003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619834","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a definitive list of prerogative powers currently exercisable by the Government.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50030","50030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619835","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on extending Small Business Rate Relief to businesses that claim Rural Rate Relief.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49976","49976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619838","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral evidence given by Philip Cassidy to the Work and Pensions Committee on 13 October 2016, Question 30, what criteria HM Revenue and Customs applied in selecting the 1.5 million high-risk working tax credit claimant records provided to Concentrix in April 2016; for what reasons Concentrix decided not to investigate a proportion of those cases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49900","49900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619840","2016-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support current and ex-service personnel to find a home.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49877","49877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619841","2016-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to local authorities of translating documents into different languages and employing interpreters.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49917","49917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619842","2016-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on reviewing the cost of democratic arrangements to ensure that they promote good governance and provide value for money.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49915","49915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619843","2016-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the Landlord Licensing Scheme introduced by the London Borough of Newham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49946","49946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619845","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will issue new guidance to local authorities on the issuing of Hackney carriage or taxi licences to include higher quality background checks and improved standards.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49978","49978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619846","2016-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) veterans sleeping rough and (b) homeless veterans in (i) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (ii) Liverpool, (iii) the Liverpool City Region and (iv) each region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50027","50027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619847","2016-10-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Independent Review of Consumer Protection Measures concerning Online Secondary Ticketing facilities, published in May 2016, what steps the Government is taking to tackle ticket touting.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50037","50037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619848","2016-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of rural broadband cover in Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49956","49956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619849","2016-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 49393, what powers she has to set the limits of the markets which Ofcom regulates.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50017","50017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619851","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian personnel in his Department have been subject to disciplinary action for non-compliance with his Department's policies on use of social media in each month since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49837","49837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619852","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) officers and (b) soldiers from the (i) Army, (ii) Royal Air Force and (iii) Royal Navy have been subject to disciplinary action for non-compliance with his Department's policies on use of social media in each month since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49838","49838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619854","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times his Department (a) terminated a contract and (b) imposed a penalty for grave professional misconduct in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49841","49841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619855","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recruitment targets his Department has set for the Royal Naval Reserve.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49857","49857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619856","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding his Department has allocated for training members of the Royal Naval Reserve in each of the last five years; and what the projected funding for such training is for each of the next five years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49858","49858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619857","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve the level of retention in the Royal Naval Reserve.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49856","49856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619858","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value of current contracts is between his Department and suppliers based in Wales.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49851","49851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619860","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the Royal Naval Reserve to support the Royal Navy in meeting its current operational commitments.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49867","49867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619861","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Saudi Arabia on dealing with the threat posed by Daesh activities in the Middle East.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49868","49868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619862","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has held with (a) the Iraqi government and (b) other governments in that region on blocking the route between Mosul and the Syrian border which Daesh forces could use to escape Mosul.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49918","49918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619863","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department was made of the effect that Turkish troops fighting in Iraq have had on the battle to regain Mosul.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49919","49919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619865","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department considers to be the standard composition of the maritime task group outlined in the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49920","49920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619866","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department holds any foreign currency reserves.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49921","49921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619867","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department takes to notify the appropriate coroner when the body of a deceased military person is repatriated to England or Wales from Scotland for burial or cremation at the wishes of the family.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49922","49922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619868","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the protocol between the Ministry of Justice, the Ministry of Defence, the Scottish Government and the Chief Coroner on dealing with military deaths in Scotland.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49923","49923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619870","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page three of the National Audit Office report, Departmental Overview 2015-16, Ministry of Defence, published on 21 October 2016, from which budget headings the 9.2 billion of planned savings referred to in that report will be made.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49886","49886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619871","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Departmental Overview 2015-16, Ministry of Defence, published on 21 October 2016, page 17, what steps he is taking to address dissatisfaction among service personnel with the standard of service family accommodation.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49897","49897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619872","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 11 of the National Audit Office report, Departmental Overview 2015-16, Ministry of Defence, published on 21 October 2016, if he will provide further details of the 2.1 billion planned savings from improved commercial terms in the Equipment Plan.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49887","49887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619874","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 11 of the National Audit Office report, Departmental Overview 2015-16, Ministry of Defence, published on 21 October 2016, how the reprioritisation of 2 billion of existing funding contributes to his Department's planned savings of 9.2 billion.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49888","49888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619875","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 11 of the National Audit Office report, Departmental Overview 2015-16, Ministry of Defence, published on 21 October 2016, from which budget headings the 2 billion planned savings from military and civilian pay restraint referred to in that report will be made.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49889","49889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619876","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the deployment of an S-300 long-range air defence system to the Tartus area of Syria by the Russian government.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49899","49899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619877","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training assistance his Department has provided to (a) Saudi Arabia, (b) the United Arab Emirates, (c) Qatar, (d) Kuwait and (e) Oman in the last five years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49869","49869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619879","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Mechanised Infantry Vehicles his Department is planning to procure in the next three years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49999","49999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619880","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to reduce the army's total number of Challenger 2 main battle tanks.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50002","50002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619881","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the new Mechanised Infantry Vehicle will reach initial operating capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49998","49998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619882","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what advice he has received on whether armed Reaper drones on missions outside Syria and Iraq are covered by the convention that Parliament has an opportunity to debate the circumstances in which armed forces are committed to military operations.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49992","49992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619883","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of the Mechanised Infantry Vehicle Programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50000","50000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619885","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on European and American defence co-operation of the withdrawal of the UK from the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49993","49993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619886","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2016 to Question 48618, how much UK steel content will be secured through the 85 per cent BAE System supply chain in the UK.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50016","50016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619887","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to replace the 120mm L30A1 rifled tank gun with the Rheinmetall 120mm L55 smoothbore gun as part of the Challenger 2 Life Extension Programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50001","50001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619888","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress his Department has made in the Army Recruiting Partnership Project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49994","49994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619890","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.48 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, Cm 9161, what estimate he has made of how many new Mechanised Infantry Vehicles will be in each of the Army's new strike brigades.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49995","49995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619891","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether armed Reaper drones engaged in operations overseas are part of the armed forces for the purposes of the Armed Forces Act 2006.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49990","49990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619892","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.48 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, Cm 9161, what estimate he has made of how many new Ajax armoured vehicles will be in each of the Army's new strike brigades.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49996","49996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619893","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether pilots who are in control of armed Reaper drones conducting operations overseas are (a) engaged in armed conflict and (b) regulated by the laws of war.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49991","49991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619895","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his Department's policy that people living in property where his Department is responsible for the supply should have the option to have water meters installed.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50014","50014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619896","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of the Challenger 2 Life Extension Programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49997","49997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619897","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Challenger 2 main battle tanks will equip each of the Army's two new armoured infantry brigades.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49979","49979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619898","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Challenger 2 main battle tank regiments will form part of the organic capability of the two new armoured infantry brigades referred to in the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49980","49980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619899","2016-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to procure for the Army the M777 155mm lightweight howitzer.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49981","49981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619901","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to recruit more service personnel to the Army.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50044","50044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619902","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of curriculum content on self-harm; and if she will bring forward legislative proposals to make teaching about self-harm compulsory as part of the national curriculum.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50026","50026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619903","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence her Department holds on the merits of grammar schools for social mobility.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50029","50029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619904","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to make more tailored support available to young people with a disability or long-term health condition who are undertaking work experience.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50004","50004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619906","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Family Drug and Alcohol Court pilots to date.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50020","50020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619907","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what cost benefit analysis her Department has carried out of the Family Drug and Alcohol Court pilots to date.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50021","50021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619908","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what future funding she plans to make available for the Family Drug and Alcohol Court project.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50022","50022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619909","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from members of the judiciary on the effectiveness of the Family Drug and Alcohol Court.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50023","50023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619911","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect on the (a) number and (b) gender of those taking A-level mathematics of the requirement that schools put in place that only those with an A at GCSE can study A-level mathematics; and if she will assess how widespread this practice is.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49973","49973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619912","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2016 to Question 48942, how many financial notices to improve have been issued to academy trusts in each year since 2010; how many such cases resulted in schools being removed from the academy trust; and what average period of time is taken from identification of a problem for a financial notice to improve to be issued.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49975","49975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619913","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the level of performance in West Sussex in the 2016 Key Stage 2 results in (a) reading, (b) mathematics and (c) reading, writing and mathematics; and if she will rank all local authorities in England by performance in those subjects.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49958","49958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619914","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions her Department has removed statistical data from her Department's website in each year since 2010; for how long each piece of data was so removed; and what the purpose was of each such removal.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49951","49951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619916","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence her Department has gathered on the effect of good quality pre-school education on social mobility in the last five years.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49952","49952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619917","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish the agreement between her Department and the Home Office on the sharing of data from the national pupil database.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49953","49953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619918","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of full day care staff had an Early Years Educator Level 3 qualification or above in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49964","49964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619919","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she intends to publish the review announced by her predecessor into the mathematics and English GCSE requirements for the Level 3 Early Years Educator qualification.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49965","49965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619920","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary and (b) secondary schools hold academy status in (i) Suffolk, (ii) East Anglia and (iii) England and Wales.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50011","50011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619922","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to Answer named day Question 48230, tabled on 12 October 2016, by the right hon. Member for East Ham on Questions 43736, 43737 and 43738, tabled on 20 July 2016 by the right hon. Member for East Ham on the Bright Tribe Multi-Academy Trust.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49906","49906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619923","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 49045, what estimate she has made of the financial contribution to be made by international students to the wider UK economy in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49913","49913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619924","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 49043, what estimate she has made of the financial contribution to be made by international students to UK universities in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49914","49914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619925","2016-10-27","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Teach First graduates were placed at schools in each region of England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49947","49947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619927","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much capital funding for (a) basic needs and (b) school maintenance has been provided from the public purse to Calderdale Council in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49866","49866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619928","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the rate of attainment of (a) five good GCSEs and (b) further education qualifications by ex-young offenders; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure that such offenders achieve such qualifications in (i) Lewisham, Deptford constituency and (ii) England.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49874","49874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619929","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support she is providing to standing advisory councils on religious education for developing syllabuses.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49850","49850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619930","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answers of 8 September 2016 to Questions 44446 and 44447, what steps she plans to take to ensure that specific language and communication, including sign language, guidelines are in place to ensure that deaf and hard of hearing pre-school children benefit from the financial investment and the early years workforce strategy referred to in those Answers.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49844","49844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619932","2016-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the average additional annual costs to domestic consumers who are unable to (a) pay utilities bills by direct debit or (b) receive utilities bills electronically in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49861","49861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619935","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much waste was recycled in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49941","49941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619936","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of waste sorted for recycling has ended up in landfill in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49940","49940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619937","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to improve the level of information provided to farmers on how claim payments under the Basic Payment Scheme are broken down.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49907","49907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619939","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will consider providing bridging payments to Rural Payment Agency claimants awaiting payment after 31 March 2017.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49898","49898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619940","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have taken the training course on humane shooting of badgers; and how many such people have failed the course.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49955","49955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619941","2016-10-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress signatories to Courtauld 2025 are making towards reducing food and drink waste by 20 per cent by 2025.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49974","49974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619943","2016-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Iraqi government on the success of an Iraqi application for support from the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50012","50012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619944","2016-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which (a) Israeli and (b) Palestinian non-governmental organisations and projects receive how much funding from his Department.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49939","49939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619945","2016-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of the financial assistance provided to (a) projects through the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund and (b) bilateral programme budgets fund projects which promote coexistence between Israelis and Palestinians.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49938","49938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619947","2016-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the report of the UN Commission of Inquiry on Human Rights in Eritrea, published in June 2016, if he will support an investigation by the Prosecutor of the International Criminal Court into violations of human rights by the government of Eritrea that may amount to crimes against humanity.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49836","49836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619948","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to fund research to improve the care and treatment of people with the limb girdle 2b form of Duchenne muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49847","49847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619950","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of care available to treat people with the limb girdle 2b form of Duchenne muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49848","49848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619951","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of the effectiveness of the Translarna drug in treating the limb girdle 2b form of Duchenne muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49849","49849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619952","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for the health of children with liver disease of continuity of care as they make the transition to adult services.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49864","49864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619953","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of breast radiologist posts were unfilled in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Sir Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49842","49842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619955","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons womb cancer is not included by name in the Be Clear on Cancer campaign run by Public Health England.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49853","49853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619957","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of womb cancer.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49854","49854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619958","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nationals of EU member states other than the UK worked in the NHS in each of the last 36 months for which figures are available (a) in total (b) as doctors, (c) as nurses and (d) as midwives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49839","49839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619959","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nationals of EU member states other than the UK  (a) started working and (b) left employment in the NHS in England in the latest period for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49840","49840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619967","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average response time was to emergency red calls for ambulance services in (a) the East Midlands and (b) England in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49830","49830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619969","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what life expectancy is for (a) men and (b) women in (i) Ashfield constituency, (ii) Rushcliffe constituency, (iii) the East Midlands and (iv) England.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49832","49832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619970","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many operations in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK had to be cancelled due to a lack of hospital beds available in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49942","49942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619971","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Health Education England plans to take to ensure that the strategic review of the cancer workforce addresses the complex needs of the growing number of people living with and beyond cancer.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49933","49933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619972","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the funding per head was for those with mental health issues in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49943","49943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619974","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were recorded with mental health issues in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49944","49944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619975","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received from NHS trusts on safeguards for EU nationals working in the NHS after the UK has left the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49912","49912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619976","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 8 September 2016 on the brain tumour task and finish group, reference ZA5004.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49904","49904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619977","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the supplementary hours worked by pharmacists on provision of pharmaceutical services in each NHS locality.","Biography information for Rebecca Harris","Rebecca Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49909","49909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619979","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to require equality impact assessments to be submitted alongside all sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49905","49905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619981","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of  ambulance waiting times in (a) London and (b) England in each month of 2016.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49984","49984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619982","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) clinical commissioning groups in England and (b) local health boards in Wales are held to account for local prescribing policy decisions which restrict patient access to drugs and borderline substances recommended for reimbursement.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50008","50008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619984","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to implement prescribing guidelines to limit variations in the provision and quality of NHS services between (a) clinical commissioning groups in England and (b) local health boards in Wales.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50007","50007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619985","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce ambulance waiting times in (a) London and (b) England.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49983","49983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619986","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many student nurses in (a) Greater Manchester and (b) England received NHS bursaries in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49959","49959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619987","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of regional disparity in successful funding applications for Exogen Ultrasound Bone Healing System treatment for NHS patients.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49972","49972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619988","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications for funding for treatment by the Exogen Ultrasound Bone Healing System have been approved for NHS patients in (a) South Tees NHS Trust, (b) the North East and (c) England since May 2015.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49970","49970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619989","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that Exogen Ultrasound Bone Healing System treatment is funded by the NHS for repairs and fusions of joints rather than just for larger bones.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49971","49971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619990","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many rough sleepers died in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) the Liverpool City Region and (d) each region in each year since 2010; and what the cause of death was in each area.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50024","50024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619991","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to hospital as a result of the adverse effects of the psychoactive substance spice in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) the Liverpool City Region and (d) each region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50025","50025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619992","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of support available to public sector workers who have witnessed someone die by suicide at work.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50028","50028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619993","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many miscarriages the NHS has registered in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50041","50041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619994","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to make available on the NHS knee injection treatment to replace knee surgery.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50042","50042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619995","2016-10-27","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to make available on the NHS high-tech neuro-protective medication for stroke patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50043","50043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619996","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that NHS services are available to people who read using braille.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50038","50038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619997","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to make the arthritis pacemaker implant available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50039","50039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619998","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the 10 million package announced on 4 September 2016 for resettled Syrian refugees, how many hours of additional English language teaching per refugee that funding will provide.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49968","49968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/619999","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the 10 million funding package for English language tuition for resettled Syrian refugees announced on 4 September 2016, how many ESOL levels those eligible to participate will be expected to attain.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49967","49967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620000","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to provide additional funding for English language tuition for refugees on the Gateway Protection Resettlement Programme.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50005","50005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620001","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to provide additional funding for English language tuition for refugees who gain settlement rights in the UK under the standard procedure for claiming asylum.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50006","50006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620002","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there is a sunset clause on her Department's use of Dungavel Immigration Removal Centre.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49896","49896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620003","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received from NHS trusts on safeguards for EU nationals working in the NHS after the UK has left the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49910","49910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620004","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on the inclusion of international students as part of the net migration figures; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49911","49911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620005","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is the Government's policy to ensure that unaccompanied children arriving in the UK to seek asylum are given dental check-ups.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49880","49880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620006","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is her Department's policy to reserve the right to continue to use Dungavel Immigration Removal Centre in the event that the plan to establish a new detention facility at Glasgow Airport does not go ahead.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49894","49894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620007","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on its plans to close Dungavel Immigration Removal Centre and to establish a new detention facility at Glasgow Airport.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49895","49895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620008","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum seeking children arriving in the UK have been given a dental check-up in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49879","49879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620009","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of non-EU students who have remained in the UK after completing their studies during the last five years.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49881","49881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620010","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the letter from the Secretary of State for Defence to the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North of 6 June 2016, what information her Department holds on the number of fighters who have returned who (a) are subject to Terrorism Prevention and Investigation Measures (TPIMS), (b) were subject to TPIMs prior to their return and (c) have been prosecuted.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49882","49882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620011","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to enable men cautioned for soliciting and importuning under section 32 of the Sexual Offences Act 1956 before 1 May 2004 to have their crimes disregarded.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49883","49883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620012","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to review immigration rules for students.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49924","49924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620013","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to reform the immigration detention estate.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49925","49925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620014","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications of the UK leaving the EU on her departmental responsibilities.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49926","49926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620015","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to new guidance issued by the Upper Tribunal on Eritrea on 10 October 2016, what steps she will take to update her Department's travel guidance on that country.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49835","49835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620016","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of reducing the fees for naturalisation applications from EEA nationals as a result of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49855","49855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620017","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to publish the results of Dame Louise Casey's review into opportunity and integration in some of the UK's most isolated communities.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49843","49843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620018","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) racially and (b) religiously motivated offences were recorded by West Yorkshire Police in June, July and August (i) 2016 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49859","49859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620019","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of Metropolitan Police Service performance against the terms set out in its service level agreement with the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49865","49865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620020","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps her Department has taken to stop rogue solicitors and legal advisers from offering immigration advice.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49875","49875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620021","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is the policy of her Department to require completion of immigration cards by UK citizens arriving at UK airports from EU destinations.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49863","49863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620022","2016-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which projects in Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories receive funding through the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49936","49936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620023","2016-10-26","Department for International Development","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent progress has been made on the Energy Africa access campaign.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49932","49932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620024","2016-10-27","Department for International Development","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which (a) Israeli and (b) Palestinian non-governmental organisations and projects receive how much funding from her Department.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49937","49937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620025","2016-10-26","Department for International Development","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, to which areas UK funds to help with the earthquake in Nepal are being dispersed; and what steps she is taking to ensure the resources are reaching the affected areas.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49934","49934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620026","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders absconded from bail hostels in (a) England and (b) Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49987","49987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620027","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests from the probation service have been made for offenders to be fitted with electronic tags in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49988","49988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620028","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have been fitted with electronic tags following a request from the probation service in each since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49989","49989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620029","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many prosecutions there have been for tobacco smuggling in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50019","50019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620030","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders housed in bail hostels have been taken back into custody as a result of notification from bail hostel staff to police in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50040","50040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620031","2016-10-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the completion rate was for education courses taken in prisons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49948","49948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620032","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have been in breach of curfew conditions at bail hostels in (a) England and (b) Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49931","49931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620033","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals to the First Tier Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum) have been awaiting allocation of a hearing for more than (a) six months and (b) twelve months in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49930","49930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620034","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps her Department has taken to tackle the rise in incidents of violence in male prisons.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49871","49871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620035","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to improve access to mental health services for young offenders.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49872","49872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620036","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the living conditions in young offender institutes.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49873","49873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620037","2016-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to reduce waiting times for the First Tier Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum).","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49852","49852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620038","2016-10-27","Prime Minister","2016-10-24","To ask the Prime Minister, (a) how many and (b) which food banks she has visited since becoming Prime Minister.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49826","49826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620039","2016-10-27","Home Office","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any Government departments, public bodies or other organisations have been allocated funds from the public purse for legal representation in connection with the resumed inquests into the murder of 21 people in the Birmingham pub bombings of November 1974.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49945","49945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620040","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which organisations and individuals have been invited to attend the logistics industry round table to discuss driver shortage and future recruitment on 17 November 2016.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49969","49969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620041","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cyclists were (a) injured and (b) killed in road traffic accidents on public roads in (i) Leigh and (ii) Greater Manchester in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49960","49960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620042","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal of access to flight and winch training on (a) the ability of local fire and rescue services to support maritime safety and (b) maritime safety.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50015","50015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620043","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the runway capacity was for each UK airport in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49986","49986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620044","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passengers travelled by (a) road and (b) train to (i) Manchester and (ii) Liverpool Airport in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49985","49985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620045","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who the members of the HS2 Ltd conflicts of interest panel have been since its inception; and what the (a) remuneration paid to them was and (b) expenses incurred by those members has been.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49833","49833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620046","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) grades and (b) number of compliance staff support the HS2 Ltd conflicts of interest panel; and what that panel's annual budgets and expenditure to date has been.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49834","49834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620047","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date Govia Thameslink Railways' application for force majeure was received; whether there is a date by which his Department (a) must and (b) plans to respond to that application; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49876","49876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620048","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will extend eligibility for the Blue Badge parking scheme to people diagnosed with dementia.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49860","49860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620049","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of whether Government guidance on crossing times at pedestrian crossings remains effective; and what steps he is taking to monitor compliance with that guidance by local authorities.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49862","49862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620050","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the pay and conditions for the incoming chief executive of HS2 Ltd will be.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49893","49893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620051","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date the current managing director of Passenger Services became a directly employed member of staff in his Department.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49901","49901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620052","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the number of (a) closed and (b) pending applications for open access operation on the national rail network that have been referred to his Department since January 2010.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49902","49902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620053","2016-10-27","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the working relationship between his Department's managing director of Passenger Services and (a) Renaissance Trains and (b) First Class Partnerships; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49903","49903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620054","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will ensure that at least half of the Board of HS2 Ltd are business professionals with exclusively private sector experience.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49892","49892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620055","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will undertake an Equality Impact Assessment of Driver Only Operation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49928","49928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620056","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess whether (a) Govia Thameslink Railway and (b) his Department have met their public sector equality duty in relation to the extension of Driver Only Operation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49929","49929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620057","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which stations on the Govia Thameslink Railway Southern routes operate unstaffed some or all of the time; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49927","49927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620058","2016-10-26","Women and Equalities","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 48607, on equality impact assessments, if her Department will publish the Public Sector Equality Duty guidance circulated across Whitehall.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49845","49845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620059","2016-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) which food banks he has visited since taking office.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49827","49827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620060","2016-10-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who are certified as self-employed in Ashfield constituency are in receipt of in-work benefits.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49831","49831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620061","2016-10-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of access to sick pay and state benefits for women who suffer from severe endometriosis.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49870","49870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620062","2016-10-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with which organisations and on which dates his Department has discussed plans to protect survivors of rape and sexual abuse whose third child was born as a result of rape and would wish to claim tax credits in the last year.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50010","50010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620063","2016-10-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what arrangements he has put in place to assess the effectiveness of the provisions in the 2012 Scheme for varying child support payments following changes in the income of the paying parent.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49935","49935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620064","2016-10-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 19 of the Children's Society Report entitled the cost of being care free: the impact of poor financial education and removal of support on care leavers, published in 2016, what plans he has to better protect care leavers.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50036","50036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620065","2016-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it is his Department's policy that compensation for subsidence damage under the Coal Mining Subsidence Act 1991 is in line with the Code of Practice which was based upon the Land Compensation Act 1973.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50031","50031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620066","2016-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to amend the Coal Mining Subsidence Act 1991 to allow the Coal Authority to take into account blight when making compensation payments.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50032","50032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620067","2016-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) minimum and (b) maximum amount payable is under the Home Loss Payments (Prescribed Amounts) (England) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50033","50033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620068","2016-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many properties affected by subsidence have been compulsorily purchased by the Coal Authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50034","50034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620069","2016-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the potential economic benefits of tidal power lagoons will be considered in the development of the Government's new Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50035","50035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620070","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 48717, how many customers were interviewed in the small-scale qualitative evaluation of the Warm Home Discount scheme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50018","50018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620071","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2016 to Question 49308, on the Warm Home Discount Scheme, how a person opts out of that scheme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49884","49884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620072","2016-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with EU Science Commissioner Carlos Moedas on potential discrimination against UK academics who bid for EU funding.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49885","49885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620073","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy that the EU Port Services Regulation is not replaced in UK law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49890","49890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620074","2016-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the renewable subsidies programme on household electricity bills.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49891","49891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620076","2016-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on research funding across all disciplines in universities in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49916","49916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620077","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Walsall North of 20 September 2016 on behalf of a constituent relating to nuisance telephone calls.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49828","49828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620078","2016-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with the senior management team at the Royal Bank of Scotland on that Bank's global restructuring group and that group's treatment of small businesses during the financial crisis.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49846","49846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620079","2016-10-26","Department for International Trade","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the possibility of the UK rejoining the European Free Trade Association.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50013","50013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620080","2016-10-27","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to his oral contribution of 12 October 2016, Official Report, column 331, what his policy is on what should be included in the British option he described; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49977","49977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620081","2016-10-27","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what legislation his Department plans to repeal using the Great Repeal Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49908","49908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620082","2016-10-26","HM Treasury","2016-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the earliest date by which the UK will be able to discharge the liabilities entered into during its time as an EU member state when exiting from the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49878","49878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620830","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-24","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the unduly lenient sentence scheme.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906822","906822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621043","2016-10-27","Women and Equalities","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of male teachers.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906861","906861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622069","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-24","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the use of the European Arrest Warrant.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906829","906829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622314","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-24","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of prosecutions for hate crime.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Fysh","Marcus Fysh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906831","906831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622315","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-24","To ask the Attorney General, what recent steps the Crown Prosecution Service has taken to set out its approach to prosecuting hate crime.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906832","906832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622316","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-24","To ask the Attorney General, what recent steps the Serious Fraud Office has taken to prevent serious fraud and other economic crimes.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906830","906830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622317","2016-10-27","Women and Equalities","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the potential implications of the UK leaving the EU for the Government's policies on equality.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906863","906863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622318","2016-10-27","Women and Equalities","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the rise in online misogyny.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906862","906862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622319","2016-10-27","Women and Equalities","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of women on boards and at senior executive levels of FTSE companies.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906865","906865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622320","2016-10-27","Women and Equalities","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to (a) tackle homophobic, biphobic and transphobic bullying in schools and (b) establish inclusive schools.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906864","906864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622321","2016-10-27","Women and Equalities","2016-10-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress has been made on changing restrictions on gay men being permitted to donate blood; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906866","906866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607500","2016-10-26","Cabinet Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress his Department has made on its work on an open address register.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49758","49758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607501","2016-10-26","Cabinet Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate his Department has made of the social and economic value to the economy of the open registers being built by the government data programme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49759","49759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607502","2016-10-25","HM Treasury","2016-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the value of salary sacrifice company cars to employers in the public sector for (a) recruiting and (b) retaining for staff.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49782","49782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607503","2016-10-26","HM Treasury","2016-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of taxation rules applied to company cars on incentivising the take-up of low and ultra-low emission vehicles.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49809","49809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607504","2016-10-26","HM Treasury","2016-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on basic rate taxpayers who drive low and ultra-low emission company cars of proposals contained in the HM Revenue and Customs' consultation on salary sacrifice for the provision of benefits in kind.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49810","49810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607505","2016-10-26","HM Treasury","2016-10-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of basic rate taxpaying company car drivers who will potentially pay more tax as a result of proposals in the HM Revenue and Customs' consultation on salary sacrifice for the provision of benefits in kind.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49811","49811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607506","2016-10-25","Department for Education","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in local authority care are awaiting placement with foster parents.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49745","49745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607507","2016-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the oral evidence of the Minister of State for Local Government to the Communities and Local Government Committee on 14 September 2016, at Questions 84 to 87, HC635, whether he plans to publish an estimated cost of the draft Homelessness Reduction Bill before its Second Reading.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49757","49757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607508","2016-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will extend the Help to Buy scheme to shared ownership housing association tenants.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49761","49761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607509","2016-10-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the games industry on the potential effects on that industry of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49776","49776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607510","2016-10-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his Department's policy that all submarines being constructed for the Royal Navy meet shock standard BR3021 as a minimum in respect of hydroplane bolts.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49743","49743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607511","2016-10-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) missions flown and (b) air strikes the armed forces have conducted within Iraqi territory in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49740","49740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607512","2016-10-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency plans his Department has for the decommissioning of nuclear-powered submarines if a suitable geological disposal facility is not identified.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49795","49795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607513","2016-10-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many nuclear-powered submarines are waiting for decommissioning work to be (a) commenced and (b) completed.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49796","49796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607514","2016-10-26","Department for Education","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that early years settings and schools are aware that socket covers should not be inserted in BS 1363 sockets.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49797","49797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607515","2016-10-25","Department for Education","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how long, on average, it took to match sponsors with schools where an Academy Order was made in each year before the Education and Adoption Act 2016 came into force.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49751","49751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607516","2016-10-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she will implement a ban on all (a) preventative use and (b) group treatments of critically important antibiotics.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49764","49764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607517","2016-10-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure that all UK supermarkets adopt a publicly available policy on antibiotic use within their supply chains.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49765","49765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607518","2016-10-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings her Department has had with supermarkets to discuss ensuring their packaging for produce and goods is recyclable.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49792","49792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607519","2016-10-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to bring forward testing regimes to monitor the emergence of E.coli and MRSA bacteria which are resistant to antibiotics in human medicine.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49766","49766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607520","2016-10-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will update the Summary of Product Characteristics of veterinary antibiotic products which are licensed for group treatments to state that those products may only be used for treatment of metaphylaxis.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49767","49767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607521","2016-10-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she will support proposals for an EU-wide ban on the routine prophylactic use of antibiotics in farming during the forthcoming negotiations on the EU Veterinary Medicinal Products and Medicated Feed Regulations.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49771","49771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607522","2016-10-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to implement the Guidelines for Selection of Biological SSSIs, revised in 2014, on extending the protection for the rarest and most vulnerable lowland grasslands to all sites that meet the criteria.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49785","49785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607523","2016-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how his Department plans to distribute money awarded by the European Solidarity Fund to flood-affected communities in the event that funds are awarded.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49807","49807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607524","2016-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will visit Keswick to meet the Keswick Flood Action Group, the Keswick Town Council and the hon. Member for Copeland to discuss flood prevention.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49805","49805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607525","2016-10-25","Department for International Trade","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46333, how much has been spent on the functions of the Department for International Trade; and what estimate he has made of how much will be spent on those functions by the end of the current fiscal year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49738","49738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607526","2016-10-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role he expects the UK to play in discussions at the UN General Assembly on multilateral nuclear disarmament; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49768","49768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607527","2016-10-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 45526, what representations he has received on the new charge brought against Nabeel Rajab by authorities in Bahrain.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49777","49777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607528","2016-10-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in other (a) NATO member states and (b) Commonwealth countries on the upcoming discussions at the UN General Assembly on multilateral nuclear disarmament; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49770","49770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607529","2016-10-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to increase the number of officials of his Department who work on issues related to the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49762","49762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607530","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure mental health services are accessible to LGBT people.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49755","49755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607531","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were treated for body dysmorphic disorder in (a) Liverpool Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) England and (d) each region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49756","49756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607532","2016-10-25","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to provide support to children's hospices which extend their services for young adults.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49749","49749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607533","2016-10-25","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to formalise the children's hospice grant for 2017-18.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49750","49750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607534","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Docklands Medical Services Ltd were registered with the Care Quality Commission for the provision of patient transport services during July, August and September 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49779","49779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607535","2016-10-25","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on requiring NHS trusts to record avoidable deaths; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49781","49781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607536","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to regulate dance movement psychotherapy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49753","49753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607537","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to set a limit on the amount GPs can charge patients for signing a debt and mental health evidence form.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49754","49754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607538","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on NHS waiting lists to receive a liver transplant.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49812","49812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607539","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has given NHS trusts on the use of Office for National Statistics population projections for service planning.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49806","49806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607540","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has plans for an opt-out system for organ donation across the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49808","49808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607541","2016-10-26","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will list the members of the neuroscience clinical reference group of NHS England.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49799","49799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607542","2016-10-25","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have (a) registered for and (b) attended events as part of the Better Health Programme.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49787","49787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607543","2016-10-25","Home Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that children coming to the UK as refugees from Calais are under 18 years olds.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49790","49790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607544","2016-10-25","Home Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) male and (b) female unaccompanied children arrived in the UK seeking asylum in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49744","49744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607545","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to reduce homophobic hate crimes since January 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49752","49752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607546","2016-10-25","Department of Health","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with Eastbourne Borough Council on steps to deter or prevent people from taking their own life on Beachy Head.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49742","49742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607547","2016-10-25","Home Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how potential victims of trafficking whose type of exploitation is recorded as unknown in the National Referral Mechanism Statistics, end of year summary 2015, published on 11 February 2016 were identified; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49737","49737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607548","2016-10-26","Home Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the unaccompanied children that have arrived in the UK from Calais under the Dublin III Regulation are (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49778","49778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607549","2016-10-25","Home Office","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department received any representations from King's College Dental School, between 2012 and 2014, on the use of dental tests to establish the age of people claiming asylum.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49763","49763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607550","2016-10-25","House of Commons Commission","2016-10-21","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, on how many days under the current Travel Office contract the ticket machines situated in the House have been unable to print hon. Members' travel tickets.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49746","49746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607551","2016-10-25","Department for International Development","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 48875, how many refugees her Department has helped to remain in, or stay as close as possible to, their countries of origin.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49793","49793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607552","2016-10-26","Department for International Development","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to increase investment in decentralised renewable energy in developing countries.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49815","49815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607553","2016-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps her Department has taken to improve education in prisons.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49741","49741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607554","2016-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drivers have avoided disqualification from driving within the last year by pleading the loss of their licence would cause exceptional hardship.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49747","49747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607555","2016-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to include legislation for exceptional hardship pleas within the forthcoming review of motoring offences and penalties.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49748","49748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607556","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many apprenticeships have been provided to date by HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49798","49798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607557","2016-10-25","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the shortage of people with rail engineering, environmental and construction skills.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49784","49784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607558","2016-10-25","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 46806 on taxis: licensing, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in licence applications from Rossendale Borough Council between 2013 and 2015.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49791","49791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607559","2016-10-25","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the recommendations made by the HS2 Ltd Residents' Commissioner in her published reports have been adopted in full by HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49783","49783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607560","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the project management section of the High Speed Rail (Preparation) Act 2013 Expenditure Report, 1 April 2015 to 31 March 2016, what incentive payments were made to HS2 Ltd's development partners and professional services contractors; to whom such payments were made; and what exceptional performance was relevant in each such case.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49780","49780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607561","2016-10-25","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost to the public purse has been to date of the National College for High Speed Rail.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49772","49772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607562","2016-10-25","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the National College for High Speed Rail will be operational.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49786","49786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607563","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.12 of the High Speed Rail (Preparation) Act 2013 Expenditure Report, 1 April 2015 to 31 March 2016, published by his Department in October 2016, if he will provide reasons for the difference between the actual and budgeted cost per person in the project management team.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49800","49800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607564","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 2.2 of the High Speed Rail (Preparation) Act 2013 Expenditure Report, 1 April 2015 to 31 March 2016, published by his Department in October 2016, if he will detail the reasons, other than the delay in completing the acquisition of large-scale commercial properties, for the 192.7 million underspend referred to in that report.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49801","49801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607565","2016-10-26","Department for Transport","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37550, what further progress has been made on reviewing the legal and financial implications of an alternative pavement parking regime; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49804","49804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607566","2016-10-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2016 to Question 47528 and the Answer of 17 October 2016 to HL 2020, if he will provide further detail on the consideration of responses to questions seven and 11 and summary paragraphs 45 and 67 of the consultation on housing benefit reform, Cm 8152, where there are references to meeting appointed housing needs through locally administered funding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49803","49803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/607567","2016-10-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what he expects the savings to his Department to be of the proposed changes to the employment and support allowance work-related activity group; and how much funding has been allocated to the proposed work and health programme.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 49760","49760"
