"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710855","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff have been seconded to her Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67737","67737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710856","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many contracts procured by her Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted for the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67768","67768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710857","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many contracts procured by her Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67753","67753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710858","2017-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67755","67755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710859","2017-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted for the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67770","67770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710860","2017-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff have been seconded to his Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67739","67739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710861","2017-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to review intelligence sharing and joint working with the US.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67723","67723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710862","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many time ambulances based in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the North West have responded to emergency calls outside the category (i) A and (ii) B response time target in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67703","67703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710863","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff have been seconded to his Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67740","67740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710864","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what costs have been (a) incurred to date and (b) committed for future periods for the development and management of sustainability and transformation plans in St Helens North constituency.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67706","67706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710865","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what disciplinary actions may be taken against medical professionals who raise concerns on standards.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67712","67712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710866","2017-03-24","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that Medway Maritime Hospital has capacity to meet the needs of the local population.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67730","67730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710867","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted for the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67771","67771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710868","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67756","67756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710869","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contracts procured by her Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67757","67757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710870","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contracts procured by her Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted for the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67772","67772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710871","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional training is provided to officials who deal with asylum claimants who are survivors of torture.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67718","67718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710872","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have been seconded to her Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67741","67741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710873","2017-03-16","Department for International Development","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff have been seconded to her Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67742","67742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710874","2017-03-20","Department for International Development","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to review her Department's spending on all education projects in the Palestine authority to ensure those projects meet her Department's criteria.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67713","67713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710875","2017-03-16","Department for International Development","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what financial assistance her Department gives to Christians in developing countries; and what assistance can be given to individual Christians within the criteria set by her Department.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67711","67711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710876","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contracts procured by her Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67759","67759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710877","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have been seconded to her Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67744","67744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710878","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff have been seconded to his Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67745","67745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710879","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67760","67760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710881","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to prevent suicides on the East Coast Main Line through Retford.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67720","67720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710882","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67762","67762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710883","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff have been seconded to his Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67747","67747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710884","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposals in the Land Registry's consultation on amending the Land Registration Rules Act 2003 relating to large-scale electronic conveyancing on (a) all small and medium-sized conveyancing companies and (b) small and medium-sized conveyancing companies based in rural areas with poor internet coverage.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67779","67779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710885","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has undertaken an assessment of the potential merits of moving responsibility for the Land Registry to the Department for Communities and Local Government.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67780","67780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710886","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) airline and (b) other companies that charge over the 0.3 per cent cap for credit card transactions.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67778","67778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710887","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff have been seconded to his Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67731","67731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710888","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67748","67748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710889","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted for the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67763","67763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710890","2017-03-20","Department for International Trade","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what basis European Council Common Position 2008/944/CFSP has in UK law.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67726","67726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710891","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff have been seconded to his Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67743","67743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710892","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67758","67758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710893","2017-03-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies are covered by TUPE regulations in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67754","67754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710894","2017-03-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted for the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67769","67769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710895","2017-03-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff have been seconded to his Department from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67738","67738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710897","2017-03-16","Attorney General","2017-03-14","To ask the Attorney General, what recent progress has been made in increasing the prosecution rate for disability hate crime offences.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67906","67906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710898","2017-03-16","Attorney General","2017-03-14","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2017 to Question 66990, what the pay grades are of the (a) 330 lawyers from the GLD's litigation group, (b) 12.5 full-time equivalent Crown Prosecution Service staff and (c) three Serious Fraud Office staff employed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68004","68004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710899","2017-03-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2017 to Question 66974, on Government contracts, who the experts on that panel were; for what reasons those experts were chosen to serve on that panel; and how frequently that panel met.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67958","67958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710900","2017-03-16","Cabinet Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of potential savings arising from increased data sharing across Whitehall.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67910","67910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710901","2017-03-16","Cabinet Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of data sharing across Whitehall.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67911","67911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710902","2017-03-20","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance government departments receive on when they are (a) required and (b) encouraged to conduct an impact assessment.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67805","67805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710903","2017-03-20","Cabinet Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2017 to Question 67375, on government responses to written questions, what his definition is of the last administration.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67896","67896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710904","2017-03-20","Cabinet Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2017 to Question 67375, on government responses to written questions, how long he expects that task of manual checking to take.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67899","67899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710905","2017-03-20","Cabinet Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on record management systems in the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67900","67900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710906","2017-03-20","Cabinet Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of his Department's records management system.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67901","67901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710907","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 65005, what the pay grades are of the 89 civil servants of his Department who manage external contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67885","67885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710909","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has received a request from the Press Recognition Panel for additional funding under the terms of the Royal Charter on Self-Regulation of the Press.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67951","67951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710910","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people paying Class 4 national insurance contributions in (a) Leeds East constituency, (b) Leeds and (c) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67829","67829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710911","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to develop an adoption allowance similar to maternity allowance for self-employed people who adopt a child as a result of the rise in Class 4 national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67855","67855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710912","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to develop a paternity allowance similar to maternity allowance for self-employed fathers as a result of the rise in Class 4 national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67856","67856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710913","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the rise in Class 4 national insurance contributions will result in the self-employed having increased access to contribution-based employment support allowance.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67857","67857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710914","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the rise in Class 4 national insurance contributions will result in the self-employed having increased access to contribution-based job seeker's allowance.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67858","67858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710915","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to introduce a measure comparable to employer national insurance contributions to provide an equivalent provision to such existing contributions for the self-employed on account of the lack of such equivalent provision driving bogus self-employment and in reducing access to benefits for the self-employed.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67860","67860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710916","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.17 of the Spring Budget 2017, what estimate the Government has made of the number of public houses that will be eligible for the £1,000 business rate discount in (a) Pendle, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67881","67881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710917","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) prosecutions for misrepresentation and (b) referrals to HM Revenue and Customs for tax and fraud have occurred in connection with Child Maintenance Support cases since the specialist Financial Investigation Unit was introduced into the 2012 child maintenance scheme.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67807","67807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710918","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, hehow many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted for the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67776","67776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710919","2017-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of making dark fibre lit for telecommunications purposes liable for business rate payments.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67794","67794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710920","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the effect on the public purse of bogus self-employment arising from there being no equivalent provision to employer national insurance contributions for self-employed.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67861","67861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710921","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans for self-employed mothers to have access to statutory maternity pay as a result of the rise in Class 4 national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67863","67863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710922","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the fund announced in the Spring Budget 2017 to mark the centenary of women's suffrage will be open for applications from Northern Ireland bidders; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67840","67840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710924","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria bidders will be required to meet to secure funding from the fund announced in the Spring Budget 2017 to mark the centenary of women's suffrage; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67841","67841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710925","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) North Swindon constituency, (b) the South West and (c) the UK have been removed from paying income tax between May 2010 and the latest date for which figures are available; and what estimate he has made of the number of people so removed as a result of measures announced in the Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67913","67913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710926","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) North Swindon, (b) the South West and (c) the UK have seen a reduction in their income tax liability since May 2010; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who will experience such a reduction as a result of measures announced in the Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67907","67907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710928","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether when considering rates of UK corporation tax it is his Department's policy to take into account the spillover effect that a reduction in the UK's rate of corporation tax would have on other countries.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67995","67995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710929","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to deter UK-headquartered multinational companies from using tax havens to avoid paying tax in developing countries.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67925","67925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710930","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to include the value of annual changes in income tax on individuals' payslips.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67991","67991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710931","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to include the value of annual changes in income tax to an individual on annual tax summaries.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67992","67992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710933","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 4.5 of the Spring Budget 2017, what share of the £300 million in discretionary relief for business rate individual hard cases will be provided to businesses in Pendle constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67993","67993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710934","2017-03-16","Church Commissioners","2017-03-14","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 64993, on procurement, what the pay grades are of the (a) five members of staff in the property investments team and (b) seven members of staff in the investment team.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67944","67944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710935","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.17 of the Spring Budget 2017, what estimate he has made of how many pubs will qualify for the £1,000 business rate discount in (a) Leeds East constituency, (b) Leeds and (c) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67831","67831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710936","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.16 of the Spring Budget 2017, what estimate he has made of how much of the (a) £435 million of further support for businesses facing significant increases in bills from the English business rates system and (b) £300 million discretionary relief to allow councils to provide support to individual hard cases in their local areas will be allocated to (i) Leeds East constituency, (ii) Leeds and (iii) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67830","67830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710938","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the expiry date for the planning permission granted for the Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67827","67827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710939","2017-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 65415, who is responsible for monitoring whether local authorities meet their statutory requirements on oral health.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67864","67864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710940","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 5.5 of the Spring Budget 2017, what estimate he has made of how much of the additional £2 billion funding for adult social care will be allocated to Leeds City Council.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67836","67836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710941","2017-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 64994, at what pay grades the 110 civil servants with contract management responsibility are employed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67824","67824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710942","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the removal of permitted development rights for the conversion or demolition of pubs on trends in pub closures.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67916","67916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710943","2017-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the application by some Dorset councils for local government reorganisation submitted on 9 February 2017 has been referred to the Local Government Boundary Commission for England.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67952","67952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710944","2017-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what date the Government invited councils in Dorset to submit a proposal for (a) a combined authority and (b) local government reorganisation.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67953","67953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710946","2017-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate the development of can-float homes in areas of flood risk; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67956","67956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710947","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Statement of Lord Bourne of Ashworth of 1 July 2016 on Security of Tenure, domestic violence, when he plans to set out the circumstances under which local authorities may exercise discretion in transferring lifetime tenancies for those seeking escape from domestic violence.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67986","67986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710948","2017-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the £300 million in discretionary rate relief for businesses which will be allocated to Warrington.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67999","67999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710950","2017-03-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the reasons were for the time taken by her Department to lay Written Ministerial Statement HCWS533, on the EU-US Umbrella Agreement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67977","67977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710951","2017-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to improve mobile telephone coverage in Pendle.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67938","67938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710955","2017-03-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2017 to Question 66775, what responsibility email account service providers have to return data to consumers when their services end.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67823","67823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710957","2017-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to lay provisions for the new Horseracing Betting Levy Scheme before Parliament.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67948","67948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710959","2017-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which broadcasters have been found in breach of the broadcasting code without being sanctioned as a result in the last 10 years; and how many times each of those broadcasters were found in breach of the broadcast code in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67924","67924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710960","2017-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times Sky Plc has been sanctioned by Ofcom under the broadcast code in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67926","67926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710961","2017-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times 21st Century Fox has been sanctioned by Ofcom under the broadcast code in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67927","67927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710962","2017-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the findings of the consultation on Better combat compensation to be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67947","67947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710963","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military personnel, (b) civilian personnel and (c) contracted workers are based at each of the military sites in the City of York Local Authority area to be disposed of by 2040.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67867","67867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710964","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to assist the Afghan National Security Forces to combat Daesh in Afghanistan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67804","67804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710965","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military personnel will be released for other duties having previously been involved with EU missions after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67786","67786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710966","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military personnel have been (a) recruited and (b) resigned or retired from the armed forces in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67791","67791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710967","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what regulations and sanctions there are related to the false written use of military rank and postnominals by non armed forces personnel.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67848","67848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710968","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what regulations and sanctions there are related to the impersonation of armed forces personnel (a) for financial gain, (b) to compromise security or gain access to his Department's property, (c) for other material gain and (d) for enhanced social standing.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67849","67849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710969","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what regulations and sanctions there are related to the false wearing of (a) uniform, (b) rank and (c) tactical recognition flashes or insignia by non armed forces personnel.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67850","67850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710970","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any property developers have expressed an interest to his Department in purchasing all or part of Hyde Park Barracks in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67969","67969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710971","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government plans to sell all or part of the Hyde Park Barracks.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67965","67965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710972","2017-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to recognise the Coleshill Auxiliers with a specific service medal.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67988","67988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710973","2017-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the indemnity provided by his Department to private land owners who make their land available for military training activities provides full cover to ensure the land area has no liability for claims arising from such training.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67943","67943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710974","2017-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the Government has for the future of Hyde Park Barracks.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67957","67957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710975","2017-03-20","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to answer Question 60529 tabled on 18 January 2017 by the hon. Member for Manchester Central.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67959","67959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710976","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure more teachers from non-leadership backgrounds are recruited as Ofsted inspectors.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67989","67989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710977","2017-03-20","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2017 to Question 64307, on Baverstock Academy, if she will publish her Department's review of the conditions at Baverstock Academy and the reasons those conditions posed a risk to interested sponsors.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67978","67978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710978","2017-03-20","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2017 to Question 64307, on Baverstock Academy, on how many occasions her Department has refused a sponsor because of the risk a school poses to that sponsor.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67979","67979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710979","2017-03-20","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 65657, on children's centres, from which local authorities the amount recovered in 2015 was received.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67821","67821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710980","2017-03-20","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authority schools have been placed in special measures by Ofsted in each of the last 10 years; and what proportion of inspected schools were placed in such measures by Ofsted in each of those years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67800","67800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710982","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new nursery places have been created by free schools that have opened since November 2015.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67839","67839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710984","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 4.14 of the Spring Budget 2017, what estimate she has made of how much of £216 million funding for school maintenance will be allocated to (a) Leeds East constituency, (b) Leeds and (c) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67833","67833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710985","2017-03-20","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will make an assessment of the financial effect of making personal, social and health education compulsory in all schools.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67902","67902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710986","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department takes to ensure that welfare standards are met in slaughterhouses; and what steps her Department takes in particular relation to such standards as they relate to pre-stunning.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67950","67950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710987","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to her Department of maintaining agricultural sector funding at Pillar 1 levels under the Common Agricultural Policy from when the UK leaves the EU until 2020; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67934","67934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710988","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64997, what the pay grades are of the 14 civil servants of her Department who oversee contracts awarded to external providers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67882","67882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710989","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether a zoo containing more than 1,000 animals has been closed by a local authority in the last 30 years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67816","67816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710990","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times zoos have been closed by local authorities in the last 20 years; and for what reasons those zoos were closed.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67815","67815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710991","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department last conducted a review of the framework for the statutory regulation of zoos.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67817","67817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710992","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations her Department has received from local authorities on the effectiveness and scope of current zoo regulations.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67818","67818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710993","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2017 to Question 66880, what information her Department holds on the number and value of individual payments which were not paid within the basic payment scheme window since 30 June 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67812","67812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710994","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to make the language requirements for non-EU national veterinary surgeons to practice the same as with those which apply to non-UK EU nationals .","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67918","67918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710995","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help local authorities in the North West whose area is affected by ash dieback.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67937","67937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710997","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the (a) number and (b) value of EU disallowance penalties incurred for late payments by the Rural Payments Agency of basic payments between 1 December 2015 and 30 June 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67975","67975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710999","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the financial effect on farming by 2020 if funding currently provided under Pillar 1 of the Common Agricultural Policy is withdrawn when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67936","67936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711000","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help facilitate research into can-float flood resilient buildings for infill development in flood risk zones.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67955","67955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711002","2017-03-20","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which countries the UK has a Memorandum of Understanding to facilitate enforced deportation to a third country.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67970","67970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711003","2017-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials in his Department are fluent in (a) Dari and (b) Pashto; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67810","67810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711004","2017-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 64998, at what pay grades the 50 civil servants who oversee major departmental contracts are employed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67811","67811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711005","2017-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK diplomats and members of staff at the UK embassy in Kabul are fluent in (a) Dari and (b) Pashto; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67806","67806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711006","2017-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what consideration has been given to the geographical location of the Western Balkans summit in 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67790","67790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711007","2017-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 64998, if he will estimate the proportion of contracts awarded to external providers that are defined as major departmental contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67949","67949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711008","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish a list of school transport plans with no mechanism for engaging schools and colleges as active stakeholders.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67935","67935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711009","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the Government's response to the accelerated access review.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67897","67897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711011","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many technology appraisals NICE has undertaken for medicines which have successfully passed through the Early Access to Medicines Scheme; and what the NICE recommendation was for each of those appraisals.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67898","67898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711012","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 63650, on clinical commissioning groups: buildings, whether the additional £127 million to fund the increase in costs is for 2016-17 only.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67880","67880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711013","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 5.13 of the Spring Budget 2017, what estimate she has made of how much of £100 million funding for implementing the Government's Ending Violence Against Women and Girls Strategy will be allocated to (a) Leeds East constituency, (b) Leeds and (c) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67834","67834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711014","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 5.8 of the Spring Budget 2017, what estimate he has made of how much of £325 million funding for local sustainability and transformation plans will be allocated to (a) Leeds East constituency, (b) Leeds and (c) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67832","67832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711015","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent in bereavement services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67872","67872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711016","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what changes to services will take place as a result of the standardisation of walk-in centres, minor injury units and urgent care centres by NHS England.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67803","67803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711017","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what account NICE takes of the fact that medicines have successfully passed through the Early Access to Medicines Scheme due to high unmet medical needs when undertaking technology appraisals.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67809","67809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711018","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what changes will be made to the workforce of NHS 111 to support on-site assessment in care homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67808","67808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711019","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs will be employed in staffing the comprehensive front door streaming model at accident and emergency departments from October 2017; and what assessment he has made of the capacity of the GP workforce to meet that demand.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67813","67813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711020","2017-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what date he plans for public health to be fully funded from local authority business rate retention.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67814","67814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711021","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what products for rare and ultra-rare disease treatment have received European Medicines Agency marketing authorisation and orphan designation since 2013; and which of those products is routinely available to patients in England.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67797","67797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711022","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage clinical commissioning groups to increase access to cough-assist machines for people with muscle-wasting conditions, such as muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67796","67796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711023","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of neuroscience centres in meeting NHS England service specifications of neurological care.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67795","67795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711024","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2016 to Question 56707, on diseases, how many of the 46 products that had received European Medicines Agency marketing authorisation and orphan designation since 2013 are undergoing assessment by NICE or NHS England; how many of those products are routinely commissioned in England; how many of those products received a positive evaluation through NICE's technology appraisal system; and how many of the six products selected for the highly specialised technologies programme received a positive evaluation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67798","67798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711025","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on recommendation 9 of the report Old Problems, New Solutions: Improving Acute Psychiatric Care for Adults in England, published by the Commission on Acute Psychiatric Care in February 2016, to pilot a new patients and carers race equality standard.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67799","67799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711026","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 5.7 of the Spring Budget 2017, what estimate he has made of how much of the £100 million funding for capital investment in accident and emergency departments in 2017-18 will be allocated to (a) Leeds General Infirmary and (b) St James' Hospital, Leeds.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67837","67837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711027","2017-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 3 of the Spring Budget 2017, how much of the additional £2 billion of additional social care funding he plans to allocate to Warrington.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67966","67966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711028","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the Mandate to NHS England as required under section 13A(7) of the National Health Service Act 2006","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67932","67932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711029","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of dealing with the missed requirements of Capita in relation to the contract for the management of primary care support services.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67933","67933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711031","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate has been made of the number of public-access defibrillators in (a) Pendle, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67939","67939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711032","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 63652, on NHS Property Services Communities Health Partnerships, whether a business case was prepared to support the plans to establish a new NHS property organisation.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67994","67994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711033","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to extend counselling opportunities for BME groups in the NHS.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67919","67919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711034","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to assist hospital trusts to reduce or restructure costs borne as a result of private finance initiatives.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67920","67920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711035","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria he plans to use to allocate the funds announced in the Spring Budget 2017 for GP surgery co-location in hospital accident and emergency departments.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67990","67990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711036","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many non-fatal suicide attempts there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67997","67997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711037","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department allocated to public information campaigns on suicide prevention in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67998","67998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711038","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects patients to be able to access their own full medical records online.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67909","67909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711039","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 66400, what the pay grade is of the 11.5 civil servants of his Department's contract management team.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68002","68002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711040","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that those people subject to disability hate crime have the confidence to report offences.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67912","67912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711041","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the introduction of safe return reviews on (a) the resources needed by her Department to implement that policy and (b) the integration of refugees into the UK.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67904","67904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711042","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to make the offence of dog fighting a specific recordable offence by police to enable more accurate recording and help target resources.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67929","67929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711043","2017-03-20","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) Facebook, (b) Twitter, (c) Google+, (d) YouTube, (e) Snapchat and (f) WhatsApp accounts have been closed or suspended on request of the Government due to involvement in (i) terrorism, (ii) hate crime and (iii) targeted harassment in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67847","67847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711044","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of parents who have sent their children to the UK as unaccompanied asylum seekers.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67781","67781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711045","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to match-fund the costs to local authorities of refugees and asylum seekers with central government funding.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67787","67787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711046","2017-03-20","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2017 to Question 66773, whether her Department (a) records, (b) collates and (c) publishes the reasons for which visas are refused which have been set out to the applicant at the time of refusal.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67822","67822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711047","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for the European Economic Area family permit have been (a) submitted, (b) rejected and (c) accepted in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67828","67828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711048","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects paragraph 11 of Schedule 10 of the Immigration Act 2016 to be brought into force.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67878","67878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711050","2017-03-20","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many custody suites in police stations were closed in 2015-16.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67894","67894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711051","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many documents have been recorded as lost by her Department since 8 May 2015.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67887","67887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711052","2017-03-20","House of Commons Commission","2017-03-14","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 65000, at what pay grades the 228 contract managers are employed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67820","67820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711053","2017-03-20","Department for International Development","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's humanitarian aid budget was disbursed for (a) one year, (b) two years and (c) three years or more in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67793","67793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711055","2017-03-16","Department for International Development","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of providing financial support to increase the level of activity at the fisheries research laboratory in Monkey Bay, Malawi.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67826","67826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711056","2017-03-20","Department for International Development","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66402, at what pay grades the 640 senior responsible owners (SROs) are employed; and at what pay grades the staff in the team of each of those SROs are employed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67825","67825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711057","2017-03-20","Department for International Development","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government plans to take to prevent famine in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67868","67868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711058","2017-03-20","Department for International Development","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government has taken to encourage the Saudi-led coalition to open up aid access to Yemen via unblocking Hodeida port and opening up airspace.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67869","67869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711059","2017-03-16","Department for International Development","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support smaller countries toward achieving the UN Sustainable Development Goal 14 on conservation and sustainable use of the marine environment.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67961","67961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711060","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many restraining orders issued (a) prohibited online contact and (b) restricted the ability of the subject of the order to take civil court actions against the victim in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67917","67917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711061","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made on developing the terms of reference for the 12 month review of the workings of the victims' code.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67923","67923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711062","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many random mandatory drug tests have been undertaken in prisons in England and Wales each of the last six years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67996","67996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711064","2017-03-20","Department of Health","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of prisons have a (a) psychiatrist, (b) psychotherapist and (c) qualified psychiatric nurse based on site.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67866","67866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711066","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer to Question 65003, on procurement, on what pay grades the 172 civil servants employed in the Commercial and Contract Management Directorate are employed; on what pay grades the 100 contract employed by the Legal Aid Agency are employed; and on what pay grades the 218 are employed by the National Offender Management Service employed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67851","67851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711067","2017-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers were on leave of absence due to mental illness in 2015-16; and for how many days each such absence lasted.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67892","67892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711068","2017-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many custody suites in courts were closed in 2015-16.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67895","67895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711069","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department plans to issue a pro forma for courts in England and Wales to assist with the precise wording of restraining orders.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67915","67915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711070","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to increase the maximum penalty for dog fighting.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67928","67928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711071","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Serious Further Offence reviews involving (a) the National Probation Service and (b) Community Rehabilitation companies in England and Wales have been conducted since February 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67914","67914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711072","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contracts procured by her Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted for the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67774","67774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711073","2017-03-20","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will hold discussions with the Secretary of State for Defence on the most efficient use of the deployment of army bomb disposal units, particularly when dealing with numerous incidents in the West and North West of Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67789","67789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711074","2017-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to accelerate the introduction of legislation to provide transparency in relation to donations to all political parties operating in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67843","67843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711075","2017-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 65004, what the pay grades are of the 10 civil servants of his Department who oversee contracts awarded to external providers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67884","67884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711076","2017-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to ensure the devolution of additional powers to the Northern Ireland Assembly after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67845","67845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711077","2017-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment he has made of the risks of removing the anonymity of donors to political parties operating in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67844","67844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711078","2017-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many (a) refugees from Syria and (b) unaccompanied refugee children from Europe have been settled in Northern Ireland in the last year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67846","67846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711079","2017-03-16","Prime Minister","2017-03-14","To ask the Prime Minister, when she next plans to visit Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67842","67842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711080","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many local authorities have applied for Bikeability funding since 2015; and how  many of those applications were successful.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67838","67838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711081","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67775","67775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711082","2017-03-20","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when HS2 Ltd plans to provide the detailed programme of works for the Chilterns.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67792","67792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711083","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer to Question 60337, on Southern: standards, when the full report and recommendations of Chris Gibb's project board into rapid improvements of Southern Rail will be published.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67853","67853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711084","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to designate stations outside the current Greater London boundary as Greater London Stations for the purposes of possible inclusion in the services devolved to Transport for London.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67835","67835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711085","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 65407, what the pay grades are of the 679 civil servants of his Department who oversee contracts awarded to external providers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67883","67883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711086","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support his Department is providing for the work of the England's Economic Heartland Strategic Alliance to improve rail and road links across the area.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67890","67890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711087","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the capacity of Swindon station.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67922","67922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711088","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the decline in demand for new tyres for pre-1960 vehicles since the requirement for an annual MOT test for such vehicles was removed in 2012; whether there has been an increase in the number of road traffic accidents involving such vehicles since 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67981","67981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711089","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of MOT testing in ensuring that vehicles with unroadworthy tyres are not used on the public highway.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67980","67980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711090","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what role the EU had in promoting the exemption of 40 year-old cars from MOT inspections; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67983","67983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711091","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people used Swindon station in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67908","67908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711092","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department is making in replacing pacer trains.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67940","67940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711093","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of using Bikeability funding to deliver Bikeability Plus on the provision of Bikeability training.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67941","67941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711094","2017-03-23","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the increased risk to road-users consequent on any future decision to exempt from MOT tests any vehicle built more than 40 years ago; and when the consultation on that proposal is due to report.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67982","67982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711095","2017-03-20","Women and Equalities","2017-03-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether her Department will have access to HM Revenue and Customs data in order to help identify non-compliant businesses once gender pay gap reporting  requirements are in place in April 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68000","68000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711096","2017-03-16","Women and Equalities","2017-03-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the effect of male primogeniture on the gender balance of hereditary peers in the House of Lords.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67854","67854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711097","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to ensure that every jobcentre has available information leaflets on suicide prevention.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67873","67873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711098","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on clients with sensory and mobility impairments, and those unable to travel independently of the closure of East Ham Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67871","67871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711099","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the closure of East Ham Jobcentre Plus on people in the local area trying to find work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67870","67870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711100","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 65535, on procurement, at what pay grades the 83 contract managers are employed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67879","67879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711101","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of increased journey times and travel costs for people currently using East Ham jobcentre of its closure.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67859","67859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711102","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobcentres were closed in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67893","67893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711103","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of parents were under (a) Direct Pay and (b) Collect and Pay schemes in each year of the operation of the (i) Child Support Agency and (ii) Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67888","67888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711104","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with which overseas banks located in which countries his Department is working on overseas state pension fraud and error.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67889","67889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711105","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on disability employment of reductions to the work-related activity group component of employment and support allowance; and whether the Government will reconsider that measure if the disability employment gap widens as a result.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67886","67886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711106","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of how physical conditions which cause significant cognitive and mental health symptoms will be affected by planned changes to mobility activity 1 of the personal independence payment assessment.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67973","67973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711107","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the change was in annual social security payments in the UK between 2012 and the projected annual cost by 31 March 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67788","67788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711108","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67777","67777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711109","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans for the referral process by which Child Maintenance Service (CMS) caseworkers can refer new CMS cases and complaints cases to the Financial Investigation Unit to be extended to cover all child maintenance cases.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67802","67802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711110","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to improve access to sick pay for the self-employed.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67862","67862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711111","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18 to 21-year olds resident in (a) the North West and (b) Warrington claim the housing costs element of universal credit.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67865","67865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711112","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department's evaluation of the work of the Financial Investigation Unit in dealing with child maintenance cases within the New Case and Complaints areas of the Child Maintenance Service has been completed.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67801","67801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711113","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people applying for (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment and support allowance have missed a medical assessment in each of the last three years; and how many of those people have lost entitlement to a benefit as a result of that missed assessment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67968","67968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711114","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to daily living activity 3 of the personal independence payment assessment, how many people with multiple sclerosis who received a daily living award scored points on descriptor b for (a) new claims and (b) disability living allowance reassessments in each year before October 2016.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67971","67971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711115","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work capability assessment appeals have been made by people in Dorset in the last year for which information is available; and what percentage of those appeals have been successful.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67954","67954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711116","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what advice his Department issues to personal independence payment claimants on their right to have a recorded home assessment.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67931","67931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711117","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department uses to determine eligibility for recorded home assessments for personal independence payment; what support his Department provides for vulnerable claimants who require home assessments; and what processes are undertaken by his Department to consider the evidence from recorded home assessments.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67930","67930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711118","2017-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the mobility activity 1 of the personal independence payment assessment, how many people with multiple sclerosis who received a mobility award scored points on descriptor b for (a) new claims and (b) disability living allowance reassessments in each year before October 2016.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67972","67972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711119","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a person who has been assessed for employment and support allowance or personal independent payments is entitled to a copy of the computer file report created by the HCP during their assessment process.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67987","67987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711120","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect full online medical record access for patients will have on the efficiency of processing employment and support allowance and personal independence payments applications.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67905","67905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711121","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what further steps he plans to take to encourage Jobcentre Plus to refer jobseekers to local charity and voluntary groups which offer advice and support to help those seeking a job.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67984","67984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711122","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of road haulage vehicles using fuels other than petrol or diesel.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67921","67921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711123","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Ministers of her Department will be representing the UK at the High-Level UN Conference to Support the Implementation of Sustainable Development Goal 14 in New York on 5 to 9 June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67962","67962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711124","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what actions she plans to recommend to the High-Level UN Conference to Support the Implementation of Sustainable Development Goal 14 in New York on 5 to 9 June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67963","67963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711125","2017-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the completion dates for renewable energy projects across the UK for which (a) planning permission has been approved and (b) the installed capacity is to be equal to or above one gigawatt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67976","67976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711126","2017-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received on the merits of banning all plastic bags in pursuit of achieving the UN Sustainable Development Goal 14 on conservation and sustainable use of the marine environment.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67964","67964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711127","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what guidance his Department issues to (a) National Grid and (b) Ofgem on the frequency of use of retrospective changes to the energy from the gas market.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67942","67942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711128","2017-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much Government funding the productivity leadership group has received.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67967","67967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711129","2017-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the amount disbursed from the £12 billion Local Growth Fund has been allocated to the London Borough of Newham since that fund was opened.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68001","68001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711130","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government has taken towards achieving the UN Sustainable Development Goal 14 on conservation and sustainable use of the marine environment since January 2016.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67960","67960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711131","2017-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the total proportion of UK energy supply which will come from renewable sources in each of the next 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67819","67819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711132","2017-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average price of electricity exported from the UK through interconnectors was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67874","67874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711133","2017-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much electricity was exported from the UK through interconnectors in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67875","67875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711134","2017-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average price of electricity imported into the UK through interconnectors was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67876","67876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711135","2017-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much electricity was imported into the UK through interconnectors in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67877","67877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711136","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2017 to Question 66151, on pay, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of providing assistance to workers who are unable to determine whether they have been paid the national minimum wage or national living wage as a result of their pay slips lacking in transparency.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67782","67782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711137","2017-03-20","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of decommissioning north sea oil and gas platforms over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67974","67974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711138","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the percentage of renewable energy as a percentage of total energy used in the (a) transport and (b) heat sectors in each of the next 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67945","67945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711139","2017-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the National Grid on support for small-scale gas energy suppliers to remain in the market.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67946","67946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711140","2017-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average wholesale price of electricity was in 2016.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67903","67903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711141","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his policy is of the inclusion of environmental goods and services in future trade agreements.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67783","67783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711142","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the Investment Court System; what the Government's policy is on that system; and what plans the UK has to promote that system to other countries as part of future trade agreements.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67784","67784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711143","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he plans to include cross-border data flows in a future trade agreement with (a) the US and (b) the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67785","67785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711144","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many contracts procured by his Department and its arms-length bodies require that the contractor pays those of its employees undertaking the work contracted for the real living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67773","67773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711145","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 65002, what the pay grade is of the 24 civil servants if his Department employed in the commercial function team.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 68003","68003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711146","2017-03-16","Department for International Trade","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the total British foreign direct investment in Poland was in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67985","67985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711147","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what impact assessment has been made of the changes in EU funds to ensure that children accessing services currently funded by the EU will not be disadvantaged by the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67891","67891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/711148","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the tenant tax on private landlords in terms of (a) rental income and (b) property standards.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67852","67852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712268","2017-03-20","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the extent of teacher shortages in Cambridgeshire.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909341","909341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/712269","2017-03-20","Department for Education","2017-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to improve the quality of primary education.","Biography information for Jeremy Quin","Jeremy Quin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 909342","909342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710431","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average time taken has been to produce tendering documents for Government contracts below £10,000 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67473","67473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710432","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average number of work hours spent producing tendering documents for Government contracts above £10,000 but below the level specified by the Official Journal of the European Union is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67474","67474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710433","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average time taken has been to produce tendering documents for Government contracts above the level specified by the Official Journal of the European Union in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67475","67475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710434","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average time taken has been to produce tendering documents for Government contracts above £10,000 but below the level specified by the Official Journal of the European Union in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67476","67476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710435","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of Government procurement is tendered through the Official Journal of the European Union; and what proportion of staff (a) hours and (b) wages is spent on that work.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67477","67477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710436","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average cost has been to produce tendering documents for Government contracts above the level specified by the Official Journal of the European Union in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67478","67478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710437","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average cost has been to produce tendering documents for Government contracts valued below £10,000 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67479","67479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710438","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average cost has been to produce tendering documents for Government contracts above £10,000 but below the level specified by the Official Journal of the European Union in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67480","67480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710439","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average amount of work hours spent producing tendering documents for Government contracts below £10,000 is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67481","67481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710440","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average amount of work hours spent producing tendering documents for Government contracts above the level specified by the Official Journal of the European Union is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67482","67482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710441","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2017 to Question 66275, on electoral register: disability, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that accessible information on the forthcoming local and mayoral elections is made available for people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67539","67539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710442","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been registered as self-employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67658","67658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710443","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are registered as self-employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67659","67659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710444","2017-03-16","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average salary of full-time equivalent employees was in East Ham constituency in April of each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67674","67674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710445","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) women and (b) men paid Class 4 national insurance contributions; and what the average amount paid was in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67673","67673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710446","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total value of receipts from stamp duty land tax in England was in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15, (d) 2015-16 and (e) 2016-17; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67675","67675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710447","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Hendon constituency his Department estimates will be affected by the proposed increase to Class 4 national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67683","67683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710448","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much he expects the higher rate of stamp duty land tax on additional properties to raise in each year from 2017-18 to 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67696","67696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710449","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many residential property transactions valued between (a) £125,000.01 and £250,000, (b) £250,000.01 and £925,000, (c) £925,000.01 and £1.5 million and (d) over £1.5 million there were in London in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014, (iv) 2015 and (v) 2016; and what the total Stamp Duty Land Tax revenue generated by those transactions was in each of those years by price band.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67561","67561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710450","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to provide guidance on changes to the flat rate VAT scheme.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67573","67573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710451","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax revenue has been generated from people encashing their pension entitlement since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67613","67613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710452","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost would be in the next financial year of raising the threshold at which people begin paying national insurance contributions (NICs) to £11,500; and how many employees would pay no tax or NICs in the event of that threshold being changed.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67615","67615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710453","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made in transposing into UK law the Fourth Money Laundering Directive.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67616","67616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710454","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2016 to Question 42176, on tax collection, for what reason technical risks not subject to litigation do not form part of the tax gap; and what proportion of unpaid corporation tax identified as technical risks not subject to litigation was collected by the Exchequer in the last two fiscal years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67540","67540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710455","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many additional residential property transactions valued between (a) £125,000.01 and £250,000, (b) £250,000.01 and £925,000, (c) £925,000.01 and £1.5 million and (d) over £1.5 million there have been in St Albans district since 2012; and what the total Stamp Duty Land Tax revenue generated by those transactions was in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014, (iv) 2015 and (v) 2016 by price band.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67559","67559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710456","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many residential property transactions valued between (a) £125,000.01 and £250,000, (b) £250,000.01 and £925,000, (c) £925,000.01 and £1.5 million and (d) over £1.5 million there have been in St Albans district since 2012; and what the total Stamp Duty Land Tax revenue generated by those transactions was in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014, (iv) 2015 and (v) 2016 by price band.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67560","67560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710457","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of Stamp Duty Land Tax receipts has been in St Albans district in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15, (d) 2015-16 and (e) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67562","67562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710458","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.17 of Budget 2017, what estimate the Government has made of the number of public houses which will be eligible for the £1,000 business rate discount in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67579","67579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710459","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding announced in Budget 2017 the Government plans to provide to help pubs with the effect on the business rate review; and on what basis that funding will be distributed among those pubs.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67580","67580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710460","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many additional residential property transactions valued between (a) £125,000.01 and £250,000, (b) £250,000.01 and £925,000, (c) £925,000.01 and £1.5 million and (d) over £1.5 million there were in London in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014, (iv) 2015 and (v) 2016; and what the total Stamp Duty Land Tax Revenue generated by those transactions was in each of those years by price band.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67563","67563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710461","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of Stamp Duty Land Tax receipts in London from additional residential properties has been in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15, (d) 2015-16 and (e) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67564","67564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710462","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Stamp Duty Land Tax receipts in London were in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15, (d) 2015-16 and (e) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67565","67565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710463","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the stamp duty land tax receipts from additional residential properties in St Albans District were in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15, (d) 2015-16 and (e) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67566","67566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710464","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to reform the minimum income floor in universal credit for self-employed people as a result of the planned increase in Class 4 national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67497","67497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710465","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to improve the access of self-employed people to a mortgage.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67498","67498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710466","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to ensure that more self-employed people pay into a private pension scheme.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67499","67499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710467","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the start-up period under universal credit exempting self-employed people from the minimum income floor in their first year of trading.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67500","67500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710468","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending provisions for voluntary contributions within Class 4 national insurance contributions to cover (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) statutory maternity pay and (c) other benefits.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67501","67501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710469","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on Welsh Government funding of changes to the personal injury discount rate.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67506","67506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710470","2017-03-15","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67471","67471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710471","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on behalf of the Roadchef Employee Benefits Trust; and if he will meet the beneficiaries of that Trust.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67453","67453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710472","2017-03-16","HM Treasury","2017-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people paying Class 4 national insurance contributions in (a) Coventry South constituency and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67530","67530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710473","2017-03-16","Church Commissioners","2017-03-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what progress has been made by the Church Commissioners in facilitating new housing and school facilities at (a) Phase 2 Paston Reserve, Peterborough and (b) Norwood, Peterborough; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67529","67529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710474","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations he has received on the effect of Section 24 of the Finance (No. 2) Act 2015 on private renters.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67549","67549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710475","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the reasons are for the time taken to appoint legal representatives to facilitate the transfer of land for new homes and a secondary school in Paston Reserve, Peterborough; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67551","67551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710476","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67456","67456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710477","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information he holds on when the Homes and Communities Agency (HCA) will put in place legal agreements to facilitate the transfer of (a) HCA land to Peterborough City Council for the purposes of constructing a new secondary school and (b) adjacent land to developers for the construction of new homes at Paston Reserve, Peterborough; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67533","67533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710478","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Help to Rent schemes piloted by his Department in 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67617","67617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710479","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 5.5 of Spring Budget 2017, what estimate his Department has made of how much of the additional £2 billion of social care funding will be allocated to (a) Wolverhampton and (b) the West Midlands Combined Authority area.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67650","67650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710480","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 5.5 of Spring Budget 2017, how much of the additional £2 billion of social care funding will be allocated to (a) Greater London and (b) the London Borough of Newham.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67649","67649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710481","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of businesses that will pay increased business rates in Hendon constituency after the business rate re-evaluation exercise.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67602","67602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710482","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what policies to encourage the provision of apprenticeships by organisations in receipt of Homes and Communities Agency funding (a) are currently in operation and (b) have been in operation at any point since 2009 but are no longer in operation.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67595","67595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710483","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will provide financial support to bring back into use derelict properties in Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67600","67600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710484","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce proposals to fund large scale replacement and redevelopment of housing in areas with high vacancy rates and high numbers of derelict properties.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67601","67601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710485","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether safeguards are in place in blocks of flats containing between three and six properties to ensure that one leaseholder does not coerce others into a Right to Manage scheme at the expense of the freeholder and the upkeep of that building.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67574","67574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710486","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the level of future demand for social care in Wolverhampton; and what estimate his Department has made of the financial cost of that care.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67586","67586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710487","2017-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what share of the £300 million in discretionary relief for business rate hard cases will be provided to businesses in Bermondsey and Old Southwark constituency.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67670","67670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710488","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 65508, on council tax: Dorset,  how the level of council tax will be determined in the absence of enforcement by the local councils concerned.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67653","67653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710489","2017-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 66171, on local government: Dorset, by what means interested parties will be able to ascertain what the last date is for further representations to be made; and how much notice will be given to those parties of that date.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67654","67654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710490","2017-03-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to make it an offence to sell or attempt to sell a ticket for more than its original cost price.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67691","67691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710491","2017-03-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of the Discover England Fund has been allocated to (a) the North East, (b) Country Durham and (c) Easington constituency since that fund was established.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67685","67685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710492","2017-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what consultation the Government undertook with the Welsh Government before deciding not to appoint a representative for Wales on the BBC Board.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67587","67587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710493","2017-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the new timetable is for the appointment of the representative for Wales on the BBC Board.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67588","67588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710494","2017-03-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what conditions the Arts Council places on funding for the Royal Opera House, the Royal Ballet and the Orchestra of the Royal Opera House to increase participation in the arts and conduct outreach work in the regions.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67599","67599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710495","2017-03-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66308, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of full-time social action on youth voter engagement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67607","67607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710496","2017-03-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66308, whether the review of full-time social action by young people will consider the implications of full-time social action on young voter engagement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67608","67608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710497","2017-03-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many and what proportion of people employed by her Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67457","67457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710498","2017-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67458","67458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710499","2017-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2017 to Question 66499, on Egypt: armed forces, how many of those service personnel are involved in operation in Yemen.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67541","67541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710500","2017-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to award contracts for the Power Improvement Project for the Type 45 destroyer class.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67575","67575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710501","2017-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many main battle tanks are deployable on NATO's eastern flank by (a) NATO and (b) Russia.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67672","67672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710502","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the (a) gain and (b) loss of funding for each primary school in (i) Wolverhampton North East constituency and (ii) City of Wolverhampton local authority in (A) the first year, (B) two years and (C) five years after implementation of the new funding formula.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67680","67680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710503","2017-03-15","Department for Education","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that repayment terms will not be affected by the proposed sale of the student loans book for those paying off such loans.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67687","67687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710504","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate the Government's new schools funding formula has made of the level of deprivation in Wolverhampton North East constituency.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67589","67589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710505","2017-03-15","Department for Education","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 65926, on overseas students: loans, for what reasons the amount lent in 2015-16 was greater than that lent in 2014-15; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67603","67603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710506","2017-03-15","Department for Education","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 65926, on overseas students: loans, what proportion of the 2.8 per cent of borrowers resident overseas are (a) British, (b) EU and (c) non-EU nationals; and what the total value of the amount lent to borrowers resident overseas is.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67604","67604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710507","2017-03-16","Department for Education","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an estimate of the increase in the number of children who will be eligible for the new offer of free travel to their closest selective school compared to the previous offer.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67583","67583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710508","2017-03-15","Department for Education","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of people employed by her Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67459","67459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710509","2017-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of people employed by her Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67460","67460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710510","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the need for more staff in her Department to deal with the effects of the UK leaving the EU on farming and fishing.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67534","67534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710511","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the role of the Scottish Government is in her Department's EU exit programme workstream on devolution.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67535","67535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710512","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consultation her Department has had with the devolved administrations on the 25-year plan for food and farming.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67552","67552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710513","2017-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the importance of street trees in reducing urban pollution; and what plans she has to increase the number of street trees in the forthcoming air quality plan being prepared by her Department.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67507","67507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710514","2017-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help those local authorities most affected by ash dieback.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67508","67508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710515","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she next plans to meet her counterparts in the Scottish Government to discuss the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the rural economy.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67536","67536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710516","2017-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to plant non-woodland trees to replace those trees lost to ash dieback.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67645","67645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710517","2017-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to introduce legislation reducing the maximum number of dog litters bred for sale from four to two a year.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67641","67641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710518","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 67200, on marine environment: microplastics, if her Department will assess the effect of microplastics entering the environment on animal welfare.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67637","67637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710519","2017-03-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to reform the model of funding for greyhound racing.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67697","67697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710520","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department estimates will be spent on flood prevention in Ribble Valley constituency over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67701","67701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710521","2017-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to reduce marine environment pollution caused by sewage processing.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67694","67694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710522","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department estimates will be spent on flood prevention in Lancashire over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67702","67702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710523","2017-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to reduce roadside littering; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67695","67695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710524","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 67199, if her Department will publish the results of her Department's consultation on the proposals to ban microbeads in cosmetics and personal care products and the evidence under review.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67656","67656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710525","2017-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, in how many years since 2010 (a) Greater London and (b) the UK has been in breach of EU air pollution levels.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67665","67665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710526","2017-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2017 to Question 66551, for what reasons the Government has not yet ratified the Protocol V of the Convention on Certain Conventional Weapons.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67660","67660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710527","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2017 to Question 60259, how much his Department spent on Iraq through the Conflict, Security and Stability Fund in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67646","67646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710528","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 64413, if he will make representations to President Mahmoud Abbas on his posing with a photograph of Dalal Mughrabi.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67669","67669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710529","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Government of Albania on the extent of Russian influence in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67678","67678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710530","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the humanitarian situation in Myanmar since publication on 3 February 2017 of a report by the Office of the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights on the rights of the Rohingya.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67692","67692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710531","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with counterparts in other countries, excluding those in Myanmar, on the human rights situation in Myanmar since the publication on 3 February 2017 of a report by the UN High Commissioner on the Rohingya.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67690","67690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710532","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total amount of funding his Department received from the (a) Conflict, Stability and Security Fund and (b) Prosperity Fund was for the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67558","67558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710533","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of how the recently amended Entry to Israel Law will affect UK citizens travelling to Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67572","67572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710534","2017-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in Sudan on the reported decision by the Sudanese Government to order the demolition of up to 27 places of worship.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67612","67612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710535","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in Myanmar since the publication of the report by the Office of the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights on the Rohingya on 3 February 2017.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67509","67509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710536","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in which countries his Department spent funds allocated from the (a) Conflict, Stability and Security Fund and (b) Prosperity Fund in 2016-17.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67568","67568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710537","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which projects were funded by his Department from the (a) Conflict, Stability and Security Fund and (b) Prosperity Fund in 2016-17.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67569","67569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710538","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the total amount to be spent by his Department in 2016-17 which will count towards the target of 0.7 per cent of gross national income spent on official development assistance.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67567","67567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710539","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to table 1.6 of Budget 2017, Departmental Resource Budgets, what proportion of his Department's estimated resource budget for (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20 consists of funding allocated from the (i) Conflict, Stability and Security and (ii) Prosperity Funds.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67582","67582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710540","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether funds spent by his Department as part of the annual 0.7 per cent of gross national income spend on official development assistance must comply with the purpose of poverty reduction set out in the International Development Act 2002.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67557","67557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710541","2017-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in Bangladesh; and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67531","67531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710542","2017-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67462","67462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710543","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to require clinical commissioning groups to transfer areas of work from GPs to pharmacists where there is evidence that such a transfer would be more efficient.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67448","67448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710544","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to require clinical commissioning groups in England to include a representative of local pharmacists on their governing boards.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67449","67449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710545","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what cost-benefit assessment he has made of GPs in England providing regular asthma testing for patients.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67450","67450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710546","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67463","67463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710547","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NHS Staff Survey results for 2016, what assessment his Department has made of the risks to patients of NHS staff reporting for work despite not feeling well enough to perform their duties.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67454","67454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710548","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken by (a) his Department, (b) the Medical and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency and (c) Public Health England to encourage research into the use of e-cigarettes.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67483","67483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710549","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of cardiologists.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67532","67532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710550","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people at NHS England are working on the development of NHS England's updated regime for the second phase of device procurement.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67485","67485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710551","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask NHS England to publish the sources of data used by clinical reference groups when drawing up their recommendations.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67484","67484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710552","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of women qualifying for free prescriptions who have requested prescriptions for sanitary products from their GP.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67493","67493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710553","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 122 of the NHS Atlas of Variation in Healthcare, published by Public Heath England in September 2016, what steps he is taking to encourage (a) clinical commissioning groups and (b) primary care clinicians to tackle variations in the provision of transcatheter aortic valve implantation procedures in (i) Rother Valley constituency and (ii) England.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67543","67543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710554","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of treating people who have inhaled nitrous oxide in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67526","67526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710555","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will cease his Department's budget spending on tobacco control programmes abroad.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67538","67538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710556","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the average cost per person to the NHS of people suffering from (a) anxiety and (b) depression.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67523","67523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710557","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will set out whether returnship support announced in the Spring Budget 2017 will include measures to encourage women to return to medical practice as GPs.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67524","67524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710558","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of treatment provision for people diagnosed with cervical cancer.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67550","67550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710559","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the publication of the review of the diagnosis, treatment and transmission routes of Lyme disease announced in May 2016.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67553","67553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710560","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications for reviews of eligibility under the Pharmacy Access Scheme have been made by pharmacies in each parliamentary constituency in the UK; and how many applications (a) are being considered, (b) have been accepted and (c) have been rejected in each constituency.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67522","67522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710561","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of NHS care and support available to people who have been diagnosed with Lyme disease.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67554","67554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710562","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he made of the potential effect of reductions in community pharmacy funding on people (a) with legally protected characteristics and (b) living in the most deprived areas in England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67597","67597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710563","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of limiting the sugar content of milk-based drinks.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67594","67594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710564","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with Action on Smoking and Health on potential grant funding for 2017-18; and whether his Department has received a formal request for such funding from that organisation.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67626","67626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710565","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential link between the location of mobile telephone masts and the increased incidence of (a) cancers and (b) migraines.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67620","67620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710566","2017-03-16","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the teenage pregnancy rate was for (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottingham and (c) Nottinghamshire in (i) the most recent period for which figures are available and (ii) each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67621","67621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710567","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has received representations on the G4S Ambulance provision of the Barking, Havering and Redbridge University Hospitals Patient Transport Service; what guidance his Department provides to the NHS when outsourcing similar provisions on ensuring the safety and security of ambulance parking areas; and whether liability for damage to ambulances on the equipment they contain rests with the NHS or with companies to whom ambulance transport services are outsourced.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67605","67605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710568","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children have contracted meningitis in each of the last five years; and how many of those children have (a) died and (b) survived.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67642","67642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710569","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) the Royal College of Nursing and (b) health representative groups on the implications of sleeping patterns for diagnoses of dementia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67643","67643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710570","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the World Health Organisation has requested that his Department provide resources to assist in the implementation of the Framework Consultation on Tobacco Control in countries other than the UK.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67651","67651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710571","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) the Royal College of Nursing and (b) other health representative groups on the implications of gum disease for diagnoses of diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67644","67644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710572","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which countries officials of his Department have visited to assist the World Health Organisation in implementing the Framework Consultation on Tobacco Control in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67652","67652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710573","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in the UK have contracted mycolobacterium chimera in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67639","67639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710574","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been infected by using a catheter in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67640","67640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710575","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 65608, whether his Department will assess the merits of collecting data on average waiting times for children seeking access to assessment for a ketogenic diet for the treatment of epilepsy.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67700","67700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710576","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance is given to NHS ambulance trusts on (a) how often ambulances should be replaced and (b) the risks of not replacing ambulances within any such specified timeframes.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67693","67693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710577","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had tinnitus in the UK in each of the last five years; and what the cost was to the NHS of treating tinnitus in each of those years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67679","67679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710578","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant the Answer of 18 November 2016 to Question 52951, on WHO Framework Convention on Tobacco Control, which countries received direct country support funded by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67655","67655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710579","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 67201, if his Department will make an assessment of the implications of micropastics entering the marine environment for human health.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67657","67657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710580","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents of violence have been reported by acute adult mental health wards in (a) England and Wales and (b) the Barnet, Enfield and Haringey Mental Health Trust area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67662","67662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710581","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions the police have been called to deal with incidents of violence in acute adult mental health wards in (a) England and Wales and (b) the Barnet, Enfield and Haringey Mental Health Trust area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67663","67663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710582","2017-03-16","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many teenage pregnancies there have been in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67671","67671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710583","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the oral contribution of Lord Prior of Brampton of 4 July 2016, House of Lords, Official Report, column 1828, on Public Health England being commissioned to update its evidence report on e-cigarettes annually until the end of the current Parliament, when Public Health England plans to publish its next evidence report.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67667","67667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710584","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many standard visitor visas to the UK were (a) granted and (b) refused, in each month since January 2016 for (i) Bangladeshi, (ii) Indian, (iii) Pakistani and (iv) Sri Lankan citizens.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67676","67676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710585","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 65944, on asylum, for what reasons her Department does not record that data; for what reasons the target was set at 28 days; and by what measure targets on asylum seekers' access to benefits, employment and accommodation are met.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67686","67686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710586","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 65944, on asylum, for what reasons her Department set a 19-day target within which asylum seekers should move from initial accommodation to dispersed accommodation; and how her Department records the transfer of asylum seekers to dispersed accommodation from initial accommodation.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67688","67688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710587","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants failed the Life in the UK Test in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67631","67631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710588","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Forced Marriage Unit Statistics 2016, published on 9 March 2017, what steps she is taking to ensure that police forces in England and Wales can recognise the signs of forced marriage.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67633","67633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710589","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Forced Marriage Unit Statistics 2016, published on 9 March 2017, what steps she is taking to prevent children under the age of 16 from becoming victims of forced marriage.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67628","67628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710590","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Forced Marriage Unit Statistics 2016, published on 9 March 2017, what representations the Government has made to the Government of Pakistan on that country's connection with forced marriage in the UK.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67634","67634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710591","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Forced Marriage Unit Statistics 2016, published on 9 March 2017, what assessment she has made of the ability of the police to identify men at risk of or male victims of forced marriage.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67629","67629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710592","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Forced Marriage Unit Statistics 2016, published on 9 March 2017, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office on encouraging other countries to strengthen their laws and policing to prevent forced marriage.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67635","67635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710593","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Forced Marriage Unit Statistics 2016, published on 9 March 2017, what steps she is taking to prevent people with learning disabilities from becoming victims of forced marriage.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67636","67636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710594","2017-03-16","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether EU citizens exercising their treaty rights as a (a) jobseeker, (b) worker, (c) self-employed person, (d) self-sufficient person or (e) student are required to have comprehensive health insurance in order to receive free NHS treatment.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67619","67619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710595","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 65370, on asylum: advisory services, what steps her Department took to monitor the work of Asylum Support Medical Advisers (ASMAs); what the status is of the current review of her Department's relationship with ASMAs; who is being consulted as part of that review; and when that review is due to be completed.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67609","67609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710596","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to monitor the compliance of internet suppliers of nitrous oxide with their obligations under the Intoxicating Substances (Supply) Act 1985.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67625","67625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710597","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional resources and funding her Department has been allocated to enable (a) processing permanent residency claims of EU nationals living in the UK and (b) other work as a result of the decision for the UK to leave the EU in the next two years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67591","67591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710598","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, at what stage the infringement proceedings against the UK launched by the European Commission under Article 258 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union on 11 June 2011 are.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67592","67592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710599","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether EU nationals studying in the UK at an (a) undergraduate, (b) post-graduate and (c) doctoral or PhD level are classified as economically non-active as it relates to the need for comprehensive sickness insurance during the time when they reside in the UK (i) for the purposes of applications for permanent residency and (ii) in accordance with Article 7 (1)(b) of Directive 2004/38/ EC if they (A) are and (B) are not affiliated with the NHS.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67593","67593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710600","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many local authorities approached her Department to support children under the Dubs scheme; and how many of those authorities have or are due to support children under that scheme.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67511","67511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710601","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training is provided to those who handle and process evidence for asylum claimants who are survivors of torture.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67518","67518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710602","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many constituent inquiries lodged with the UK Visas and Immigration office in the Scotland and Northern Ireland Account Management Team originated in Glasgow Central constituency.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67555","67555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710603","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many crimes have been committed by drivers of private hire vehicles in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67525","67525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710604","2017-03-16","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children under 14 in England and Wales hold certificates that allow them to use shotguns under the supervision of an adult.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67527","67527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710605","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for permanent residency made by (a) non-UK EU nationals and (b) non-EU nationals were processed within official target times in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67542","67542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710606","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to review previous signed deportation orders concerning EU citizens imprisoned in the UK in cases which the person concerned is still awaiting removal.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67576","67576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710607","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of people employed by her Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67464","67464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710608","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for permanent residency from EU citizens were successful (a) before and (b) after 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67445","67445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710609","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to expedite the process of permanent residency applications from nationals of other EU member states.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67446","67446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710610","2017-03-15","Home Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ensure there are sufficient staff in her Department to process the increase in applications for permanent residency in the UK from citizens of other EU member states.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67447","67447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710611","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has made an estimate of the value of UK humanitarian aid to Yemen that has been prevented from entering Yemen by the Saudi-led coalition in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67451","67451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710612","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the value of UK humanitarian aid to Yemen that has been prevented from entering Yemen by Houthi forces in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67452","67452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710613","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many and what proportion of people employed by her Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67465","67465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710614","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what school or nutrition programmes for children in Africa specifically linked to locally produced foods and agroecological production her Department supports.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67494","67494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710615","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's overseas aid supports research and development of agroecological farming in Africa.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67495","67495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710616","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, (a) how much and (b) what proportion of her Department's overseas aid is used to support food production in Africa.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67496","67496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710617","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that UK aid to Myanmar reaches the Rohingya people in the Rakhine State.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67510","67510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710618","2017-03-15","Department of Health","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government will adopt the recommendation from the High Level Meeting of the General Assembly on Anti-Microbial Resistance for research and development to be guided by principles of affordability in relation to the Ross Fund.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67610","67610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710619","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department plans to take to support the comprehensive sexual and reproductive health rights of those people affected by the US Administration's Mexico City policy.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67611","67611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710620","2017-03-15","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Government and Civil Society programme run by her Department in Myanmar.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67689","67689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710621","2017-03-16","Department for International Development","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that UK international development aid is not spent on the promotion of terrorism.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67699","67699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710622","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the prisons budget was spent on prisoners' (a) education, (b) healthcare and (c) rehabilitation in 2015-16.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67677","67677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710623","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for (a) personal independence payments, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) incapacity benefit, (d) disability living allowance and (e) disability living allowance for adults that were refused at mandatory consideration were (i) appealed, (ii) subsequently overturned at tribunal and (iii) dismissed at tribunal in (A) Blackburn constituency, (B) local authorities in Lancashire and (C) the UK in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67668","67668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710624","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 65939, whether she plans that prisoners following a prison education regime will be tested in line with the core common curriculum set nationally by accredited examination boards; and whether it is her policy that the results of prisoner examinations at GCSE or A-level will be considered in national education averages and in national examination grade curves.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67630","67630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710625","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what sentencing guidelines have been put in place to deal with people who repeatedly offend in relation to (a) possession of and (b) threatening with a bladed article or offensive weapon.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67546","67546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710626","2017-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much her Department has spent on utility bills in prisons which have been officially closed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67528","67528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710627","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people employed by her Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67467","67467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710628","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps Sodexo has taken to address the issue of unfit accommodation at HM Prison Northumberland.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67486","67486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710629","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of alleged contractual breaches by (a) Sodexo Justice Services and (b) Novus at HM Prison Northumberland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67487","67487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710630","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she has taken to ensure that inmates at HM Prison Northumberland are receiving educational services; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67488","67488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710631","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hearings and trials involving a video link or similar technology in the last year experienced problems related to that technology; and what the estimated cost was of those disruptions.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67489","67489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710632","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps Sodexo has taken to address allegations of drug use and violence within HM Prison Northumberland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67490","67490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710633","2017-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hearings and trials across the HM Courts and Tribunal Service estate used a video link or similar technology in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67491","67491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710634","2017-03-15","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67468","67468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710635","2017-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what work the British-Irish Council will undertake during the period before the restoration of devolved government in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67614","67614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710636","2017-03-15","Cabinet Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people who work in 10 Downing Street are not employed in the Civil Service.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67648","67648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710637","2017-03-15","Scotland Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67469","67469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710638","2017-03-15","Department for Transport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of people employed by his Department are from other EU countries.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67470","67470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710639","2017-03-15","Department for Transport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to address the fact that Network Rail did not deliver the Great Western electrification scheme on time.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67577","67577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710640","2017-03-15","Department for Transport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has commissioned into what proportion of bus (a) drivers and (b) workers are non-UK EU nationals.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67519","67519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710641","2017-03-15","Department for Transport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 64008, on Driver Vehicle Licensing Agency, how much was paid by each local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67513","67513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710642","2017-03-15","Department for Transport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what rail infrastructure investment was in the South West region from 1997-98 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67647","67647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710643","2017-03-15","Department for Transport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which contracts issued by his Department or its executive agencies are held by (a) Balfour Beatty, (b) Mott MacDonald and (c) Balfour Beatty Mott MacDonald joint venture.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67666","67666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710644","2017-03-15","Department for Transport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of level crossing safety in Bassetlaw constituency.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67682","67682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710645","2017-03-16","Department for Transport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the London and South Coast Rail Corridor Study, published on 2 March 2017, what further work his Department has agreed should be undertaken in relation to Network Rail's plans to upgrade the Brighton Main Line through its proposals in the Croydon area; and what estimate he has made of the time that will be taken to carry out that work.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67584","67584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710646","2017-03-15","Department for Transport","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the Dutch Reach method of opening car doors on the safety of cyclists.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67578","67578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710647","2017-03-15","Wales Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Department for Work and Pensions on proposed jobcentre closures in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67515","67515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710648","2017-03-15","Wales Office","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on proposed changes to national insurance contributions for the self-employed in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67517","67517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710649","2017-03-16","Women and Equalities","2017-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what information she holds on who made the decision at the Equality and Human Rights Commission to dismiss 10 employees at short notice in February 2017; what representations she has received on those dismissals; and whether she has discussed the reasons for the selection of those so dismissed with that Commission.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67623","67623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710650","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the reasons are for there being a difference in the level of entitlement depending on date of claim for existing employment and support allowance (ESA) claimants entitled to the former work-related activity group rate and the new ESA claimants who will receive a reduced rate.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67622","67622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710651","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to monitor the performance of Atos in conducting personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67632","67632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710652","2017-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will review and enhance statutory protections in the labour market for women who are pregnant or have recently given birth.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67638","67638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710653","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that pension providers simplify, expedite and ensure the security of transfer between providers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67606","67606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710654","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of recording all personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67684","67684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710655","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to improve training in conditions with fluctuating symptoms of healthcare professionals undertaking assessments for disability benefits.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67520","67520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710656","2017-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of the 2 March 2017 to Question 65538, on personal independence payment, if he will assess the potential merits of the  personal independence payment assessment guide to permit claimants' companions to provide an account of the claimant's health condition or impairment in cases where that claimant has speech or hearing problems.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67548","67548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710657","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many application fees to the Child Maintenance Service have been refunded after it became clear that the parent with care was a victim of domestic violence in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67512","67512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710658","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on proposed jobcentre closures in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67516","67516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/710659","2017-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with epilepsy have (a) had their personal independence payment award decreased or disallowed following disability living allowance reassessments in (i) each year before and (ii) the period since November 2016 and (b) successfully appealed a disability living allowance reassessment where their award was decreased or disallowed.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 67503","67503"
