"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917079","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Cameroonian counterpart on respect for human rights of the Anglophone communities in that country.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149710","149710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917080","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing overnight seizure monitoring devices for epilepsy patients.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149711","149711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917081","2018-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of crown guaranteed pension schemes that operate under the pension protection fund; and if she will provide (a) a list of the names of those schemes, (b) details of the crown guarantee liability and (c) the date when those schemes entered that fund.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149712","149712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917082","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the contribution of prescription charges to the public purse in 2017-18.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149677","149677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917083","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the contribution to the public purse of prescription charges from people who paid for four or more prescriptions 2017-18.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149678","149678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917084","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has assessed the number of NHS employees (a) who work while being sick enough to stay at home and (b) the potential effect of that practice on the NHS.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149664","149664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917085","2018-06-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 136508, what proportion of the Medical Research Council's budget was spent on mental health research in 2017-18.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149626","149626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917086","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to implement the recommendations of the independent review of community pharmacy clinical services commissioned by the NHS.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149705","149705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917087","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to roll-out a minor ailments scheme through community pharmacies as recommended by the independent review of community pharmacy clinical services.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149706","149706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917088","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of community pharmacist supplementary and independent prescribing clinics in Scotland for England.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149707","149707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917089","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the merits of proposals to permit community pharmacists to identify and manage uncomplicated cases of hypertension  as part of the forthcoming community pharmacy funding negotiations.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149708","149708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917090","2018-06-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he had with (a) workers, (b) trade unions and (c) employers in advance of the Government's annual advertising campaign to encourage workers to take action if they are not receiving the national living wage or the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149680","149680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917091","2018-06-06","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of including information on stem cell donation in the national curriculum.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149684","149684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917092","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, to what financial support his Department has provided to projects that collaborate with international stem cell donor banks to diversify the UK's stem cell donor register.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149685","149685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917093","2018-06-07","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to respond to the letter of 18 May from the hon. Member for Greenwich and Woolwich on The John Roan School, Royal Borough of Greenwich.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149693","149693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917094","2018-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to bring air pollution within legal limits in (a) West Midlands; (b) Coventry and (c) Coventry South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149591","149591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917095","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many gambling addiction treatment services there are in (a) Merseyside, (b) Wirral and (c) Wallasey constituency; and whether his Department has plans to increase provision of those services.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149612","149612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917096","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to encourage BAME people to sign up to the stem cell donor register.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149695","149695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917097","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many in-patient eating disorder beds have been available at Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust for (a) adults and (b) children in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149613","149613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917098","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  how much funding has been allocated to Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust for the provision of mental health services in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149614","149614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917099","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many walk-in centres have closed in (a) the North West, (b) Merseyside and (c) Wirral since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149615","149615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917100","2018-06-07","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on its negotiations with East Midlands Trains on compensation payments as a result of peak-time trains not stopping at Bedford.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149696","149696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917101","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the potential effect of the proposed works to Bromham Road bridge on journey times for passengers travelling on the replacement bus service from Wellingborough to Bedford.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149697","149697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917102","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train services from Bedford to London have not stopped at West Hampstead since 20 May 2018; and what discussions he has had with Govia Thameslink on those services no longer stopping at West Hampstead.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149698","149698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917103","2018-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2018 to Question 142352 on Personal Independence Payment, for what reasons that information is not held centrally.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149616","149616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917104","2018-06-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have undertaken unpaid work trials in 2017-18.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149681","149681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917105","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to address the findings of the Anthony Nolan Trust on the comparatively low survival rates for people with blood cancer from BAME backgrounds.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149686","149686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917106","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to provide information on (a) blood, (b) stem cell and (c) organ donation to enable young people to make informed choices on being a donor.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149687","149687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917107","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many walk-in centres have closed in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149592","149592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917108","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding has been allocated to University Hospitals Coventry and Warwickshire NHS Trust for the provision of mental health services in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149593","149593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917109","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many in-patient eating disorder beds there have been for (a) adults and (b) children in University Hospitals Coventry and Warwickshire NHS Trust in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149594","149594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917110","2018-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Nigerian counterpart on reports of violence and the destruction of churches in northern Nigeria.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149572","149572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917111","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many addiction treatment services there are for gambling in (a) the West Midlands, (b) Coventry and (c) the Coventry South constituency; and whether he plans to increase the provision of those services.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149595","149595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917112","2018-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of protections on discrimination against religious minorities in the northern and central states of Nigeria.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149573","149573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917113","2018-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of reports that Nigeria’s armed forces may be complicit in attacks by Fulani militia on communities in northern Nigeria.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149574","149574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917114","2018-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of (a) violence and (b) disturbance there has been in each prison since the implementation of the smoking ban.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149636","149636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917115","2018-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of violence in prisons between (a) inmates and (b) inmates and prison staff since the implementation of the ban on tobacco.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149637","149637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917116","2018-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons that have implemented a ban on smoking tobacco have put in place special measures including increased security to manage prisoners’ behaviour.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149638","149638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917117","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what criteria his Department uses to call in major planning applications in London.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149584","149584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917118","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to make a decision on whether to call in the application by  VCI Property Holdings to develop the island site at Vauxhall Cross.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149585","149585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917119","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has plans to upgrade the A75 in Dumfries and Galloway.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149642","149642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917120","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with (a)  Mid and East Antrim Council and (b) the Dumfries and Galloway Council on the effect on the local economy of improvements on the A75.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149643","149643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917121","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time taken to process planning applications for shale gas extraction.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149644","149644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917122","2018-06-06","Church Commissioners","2018-06-04","To ask the Honourable Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, how much the Church of England spent on the employment tribunal involving Jeremy Pemberton; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149586","149586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917123","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average time taken to process a shale gas exploration application  was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149645","149645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917124","2018-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to ensure that the labelling on products containing palm oil specifies whether that palm oil was produced sustainably.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149688","149688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917126","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to Question 136374, tabled on 17 April 2017 by the hon. Member for Tottenham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149581","149581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917127","2018-06-07","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department plans to respond to the letters by the hon. Member for Tottenham to the Commonwealth Taskforce dated 24 April 2018, 30 April 2018, 8 May 2018, 9 May 2018, 11 May 2018 and 26 May 2018, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149582","149582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917128","2018-06-07","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Windrush cases has his Department (a) resolved and (b) not resolved within the two week target period.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149583","149583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917129","2018-06-07","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of students that have studied music at higher education establishments by ethnic group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149622","149622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917130","2018-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the Russian military threat in the High North.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149565","149565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917131","2018-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the security implications of climate change in the high north.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149566","149566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917132","2018-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of people entering courses at the Britannia Royal Naval College at Dartmouth in each of the last five years; and on which courses each of those enrolled.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149567","149567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917133","2018-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of people entering courses at the Royal Air Force College at Cranwell in each of the last five years; and on which courses each of those enrolled.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149568","149568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917134","2018-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of people entering courses at the Royal Military Academy at Sandhurst in each of the last five years; and on which courses each of those people enrolled.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149569","149569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917135","2018-06-07","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students (a) in total and (b) eligible for free school meals took GCSE Music in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149623","149623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917136","2018-06-07","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  how many students (a) in total and (b) eligible for free school meals took A Level Music in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149624","149624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917137","2018-06-07","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of students (a) in total and (b) eligible for free school meals who studied music in higher education in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149625","149625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917138","2018-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's Clean Growth Strategy, published in October 2017, what the timetable is for the establishment of the first forestry investment zone.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149587","149587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917139","2018-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish the areas of England that will be designated as forestry investment zones.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149588","149588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917140","2018-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's 25-Year Environment Plan, when he plans to appoint a national tree champion.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149589","149589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917141","2018-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to consult the Committee on Climate Change on the tree-planting targets required in England to meet the UK's climate change commitments.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149590","149590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917142","2018-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the the Scottish Government on protecting workers pensions after Crummock went into receivership.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149702","149702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917144","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the arable sector as the UK prepares to leave the EU.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149689","149689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917145","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made on the contribution of the arable sector to the economy in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149690","149690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917146","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the economic value of grain to the UK’s food supply chain.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149691","149691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917147","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the  Secretary of State for International Trade on the potential export market for UK grain after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149692","149692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917148","2018-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to meet staff representatives of the National Probation Service to discuss their pay and conditions.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149657","149657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917149","2018-06-07","Department for International Trade","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to ensure that information on licences granted by the Export Control Joint Unit is (a) accessible and (b) comprehensible to the public.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149658","149658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917150","2018-06-06","Treasury","2018-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of LINK’s proposed reduction in the ATM interchange fee on the ability of older people to access cash free of charge.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149703","149703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917151","2018-06-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2018 to Question 147814, if he will publish the (a) names and (b) registered postcode locations of the 190 theatres and touring companies into which £100 million of public money is being invested over four years.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149603","149603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917152","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on reciprocal healthcare arrangements with the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149673","149673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917153","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he make an estimate the merits of making free prescriptions available to all people with lifelong diseases.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149713","149713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917154","2018-06-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2018 to Question 147813 on Museums and Galleries: Closures, if he will publish the (a) names and (b) postcode locations of the 29 museums which gained museum accreditation from Arts Council England in 2017-18.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149604","149604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917155","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of UK residents that have travelled abroad for medical treatment in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149674","149674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917156","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have visited the UK for medical treatment in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149675","149675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917157","2018-06-06","Scotland Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on improving broadband (a) connections and (b) speeds in Scotland.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149704","149704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917158","2018-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 February 2018 to Question 128402, when the review of the Incentives and Earned Privileges scheme will conclude; and what steps are being taken to ensure that that scheme is not used as a determining factor for access to family days for any prisoner regardless of their gender.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149628","149628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917159","2018-06-07","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department’s consultation entitled Windrush compensation: call for evidence, published on 10 May 2018, what meetings he has had with black majority church leaders since announcing that review.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149668","149668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917160","2018-06-06","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department provides guidance to further education institutions on the sale of land for student accommodation to private developers.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149629","149629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917161","2018-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of personal independence payment decisions have been overturned at (a) the mandatory reconsideration, (b) the appeal and (c) any other stage as a result of information being incorrectly recorded during face-to-face consultations.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149619","149619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917162","2018-06-06","Treasury","2018-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to The Guardian article entitled Revealed: the developers cashing in on privatisation of student housing, published on 27 May 2018, what his Department's policy is on private providers of student accommodation using offshore companies to minimise their tax liability, and whether his Department is taking steps to limit that practice.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149630","149630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917163","2018-06-06","Treasury","2018-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the tax liabilities of (a) private companies and (b) overseas investors that collect rental income from student accommodation.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149631","149631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917164","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an estimate of the number of (a) private companies and (b) overseas investors that collect rental income from student accommodation.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149632","149632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917166","2018-06-07","Department for International Development","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2018 to Question 144381 on Developing Countries: Private Education, for what reason that Question could only be answered at disproportionate cost when such information was provided in the Answer of 17 November 2016 to Question 52765 on Developing Countries: Private Education.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149699","149699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917167","2018-06-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people were employed in the (a) cement production, (b) steel production and (c) sugar production industries in the UK for each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149639","149639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917168","2018-06-07","Department for International Development","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that existing Save the Children projects continue following the decision of that organisation not to bid for further UK funds.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149700","149700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917169","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish his Department’s action plan for carers.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149627","149627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917170","2018-06-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what research his Department has undertaken on the factors responsible for the recent increase in coal consumption globally; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149640","149640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917171","2018-06-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in other governments on the UK supplying coal for their domestic power, steel and cement markets after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149641","149641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917172","2018-06-07","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education for what reasons the Post-16 skills plan for (a) protective services, (b) sales, marketing and procurement, (c) Social Care and (d) transport and Logistics will be delivered primarily through apprenticeships.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149665","149665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917173","2018-06-07","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) current year 9 learners and (b) future cohorts are aware of T-levels.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149666","149666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917174","2018-06-07","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that T-levels enable learners to move between disciplines as their priorities and interests change.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149667","149667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917175","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on the establishment of private car parks in retail areas.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149682","149682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917176","2018-06-07","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) police officers, and (b) PSCOs funded by Government in each (i) police authority area, (ii) local authority area, and (iii) Welsh parliamentary constituency in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149620","149620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917177","2018-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copies of the (a) guidance and (b) procedures his Department has issued to tackle long waiting times for personal independence payment appeal tribunal dates.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149621","149621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917178","2018-06-07","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many responses his Department has received to its consultation paper entitled Windrush compensation, published on 10 May 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149669","149669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917179","2018-06-07","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for his Department's response to its consultation on Windrush compensation.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149670","149670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917180","2018-06-07","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 May 2018 to Question 138436 on Immigrants: Caribbean, how many outreach community ambassadors have carried out that activity.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149671","149671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917181","2018-06-07","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Answer of 4 May 2018 to Question 138436 on Immigrants: Caribbean, how many African Caribbean touch points were included in each of the five cities.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149672","149672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917182","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many rest days are owed to police officers by forces in England and Wales  as at 1 June 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149618","149618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917183","2018-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many veterans have paid solicitors to represent them at tribunals to challenge decisions made under the Armed Forces Compensation Scheme since 2015.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149676","149676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917184","2018-06-06","Cabinet Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in how many marriages was the (a) woman or (b) man between the 16 and 18 years of age for each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149646","149646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917185","2018-06-06","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) women and (b) men who have progressed into higher and further education who were married before the age of 18 years for each year for which such information is available.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149647","149647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917186","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of marriages involving a party under the age of 16 years worldwide for each year that information is available.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149648","149648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917187","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his Department's policy is on police forces reporting the immigration status of victims of crime in relation to non-immigration related offences.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149649","149649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917188","2018-06-06","Cabinet Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of marriages involving a party under 18 years old in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149650","149650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917189","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data his Department collects on domestic abuse cases involving a male victim.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149651","149651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917190","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people entered the UK on a spousal visa and what the average age was of those applicants in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149652","149652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917191","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what statutory duties local authorities have to ensure the protection of (a) male and (b) female victims of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149715","149715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917192","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons (a) the Bridgewater NHS Trust's retinal screening staff administration team are being transferred to the private company Emis Care and (b) the timing is before the end of the contract due in to finish in April 2019.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149605","149605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917193","2018-06-07","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on the effect on local authority fire and rescue services of his Department's proposal to contract out the Defence Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149694","149694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917194","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 136485, what recent assessment he has made of the level of uptake and adoption of technology for reducing inadvertent dispensing errors in (a) pharmacies and (b) acute settings.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Sir Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149596","149596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917195","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 123567, if he will encourage the owners of pharmacies not meeting the standards set by the General Pharmaceutical Council to adopt technology for reducing inadvertent dispensing errors as part of their action plans to improve the services they provide and safeguard the health, safety and well-being of patients and the public.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Sir Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149597","149597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917196","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the publication of an updated five year antimicrobial resistance strategy.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Sir Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149598","149598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917197","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the availability of (a) effective and (b) up to day diagnostic equipment with 24-hour remote communication facilities in the reorganisation of microbiology laboratory services in the NHS.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Sir Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149599","149599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917198","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to SMI B 37: Investigation of blood cultures (for organisms other than Mycobacterium species), if he will make it his policy that each microbiology laboratory in the NHS undertakes an audit of their blood culture pathway to ensure effective antibiotic stewardship.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Sir Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149600","149600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917199","2018-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the maximum tonnage of waste is that the Viridor Energy is entitled to burn at its waste facility in Runcorn under its permit; and what the tonnage of waste is that is currently being burnt at that site.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149606","149606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917200","2018-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reason the composition of fuel being burned at the Viridor Runcorn Energy from Waste facility been allowed to be changed from that permitted under its original permit.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149607","149607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917201","2018-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Proposal to amend the Tribunal Procedure (First-Tier Tribunal) (Health, Education and Social Care Chamber) Rules 2008, published on 22 March 2018 by the Tribunal Procedure Committee, what estimate his Department has made of the potential savings to the public purse of the recommendations in that document of (a) abolishing pre-hearing examinations and (b) giving First-Tier Mental Health Tribunals the power to take decisions without an oral hearing where a patient has been automatically referred to a Tribunal.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149659","149659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917202","2018-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what number and proportion of patients discharged at tribunal (a) had and (b) had not received a pre-hearing examination in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149660","149660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917203","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons the NHS recruitment agency HCC is rejecting BCP, UKCP, and BACP accredited and registered child and adolescent psychotherapists for CAMHS roles.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149661","149661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917204","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hours of unpaid training a trainee child and young person’s psychotherapist has to undertake during their training period.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149662","149662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917205","2018-06-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much of the funding allocated to Future in Mind was spent in financial year 2017-18.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149663","149663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917206","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the potential to use Article 36 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the EU, which allows for trade restrictions on grounds of public morality among other reasons, to ban the import of animal fur while the UK is still a member of the Single Market.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149655","149655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917207","2018-06-07","House of Commons Commission","2018-06-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate has been made of the amount of money raised for charity from the change collection boxes at cash tills in catering outlets on the Parliamentary Estate.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149683","149683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917208","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 May 2018 to Question 143645, if he will (a) call for all charges against Noura Hussein to be dropped and (b) make further representations to the Sudanese authorities to that effect.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149656","149656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917209","2018-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her decision to amend the ordering restriction on the exemption from the two child limit for children in kinship care, whether she has plans to amend the ordering restriction on the exemption for children born as a result of non-consensual conception.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149575","149575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917210","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the (a) extent and (b) causes of regional variation in the proportion of deaths in hospital in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149608","149608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917211","2018-06-07","Department for International Trade","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of which non-EU markets have the greatest potential for increasing UK financial services exports after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149576","149576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917212","2018-06-06","Department for Education","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department provides to schools on the use and possession by pupils of smartphones and tablets (a) in schools and (b) during classes.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149714","149714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917213","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to allocate additional funding to local authorities who own aerodromes to release the economic potential of those facilities.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149562","149562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917214","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of people dying in hospital in areas where there is a high incidence of such deaths.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149609","149609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917215","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many commercial pilots were trained in the UK in each of the last five years of which information is available.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149563","149563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917216","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the number of pilots that are trained in the UK.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149564","149564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917217","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking taken to increase the provision of high quality end-of-life care.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149610","149610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917218","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how Sustainability and Transformation Partnerships plan to measure choice in end of life care in line with his Department's commitment in its 2018-19 mandate to NHS England.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149611","149611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917219","2018-06-07","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who the members of the Rail Industry Readiness Board are.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149570","149570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917220","2018-06-07","Department for Transport","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions in the last year he has met the rail Industry readiness Board.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149571","149571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917221","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if  she will ban the Al Quds march planned for Sunday 10 June as a result of the potential threat to public order.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149602","149602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917222","2018-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information he holds on the amount of litter that was dropped in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149634","149634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914701","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of requiring the labelling of alcoholic drinks to include information on calorie content, Chief Medical Officer low-risk drinking guidelines or other health information.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148863","148863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914702","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will take steps to introduce grants to support small-scale local food producers.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148864","148864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914703","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2018 to Question 136076, how many live music venues have closed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148865","148865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914704","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will publish further guidance to local authorities advising them of the benefits of street play for children and of the powers that local authorities have to permit road closures in residential areas for that purpose.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148866","148866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914705","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for how long her Department has required Access to Work claimants to provide invoices for the services of their self-employed support workers; and what guidance and notification was given to Access to Work claimants about that change of practice.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148867","148867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914706","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his oral contribution of 16 May 2018, Official Report, column 303, what plans his Department has to fund the first phase of the Metro West project, and (a) reopening of (b) the Portishead to Bristol line.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148868","148868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914707","2018-06-06","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2018 to Question 120514 on music education, if he will hold a public consultation on whether to change or extend the National Plan for Music Education.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148869","148869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914708","2018-06-06","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has taken to help ensure humanitarian and commercial access to all sea and air ports in Yemen.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148870","148870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914709","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is his Department's policy that EU residents who are acting as carers and will have been living in the UK lawfully and continuously for five years by 29 March 2019 will be considered as workers and able to apply for settled-status.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148588","148588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914710","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it his policy that EU residents who have disabilities and (a) have not been able to work, (b) have not worked sufficiently or continuously and (c) who might never work due to their disabilities but who will have been living in the UK lawfully and continuously for five years by 29 March 2019 will be able to apply for settled status.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148589","148589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914711","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 136434, for what reasons the answer to that question did not reference whether an impact assessment has been carried out on the effect on people with spinal cord injuries of the planned NHS Continuing Healthcare budget savings of £855 million by 2020-21.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148712","148712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914712","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Written Statement of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 20 October 2016, Official Report, column 971, for what reason the Government has not encouraged the national roll-out of the pharmacy minor ailments scheme with clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148839","148839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914713","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons independent community pharmacies and other  primary healthcare providers are designated as a public authority for the purpose of General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148840","148840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914714","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the total cost has been of GP patient surveys issued over the period of 2013 to 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148590","148590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914715","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the criminal charges issued by the Iranian authorities against BBC Persian staff; and what representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on that subject.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148591","148591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914716","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will personally raise the matter of criminal charges against BBC Persian staff during his next meeting with his Iranian counterpart or at the earliest opportunity.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148592","148592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914717","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to allow UK citizens currently residing in the EU to qualify for home-student tuition fees after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148593","148593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914718","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has plans to appoint a broadband consumer champion.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149100","149100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914719","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the recent delays at the Maritime and Coastguard Agency of six weeks in issuing a Coding Certificate for UK registered vessels.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149099","149099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914720","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many sexual assault referral centres offer therapeutic services for (a) adults and (b) children under 18.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148771","148771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914721","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many claims of sexual abuse within the NHS were made to the NHS Litigation Authority in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148772","148772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914722","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the marketing budget for Public Health England is being spent on (a) alcohol, (b) tobacco, (c) obesity and physical health, (d) sexual health and (e) drugs campaigns.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148773","148773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914723","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have met the Chief Medical Officer in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148827","148827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914724","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many claims of sexual harassment and abuse of patients by staff have been made in mental health inpatient wards in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148774","148774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914725","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to review the three-year time limit on legal action for clinical negligence claims against the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148710","148710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914726","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to establish consistency and clarity on the succession rights of remaining social housing tenants after the death of the secure tenant.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148785","148785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914727","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on developing improved fuel efficiency technologies for domestic shipping.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148586","148586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914728","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to introduce a modified generation license for storage to improve regulatory clarity.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148587","148587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914729","2018-06-05","Women and Equalities","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 24 May 2018 to Question 146160 on LGBT People: Surveys, whether she plans to include legislative proposals on gay conversion therapy in her Department’s LGBT Action Plan.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148680","148680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914730","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Iraq (a) Government bodies, (b) non-Governmental organisations, (c) parliamentary bodies and (i) UK and (ii) Iraq (d) research foundations and (e) training entities have contracts with the UK Government for the provision of services in Iraq (A) currently and (B) which were signed in the last two years; what sums have been made available for each such contract; and what the purpose is of each contract.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148627","148627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914731","2018-06-06","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the (a) start-up and (b) operation costs of the Government's rapid rebuttal unit; what the scope of that unit is; and what operations that unit has conducted so far.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148626","148626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914732","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been deported to Togo in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148614","148614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914733","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the prospects for a durable peace settlement to end the civil war in South Sudan following the Intergovernmental Authority on Development-mediated negotiations between the parties to that conflict.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148682","148682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914734","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of instances of (a) obstruction of free movement of UN peacekeepers and (b) other violations of the status of forces agreement between the UN and South Sudan by the Government of that country in (i) 2017 and (ii) 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148683","148683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914735","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to UN Security Council Resolution 2406, what steps the Government is taking to support the provision of technical advice and assistance to the Government and security forces of South Sudan on (a) compliance with international humanitarian law and (b) the investigation and prosecution of human rights abuses.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148684","148684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914736","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the merits of the August 2015 agreement on the resolution of the conflict in the Republic of South Sudan as a framework for ending the civil war in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148685","148685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914737","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether the composition of the Government of South Sudan constitutes a transitional government of national unity in accordance with the terms of the August 2015 agreement on the resolution of the conflict in the Republic of South Sudan.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148686","148686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914738","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress towards full deployment of the Regional Protection Force to South Sudan in accordance with UN Security Council Resolution 2304 of August 2016.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148687","148687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914739","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether 4,000 troops is the appropriate level for the Regional Protection Force in South Sudan; and what recent discussions he has had with the UN Secretary-General on the proposed number of troops to be deployed as part of that force.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148688","148688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914740","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Administration on its review of financial assistance to South Sudan; what information his Department holds on the options under consideration; and when he expects that review to be completed.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148689","148689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914741","2018-06-05","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent representations she has made to her counterpart in South Sudan on the protection of aid workers from violence in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148690","148690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914742","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the findings of the report on the right to freedom of opinion and expression in South Sudan since the July 2016 crisis, published by the UN Mission in South Sudan and the Office of the High Commissioner for Human Rights on 22 February 2018, what recent representations he has made to his South Sudanese counterpart on the importance of a free press.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148691","148691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914743","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of violations of the cessation-of-hostilities agreement on South Sudan since December 2017; and what information his Department holds on the number of such violations documented by the ceasefire transitional security arrangements monitoring mechanism to date.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148692","148692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914744","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts in (a) the Intergovernmental Authority on Development and (b) African Union member states on (i) the compliance of parties to the civil war in South Sudan with the cessation-of-hostilities agreement of December 2017 and (ii) the imposition of multilateral sanctions by those organisations against those responsible for violations of that agreement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148693","148693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914745","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to (a) his counterparts in the Intergovernmental Authority on Development member states and (b) officials from that organisation on the publication of all reports of the ceasefire transitional security arrangements monitoring mechanism on ceasefire violations since December 2017.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148694","148694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914746","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in South Sudan on  the establishment of a hybrid court; and when he expects that court to begin adjudicating cases of alleged war crimes and crimes against humanity in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148695","148695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914747","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government’s policy is on the establishment by the UN Security Council of an adhoc international tribunal in the event of a failure to establish hybrid court for South Sudan.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148696","148696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914748","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the August 2015 agreement on the resolution of the conflict in the Republic of South Sudan, what recent representations he has made to his South Sudanese counterpart on the establishment of (a) a national Commission for Truth Reconciliation and Healing and (b) a Compensation and Reparations Authority.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148697","148697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914749","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department’s policies of the findings of the Amnesty International report on human rights and the Nigerian military, They betrayed us, published in May.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148698","148698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914750","2018-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy of providing military assistance to the Nigerian armed forces of the Amnesty International Report, They betrayed us, published on 24 May 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148699","148699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914751","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Cameroonian counterpart on reports of forced repatriation of Nigerian refugees by the Government of that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148700","148700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914752","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps he has taken to tackle anti-social behaviour; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149084","149084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914753","2018-06-05","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is she taking to enable women and children to access education in developing countries.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149085","149085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914754","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2017 to Question 120087 on Ovarian Cancer, what the timetable is for a decision to be announced on the next round of cancer audits; and whether ovarian cancer will be included within those audits.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149057","149057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914755","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that ovarian cancer is either diagnosed or ruled out within 28 days.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149058","149058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914756","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of running an awareness campaign on the symptoms of ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149059","149059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914757","2018-06-06","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to commission a commemorative 50p coin to mark the UK leaving the EU on 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148989","148989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914758","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the average amount of time her Department has taken to respond to correspondence from (a) hon. Members and (b) hon. Members' offices over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149089","149089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914759","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government has a policy on the re-opening of Plymouth City Airport; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149090","149090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914760","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce funding for additional railway resilience work at Dawlish and Teignmouth.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149091","149091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914761","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reduce the rate of VAT charged on work to reclad tower blocks resulting from the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149092","149092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914762","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of VAT which will be accrued to the public purse from the £400m allocated by the Government to renew cladding on tower blocks that have failed fire safety tests.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149093","149093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914763","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions the power under section 41 of the Civil Aviation Act 1982 to acquire and manage land for any purpose connected to civil aviation has been used; and on what dates that power was exercised.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149094","149094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914764","2018-06-06","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Strategic Review of General Aviation, published by the Civil Aviation Authority in July 2006, whether his Department has conducted a review of whether the current VAT treatment applied to flight training places UK flying schools at a competitive disadvantage to those based in other countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148711","148711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914765","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent from the public purse to Arriva Rail North to reimburse or ameliorate net losses of the franchisee arising from industrial action.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148740","148740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914766","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of UK ODA spending has been spent on UN peacekeeping in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148703","148703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914767","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the reported cancellation of over 2,500 trains in April puts Arriva Rail North in default of its franchise obligations.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148741","148741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914768","2018-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to ensure that young cancer patients who are claiming personal independence payments can access financial support backdated from the day of their diagnosis.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148701","148701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914769","2018-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was from application to a decision being made for young people with cancer who applied for personal independence payments over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148702","148702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914770","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government has made available for research into knife crime prevention in the last two years; and how much funding is being made available in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148990","148990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914771","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with major car dealerships on promoting the sale of electric and other ultra-low emission vehicles.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148713","148713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914772","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many consumers eligible for the guarantee credit element of pension credit are customers of (a) energy suppliers with more than and (b) fewer than 250,000 customers.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149095","149095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914773","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many consumers in social grade DE are customers of (a) energy suppliers with more than and (b) fewer than 250,000 customers.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149096","149096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914774","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of whether there will be an increase in the number of people who will be ineligible to receive the discount on energy through the Warm Home Discount Scheme as more people are choosing to move from large to small energy suppliers.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149097","149097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914775","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated for arts and culture in Doncaster (a) in total, (b) per head of the local population and (c) per head in England for the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148667","148667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914776","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the per capita heritage lottery funding was in (a) Doncaster and (b) England in the last year for which data are available.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148668","148668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914777","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the per capita big lottery fund resource spending was in (a) in Doncaster and (b) England in the last year for which data are available.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148669","148669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914778","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people from the Doncaster North constituency entered higher education institutions in the latest year for which figures are available; and how that figure compares with other constituencies.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148670","148670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914779","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the most recent (a) youth unemployment, (b) unemployment and (c) employment rates are in Doncaster North constituency; and what proportion of the working age population are recipients of employment support allowance in that constituency.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148671","148671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914780","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people have received support through the Youth Obligation to date; and how many of those people have subsequently gone on to (a) an apprenticeship, (b) a traineeship and (c) a work placement.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148818","148818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914781","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of young people have stopped receiving benefits since being on the Youth Obligation programme.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148819","148819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914782","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people have been sanctioned while receiving support through the Youth Obligation programme.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148820","148820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914783","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support his Department has provided to (a) local authorities and (b) other providers to help them retrospectively fund sleep-in shifts at the national minimum wage rate.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148821","148821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914784","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of the Social Care Compliance Scheme participants that will cease to be viable by the completion of that scheme.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148822","148822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914785","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of the implementation of the new IT system ATLAS on the time taken for asylum seekers to access asylum support.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149079","149079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914786","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to resolve issues with the transition to the new IT system ATLAS.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149080","149080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914787","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to his Answer of 24 May 2018 to Question 146070 on immigration: EU nationals, how his Department will define what a standard application is in respect EU citizens applying for settled or temporary status.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148605","148605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914788","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 May 2018 to Question 146070 on immigration: EU nationals, what factors or variables might result in an application for settled or temporary status being considered non-standard.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148606","148606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914789","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether any arms licensed for export from the UK to Israel over the last three years have been used by the Israeli authorities in their policing of the Gaza border in recent weeks.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149035","149035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914790","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support and protect media workers in Turkey.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149036","149036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914791","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans the Government has to respond to the reported surge in the repression of human rights defenders worldwide; and whether the Government plans to commit to a renewed strategy of support and protection.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149037","149037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914792","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to maintain the level of funding that is given to the EU to support human rights defenders after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149038","149038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914793","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to reduce the number of young people not in education, employment or training in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149072","149072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914794","2018-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of ending the protected places scheme on (a) organisations that receive funding from and (b) disabled people in work who are supported by that scheme.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149039","149039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914795","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils achieved a NVQ3+ or equivalent in (a) Mansfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) East Midlands in 2017.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149073","149073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914796","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many incidents of asbestos released in schools were reported to his Department in each year between September 2011 and September 2017; how many school staff and pupils have been exposed in such incidents; and what action was taken by the Heath and Safety Executive in relation to those incidents.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148681","148681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914797","2018-06-06","Women and Equalities","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the Government assess all policy and legislation for its effect on women before implementation.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149025","149025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914798","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on split payments of universal credit.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149026","149026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914799","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his announcement of 5 April 2018, for what reasons his Department decided not to amend regulations to permit Mobile Batching Concrete Plants (MCBPs) to continue to operate outside standard legal gross vehicle weight limits after the inclusion of MCBPs within statutory goods vehicle testing from 20 May 2018.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148672","148672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914800","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the £700 million allocated in Spring Budget 2016 to boost spending on flood defences and resilience funded by the 0.5 per cent rise in Insurance Premium Tax has been (a) allocated and (b) spent.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148969","148969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914801","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the evidential basis is for the decision that if Mobile Batching Concrete Plants (MCBPs) continue to operate outside standard legal gross vehicle weight limits it would create an enduring regulatory discrepancy between businesses competing in the same market when operators of barrel mixers are free to purchase and operate MCBPs as many already do.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148673","148673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914802","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his announcement of 5 April 2018, what the evidential basis is for his Department’s decision that fair competition would be sustained in the wet concrete market industry when Mobile Batching Concrete Plants (MCBPs) will have their payloads reduced, on average by 35%, to below the payloads currently carried by Barrel Concrete Mixers.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148674","148674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914803","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his letter of 10 March 2017 which stated that VSOs would be valid up to 2032, for what reason his announcement of 5 April 2018 decided to institute a temporary weight regime for a period of 10 years with a cut off for new registrations to the end of December 2018.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148675","148675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914804","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's letter entitled Regulation of mobile concrete batching plant – decision on operating weight arrangements, published on 5 April 2018, for what reason his Department did not undertake an assessment of the economic effect on the viability of businesses of his decision against a permanent specific arrangement for mobile batching concrete plants prior to that announcement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148676","148676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914805","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will confirm that his policy on applicable weight limits for Mobile Concrete Batching Plants (MCBPs) has resulted in a significant change that will apply to all (a) old and (b) new registrations for MCBPs not eligible to operate under a Vehicle Special Order after 1 September 2018.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148677","148677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914806","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his announcement of 10 March 2017 that the only preconditions were (a) to ensure that the weights envisaged for both the STGO regime and VSOs were within the accepted tolerances of the standard national loading model for road structures and (b) technical legal drafting, for what reasons his announcement of 5 April 2018, decided against an amendment to the special types rules to enable Mobile Concrete Batching Plants (MCBPs) to continue to operate outside standard legal gross vehicle weight limits, but within standard axle weights, in order to maintain similar payloads to current operations.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148678","148678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914807","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his announcement of 10 March 2017 that a permanent specific weight regime for Mobile Concrete Batching Plants (MCBPs) was a specific solution proposed for the very specific circumstances related to MCBPs, for what reasons his Department now concludes that it would be highly likely to receive demands for similar treatment from operators of other types of vehicles that would benefit from operating at a higher gross weight, including tippers and barrel mixers.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148679","148679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914808","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 May to Question 139444 on World War 2: compensation, what consultations his Department had with veterans ahead of the decision to sign the Treaty of Final Settlement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148705","148705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914809","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what measures are in place to provide long-term protection of (a) pay and (b) pensions of NHS staff transferring to wholly owned subsidiaries established by NHS Trusts.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148828","148828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914810","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether there are mechanisms in place to prevent the sale of wholly owned subsidiaries established by NHS Trusts to external private companies.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148829","148829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914811","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has issued guidance to NHS Trusts on consulting their staff before establishing wholly owned subsidiaries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148830","148830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914812","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with the Treasury on the use of wholly owned subsidiaries established by NHS Trusts for tax avoidance.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148831","148831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914813","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations his Department has received on the effect of wholly owned subsidiaries established by NHS Trusts on patient safety.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148832","148832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914814","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to re-open the Cowley branch line in Oxford to passenger services.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149063","149063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914815","2018-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to abolish employment tribunal fees.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149027","149027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914816","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many individual sites have submitted planning applications for exploratory drilling for shale gas since the lifting of the moratorium on hydraulic fracturing in 2012.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149060","149060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914817","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many individual sites have received planning permission for exploratory drilling for shale gas since the lifting of the moratorium on hydraulic fracturing in 2012.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149061","149061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914818","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate the Government has made of the number of hydraulic fracturing wells required in the UK to replace gas imports for the period 2021 to 2035.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149062","149062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914819","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department plans to publish its response to the Draft Animal Welfare (Sentencing and Recognition of Sentience) Bill 2017 Consultation, published on 12 December 2017.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148736","148736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914820","2018-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to deploy additional troops to Afghanistan; what role those troops will have; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149000","149000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914821","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the likelihood of a peace deal between the Government of Afghanistan and the Taliban; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149001","149001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914822","2018-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will bring forward legislative proposals for a statute of limitations to protect British veterans of combat operations in (a) Northern Ireland, (b) Iraq, (c) Afghanistan, (d) the Falklands and (e) all other combat theatres from (i) repeat prosecutions and (ii) unfounded historical allegations.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149002","149002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914823","2018-06-06","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse has been of (a) Gift Aid and (b) tax relief on charity donations declared on tax returns in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148609","148609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914824","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the return to the UK of Andy Tsege.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148594","148594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914825","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on food security.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148595","148595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914826","2018-06-05","Department for International Trade","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that food standards are maintained in future trade deals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148596","148596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914827","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the poultry meat sector has adequate access to skilled staff after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148597","148597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914828","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of leaving the EU on the labour requirements of the poultry business to (a) sustain  and (b) increase levels of production.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148598","148598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914829","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the maintenance of the poultry meat sector workforce after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148599","148599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914830","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the UK providing and maintaining funding allocated by the European Regional Development Fund at the same level after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149028","149028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914831","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to investigate the reasons for changes in the level of electoral registration in each local authority in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148872","148872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914832","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds from electoral registration officers on the number of names removed from electoral registers in each local authority, for each permissible reason, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148873","148873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914833","2018-06-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the UK providing and maintaining the funding allocated by the EU's Horizon 2020 programme at the same level after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149029","149029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914834","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the UK providing and maintaining funding allocated by the European Maritime and Fisheries Fund at the same level after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149030","149030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914835","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the UK providing and maintaining funding allocated by the EU's LEADER programme at the same level after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149031","149031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914836","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost was of the transfer to Individual Electoral Registration; and what proportion of such costs was borne by local government.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148874","148874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914837","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to support the development of regional infrastructure in Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149074","149074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914838","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department allocated to schools in Nottinghamshire in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149075","149075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914839","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many (a) 16 to 24 year old and (b) 25 to 30 year old homeless people have been temporarily housed in bed and breakfast accommodation by their local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148875","148875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914840","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people between 16 and 24 years old are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148876","148876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914841","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people between 16 and 24 years old in full-time employment are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148877","148877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914842","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many non-UK EU citizens living in the UK voted in the 2018 local government elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148878","148878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914843","2018-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Government holds information on the number of times the (a) Police Service of Northern Ireland, (b) Northern Ireland Fire and Rescue Service and (b) Northern Ireland Ambulance Service have crossed the border into the Republic of Ireland to assist with the response to an emergency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148642","148642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914844","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whats steps his Department took to increase voter registration prior to the 2018 local government elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148879","148879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914845","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the efficacy of the  design of ballot papers for people who have difficulties of sight.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148880","148880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914846","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with Ministers of the devolved administrations on increasing the levels of voter registration.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148881","148881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914847","2018-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Chagossians have been invited to participate in scientific expeditions to the Chagos Archipelago in 2018 to date.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148860","148860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914848","2018-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Chagossians have participated in any conservation, enforcement, or science work in the Chagos Islands area as envisaged by his Department's 2015 consultation paper.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148861","148861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914849","2018-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that scientific organisations granted permission to work in the British Indian Ocean Territory include Chagossian participants.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148862","148862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914850","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to A regulatory review of the UK’s party and election finance laws: Recommendations for Change, published by the Electroal Commission in June 2013, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Electoral Commission's recommendation that political parties that receive and spend less than £500 annually should be exempt from submitting a full statement of accounts.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148882","148882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914851","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to promote participation of National Citizen Service in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148883","148883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914852","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to work with university, college and further education providers to integrate electoral registration into academic enrolment prior to the commencement of the 2018-19 academic year.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148884","148884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914853","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government took to encourage people unable to vote in person to apply for a postal vote for the 2018 local government elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148885","148885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914854","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to replicate the Northern Ireland electoral registration schools initiative to increase electoral registration among people aged 16 in England.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148886","148886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914855","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will add public health to the list of public goods that will receive support as part of the UK’s agricultural policy framework after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148658","148658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914856","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer 21 May 2018 to Questions 144263 and 144264 on In Vitro Fertilisation, for what reason his Department does not collect information on IVF provision centrally; and what assessment he has made of the effect of not holding that information centrally on (a) women seeking IVF and (b) the ability of his Department's to analyse the provision and resourcing of fertility treatment options available in England.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148775","148775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914857","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 3 May 2018 to Question 139363 on Diabetes, what steps his Department is taking to support NHS England in achieving a measurable reduction in variation in the management and care for people with diabetes.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148610","148610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914858","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of cases of alleged electoral fraud relating to nomination that took place at the 2018 local government elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148887","148887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914859","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to encourage youth engagement in (a) national and (b) local elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148888","148888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914860","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost to the public purse was of conducting the 2018 local government elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148889","148889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914861","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the implications are for his policies of the recent data for Fertility Fairness on the number of clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) in England offering the recommended three IVF cycles to eligible women under 40 years of age having halved in the last five years and only 12 per cent of all CCGs following national guidance; what assessment he has made of the reasons for that reduction in the number of CCGs offering three cycles and following that guidance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148776","148776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914862","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the availability of helium gas on suicide rates.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148890","148890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914863","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Oral Answer of the Minister for Agriculture, Fisheries and Food of 26 April 2018, Official Report, column 1007, how many charities have made representations to his Department to register (a) concerns about the potential burden of and (b) support for introducing licensing and regulation for animal rescue homes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149081","149081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914864","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has had recent discussions with representatives of the animal charity sector on the potential merits of introducing legislative proposals for the regulation and licensing of animal rescue centres.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149082","149082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914865","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the merits of offline access to benefit claims; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148833","148833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914866","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions,what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding to (a) Salford City Council and (b) all local authorities to meet their statutory requirements on benefits.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148834","148834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914867","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase take-up of design and technology alongside the EBacc; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148743","148743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914868","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on the EU-Horn of Africa migration route initiative to tackle irregular migration from the Horn of Africa.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148638","148638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914869","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress on the UK-Sudan strategic dialogue; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148639","148639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914870","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of respect for freedom of religion or belief in Sudan.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148640","148640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914871","2018-06-06","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for his Department to receive the 2018 report of the School Teachers’ Review Body.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149064","149064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914872","2018-06-06","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the 2018 report of the School Teachers’ Review Body.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149065","149065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914873","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that not-for-profit community bus services are not treated as commercial operators under the proposed changes to sections 19 and 22 of the Transport Act 1985.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149086","149086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914874","2018-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 134413 on Army: Recruitment, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to that Question.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148984","148984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914875","2018-06-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect on London of the UK leaving the customs union.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148786","148786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914876","2018-06-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect on London of the UK leaving the single market.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148787","148787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914877","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made on the settled status system for EU nationals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148788","148788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914878","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how he plans to determine the level of compensation payable to Windrush migrants.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148789","148789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914879","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to enable Commonwealth migrants to work in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148790","148790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914880","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to help prevent people under 19 years old who are convicted of knife crime from reoffending.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148791","148791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914881","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Administration on its assessment of crimes committed against Rohingyas in Myanmar.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148792","148792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914882","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to provide additional funding to local authorities in London to help respond to homelessness.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148793","148793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914883","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of young people classified as homeless who were previously in care in (a) London and (b) Bethnal Green and Bow.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148794","148794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914884","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on the long-term financial viability of local authorities which use their reserves to fund adult social care.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148795","148795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914885","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to improve child health outcomes.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148796","148796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914886","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal of NHS bursaries on the number of applications for nursing degrees.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148797","148797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914887","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the NHS of an agreement not being reached with the EU on mutual qualification recognition for (a) doctors and (b) nurses after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148798","148798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914888","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of teachers recruited to (a) primary schools and (b) secondary schools in London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148799","148799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914889","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to include a new statutory requirement on social media companies to stop the spread of online hate speech in the forthcoming internet safety strategy white paper.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148800","148800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914890","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will include penalties for social media companies that fail to remove hate speech flagged by users in the forthcoming internet safety strategy white paper.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148801","148801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914891","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to diverge from EU standards for data protection after the end of the transition period.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148802","148802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914892","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment the Government has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the creative industries.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148803","148803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914893","2018-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what weighting will be given to national security objective 3 on UK prosperity in the procurement of the replacement long-range air defence deployable radar.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149083","149083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914894","2018-06-06","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of changing conflict dynamics in South Sudan on the ability to deliver aid in that country.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149003","149003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914895","2018-06-06","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve humanitarian access to South Sudan.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149004","149004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914896","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees based in Shettleston JobCentre have received basic training on administering universal credit claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148841","148841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914897","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees were based in Shettleston JobCentre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148842","148842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914898","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees were based in Partick JobCentre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148843","148843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914899","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees were based in Castlemilk JobCentre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148844","148844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914900","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees were based in Govan JobCentre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148845","148845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914901","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees were based in Laurieston JobCentre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148846","148846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914902","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees were based in Springburn JobCentre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148847","148847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914903","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees were based in Newlands JobCentre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148848","148848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914904","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees based in Springburn JobCentre have received basic training on administering universal credit claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148849","148849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914905","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees based in Newlands JobCentre have received basic training on administering universal credit claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148850","148850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914906","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees based in Partick JobCentre have received basic training on administering universal credit claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148851","148851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914907","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees based in Govan JobCentre have received basic training on administering universal credit claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148852","148852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914908","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees based in Laurieston JobCentre have received basic training on administering universal credit claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148853","148853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914909","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees based in Castlemilk JobCentre have received basic training on administering universal credit claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148854","148854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914910","2018-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current value is of the UK stake in the Meteor Beyond Visual Range Air-to-Air Missile programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148633","148633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914911","2018-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current proportional value is of the UK stake in the Meteor Beyond Visual Range Air-to-Air Missile programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148634","148634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914912","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees based in Drumchapel JobCentre have received basic training on administering universal credit claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148855","148855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914913","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees were based in Drumchapel JobCentre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148856","148856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914914","2018-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current value is of each partner nation's stake in the Meteor Beyond Visual Range Air-to-Air Missile programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148635","148635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914915","2018-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals have been made by claimants of personal independence payment since its inception.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148716","148716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914916","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that employers comply with the national minimum wage.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148717","148717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914917","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has taken to promote awareness of the symptoms of prostate cancer; and whether his Department plans to take steps to encourage men to be tested for prostate cancer.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148718","148718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914918","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have received a cochlear implant in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148719","148719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914919","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for people's health of using artificial sweeteners.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148720","148720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914920","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cattle tested positive for bovine tuberculosis in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148721","148721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914921","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many fines were issued by his Department for non-attendance at school by children in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148722","148722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914922","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support children in rural areas who do not have access to free school transport.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148723","148723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914923","2018-06-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent meetings he has held with representatives of technology firms on the use of technology at the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148724","148724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914924","2018-06-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings has he held with the heads of the devolved institutions since the creation of his Department.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148725","148725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914925","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the  policy and practice guidance her Department issues to decision-makers on supporting vulnerable people who claim for universal credit.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148857","148857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914926","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many social sector landlords have registered with the Landlord Portal to date.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148858","148858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914927","2018-06-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2018 to Question 136214 on Insulation: Preston, whether the remaining properties includes all of the properties affected in the Fishwick area; and what the timeframe is for the completion of the structural surveys.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148623","148623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914928","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 125862 on Restraint Techniques: Children and Young People, what the timetable is for the publication of the response.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148783","148783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914929","2018-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for universal credit have been closed as a result of an incomplete identity verification.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148859","148859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914930","2018-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 May 2018 to Question 146091 on State Retirement Pensions: Females, what the duties of the additional 13 staff will be; assessment she has made of the effect of the additional staff on the time taken to conclude (a) all complaints and (b) WASPI complaints; and when he plans for the additional staff to begin (a) training and (b) work with the Independent Case Examiner.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148611","148611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914931","2018-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to allocate additional resources to the Pensions Ombudsman as a result of the level of caseload from WASPI complainants.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148612","148612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914932","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) Members of Parliament and (b) staff working for Members of Parliament that communicated on immigration enforcement hotlines during 2017; and which political parties they belonged to.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148604","148604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914933","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Bovine TB Strategy Review committee chaired by Sir Charles Godfray will include a review of badger culling; and what the timetable is for that committee to report.","Biography information for Mr Bob Seely","Mr Bob Seely","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149087","149087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914934","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timetable is for the introduction of  the improved testing methods for (a) bovine tuberculosis testing and (b) Phage.","Biography information for Mr Bob Seely","Mr Bob Seely","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149088","149088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914935","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many biometric residence permits were issued in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148811","148811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914936","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which company or Government facility prints biometric residence permits for his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148812","148812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914937","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the issuing of biometric residence permits for Windrush cases has been prioritised by his Department over other cases in the last two months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148813","148813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914938","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many biometric residence permits have been issued for Windrush cases in the last two months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148814","148814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914939","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, the total cost of travel claims for staff redeployed from their normal location of work as part of the Windrush taskforce in each of the last two months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148815","148815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914940","2018-06-06","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) deportation and (b) removal flights were chartered by his Department to (i) Jamaica, (ii) India, (iii) Pakistan, (iv) Bangladesh, (v) China and (vi) Nigeria in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148816","148816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914941","2018-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2017 to Questions 116517, 116519, 116520, 116523 on Army: Training, when he plans to publish a substantive answer to the Questions.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148985","148985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914942","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the mean average wait is for cases to  be (a) accepted for arbitration and (b) concluded by the Office of the Pub Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148945","148945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914943","2018-06-06","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have made a claim to the Adoption Support Fund; and what the average award has been for a successful claim in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148946","148946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914944","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2018 to Questions 144259, 144260 and 144261 on Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS Foundation Trust, when he next plans to meet with representatives of North Lincolnshire and Goole NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148777","148777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914945","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2018 to Questions 144259, 144260 and 144261 on Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS Foundation Trust, if he will publish the range of actions have been taken and are underway to help improve performance at the Trust.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148778","148778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914946","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Questions 144259, 144260 and 144261 Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS Foundation Trust, when he expects the Emergency Care Improvement Programme to formulate and enact an action plan for North Lincolnshire and Goole NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148779","148779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914947","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what environmental impact assessment he has carried out in relation to the proposed revisions to the National Planning Policy Framework; and if he will place a copy of the assessments in the Library.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148659","148659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914948","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what environmental impact assessment his Department has carried out in relation to the proposed changes to the planning rules relating to Sites of Interest for Nature Conservation contained in the National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148660","148660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914949","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what meeting he has held with organisations on the proposed changes to the planning rules relating to Sites of Interest for Nature Conservation, set out in the National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148661","148661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914950","2018-06-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to retain the current level of protection for Sites of Importance for Nature Conservation set out in the National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148662","148662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914951","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he last discussed steps to maintain the welfare of gamebirds with the Animal and Plant Health Agency.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148663","148663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914952","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the work of the Animal and Plant Health Agency in ensuring that the Animal Welfare Act 2006 is complied with in respect of gamebirds.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148664","148664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914953","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to (a) identify visa applicants wrongly accused of cheating in the TOIEC English language test, (b) ensure that appeals against the Home Office’s decision to cancel their leave are heard in the UK; and offer applicants wrongly accused of fraud and refused a visa appropriate compensation.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148977","148977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914954","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of myalgic encephalomyelitis among the public and medical practitioners.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148978","148978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914955","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of the recommendations contained in the report Seven tests for the social care green paper, published by Independent Age on 3 May 2018.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148665","148665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914956","2018-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress he has made on ensuring that Overseas Territories establish public registers for company beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148666","148666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914957","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people with no (a) fixed and (b) permanent address will be able to register to vote using the online registration service.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148891","148891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914958","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of people who registered to vote by means of the online registration service did so without providing a national insurance number in (a) 2014, (b) 2015, (c) 2016, (d) 2017 and (e) 2018.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148892","148892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914959","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to Every Voice Matters: Building A Democracy That Works For Everyone, published by his Department on 19 December 2017, whether his Department has had recent discussions with the Department for Education on increasing the level of political education in schools for young people in line with the objectives of that document.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148893","148893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914960","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Government's policy is on extending the franchise to all legal residents of the UK.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148894","148894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914961","2018-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 May 2018 to Question 146960 on European Fighter Aircraft, what proportion of the £45 million has been assigned to the installation of the the Enhanced Collision Awareness System.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149023","149023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914962","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of piloting polling day voter registration to increase voter turnout.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148895","148895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914963","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on the implementation of the recommendations contained in the Cancer Strategy for England; and whether his Department plans to implement those recommendations by 2020.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148636","148636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914964","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of  the introduction of all-postal voting in local elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148896","148896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914965","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to support people living with cancer after 2020.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148637","148637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914966","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to ring-fence funding allocated from National Productivity Investment Fund to the devolved administrations.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149022","149022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914967","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that polling stations are accessible for people with disabilities.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148897","148897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914968","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has made an assessment of (a) the adequacy of the tactile voting device used in polling stations for blind and visually impaired voters and (b) the potential merits of a replacement of that device to increase accessibility.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148898","148898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914969","2018-06-05","Women and Equalities","2018-06-01","To ask the  Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to section 106 of the Equality Act 2010, when the Government plans to bring into force a statutory requirement for political parties to publish their parliamentary candidate diversity data for general elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148899","148899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914970","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect the introduction of the 2019 loan charge on people who used umbrella companies on the advice of professionals after the introduction IR35.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148628","148628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914971","2018-06-05","Women and Equalities","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the Government plans to extend the timeframe for the Sex Discrimination (Election Candidates) Act 2002 to enable political parties to use all-women shortlists after 2030.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148900","148900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914972","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the number of places for agricultural apprenticeships.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148871","148871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914973","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Arfon constituency, (b) Wales, and (c) the UK who will be affected by the introduction of the 2019 loan charge.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148629","148629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914974","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department undertook a consultation exercise on the effect on individuals of the introduction of the 2019 loan charge.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148630","148630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914975","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to measure the effect of the introduction of the 2019 loan charge on people affected by the charge.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148631","148631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914976","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of applying the 2019 loan charge only to arrangements made after the Finance Act 2017 came into force.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148632","148632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914977","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect on trends in the level of voting in elections of opening polling stations at weekends.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148901","148901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914978","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to increase voter registration within Commonwealth communities in the UK.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148902","148902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914979","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Police and Crime Commissioners are subject to a purdah period in relation to elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148903","148903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914980","2018-06-05","Prime Minister","2018-06-01","To ask the Prime Minister, when her office plans fully to respond to the letter of the hon. Member for West Dunbartonshire dated 25 April 2018 on his constituent, Jagtar Singh Johal.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148825","148825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914981","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has made a comparative assessment of the adequacy of national electoral registers used by (a) EU and (b) other countries in relation to the introduction of a centralised, national electoral register in the UK.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148904","148904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914982","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contingency plans his Department has in the event that it is alerted to online interference with information systems for UK elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148905","148905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914983","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent the mining and trading of conflict minerals overseas.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148706","148706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914984","2018-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to undertake a consultation exercise on changes to the Local Air Quality Management framework.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148708","148708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914985","2018-06-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made on the effect of fake news disseminated on the internet on voting in the UK; and what steps he is taking to tackle fake news in relation to elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148906","148906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914986","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much has been spent from the public purse to date on the 2018 boundary review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148907","148907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914987","2018-06-05","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department provides to help prevent children from being forced into the mining of conflict minerals in the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148707","148707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914988","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions has he had with the Electoral Commission on changes to electoral law.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148908","148908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914989","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many allegations of impersonation were made to the police in relation to the 2018 local government elections; how many of those allegations are under investigation; and what the proportion of the votes cast at those elections those cases represent.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148909","148909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914990","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many allegations of impersonation were made to the police in each of the five local authorities piloting voter ID at the 2018 local government elections; and what proportion of votes cast in each of the five local authorities those cases represent.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148910","148910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914991","2018-06-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to phase out the use of coal to generate electricity.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148709","148709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914992","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133664 on Syria: Overseas Aid, what the security reasons are for not disclosing the armed opposition groups that the UK is supporting in Syria.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149009","149009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914993","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his Answer of 28 March to Question 133664 on Syria: Overseas Aid, if he will publish the (a) communications equipment and (b) logistics equipment provided to the armed opposition groups in Syria.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149010","149010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914994","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether officials of his Department have met with Ahrar al-Sham in Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149011","149011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914995","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2018 to Question 135452 on Overseas Trade: Occupied Territories, what criteria the Government uses to distinguish between Israel and the Occupied Territories under UN Resolution 2334.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149012","149012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914996","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2018 to Question 133853 on Overseas Trade: Occupied Territories, how the Government’s policy to allow individual companies to decide whether to operate in the Occupied Territories is in compliance with UN resolution 2334.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149013","149013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914997","2018-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to preserve the integrity of UK sovereign waters around Gibraltar.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148737","148737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914998","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many ministerial visits have been conducted to Israel in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018 to date.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149014","149014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914999","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the role of the Israeli navy in the enforcement of the blockade against Gaza.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149015","149015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915000","2018-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role (a) RAF and (b) UK-contracted personnel have played in weapons (i) loading and (ii) maintenance for Saudi aircraft taking part in operations in Yemen since 2015.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149016","149016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915001","2018-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military exercises the Royal Navy has conducted with the Israeli navy since 2016; and if he will make a statement on the (a) nature and (b) extent of naval military co-operation between the two countries.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149017","149017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915002","2018-06-05","Department for International Trade","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what UK military equipment has been exported for use by the Israeli navy since 2016.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149018","149018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915003","2018-06-05","Department for International Trade","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether restrictions on end-use are applied to UK exports of military equipment to Israel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149019","149019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915004","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether UK-supplied military equipment has been used by Turkey in its operations in Afrin; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149020","149020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915005","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many control orders on Libyan nationals living in the UK who were suspected members of the Libyan Islamic Fighting Group were lifted in 2011.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149021","149021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915006","2018-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to attend the 2018 NATO summit; and what recent assessment he has made of the level of commitment of other NATO member states to two per cent of GDP as a minimum investment in defence.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148738","148738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915007","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Indefinite Leave to Remain have been rejected as a result of evidence included in previous applications being classified as expired.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148624","148624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915008","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of replicating the EU Shareholder Rights Directive 2017 after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148727","148727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915009","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to include in corporate governance rules the requirement for companies to publish the end investor on company registers.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148728","148728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915010","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to improve the transparency of corporate governance structures.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148729","148729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915011","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to increase the involvement of company workforces in the development of remuneration packages.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148730","148730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915012","2018-06-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing legislative proposals to introduce mandatory worker representation on remuneration committees.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148731","148731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915013","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains servicing Bedford have been (a) cancelled and (b) delayed since the introduction of the new rail timetable on 20 May 2018; and what the average time was for the trains that were delayed.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148994","148994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915014","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether there are cost implications for his Department as a result of the delays and cancellations on services provided Govia Thameslink since the introduction of the new rail timetable on 20 May 2018; and whether those delays and cancellations are in breach of the franchise agreement.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148995","148995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915015","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the compensation procedures for passengers experiencing delays on (a) Govia Thameslink and b) East Midlands train services since 20 May 2018.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148996","148996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915016","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to reintroduce peak-time East Midland Trains services to Bedford until the problems with the timetable introduced in May 2018 are resolved.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148997","148997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915017","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the May 2018 timetable changes on overcrowding on rail services at Bedford station.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148998","148998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915018","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons his Department did not respond to the Independent Monitoring Board at Campsfield House Immigration Removal Centre Annual Report of 2016 within the six-week timeframe set out in Detention Services Order DSO 04/2014.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149066","149066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915019","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans to respond to the Independent Monitoring Board at Campsfield House Immigration Removal Centre Annual Report of 2017 within the six-week timeframe set out in Detention Services Order DSO 04/2014.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149067","149067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915020","2018-06-05","Home Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department's process of sending voluntary withdrawal forms to asylum-seeking minors was introduced; when his Department has reviewed that process; and how many minors have been sent such forms since the introduction of that policy.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148999","148999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915021","2018-06-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) open access youth work for 13 to 19 year olds, (b) wages for qualified Joint Negotiating Committee youth workers and (c) youth only (i) spaces and (ii) buildings per young person in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148911","148911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915022","2018-06-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospitals are complaint with the Accessible Information Standard.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148625","148625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915023","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the BBC Panorama programme of 21 May 2018 on fire safety testing, if the Government will introduce regulations to ensure that testing a building's cladding system involves testing the cladding and insulation together for safety and combustibility.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149076","149076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915024","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that combustible products which produce cyanide when burned are banned from buildings on the grounds of fire safety.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149077","149077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915025","2018-06-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that cladding and building insulation will use only Euroclass A1 and A2 materials that are graded as non-combustible.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149078","149078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915026","2018-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of children that spent a night in custody in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148817","148817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915027","2018-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that the recent ceasefire between India and Pakistan (a) lasts and (b) marks the beginning of a peace process in the region.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148744","148744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915028","2018-06-05","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on medical facilities in Yemen of the recent cyclone in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148745","148745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915029","2018-06-05","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on access to clean drinking water in Yemen of the recent cyclone in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148746","148746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915030","2018-06-05","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle sexual exploitation and trafficking of Rohingya refugee women and girls.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148747","148747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915031","2018-06-05","Department for International Development","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the risk of sexual exploitation of women and girls at refugee camps in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148748","148748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915032","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the driver shortages on train services to Hitchin in the first week of the new Govia Thameslink timetable.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149032","149032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915033","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local education authorities have top sliced funding from the Dedicated Schools Grant for services previously funded out of the general funding element of the Education Services Grant.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149068","149068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915034","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral Statement of 17 July 2017 on Schools Update, Official Report, column 563, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policy on free schools presumption of the 30 free schools delivered through the local authority route.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149069","149069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915035","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the efficacy of the Govia Thameslink franchise in relation to the changes to the timetable on the rail network.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149033","149033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915036","2018-06-05","Department for Education","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Oral Statement of 17 July 2017 on Schools Update, Official Report, column 563, which of his Departments' programmes will have funding reduced as a result of the decision to redirect £200 million into the core schools budget; and what the level of that reduction will be for each such programme.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149070","149070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915037","2018-06-05","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the introduction of the new Govia Thameslink timetable.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149034","149034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915038","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish his Department's consultation on the introduction of a deposit return scheme.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148948","148948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915039","2018-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether (a) he or (b) officials in his Department have met with representatives of the (i) Scottish and (iii) Welsh Government to discuss the potential scope of a deposit return scheme.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148949","148949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915040","2018-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure adequate access to and from Ascension Island for (a) civilians and (b) military personnel during the Ascension Island runway resurfacing programme.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148966","148966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915041","2018-06-06","Department for Transport","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of vehicles registered abroad in the UK; and what steps his Department has taken to ensure that those vehicles are fully taxed, insured and registered.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148607","148607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915042","2018-06-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people in each district of Gloucestershire are eligible to receive Healthy Start vouchers; and what estimate he has made of the number of people that are in receipt of those vouchers.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148608","148608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915043","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) cost of and (b) timetable for implementation of the infrastructure which will be required at UK borders to add VAT when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148600","148600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915044","2018-06-05","Treasury","2018-06-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual costs are for the (a) systems, (b) physical infrastructure, and (c) staff for the processing of VAT for goods entering and leaving the UK from countries outside the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148601","148601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915045","2018-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 29 May 2018 to Question 146325 on European Fighter Aircraft: Safety Measures, how the Typhoon’s Enhanced Collision Awareness System will meet the requirement for an independent Airborne Collision Avoidance System.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149024","149024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915046","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress he has made on reforming the annual canvass of electors.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148912","148912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915047","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress his Department has made on electoral registration improvement programmes.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148913","148913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915048","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress he has made on the introduction of changes to the Register to vote website.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148914","148914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915049","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Government's policy is on the recommendation by the Committee on Standards in Public Life Review of Intimidation in Public Life to extend electoral law requirements for an imprint on campaigning materials to electronic communications.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148915","148915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915050","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New Electoral Laws proposed to combat intimidation in public life, published on 6 February 2018, what progress has been made on removing the requirement for candidates’ home addresses to be included on ballot papers.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148916","148916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915051","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has plans to remove the statutory requirement to publish the home address of election agents.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148917","148917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915052","2018-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department provides to (a) the families of children who are severely disabled and (b) other families in similar circumstances in completing applications for disability living allowance.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148991","148991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915053","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many youth democracy ambassadors have been recruited for the Suffrage Centenary Programme; and how many youth democracy ambassadors are in receipt of free school meals.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148918","148918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915054","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the Government's partners that will deliver National Democracy Week 2018.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148919","148919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915055","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions his Department has had with Royal Mail on mailing options for poll cards.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148920","148920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915056","2018-06-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-06-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many countries have made a written declaration that treaties signed with the EU will continue to apply to the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148602","148602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915057","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent conversations he has had with the devolved administrations on  the potential merits of extending the franchise to 16 and 17 year olds.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148921","148921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915058","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the current average public sector office space in square meters per full-time employee.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149043","149043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915059","2018-06-05","Cabinet Office","2018-06-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much has accrued to the public purse in capital receipts from estate disposals since the publication of the Government's Estate Strategy in October 2014.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149044","149044"
