"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470374","2016-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on reducing homelessness in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30970","30970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470375","2016-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what cross-departmental working groups or structures are in place in respect of (a) litter policy and (b) marine litter at (i) official and (ii) ministerial level.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30918","30918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470377","2016-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 27 January 2016 on the local government finance settlement.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30886","30886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470378","2016-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on determining the appropriate local media outlets for publication of planning notices with respect to those outlets' geographical coverage.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30888","30888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470379","2016-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from homelessness charities in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30906","30906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470380","2016-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding his Department has allocated to arts groups in Romford in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30904","30904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470382","2016-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to commemorate the 400th anniversary of the 1620 voyage of the Mayflower.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30909","30909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470383","2016-03-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2016 to Question 28851, what assessment he has made of the potential benefit to international sales of British content of the commissioning of content with diverse voices.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30991","30991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470384","2016-03-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps he has taken to support UK cities considering a bid for the title of European Capital of Culture 2023.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31009","31009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470385","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2016 to Question 30090, what the timeline is for the procurement of a collision warning system for the Typhoon aircraft.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30993","30993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470387","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military and (b) civilian personnel from his Department are based in Jordan.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30994","30994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470388","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2016 to Question 28161, how many (a) military and (b) civilian personnel are deployed to which UN agencies.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31004","31004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470389","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2016 to Question 28161, how many of the (a) military and (b) civilian personnel deployed on UN peacekeeping operations are women.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31005","31005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470390","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2016 to Question 28161, whether the numbers of civilian personnel provided in that Answer include personnel deployed by other government departments.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31006","31006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470391","2016-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether people rescued by (a) Royal Fleet Auxiliary and (b) Royal Navy vessels are able to claim for asylum in the UK if flagged in international waters.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31045","31045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470392","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what UK military equipment has been deployed on UN peacekeeping operations in each of the last six years; and on what operations that equipment has been so deployed.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31007","31007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470393","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 10 March 2016, WS605, what impact assessment his Department carried out on its decision to disband air cadet gliding squadrons in Scotland before making that decision; and what assessment he has made of the effect of that decision on future RAF recruitment.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31041","31041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470395","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment his Department has made of North Korea's nuclear capability in (a) general and (b) relation to claims by that country that it has developed nuclear-tipped missiles.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30954","30954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470396","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many defence personnel are based overseas (a) at each of Her Majesty's Armed Forces bases and (b) as part of a joint operation abroad.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30877","30877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470397","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many submissions from local (a) residents and (b) businesses his Department received to its consultation on the Submarine Dismantling Project: site for the interim storage of Intermediate Level radioactive Waste.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30885","30885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470398","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many drone strikes have taken place against Daesh targets in (a) Iraq and (b) Syria since September 2014.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30887","30887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470399","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many direct joint training exercises with the US armed forces have been carried out in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30878","30878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470401","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many direct joint training exercises with the Royal Australian armed forces have been carried out in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30879","30879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470402","2016-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of officials of his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in each of the last five years; and what proportion of total sick leave that leave was in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30863","30863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470403","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to publish its consultation on the Submarine Dismantling Project: site for the interim storage of Intermediate Level radioactive Waste.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30883","30883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470404","2016-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many submissions his Department received to its consultation on the Submarine Dismantling Project: site for the interim storage of Intermediate Level radioactive Waste.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30884","30884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470406","2016-03-17","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many police officers are employed by schools on a (a) full-time and (b) part-time basis.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30895","30895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470407","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Education Funding Agency takes to discover related party transactions which are not disclosed Academy Trust financial statements.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30912","30912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470408","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse was of monitoring related party transactions in Academy Trusts in the (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15 financial years; and what the projected cost of such transactions is in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30913","30913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470409","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many trainee teachers have carried out practical teaching experience at pupil referral units.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30919","30919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470410","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the Education Funding Agency determines whether related party transactions by Academy Trusts are made at cost in the case of payments to consultants with variable rates.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30915","30915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470412","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupil referral units have converted to academy status since 2013.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30921","30921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470413","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many related party transactions by Academy Trusts were classified as irregular or improper by the Education Funding Agency in each of the last two financial years; and how many such cases resulted in re-payment.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30916","30916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470414","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the Education Funding Agency determines whether related party transactions by Academy Trusts are made at cost.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30914","30914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470415","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools and academies have opened as pupil referral units since 2013.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30920","30920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470417","2016-03-17","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to evaluate the effect of the introduction of education, health and care plans.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30971","30971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470418","2016-03-17","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times HM Chief Inspector of Schools has visited a school in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30972","30972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470419","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are eligible for free school meals in (a) Lancashire and (b) Burnley.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31001","31001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470420","2016-03-17","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2016 to Question 30215, how much has been allocated by local authorities to primary and secondary schools in the form of top-up funding for pupils with SEN in each academic year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31016","31016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470421","2016-03-17","Department for Education","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary and (b) secondary school teacher vacancies there were in each English region in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31029","31029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470423","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential for windfarms to reduce energy costs during the winter months.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31023","31023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470424","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the contribution of the Prime Minister on 17 October 2012, Official Report, column 316, what steps the Government has taken to bring forward legislative proposals to compel energy companies to give the lowest tariff to their customers.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31024","31024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470425","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to paragraph 36 of the Competition and Markets Authority report on energy market investigation published on 10 March 2016, if her Department will prioritise customers with dumb prepay meters in the smart meter rollout.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31036","31036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470426","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of gas produced in the UK was exported to Western Europe in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31037","31037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470428","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the competitiveness of the UK gas industry compared to its European counterparts.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30903","30903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470429","2016-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many and what proportion of officials of her Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in each of the last five years; and what proportion of total sick leave that leave was in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30866","30866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470431","2016-03-16","Cabinet Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what dates the National Flood Resilience Review met; what the dates are for future meetings of that review; and if he will publish the (a) agendas for and (b) minutes of meetings of that review.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30933","30933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470432","2016-03-16","Cabinet Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the membership of the National Flood Resilience Review team is.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30932","30932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470433","2016-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs were imported into Northern Ireland for (a) non-commercial reasons under the PETS scheme and (b) commercial reasons in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what the countries of origin of those dogs were in each category.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30948","30948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470435","2016-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs brought into the UK under the Pet Travel Scheme have been (a) seized and (b) put through quarantine in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30917","30917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470436","2016-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the National Flood Resilience Review will assess the (a) maintenance requirements of flood assets and (b) capacity of the Environment Agency to maintain flood defences.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30934","30934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470437","2016-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the National Flood Resilience Review team has made on assessing the damage that extreme rainfall could cause across England.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30935","30935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470438","2016-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the mean time was between application for payment and receipt of payment of the (a) Basic Farm Payment and (b) Single Farm Payment to individual farms in Kent in the financial year 2014-15.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31021","31021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470439","2016-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the mean time taken was between application for payment and receipt of the (a) Basic Farm Payment and (b) Single Farm Payment to individual farms in the UK in the financial year 2014-15.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31022","31022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470440","2016-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what controls arising from health considerations are placed on manufacturers on the use of formaldehyde.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30999","30999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470442","2016-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the proportion of rivers, lakes, coastal and ground waters in the UK that (a) are compliant with the EU Water Framework Directive and (b) will be so compliant by 2020; and when she expects all UK waters to achieve good status.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31014","31014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470443","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on protecting the dual citizenship of people with British citizenship living in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30967","30967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470444","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the government of the United Arab Emirates on the continued imprisonment of David Haigh.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31003","31003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470445","2016-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what financial contribution his Department has made to each of the 16 UN peacekeeping operations which are underway.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31017","31017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470446","2016-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on how much and what proportion of the total budget for UN peacekeeping was spent in support of the UN Peacekeeping Force in Cyprus in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31050","31050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470448","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the political and security situation in Turkey since the recent terrorist bombing in Ankara; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30953","30953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470449","2016-03-17","HM Treasury","2016-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value is of sanctioned Iranian assets that have been released by (a) UK Government and (b) other UK entities since the conclusion of the agreement with that country in May 2015.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30977","30977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470450","2016-03-17","HM Treasury","2016-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what timetable the Government has set for the release of sanctioned Iranian assets; and what value of assets the Government expects to release in 2016 and 2017.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30976","30976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470451","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on protecting the rights of citizens with dual British and Chinese nationality living in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30966","30966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470452","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent to which there is a threat to freedom of speech in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30965","30965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470453","2016-03-17","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on treasuring commercial flights to Sharm el Sheikh.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30988","30988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470455","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that China maintains its commitment to the Sino-British Joint Declaration on Hong Kong.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30963","30963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470456","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of China's record in observing the agreements made in the Sino-British Joint Declaration on Hong Kong.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30964","30964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470457","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on alleged mistreatment and torture of British citizens in detention in the United Arab Emirates since 2011.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30942","30942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470458","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Turkish government on the security screening and monitoring processes for refugees entering from Syria; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of those processes during the last six months.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30901","30901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470460","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the human rights situation in Turkey during negotiations on the proposed EU-Turkey refugee deal.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30902","30902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470461","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what mechanisms are included in the proposed EU-Turkey refugee agreement to monitor the use of funds sent to Turkey under the terms of that agreement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30905","30905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470462","2016-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the government of Iraq in re-assimilating newly liberated regions from Daesh/ISIL; what steps the Government is taking to assist Iraq with such assimilation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30880","30880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470463","2016-03-17","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with mental health charities on the potential effect of the removal of mental health quality premium measures in NHS England's Quality Premium Guidance 2016-17 on mental health outcomes.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30896","30896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470465","2016-03-17","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the removal of mental health quality premium measures in NHS England's Quality Premium Guidance 2016-17 on mental health outcomes.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30897","30897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470466","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS was of treating children born with recurrent respiratory papillomatosis in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30900","30900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470467","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average amount of time taken for an autism diagnosis was in (a) Leeds, (b) Yorkshire and (c) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30910","30910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470468","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what international comparisons his Department is drawing on to inform implementation of a gender-neutral HPV vaccination programme.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30899","30899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470469","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings of the First Annual Report of the National Clinical Audit for Rheumatoid and Early Inflammatory Arthritis, published on 22 January 2016, on the proportion of patients in England and Wales referred within three working days of their GP appointment, what steps he is taking to improve the referral rate from GPs when inflammatory arthritis is suspected.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30862","30862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470471","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications for his policies are of the findings of the Annual Report of the National Clinical Audit for Rheumatoid and Early Inflammatory Arthritis on treatment targets in England and Wales for patients with rheumatoid arthritis.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30929","30929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470473","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average ambulance response times in East Lancashire were for (a) Red One and (b) Red Two emergencies in 2015.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30941","30941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470474","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children have been diagnosed with autism in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30939","30939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470475","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Annual Report of the National Clinical Audit for Rheumatoid and Early Inflammatory Arthritis, published on 22 January 2016, what plans his Department has to introduce national measurements for rheumatology services for commissioners and NHS England to inform service design and funding.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30930","30930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470476","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to introduce early inflammatory arthritis clinics throughout the country.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30926","30926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470477","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Annual Report of the National Clinical Audit for Rheumatoid and Early Inflammatory Arthritis, published on 22 January 2016, what steps he is taking to ensure that patients with suspected inflammatory arthritis have their first specialist appointment within the three weeks recommended by NICE.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30925","30925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470478","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Annual Report of the National Clinical Audit for Rheumatoid and Early Inflammatory Arthritis, published on 22 January 2016, what plans his Department has to improve systems for capturing, coding and integrating data from NHS outpatient clinics which will also enable coordinated patient-centred care.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30931","30931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470480","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings of the Annual Report of the National Clinical Audit for Rheumatoid and Early Inflammatory Arthritis, published on 22 January 2016, on timely access to patient education, what steps he is taking to provide patients with rheumatoid and early inflammatory arthritis self-education and self-management tools.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30927","30927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470481","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications for his Department's policies on people with rare forms of kidney disease are of the report of the Rare Disease Forum, Delivering for patients with rare diseases: Implementing a strategy, published on 29 February 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30936","30936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470482","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people waited six weeks or longer for a diagnostic test in Lancashire in 2015.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30937","30937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470483","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is from referral for an autism diagnosis in Lancashire.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30938","30938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470484","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has plans to change the workforce requirements for learning disability nurses.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30951","30951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470485","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many student training places there were in England for learning disability nursing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30950","30950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470487","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings of the Annual Report of the National Clinical Audit for Rheumatoid and Early Inflammatory Arthritis, published on 22 January 2016, on links between waiting times and consultant numbers, what steps he is taking to increase the number of consultant rheumatologists.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30928","30928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470488","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to encourage students to train as  learning disability nurses.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30952","30952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470489","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that there should be a learning disability liaison nurse in every acute hospital in England.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30949","30949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470490","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) Leeds and (b) Yorkshire have been diagnosed with autism.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31042","31042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470491","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2016 to Question 27968, what the opening and closing dates are for the public consultation of the UK National Screening Committee's review of group B streptococcus policy; and on what date the meeting at which a decision will be made is planned.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31026","31026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470493","2016-03-17","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the forecast deficit or surplus run for each NHS trust in each of the (a) last and (b) next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31027","31027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470494","2016-03-17","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of local authorities that will exercise their right to levy the two per cent social care tax precept; and what assessment he has made of whether the revenue so raised will be sufficient to cover the funding gap for adult social care.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31013","31013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470495","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cancer patients in Lancashire started treatment within 62 days of an urgent referral from a GP in 2015.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31002","31002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470496","2016-03-17","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2016 to Question 22896, whether his Department records the number of junior doctors working 91 hours or more each week.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31011","31011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470497","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the NHS has made of the potential health risks of exposure to formaldehyde used in the manufacture of everyday products.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31000","31000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470498","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of current penalties to deter stone theft.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30959","30959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470499","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with police authorities on tackling stone theft.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30960","30960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470500","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on local economies of stone theft.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30958","30958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470502","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received from local authorities on tackling stone theft.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30956","30956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470503","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to tackle stone theft.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30957","30957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470504","2016-03-17","Home Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals were received by the Counter-Terrorism Internet Referral Unit in each of the last five years; how many of those referrals were investigated by that unit in full; how many of those investigations led to a recommendation being made for web content to be removed; and on how many occasions web content was removed following such a recommendation.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30893","30893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470506","2016-03-17","Home Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total (a) budget and (b) full-time equivalent workforce was of the Counter-Terrorism Internet Referral Unit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30894","30894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470507","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases related to the Independent Police Complaints Commission  have been referred back to the police for investigation in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30882","30882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470508","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in what circumstances the Independent Police Complaints Commission can refer a case back to the police.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30881","30881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470509","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has for post-conflict assistance in Burundi.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30922","30922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470510","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which (a) fixed and (b) mobile structures funded by her Department in Area C of the Occupied Palestinian Territory have been (i) demolished and (ii) confiscated by the Israeli authorities in (A) 2015 and (B) 2016.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30875","30875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470512","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the value of UK-funded structures that were demolished or confiscated in Area C of the Occupied Palestinian Territory in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30873","30873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470513","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's decision making process is on the (a) provision and (b) removal of (i) bilateral and (ii) other aid assistance programmes.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30874","30874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470514","2016-03-17","Department for International Development","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many and what proportion of officials of her Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in each of the last five years; and what proportion of total sick leave that leave was in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30865","30865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470515","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds on how many buildings the construction of which was funded by the (a) UK and (b) EU there are in the (i) Gaza Strip and (ii) other Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30955","30955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470517","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what contingency plans her Department has for additional support to Burundi in the event of a further escalation of violence in that country.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30924","30924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470518","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to reinstate the bilateral aid programme with Burundi.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30923","30923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470519","2016-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many witnesses have been cross-examined in a family court by the alleged perpetrator of abuse against them who is acting as litigant in person in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30979","30979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470520","2016-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2016 to Question 30414, on terrorism; Hyde Park, if the Secretary of State for Justice will support the Hyde Park victims by providing financial assistance outwith the Legal Aid Agency process.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30969","30969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470521","2016-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether recent representations have been made to his Department about the extent to which former employees of Just Solutions International (JSI) followed proper procedures in accepting employment in the private sector that was related to their previous work for JSI.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30987","30987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470523","2016-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of officials of his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in each of the last five years; and what proportion of total sick leave that leave was in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30864","30864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470524","2016-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many and which courts in England and Wales court counters have closed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30911","30911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470525","2016-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many citizens of each other EU member state were convicted in the UK of (a) murder, (b) sexual offences and (c) serious violent crimes in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30997","30997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470526","2016-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national offenders from each other EU member state serving a custodial sentence in the UK in each of the last 10 years have been transferred to serve the remainder of their sentence in another EU member state.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30998","30998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470528","2016-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many EU nationals were convicted of a criminal offence in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31025","31025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470529","2016-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national offenders of each nationality are serving custodial sentences of (a) less than six months, (b) six months to one year, (c) one year to two years, (d) two years to three years, (e) three years to four years, (f) four years to five years, (g) five years to 10 years and (h) more than 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31039","31039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470530","2016-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many public interest immunity applications her Department has (a) received and (b) approved in the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30968","30968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470531","2016-03-17","Prime Minister","2016-03-14","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will respond to the open letter from the Yorkshire Post entitled Mr Cameron please don't ignore our nightmare, dated Tuesday 26 January 2016.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30973","30973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470533","2016-03-16","Prime Minister","2016-03-14","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on compliance with Privy Council rules.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31032","31032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470534","2016-03-16","Prime Minister","2016-03-14","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to issue guidance on adherence to Privy Council rules in the period preceding the EU referendum.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31033","31033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470535","2016-03-16","Prime Minister","2016-03-14","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will carry out an investigation into whether there was a breach of Privy Council rules in relation to the story in The Sun of 9 March 2016 relating to HM The Queen and the referendum on EU membership.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31034","31034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470536","2016-03-16","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many foreign-registered HGVs entered the UK in 2015.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30995","30995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470537","2016-03-17","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress he has made on the electrification of the Leeds- Harrogate-York railway line.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31010","31010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470539","2016-03-17","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the level of uptake of low-emission vehicles has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31044","31044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470540","2016-03-17","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which organisation or company has been commissioned to conduct further environmental impact studies regarding possible expansions at (a) Heathrow and (b) Gatwick Airport.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30984","30984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470541","2016-03-16","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department has allocated to Plymouth City Council for pothole maintenance since 2010; and what estimate he has made of how many potholes have been repaired as a result of that funding.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30961","30961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470542","2016-03-21","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparative assessment he has made of the safety of railways in the UK and other European countries.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30992","30992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470544","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department has allocated to Solihull Metropolitan Borough Council for local road maintenance in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31018","31018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470545","2016-03-17","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 27209, on British Transport Police: finance, what assessment he has made of the operational implications of the planned reduction in the British Transport Police budget in 2016-17.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30898","30898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470546","2016-03-17","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on commissioning an independent Road Safety Management Capacity Review.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30892","30892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470547","2016-03-17","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reports he has had from Highways England on the recent closure of the M5 between Junction 5 and Junction 4A northbound due to a gantry removal; and if he will publish each of those reports on that closure.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30891","30891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470549","2016-03-16","Department for Transport","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Le Bureau d'Enguetes et d'Analyses report into Andreas Lubitz, published on 13 March 2016, if his Department will bring forward proposals to enable airlines to access mental health records of pilots within their employment.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30876","30876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470551","2016-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his Department's policy to accept data protection forms relating to queries arising from hon. Members' casework by email.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30872","30872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470552","2016-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost to the public purse was of a work capability assessment case that ended in appeal from the beginning of the assessment process to the outcome and implementation of the appeal in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30889","30889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470553","2016-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2016 to Question 30251, how many universal credit claimants have (a) applied for a back payment of more than one month, (b) received a back payment of more than one month and (c) received a back payment of one month.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30989","30989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470555","2016-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2016 to Question 30251, how much expenditure has been incurred on back payments to universal credit claimants; and how much additional expenditure would have been incurred had back payments been allowed to exceed one month.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30990","30990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470556","2016-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what scope there is for new claimants of universal credit to negotiate the terms of their claimant commitment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30974","30974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470557","2016-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the minimum income floor on levels of relative child poverty.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30985","30985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470558","2016-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of universal credit on the number of children in relative poverty.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30986","30986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470560","2016-03-16","Cabinet Office","2016-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been employed on zero-hours contracts in (a) Burnley and (b) Lancashire in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30940","30940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470561","2016-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 14 March 2016, Official Report, on unemployment, if he will publish the Government's employer engagement strategy referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31040","31040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470562","2016-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department received from the European Social Fund between (a) 2007 and 2014 and (b) 2014 and the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31047","31047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470563","2016-03-16","HM Treasury","2016-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many foreign nationals living in the UK have been (a) investigated and (b) prosecuted for a fraudulent child benefit claim for a child living in the EU in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31049","31049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470564","2016-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2016 to Question 30367, at which schools in East London Jobcentre Plus plans to offer Support for Schools in the 2015-16 academic year.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31015","31015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/470565","2016-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average time taken to provide reimbursement when a benefit sanction is overturned by appeal in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31030","31030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/475581","2016-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment she has made of the effect of recent floods on small businesses.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904152","904152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479378","2016-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to put in place a blue belt to protect marine habitats and species.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904164","904164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479379","2016-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the contribution of farmers and landowners to supporting bees and pollinators.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Fysh","Marcus Fysh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904167","904167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461209","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to UK businesses of implementing EU harmonised legislation.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30817","30817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461210","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many enquires Acas received from (a) employees and (b) employers (i) from each employment sector and (ii) relating to each topic on its database in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30831","30831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461212","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many referrals Acas made to each public body relating to each (a) employment sector and (b) topic on its database in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30832","30832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461214","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many arbitration proceedings were started by Acas (a) in each employment sector and (b) relating to each topic on its database in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30833","30833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461215","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the proportion of the working population in Southampton which was working in small retail outlets over the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30844","30844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461217","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the proportion of weekend retail transactions which have been conducted on a Sunday over the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30845","30845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461225","2016-03-15","Department for International Development","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has produced a cross-departmental strategy for the UK to implement the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30790","30790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461226","2016-03-15","HM Treasury","2016-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of his proposals to abolish Class 2 National Insurance contributions on low-earning theatre actors and workers.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30806","30806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461228","2016-03-16","HM Treasury","2016-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of UK policies on tax and overseas territories on the effectiveness of Government steps to tackle global poverty.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30819","30819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461230","2016-03-16","HM Treasury","2016-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies on making country-by-country tax reports public of the survey results published by Christian Aid in September 2015 on the attitudes of FTSE100 companies to that issue.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30820","30820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461231","2016-03-15","HM Treasury","2016-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies on corporate taxation of the OECD's report, Countering harmful tax practices more effectively, taking into account transparency and substance, published in September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30815","30815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461236","2016-03-15","HM Treasury","2016-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what work his Department is undertaking on establishing the amount of income tax and national insurance that is paid by people who were non-UK nationals at the time of issue of their national insurance number; if his Department will undertake that analysis by nationality; and what plans his Department has to publish the outcome of such work.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30843","30843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461237","2016-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Questions 26101 and 29935, if he will publish the data referred to in the latter Answer as the basis for the statement that even if all authorities increase council tax by the maximum under the referendum principles, it will be lower in 2019-20 in real terms compared to 2010.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30849","30849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461242","2016-03-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Changing Places toilets are provided by each local authority in North West England.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30797","30797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461243","2016-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding his Department has provided for (a) museums and (b) heritage in (i) the East Midlands and (ii) Nottinghamshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30795","30795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461245","2016-03-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations he has received from Nottinghamshire County Council and the Heritage Lottery Fund on the proposed closure of the DH Lawrence Heritage Centre in Eastwood, Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30796","30796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461249","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on the UK tourism sector of the French ban on parity clauses for online travel agents.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30811","30811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461250","2016-03-15","Department for Education","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, within what timescale the Risk Protection Arrangement will cover (a) the costs of temporary accommodation while the original building is reinstated and (b) all other storm-related costs incurred by Burnley Road Academy.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30851","30851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461251","2016-03-15","Department for Education","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will update the actuarial analysis used for the Risk Protection Arrangement to include the effect of the recent storms in the assessment of exposure to risk.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30818","30818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461254","2016-03-16","Department for Education","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps Ofsted is taking to ensure that home schooled children are (a) taught about British values and (b) integrated into British society.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30801","30801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461257","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations she made on raising the EU's 2030 greenhouse gas target at the Environment Council on 4 March 2016.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30791","30791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461258","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will ask her German counterpart to supply the Government with emissions data from new ultra super-critical coal-fired power stations in that country; and if she will place that data in the Library.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30808","30808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461260","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will ask her Chinese and Japanese counterparts to supply the Government with cost data relating to their new ultra super-critical coal-fired power stations.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30810","30810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461262","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to prevent electricity shortages in the winter of 2016-17.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30822","30822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461263","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she was consulted about the decision to remove the discussion on raising EU climate ambition in light of the Paris Agreement from the European Council agenda for 17 to 18 March 2016.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30799","30799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461264","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which Minister in her Department is planned will lead work on Energy Union negotiations with other EU member states and the European Commission.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30800","30800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461266","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what submission she has made to the Prime Minister in preparation for the European Council on 17-18 March on the proposal to raise the EU's greenhouse gas target for 2030 to take account of the Paris Agreement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30826","30826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461268","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what infrastructure the UK has in place to ensure that households and businesses do not face energy shortages in the next (a) five and (b) 10 years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30838","30838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461269","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the UK's energy capacity can keep up with demand.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30839","30839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461271","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's governance arrangements are for the smart meter rollout.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30829","30829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461273","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's project management arrangements are for the smart meter rollout.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30830","30830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461274","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2016 to Question 29325, how much of the 0.6GW diesel generating capacity is (a) privately owned and (b) owned by the Government; and which companies are involved in providing that capacity.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30852","30852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461277","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she plans to take to ensure that suppliers that are awarded smart meter derogations relating to in-home displays provide alternatives to such devices that are appropriate for all energy customers.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30853","30853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461278","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of making all smart meter derogations subject to randomised control trials.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30854","30854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461279","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the smart meter roll out public awareness campaign led by Smart Energy GB.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30855","30855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461282","2016-03-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 23417, whether she plans to issue a direction to hold a Contracts for Difference round for carbon capture and storage.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30856","30856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461283","2016-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage consumers to buy local produce.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30841","30841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461284","2016-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate she has made of the (a) annual contribution to the economy of food production and (b) number of people employed in the food production industry.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30842","30842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461287","2016-03-16","Department for Transport","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government plans to ratify the 2004 Ballast Water Management Convention.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30802","30802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461288","2016-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the economic, ecological and public health effects on the UK of aquatic invasive species introduced by shipping discharging ballast water.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30803","30803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461291","2016-03-16","Department for Transport","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to reduce the risk to the UK (a) posed by ballast water and (b) that diseases such as cholera may be transferred around the world through ballast water given rises in sea water temperature.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30804","30804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461292","2016-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on developing a futures market for dairy in the UK; and when she expects to implement that futures market.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30809","30809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461296","2016-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UN and African Union missions in South Sudan; and what discussions he has had with the UN since the publication of its report, Assessment Mission by the Office of the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights to improve human rights, accountability, reconciliation and capacity in South Sudan: detailed findings, published March 2016.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30812","30812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461298","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will publish a patient-friendly guide to inform responses to the consultation on proposals for a new Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30807","30807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461299","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average number of hours of weekly respite or support family carers are able to access; and what targets his Department has for such provision.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30816","30816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461306","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking in response to the Oxleas Plus supplement option for pensions offered by Oxleas NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30821","30821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461308","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to signpost commissioners to other appropriate services since the decision was taken not to prescribe specialist psychological services for deaf people as a specialised service; and what (a) number and (b) proportion of clinical commissioning groups commission specialist psychological services for deaf people.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30834","30834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461310","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the proportion of people aged (a) under and (b) over 18 who have a diagnosable mental health condition who access medical support.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30835","30835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461311","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2016 to Question 30123, on prescriptions: learning disability, what he plans to include in the programme of work to reduce inappropriate prescribing; and what the timetable for that programme is.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30836","30836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461312","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2016 to Question 23475, on what date in March 2016 he expects the first report on progress against the referral to treatment element of the Early Intervention Psychosis access standard to be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30837","30837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461314","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2016 to Question 29233, how much of the annual allocation of 130 million for carers' breaks has been spent so far in 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30859","30859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461316","2016-03-16","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he last met junior doctors or their representatives.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30858","30858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461317","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms are in place to ensure that the contracting out of healthcare provision to the private and charity sector does not lead to fragmentation or waste in NHS provision.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30846","30846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461319","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase stem cell donations from the 16 to 30 age group.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30847","30847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461321","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2016 to Question 30239, if her Department will collect centrally information on the number of warrants that are being issued in order to establish whether women are being trafficked.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30860","30860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461322","2016-03-15","Home Office","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Prevent strategy.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30840","30840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461325","2016-03-15","Home Office","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many initially rejected visa applications have been reconsidered as a result of changes in circumstances during the assessment process.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30823","30823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461327","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the UK has requested information (a) under the Prm convention DNA sharing, (b) relating to the European Arrest Warrant about criminal records, (c) from the EU Passenger Name Record sharing scheme, (d) from a Europol Joint Investigation Team, (e) under the Schengen Information System, (f) from Europol's HAVEN project to combat sexual abuse and trafficking and (g) from other EU member states about stadium bans and previous offenders at football matches.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30794","30794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461329","2016-03-15","Department for International Development","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to protect and support the rights of women and girls in South Sudan.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30813","30813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461330","2016-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much in legal aid was granted to prison inmates in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30825","30825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461333","2016-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many inmates of Wakefield prison have been granted legal aid to pursue civil action in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30827","30827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461334","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will ensure that the Government publishes a family impact test in respect of all future primary and secondary legislation.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30789","30789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461335","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make representations to Highways England and Transport for the North on extending the A64 dual carriageway to Barton Hill.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30814","30814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461337","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to lower the blood alcohol limit for drivers from 80mg to 50mg of alcohol per 100ml.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30848","30848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461339","2016-03-15","Department for Education","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the study of STEM subjects by girls at GCSE.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30857","30857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461340","2016-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the number of disabled people who will lose their entitlement to the (a) standard rate of and (b) enhanced rate of personal independence payment as a result of changes to the assessment criteria regarding the use of aids and appliances for activities five and six.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30850","30850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461342","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time is for a reassessment of an award for disability living allowance to be conducted before a person is migrated to the personal independence payment.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30828","30828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461344","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and which family test assessments he has seen in the last six months.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30824","30824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461346","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to enforce section 54 of the Pensions Act 2008.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30793","30793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461347","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on employers offering higher salaries to employees who opt of occupational pension schemes.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30792","30792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461349","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what social security benefits are being claimed by patients in (a) Ashworth, (b) Broadmoor and (c) Rampton high security psychiatric hospitals.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30805","30805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/461351","2016-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Changing Places toilets are provided at his Department's offices in the North West of England.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30798","30798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459286","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what change there has been to the number of deaf people achieving further and higher education qualifications in the last five years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30611","30611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459287","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the changes to the Disabled Students' Allowance on the number of university applications in the forthcoming academic year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30639","30639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459288","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to conduct an equality impact assessment on the effect of changes to the Disabled Students' Allowance.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30650","30650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459289","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2016 to Question 26318, what the reasons are for the differences between the total amount of arrears owed by the 92 employers named and shamed by his Department on 5 February 2016 for non-compliance with the national minimum wage and the total amount of the financial penalties imposed on those employers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30640","30640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459290","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information the Certification Officer holds on the number of members of the National Union of Mineworkers in each year from 2003-04 to present.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30658","30658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459291","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information the Certification Officer holds on the number of members of the Northumberland branch of the National Union of Mineworkers in each year from 2003-04 to present.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30659","30659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459292","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance the Certification Officer has produced for trades unions on requirements to compile and maintain an accurate register of members; and what monitoring the Certification Officer undertakes of trades unions' compliance with those requirements.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30660","30660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459293","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what sanctions the Certification Officer can implement against trades unions which fail to compile and maintain an accurate register of members; and on what occasions such sanctions have been used in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30661","30661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459294","2016-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 25985, whether he plans to publish his response to his Department's consultation on tips, gratuities, service and cover charges before the period of purdah for the EU membership referendum begins.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30709","30709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459295","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many names were provided to Ministers to enable them to take a formal decision on the appointment of the Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30687","30687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459296","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the actual or potential conflicts of interest declared by the Pubs Code Adjudicator, Mr Paul Newby, prior to his appointment.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30688","30688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459297","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applicants to the Pubs Code Adjudicator role declared actual or potential conflicts of interest.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30689","30689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459298","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department or its employment agency adviser had with Mr Paul Newby about actual and potential conflicts of interest prior to his appointment as the Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30690","30690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459299","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people applied to the Pubs Code Adjudicator vacancy; and how many such people were (a) longlisted and (b) shortlisted.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30691","30691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459300","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for how long Saxton Bampfylde Ltd has acted as an employment adviser to his Department.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30692","30692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459301","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department or Saxton Bampfylde Ltd approached any person to apply for the Pubs Code Adjudicator vacancy.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30693","30693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459302","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations were (a) made by his Department to pub companies and (b) received from such companies on the recruitment of the Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30694","30694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459303","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people were invited to interviews for the post of Pubs Code Adjudicator; and how many people attended such interviews.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30695","30695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459304","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who was on the interview panels for the recruitment of the Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30696","30696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459305","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department had with Mr Paul Newby's employer on his contributions to the draft Pubs Code.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30697","30697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459306","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what role Ministers played in the recruitment process for the Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30698","30698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459307","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applicants to the Pubs Code Adjudicator vacancy were subject to departmental clearance checks; and how many applicants did not pass those checks and for what reasons.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30699","30699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459308","2016-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to answer Question 28906, tabled on 3 March 2016 by the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, on the living wage.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30776","30776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459309","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that the manufacturing sector in Northern Ireland is able to contribute to the UK aerospace industry.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30756","30756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459310","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Pubs Code Adjudicator on (a) the length of leases given to pub tenants by owners of pubs, (b) implementation of the market rent only option for pub tenants and (c) the independence of the adjudicator from pub companies.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30726","30726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459311","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what cross departmental work his Department has undertaken with the Department for Education to ensure that the needs of business are met by the education system.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30763","30763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459312","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that businesses are able to recruit employees with the required level of skills.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30764","30764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459313","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister for Skills of 10 March 2016, what assessment he has made of the potential take-up of the apprenticeship levy by employers.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30769","30769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459314","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the potential number of large employers who will require existing training expenditure as a result of the introduction of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30770","30770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459315","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the nature of the contribution of Mr Paul Newby was to the drafting of and consultation process for the Pubs Code; and when those contributions were delivered.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30732","30732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459316","2016-03-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Skills of 10 March 2016, whether the 1.5 billion raised by the apprenticeship levy in England referred to will be part of the 2.5 billion for 2019-20 or additional to it.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30771","30771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459317","2016-03-15","Cabinet Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing requirements on responsible tax behaviour into government procurement policy.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30757","30757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459318","2016-03-15","Cabinet Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of officials of his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in each of the last five years; and what proportion of total sick leave that leave was in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30645","30645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459319","2016-03-15","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he has made to date on negotiating with the European institutions for permission to apply a zero-rate of VAT on women's sanitary products.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30606","30606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459320","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of (a) minimum pack-size requirements and (b) other elements of the new Tobacco Products Directive.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30625","30625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459321","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of when the tax optimisation for cigarettes will be reached.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30626","30626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459322","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of future tobacco excise increases on the black market in tobacco products.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30627","30627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459323","2016-03-15","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the European Commission to publish the VAT Action Plan; and what plans he has to respond to that plan.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30608","30608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459324","2016-03-15","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) Government's net contribution to EU institutions and (b) UK's current account balance with those institutions in 2014; and what estimate the European Commission has made of that contribution and that account balance.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30622","30622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459325","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he intends to answer the letter dated 12 January 2016 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms Sara Lyons, transferred from the Department for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30630","30630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459326","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs supported by the Scotch whisky industry in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30700","30700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459327","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the value to the economy of the Scotch whisky industry.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30701","30701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459328","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to UK firms of implementing Capital Requirement Directive IV.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30666","30666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459329","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the level of duty on Scotch whisky on the export of that product.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30667","30667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459330","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 26567, how many (a) calls and (b) enquiries the Pay and Work Rights helpline received (i) by each employment sector of caller and (ii) regarding each of the topics on the Pay and Work Rights Helpline's database.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30738","30738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459331","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how (a) much funding has been paid to and (b) many full-time equivalent staff were employed by the Advisory. Conciliation and Arbitration Service in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30781","30781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459332","2016-03-15","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential costs and benefits of making available to the public country-by-country taxation reports submitted to HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) by multinational companies; and whether HMRC plans to make those reports available to taxation authorities in other countries.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30785","30785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459333","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the proportion of total duty paid on alcohol in the EU that is paid by people in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30713","30713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459335","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date the leases for HM Revenue and Customs offices Abbey House and Parkside Court will end.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30728","30728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459336","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help people with disabilities with the cost of housing in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Mary Robinson","Mary Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30723","30723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459337","2016-03-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether local authorities are required to consider environmental factors when awarding contracts.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30777","30777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459338","2016-03-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to make available to the Northern Ireland Executive funds received from the Government's application to the EU Solidarity Fund to help flood affected areas.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30747","30747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459339","2016-03-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of officials of his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in each of the last five years; and what proportion of total sick leave that leave was in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30646","30646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459340","2016-03-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many and what proportion of officials of his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in each of the last five years; and what proportion of total sick leave that leave was in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30644","30644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459341","2016-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people learn to swim.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30734","30734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459342","2016-03-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential of the arts to contribute to mental well-being for people with mental illness; and what programmes his Department has in place to help deliver that contribution.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30741","30741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459343","2016-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral statement by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, Official Report, column 426, on arms sales to Saudi Arabia, what UK-supplied defence equipment has been used in Yemen; what arms export licences were issued for that equipment; and whether any arms export licences for that equipment have now been revoked.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30754","30754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459344","2016-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 21 July 2015 to Question 7583 and 9 September 2014 to Question 207819, how many (a) military, (b) civilian and (c) liaison personnel are now stationed at each of those sites in Saudi Arabia; how many of each of those personnel are in locations where Saudi Arabia plans and executes military operations in Yemen; and how many (i) military, (ii) civilian and (iii) liaison personnel are in the command and control centre for Saudi airstrikes in Yemen.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30727","30727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459345","2016-03-15","Department for Education","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations her Department has received from businesses on the inclusion of design technology within the EBacc qualification.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30762","30762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459346","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the contribution of nurseries to improving literacy rates.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30751","30751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459347","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support the academies risk protection arrangement is providing to schools affected by the recent floods.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30744","30744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459348","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2016 to Question 28606, how many cleaners working in buildings managed by her Department are paid at the rate of (a) 7.85 and (b) 9.15.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30664","30664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459349","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policy on extending 30 hour free childcare to three and four year olds of the findings of the Family and Childcare Trust 2016 childcare survey on the ability of nurseries to provide places for the current offer of 15 hours.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30662","30662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459350","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to make the entitlement to an early education place a legal requirement.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30663","30663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459351","2016-03-15","Department for Education","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children's social workers were employed by London local authorities in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30676","30676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459352","2016-03-15","Department for Education","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department takes to ensure that university training of children's social workers is maintained at a high standard.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30677","30677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459353","2016-03-15","Department for Education","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department provides for local authorities to share best practice on children's social work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30678","30678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459354","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she plans to take forward talks on reaching an intergovernmental agreement with Ireland on expanding electricity interconnection capacity in response to the conclusions of the National Infrastructure Commission's report on Smart Power, published in March 2016.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30686","30686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459355","2016-03-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Memorandum of Understanding on renewable energy trade agreed between the UK and Ireland in January 2013, what progress has been made on reaching an intergovernmental agreement with Ireland.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30685","30685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459356","2016-03-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2016 to Question 28603, how many cleaners working in her Department are paid at the rate of (a) 7.85 and (b) 9.15.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30737","30737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459357","2016-03-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what support her Department plans to provide to communities that will be affected by closure of coal-fired power stations.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30788","30788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459358","2016-03-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding the Government allocated to incentivising installation of (a) solar panels and (b) home insulation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30733","30733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459359","2016-03-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent progress has been made on the Government's application to the EU Solidarity Fund to help flood affected areas.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30729","30729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459360","2016-03-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the Government's recent application to the EU Solidarity Fund to help flood affected areas.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30730","30730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459361","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to improve the speed with which payments are made to small farmers under the Basic Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30742","30742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459362","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to promote the export of Scotch whisky.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30712","30712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459363","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to improve the protection of areas of outstanding natural beauty in marine areas.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30628","30628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459364","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress she has made in setting out and implementing a national strategy for areas of outstanding natural beauty; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30629","30629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459365","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been identified as illegally importing puppies under the Pet Travel Scheme during the Dogs Trust's pilot quarantine initiative.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30615","30615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459366","2016-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her (a) ministerial colleagues and (b) the European Commission on the potential effects of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership on (i) animal welfare standards, (ii) environmental protection and (iii) food standards.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30617","30617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459367","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions have occurred or proceedings been commenced as the result of the seizure of illegally imported puppies taken into the Dogs Trust's care via its pilot quarantine initiative since the start of that pilot.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30604","30604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459368","2016-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of crop fed anaerobic digestion on food production and land rents.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30612","30612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459369","2016-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons waste reduction, improved resource efficiency and increasing recycling rates were not included in her Department's Single Department Plan: 2015 to 2020, published on 19 January 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30616","30616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459370","2016-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of officials of her Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in each of the last five years; and what proportion of total sick leave that leave was in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30679","30679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459371","2016-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations were made by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Environment and Rural Affairs at the EU Environment Council on 4 March 2016 on the EU action plan for the circular economy.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30707","30707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459372","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the recommendations of the Pitt Review on the 2007 floods, whether her Department plans to (a) change building regulations to make homes more resilient in flood risk areas and (b) increase the adoption of sustainable drainage systems in order to better manage urban flood risk in the long term.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30637","30637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459373","2016-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish her Department's Spending Review Settlement letter from HM Treasury.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30623","30623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459374","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what expenses were claimed by the five most senior people at the Environment Agency during the last financial year.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30631","30631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459375","2016-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterparts in countries that are members of the International Syria Support Group on reported Russian violations of the ceasefire in Syria.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30641","30641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459376","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a partition plan in Iraq relating to independence for Kurdish people.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30636","30636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459377","2016-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the extent of Russian support for Kurdish forces in Syria and that support's effect on the ceasefire and peace process in that country.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30642","30642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459378","2016-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many and what proportion of officials of his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in each of the last five years; and what proportion of total sick leave that leave was in each such year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30643","30643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459379","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who has (a) visited and (b) stayed at Chevening House since 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30669","30669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459380","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of Government support for Kurdish minority groups in Syria on the peace process in that country.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30668","30668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459381","2016-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what further consultation he plans to hold before a final decision is made on possible resettlement of the Chagos Islanders; whom that consultation will involve; and who will make that final decision.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30618","30618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459382","2016-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the timetable is for the outcome of the consultation on the resettlement of Chagos Islanders to the British Indian Ocean Territory and on the funding for that resettlement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30619","30619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459383","2016-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans not to make a final decision on resettlement of the Chagos Islanders until after the Supreme Court judgement on the 2008 decision of the House of Lords.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30620","30620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459384","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proposals the UK plans to take to the Nuclear Security Summit in Washington DC in March and April 2016; and whether he plans to attend that summit.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30783","30783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459385","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has received in the case brought at the International Court of Justice in the Hague from 8 March 2016 by the Marshall Islands against the UK and other states on obligations concerning negotiations relating to cessation of the nuclear arms race and to nuclear disarmament.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30784","30784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459386","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the firing of two long-range missiles from the Alborz mountain range by Iran.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30706","30706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459387","2016-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which overseas territories and crown dependencies have published registries of the beneficial ownership of the legally registered companies that are conducting business through their jurisdictions.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30786","30786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459388","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who will represent the Government at the UNHCR conference on the Syrian refugee crisis on 30 March 2016.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30780","30780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459389","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of civilians who have died in South East Turkey during the current conflict in that region.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30721","30721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459390","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Sudan on behalf of Telahoon Rata and Rev. Hassan Taour, arrested on 13 and 21 December 2015 respectively; and what information his Department holds on their (a) location and (b) physical and mental condition.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30739","30739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459391","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Turkish government on the conflict in South East Turkey and further steps to protect the civilian population in that region.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30722","30722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459392","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost was of transferring the services previously provided by the General Social Care Council (GSCC) to the Health and Care Professions Council after the GSCC was abolished in 2012.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30787","30787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459393","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what public awareness campaigns his Department has planned to improve awareness of work-related respiratory illness.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30719","30719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459394","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of closing down the General Social Care Council.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30718","30718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459395","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of winding up the College of Social Work.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30720","30720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459396","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with epilepsy in each of the last ten years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30716","30716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459397","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2016 to Question 29770, how much funding for (a) service fees and (b) allowances NHS England allocated to community pharmacies in (i) London and (ii) Hampstead and Kilburn constituency in (A) 2015-16 and (B) 2016-17.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30715","30715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459398","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to commission a National Clinical Audit on the number of avoidable deaths resulting from epilepsy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30761","30761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459399","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the life outcomes of people diagnosed with epilepsy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30758","30758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459400","2016-03-15","Cabinet Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of children aged under 18 resulting directly from epilepsy have been recorded in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30759","30759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459401","2016-03-15","Cabinet Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths resulting directly from epilepsy have been recorded in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30760","30760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459402","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of emergency respite places for people being cared for by family or friends in (a) England, (b) Birmingham and (c) Swindon.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30778","30778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459403","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of respite care and support for family carers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30779","30779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459404","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2016 to Question 28970, how much public funding for stem cell research has been allocated through the National Institute for Health Research in each year since 2003-04.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30710","30710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459405","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2016 to Question 28967, on stem cells: transplant surgery, which five transplant centres were found to be non-compliant with the NHS England specification.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30711","30711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459406","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the 2014 Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey to be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30670","30670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459407","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of women accessing mental health services experienced sexual or domestic abuse in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30671","30671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459408","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children and (b) adults of each gender have experienced (a) sexual and (b) physical abuse in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30672","30672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459409","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was to the NHS of prescriptions dispensed for psychopharmaceutical drugs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30673","30673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459410","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions have been dispensed for psychopharmaceutical drugs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30674","30674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459411","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides for local authorities to share best practice on adult social work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30675","30675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459412","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he intends to Answer the letter to him dated 2 January 2016 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr S Galsworthy.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30702","30702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459413","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were diagnosed with microcephaly in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30703","30703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459414","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Minister for Public Heath will meet representatives of (a) Public Health England and (b) NHS England to discuss services for families that have children with microcephaly.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30704","30704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459415","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what specialist support is available through the NHS for children with microcephaly and their families; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30638","30638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459416","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidelines are issued to providers of NHS services on marketing of NHS services alongside private services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30609","30609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459417","2016-03-15","Department of Health","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of lipreading and managing hearing loss classes available; and if he will ask Public Health England to investigate the availability of such classes.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30610","30610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459418","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle websites which promote and encourage anorexia; and what assessment she has made of the potential merits of making it a criminal offence to publish pro-anorexia material online.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30634","30634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459419","2016-03-15","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) unaccompanied children and (b) partners of refugees who had already been granted asylum in the UK (i) applied for and (ii) were granted asylum in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30647","30647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459420","2016-03-15","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) unaccompanied children and (b) partners of refugees who had already been granted asylum in the UK have a pending application for asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30648","30648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459421","2016-03-15","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to review the policy limiting the reuniting of refugee families to children under the age of 18 and partners of refugees who have been granted asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30649","30649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459422","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 23 February 2016 to Questions 27190, 27129, 27130 and 27131, what the nature and scope of the review of the Collective Passport Service is; which stakeholders and officials have been engaged on that review; when she plans to inform hon. Members about that review; when that review will be completed; and when the outcome of that review will be known.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30705","30705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459423","2016-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people under the age of 18 have been convicted under section 141A of the Criminal Justice Act 1998 since that Act's implementation; and what the average length of custodial sentence was received for such convictions.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30708","30708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459424","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria she plans to use for determining which non-governmental organisations will collaborate with Polaris on providing helpline services for trafficking victims; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30665","30665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459425","2016-03-15","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to develop a strategy to support BAME specialist domestic violence charities.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30607","30607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459426","2016-03-16","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of collecting data about the specific region or town of origin of all victims of human trafficking; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30684","30684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459427","2016-03-15","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of immigration cases were designated as complex in (a) 2015, (b) 2014 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30682","30682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459428","2016-03-15","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time was for immigration cases designated as complex in (a) 2015, (b) 2014 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30683","30683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459429","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with the Department for Culture, Media and Sport on the tendering process for masts for the Emergency Services Mobile Communications Programme's Extended Areas Services project.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30752","30752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459430","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions the Government has had with mobile operator EE on the Emergency Services Mobile Communications Programme's Extended Areas Services project.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30753","30753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459431","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) a ban on laser pens and (b) setting a minimum age for the purchase of laser pens; and what steps he is taking to ensure online sales of laser pens are regulated.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30714","30714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459432","2016-03-14","Cabinet Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many nationals of other EU member states who were (a) originally born outside of the EU and (b) originally born outside of the EU and became a citizen of that EU member state entered the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30748","30748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459433","2016-03-14","Cabinet Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many nationals of other EU member states have given birth in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30749","30749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459434","2016-03-14","Cabinet Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people from other EU member states have (a) entered the UK in each year since 2006 and (b) are living in the UK; and under what heading those people are classified in the provisions of the Immigration (European Economic Area) Regulations 2006.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30750","30750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459435","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people with a criminal conviction have been deported in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30746","30746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459436","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to announce new mast sites for the Emergency Service Mobile Communications Programme's Extended Areas Service project.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30736","30736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459437","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2016 to Question 29595, what the reasons were for refusal of the Tier 2 (Minister of Religion) Visas.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30743","30743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459438","2016-03-14","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK is taking to support the provision of climate risk insurance to people who are most vulnerable to the impact of climate change; and how much funding she plans to allocate to such support.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30717","30717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459439","2016-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2016 to Question 28610, which outsourced providers his Department uses for cleaning services; and if he will request information from those providers on the rate of pay for cleaners providing services for his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30745","30745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459440","2016-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2016 to Question 27240, on family courts: domestic violence, when his Department last reviewed the security standards referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30621","30621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459441","2016-03-15","Prime Minister","2016-03-10","To ask the Prime Minister, how many special advisers have notified the Prime Minister's Principal Secretary that they are supporting ministers who are campaigning against the Government's position on the EU referendum.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30652","30652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459442","2016-03-15","Prime Minister","2016-03-10","To ask the Prime Minister, how many special advisers have (a) requested and (b) been granted the Prime Minister's approval for working part or full-time for a Leave campaign in the EU referendum.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30651","30651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459443","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to implement the installation and use of audio-visual displays on public transport vehicles.","Biography information for John McNally","John Mc Nally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30653","30653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459444","2016-03-14","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans there are to sell property of the British Transport Police.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30633","30633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459445","2016-03-14","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much security guards in his Department are paid.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30614","30614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459446","2016-03-14","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what commercial sensitivity applies to section 106 (staff using handheld tablets) and section 28.1 (movement of staff) of the agreement between NXET Trains Limited and his Department of 15 July 2014 regarding the Essex Thameside franchise.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30602","30602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459447","2016-03-14","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether there is any provision in the agreement between NXET Trains Limited and his Department of 15 July 2014 on the Essex Thameside franchise relating to the closure of ticket offices.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30603","30603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459448","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason a number of the Committed Obligations agreed between NXET Trains Limited and his Department on 15 July 2014 regarding the Essex Thameside franchise are redacted in the published version of the agreement.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30605","30605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459449","2016-03-14","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will commission a cost-benefit analysis on the potential benefit of extending the M54 to Shrewsbury on Shrewsbury and the surrounding area.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30782","30782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459450","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to improve roads to ensure that they are safe for both motorists and cyclists.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30755","30755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459451","2016-03-14","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the consolidated local transport budget for Greater Manchester after implementation of the devolution deal (a) in total and (b) per capita.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30724","30724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459452","2016-03-14","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) total and (b) per capita consolidated local transport budget for London is for (i) 2015-16 and (ii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30725","30725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459453","2016-03-14","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding the Government has allocated to cycling schemes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30735","30735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459454","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information he holds on whether Network Rail plans to release a contribution to the cost of a disabled access footbridge at Bingham railway station in Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30767","30767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459455","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the Cross Government Working Group on Drones to finish its work; and when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30772","30772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459456","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Cross Government Working Group on Drones will conduct a detailed examination of the security threats posed by drones as part of its work.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30773","30773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459457","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Cross Government Working Group on Drones will examine the feasibility of introducing a system of registration for drones, including an element of mandatory training and evaluation for the larger classes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30774","30774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459458","2016-03-15","Department for Transport","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure disabled access on all platforms at Bingham railway station.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30775","30775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459459","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much security guards in his Department are paid.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30613","30613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459460","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that absent parents financially support their children.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30635","30635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459461","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the risk register for the universal credit programme.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30624","30624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459462","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the proportion of (a) mothers and (b) fathers in the labour force who were not able to claim statutory parental leave because of the requirement for 26 weeks of continuous employment with the same employer in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30632","30632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459463","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many patients in (a) Ashworth, (b) Broadmoor and (c) Rampton high security psychiatric hospitals received personal independence payment between 2012 and 2015; and what the average weekly payment of that benefit was to such recipients.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30654","30654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459464","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many patients in (a) Ashworth, (b) Broadmoor and (c) Rampton high security psychiatric hospitals received income support between 2012 and 2015; and what the average weekly payment of that benefit was to such recipients.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30655","30655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459465","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many patients in (a) Ashworth, (b) Broadmoor and (c) Rampton high security psychiatric hospitals received employment and support allowance between 2012 and 2015; and what the average weekly payment of that benefit was to such recipients.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30656","30656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459466","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many patients in (a) Ashworth, (b) Broadmoor and (c) Rampton high security psychiatric hospitals received pension credit between 2012 and 2015; and what the average weekly payment of that credit was to such recipients.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30657","30657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459467","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been migrated from disability living allowance to personal independence payments in (a) the UK (b) London and (c) Hornsey and Wood Green constituency since the introduction of those payments.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30731","30731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459468","2016-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to update the document, Medical guidance for DLA decision makers (child cases): staff guide, last updated on 8 December 2015, to incorporate references to congenital, inherited or acquired heart disease.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30740","30740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459470","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the administration of changes to migrant benefits proposed under the planned emergency brake on in-work benefits for EU citizens in employment in the UK.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30766","30766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459471","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2016 to Question 29762, on universal credit, how long it took to complete the reset.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30768","30768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459472","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with (a) disability charities and other third sector groups, (b) disabled people, their families and informal carers and (c) organisations led by disabled people on his Department's planned white paper on improving support for disabled people and people with health conditions.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30765","30765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459473","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people using the Chorlton Benefit Delivery Centre applied for funeral payments in each month in 2015; how many of those applications were granted; and what the average amount awarded was in each of those months.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30681","30681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/459474","2016-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people using the Chorlton Benefit Delivery Centre required a mandatory reconsideration of funeral payments in each month in 2015; and how many of the decisions on those reconsiderations were in the claimant's favour.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30680","30680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/477985","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department plans to provide to refugees from Burundi.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904132","904132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/477986","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to support refugees in camps in the Middle East.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904134","904134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/477987","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that children's right to education is protected across the world.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904130","904130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/477988","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress has been made on delivering the commitments made to Jordan at the Syria Donors Conference.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904137","904137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/477989","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of Overseas Development Assistance funding the Government plans will be spent by (a) her Department and (b) other government departments in the current Parliament; and what measures are in place to monitor how that funding is spent.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904138","904138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/477990","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the Government is providing to enable developing countries to harness mobile phone technology.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904133","904133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/477991","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to protect schools in conflict zones.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904136","904136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/477992","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of Overseas Development Assistance funding the Government plans will be spent by (a) her Department and (b) other government departments in the current Parliament; and what measures are in place to monitor how that funding is spent.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904131","904131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/477993","2016-03-16","Department for International Development","2016-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the Government is providing to enable developing countries to harness mobile phone technology.","Biography information for Lucy Frazer","Lucy Frazer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904139","904139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458860","2016-03-14","Attorney General","2016-03-09","To ask the Attorney General, what the cost to the public purse of legal proceedings involving actions taken by the Government against (a) devolved administrations, (b) local government in England and (c) non-departmental public bodies has been in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30454","30454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458861","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that non-approved, sub-standard or fake safety products are not sold or passed on to the consumer.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30467","30467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458862","2016-03-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answers of 11 February and 2 March 2016 to Questions 27077 and 28765, if he will commission a review of the legality of arms sales to Saudi Arabia which takes account of all recent representations on that matter.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30457","30457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458863","2016-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received from the Union of Construction Allied Trades and Technicians on the effect of proposed changes to the budget for training expertise of the Construction Industry Training Board on the future of the construction industry.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30416","30416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458864","2016-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate he has made of the number of (a) men and (b) women in each of the sectors covered by his Department's 11 industrial strategies.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30420","30420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458865","2016-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to promote opportunities to access high growth markets abroad to businesses in the Leeds City Region.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30397","30397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458866","2016-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to regulate the power level of laser pens offered for sale in Britain.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30477","30477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458867","2016-03-14","Cabinet Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, who is responsible for authorising pay rises of more than one per cent in (a) his Department and (b) HM Treasury; and what procedure is followed when it is proposed to grant a pay rise of more than one per cent to an adviser.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30455","30455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458868","2016-03-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure independent assurance of large tax settlements at HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30442","30442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458869","2016-03-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to offer compulsory purchase payments at 150 per cent of market value.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30437","30437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458870","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to consult on the draft Regulations to implement the Mutuals' Deferred Shares Act 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30412","30412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458871","2016-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost to (a) private and (b) public sector organisations of implementing the National Living Wage in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30418","30418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458872","2016-03-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the (a) administrative and (b) staff cost to local authorities of implementing the National Living Wage in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30419","30419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458873","2016-03-14","HM Treasury","2016-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total value of VAT arrears that had been owed for more than 12 months was recovered by HM Revenue and Customs in (a) Cardiff South and Penarth constituency, (b) Wales and (c) the UK in last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30450","30450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458874","2016-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what factors he took into account when setting the new state pension age cut-off date.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30391","30391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458875","2016-03-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will increase funding for local roads and Government support for local bus services.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30482","30482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458876","2016-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been charged under the Clean Neighbourhoods and Environment Act 2005 for selling private vehicles on public roads; and how many such cases were successfully appealed.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30441","30441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458877","2016-03-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which charities have received grant funding from his Department since the introduction of the anti-lobbying clause.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30411","30411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458878","2016-03-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to increase access to sporting activities for children in low income households.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30417","30417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458879","2016-03-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 28855, how much of that spending in each of the last three years is subject to the provisions of the International Development Act 2002.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30421","30421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458880","2016-03-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who is responsible for the future of the London 2012 athletics warm-up track.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30439","30439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458881","2016-03-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the extent of the rollout of super-fast broadband in the Northampton South constituency.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30395","30395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458882","2016-03-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2016 to Question 29543, which areas of the BBC are exempt from the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30400","30400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458883","2016-03-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which areas of the BBC Charter he will seek to reform in upcoming negotiations with the BBC Trust.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30401","30401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458884","2016-03-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 March 2016 to Question 29543, what steps he plans to take to reform the BBC's exposure to the Freedom of Information Act 2000 as part of the Charter Review.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30402","30402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458885","2016-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian casualties have resulted from direct UK military action in each theatre of operation in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30452","30452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458886","2016-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilians rescued from the Mediterranean Sea by the Royal Navy in the last two years requested medical evacuation; and to what locations such people were transported for treatment.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30453","30453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458887","2016-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has assessed the potential merits of giving the Rosyth Dockyard strategic asset status.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30509","30509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458888","2016-03-11","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential benefits of extending the 50 per cent cap on religious selection in free schools to all state-funded schools in England.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30443","30443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458889","2016-03-11","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of religious selection on the availability of school places and the number of parents who are unable to get their children into their local school.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30444","30444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458890","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of (a) divergences between schools' admission arrangements and (b) the effect of such divergence on parents' ability to navigate the admissions process.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30468","30468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458891","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 27310, if she will extend the remit of regional school commissioners to include an active role in monitoring the compliance of schools' admission policies with the School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30471","30471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458892","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 27309, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring religiously selective schools to prioritise looked-after and previously looked-after children without reference to religion in the upcoming consultation on the School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30415","30415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458893","2016-03-11","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2016 to Question 24532, which secondary schools took part in the 2015 summer school programme.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30406","30406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458894","2016-03-11","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2016 to Question 24532, how much funding from the pupil premium her Department plans to make available to support schools in delivering summer school programmes in 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30407","30407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458895","2016-03-11","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2016 to Question 24532, on pupils: disadvantaged, how many of the 2,171 secondary schools that chose to take part in the 2015 summer schools programme have confirmed that they will be taking part in 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30408","30408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458896","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department is giving to teachers to assist them with the new Key Stage 1 and Key Stage 2 tests.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30449","30449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458897","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many enterprise advisers her Department has appointed to work with (a) schools and (b) further edcuation colleges in England.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30445","30445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458898","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what administrative resources her Department is providing for enterprise advisers.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30446","30446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458899","2016-03-14","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial support her Department plans to provide to support enterprise advisers in their work in schools and colleges in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30447","30447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458900","2016-03-11","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is her policy that a school should be rated as requiring improvement by Ofsted if it does not teach sex and relationships education.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30389","30389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458901","2016-03-11","Department for Education","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of identified violations of the Schools Admissions Code since 2011 related to schools not properly prioritising the children of armed forces service personnel.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30390","30390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458902","2016-03-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Annex on a Comprehensive Franco-British Partnership on Civil Nuclear Energy, Franco-British Summit, dated 3 March 2016, if she will set out the evidential basis for the statement that civil nuclear energy helps to guarantee the UK's long-term energy independence and contributes to economic growth and the competitiveness of industries.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30427","30427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458903","2016-03-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will assess the progress all Government Departments are making on meeting the Government's carbon reduction targets and what steps the Government is taking to meet the target set in (a) the fourth carbon budget period 2023 to 2027 and (b) the fifth carbon budget period 2028 to 2032.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30479","30479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458904","2016-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the adequacy of filtration systems to remove microplastics prior to entry into the sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30409","30409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458905","2016-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department made of the adequacy of voluntary agreements to phase out microplastics from toiletries.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30410","30410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458906","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's Single Department Plan: 2015 to 2020, published on 19 February 2016, what discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on reforms to ensure that animals are only sent to slaughterhouses that meet high welfare standards.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30472","30472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458907","2016-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's Single departmental plan: 2015 to 2020, published on 19 February 2016, what steps she is taking to champion the use of the Groceries Code Adjudicator; and if she will support an extension of the Adjudicator's remit.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30461","30461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458908","2016-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his North Korean counterpart following that country's claims that it has nuclear warheads capable of being installed on ballistic missiles.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30438","30438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458909","2016-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Indian counterpart about the case of a 16 year old girl who was raped and set on fire in Greater Nioda on 9 March 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30435","30435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458910","2016-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support religious freedom in Tibet.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30436","30436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458911","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30448","30448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458912","2016-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Iran on the blocking by Hezbollah of humanitarian access to civilian areas in Syria in the last six months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30451","30451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458913","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 27828, what the average change in the level of pay will be for those junior doctors not expected to experience a rise in earnings as a result of pay protection.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30426","30426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458914","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government plans to make funding available to councils for care homes in addition to the two per cent council tax precept to cover costs arising from the increase in the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30413","30413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458915","2016-03-11","Department of Health","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what weekend visits he has made to front-line health service providers in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30434","30434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458916","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the difference is between NICE's clinical guidelines and its positive guidance; and what steps his Department is taking to make healthcare commissioners aware of when they may prescribe outside guidelines.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30469","30469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458917","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether clinical commissioning groups are permitted to prescribe medications which NICE does not recommend as cost effective.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30470","30470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458918","2016-03-14","Department of Health","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative information his Department holds on the length of time women stay in health facilities after giving birth in the UK and other developed countries; and if he will commission a review into the process of discharging women from maternity wards.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30456","30456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458919","2016-03-11","Department of Health","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will conduct an equality impact assessment on the removal of nursing bursaries.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30393","30393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458920","2016-03-11","Department of Health","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what timetable he has set for the consultation on reductions to nursing bursaries.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30394","30394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458921","2016-03-11","Department of Health","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department is developing a plan to enhance the role of social enterprises in delivering healthcare services.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30396","30396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458922","2016-03-11","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to increase the proportion of domestic abuse perpetrators who receive specialist intervention to change their behaviour.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30440","30440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458923","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress she has made on reducing the number of genetically modified animals bred for experiments but killed as surplus to requirements.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30465","30465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458924","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many take charge requests under the Dublin III Regulation she has received in relation to unaccompanied asylum-seeking children in France with either parents or alleged parents in the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30422","30422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458925","2016-03-14","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to improve the speed and effectiveness of asylum processes for reuniting unaccompanied asylum-seeking children in France with either parents or alleged parents in the UK.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30423","30423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458926","2016-03-11","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to exercise her powers under section 101(3) of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 only with the agreement of Ministers of the Scottish Government, as set out under section 101(7) of that Act.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30428","30428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458927","2016-03-11","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department takes to investigate complaints about outsourced asylum accommodation centres; and whether she has received complaints on the operation in Glasgow of her Department's outsourced asylum accommodation contract with Serco and its sub-contractor Orchard and Shipman.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30429","30429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458928","2016-03-11","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many dedicated Child Exploitation and Online Protection Centre (CEOP) police officers transferred to the National Crime Agency in 2013; and how many police officers are in the CEOP Command in 2016.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30503","30503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458929","2016-03-11","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to improve the provision of support from specialist services for LGBT victims of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30480","30480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458930","2016-03-11","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to encourage BAME victims of domestic abuse to report that abuse to the police.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30481","30481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/458931","2016-03-11","Home Office","2016-03-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the 168 posts advertised for the National Crime Agency in 2015 were allocated to Child Exploitation and Online Protection Command.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 30499","30499"
