"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797478","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure the continuation of European Whole Vehicle Type Approval certificates for cars after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116441","116441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797479","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to increase the take-up of hydrogen fuelled private vehicles.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116442","116442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797480","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of police officers in England and Wales have received training on controlling or coercive behaviour in an intimate or family relationship since 29 December 2015?","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116443","116443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797481","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support the research and development of alternative methods of powering vehicles.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116444","116444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797482","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dolphins, porpoises, whales, harbour seals and other protected species have been accidentally caught by commercial fishing vessels operating in UK waters by vessels registered (a) in the UK, (b) in other EU countries and (c) elsewhere in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116445","116445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797483","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he plans to make of the implications for his Department's policy on agreeing access to territorial waters for commercial fishing vessels registered in the EU of the Whale and Dolphin Conservation report on compliance on EU cetacean bycatch Regulation 812/2004.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116446","116446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797484","2017-12-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made on the effect of changes to local authority budgets on museum opening hours.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116447","116447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797485","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 10275, on electronic government, what services were bought by HS2 Ltd; and what the cost of each of those services was.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116448","116448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797486","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of the immigration skills charge on the creative industries.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116449","116449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797487","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 110275, on electronic government, to what Supplier Nil Return refers to in that Answer.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116450","116450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797488","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether Morecambe and Lunesdale will be eligible for funding from the additional £76 million announced for flood defence schemes in the Autumn Budget; what the (a) qualifiying criteria and (b) process for application for that funding will be; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116451","116451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797489","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2017 to Question 114635, how close to the area in which an exercise, training or selection event is taking place must a Wet Bulb Globe Temperature reading be taken.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116452","116452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797490","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 114635, how does a Commander assess humidity, wind speed and air temperature and other atmospheric conditions which may affect the safety of those under his command during an exercise, training or selection event without the use of a Wet Bulb Globe Temperature.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116453","116453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797491","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 114637, in how many cases of heat exhaustion being reported during an exercise, training or selection event was no pause and reassessment carried out by the Commander before deciding to continue or cancel the event.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116454","116454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797492","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials of his Department have core responsibilities which include non-emergency patient transport?","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116455","116455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797493","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data the Department of Health collects from Clinical Commissioning Groups and NHS hospital trusts on non-emergency patient transport.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116456","116456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797494","2017-12-01","Attorney General","2017-11-29","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116457","116457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797495","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116458","116458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797496","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116459","116459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797497","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to collect data recording the reasons why NHS patients miss their appointments.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116460","116460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797498","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116461","116461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797499","2017-12-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants her Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116462","116462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797500","2017-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116463","116463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797501","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants have been recruited so far to his Department to work on matters relating to the UK leaving the EU; and how many more civil servants his Department plans to recruit for such work.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116464","116464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797502","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2017 to Questions 110785, 110786 and 110787, how many children diagnosed with autism have received a permanent or fixed period exclusion in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116465","116465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797503","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116466","116466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797504","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with an (a) Education, Health and Care Plan and (b) Statement of Educational Needs and Disability (SEND) received a permanent or fixed-term exclusion in each local authority in the South West in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116467","116467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797505","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116468","116468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797506","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116469","116469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797507","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure value for money on pharmaceutical procurement.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116470","116470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797508","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants her Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116471","116471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797509","2017-12-01","Department for International Trade","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116472","116472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797510","2017-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116473","116473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797511","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the NHS is not charged a premium price for pharmaceutical products, especially Liothyronine by (a) Concordia, (b) Morningside and (c) Teva.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116474","116474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797512","2017-12-04","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116475","116475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797513","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116476","116476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797514","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what medicines NHS England has approved for patients with thyroid conditions","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116477","116477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797515","2017-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to ensure that the issues relating to staff overwork identified in the Probation Inspectors Report on Gloucestershire (a) in general and (b) relating to the Community Rehabilitation Company Working Links are rectified.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116478","116478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797516","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116479","116479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797517","2017-12-01","Scotland Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department (a) has recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116480","116480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797518","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that liothyronine will remain available on the NHS.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116481","116481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797519","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure liothyronine is competitively priced and provides value for money.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116482","116482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797520","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108977, on Post Office Card Account, what the annual cost per customer is to the public purse of administering pensions and benefits payments through Post Office Accounts.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116483","116483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797521","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108977, Post Office Card Accounts, what the cost per transaction is to the public purse of administering pensions and benefits payments through Post Office Accounts.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116484","116484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797522","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many allegations of ill-treatment of a subordinate have been made in each of the last ten years; and in which bases such incidents were alleged to have occurred.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116485","116485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797523","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108977, on Post Office Card Accounts, what the annual cost per person is to the public purse of administering pensions and benefits payments through bank accounts.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116486","116486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797524","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2017 to Question 108977, on Post Office Card Accounts, what the cost per transaction is to the public purse of administering pensions and benefits payments through bank accounts.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116487","116487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797525","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of levels of indebtedness among people who use (a) bank accounts and (b) Post Office Card Accounts for payment of pensions and benefits.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116488","116488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797526","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers who enlisted in the Army aged (a) under 18 and (b) 18 years or above dropped out before completing phase two training in the last five financial years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116489","116489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797527","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trainee soldiers who enlisted at (a) Army Foundation College (Harrogate) and (b) Infantry Training Centre (Catterick) dropped out before the completion of phase two training in each of the last four financial years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116490","116490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797528","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army recruits who left before the end of their Phase 2 training enlisted at the age of (a) 16 and (b) 17 in the last five financial years for which data is available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116491","116491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797529","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers who enlisted (a) under 18 years old and (b) 18 years old or above left the Army before completion of their Phase Two training in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116492","116492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797530","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has made an estimate of the number of Daesh fighters and supporters who have returned to the UK from both Iraq and Syria since January 2017.","Biography information for Trudy Harrison","Trudy Harrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116493","116493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797531","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to support the pedestrianisation of more town and city centres to encourage walking and tackle poor air quality.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116494","116494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797532","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he will publish an acquisition strategy for the Mechanised Infantry Vehicle programme.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116495","116495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797533","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding his Department has allocated to the Mechanised Infantry Vehicle programme.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116496","116496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797534","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding for the Mechanised Infantry Vehicle programme.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116497","116497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797535","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department is taking steps to raise awareness of the banking services that Post Office branches provide.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116498","116498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797536","2017-12-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings her Department has had with (a) Facebook and (b) Twitter on (i) fake news and (ii) methods of removing fake news before it becomes viral.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116499","116499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797537","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to include provision similar to the Severe Disability Premium as part of universal credit.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116500","116500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797538","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure (a), Northern Lincolnshire, (b) East Yorkshire and (c) other rural areas have suitable road infrastructure to encourage economic growth.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116501","116501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797539","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve the quality of local trains in Northern Lincolnshire and East Yorkshire.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116502","116502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797540","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken within planning and other guidance to local authorities to support the continued ringing of church bells and traditional chimes.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116503","116503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797541","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his overseas counterparts on mediation of conflicts in (a) the Nuba Mountains and (b) the River Nile area of Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116504","116504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797542","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Serbia on that country's request to join the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116505","116505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797543","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to assist in ongoing talks to bring a lasting peace between the Turkish and Greek communities in Cyprus.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116506","116506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797544","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average annual cost is of detaining a person in Brook House.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116507","116507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797545","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of people released from Immigration Removal Centres in the detention estate were released into the UK in the past 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116508","116508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797546","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost of unlawful detention claims paid by the Home Office has been in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116509","116509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797547","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with (a) Ofcom and (b) the Phone-paid Services Authority on call connection service access to the helplines his Department provides.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116510","116510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797548","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) the gov.uk website and (b) internet providers advertise the correct information about the cost of calls to his Department's helplines (i) before and (ii) after calls to those lines become free of charge.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116511","116511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797549","2017-12-04","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 110803, what discussions have taken place between his Department, Ofcom and the Phone-paid Services Authority on call connection services access to Government provided helplines.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116512","116512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797550","2017-12-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with (a) Ofcom and (b) the Phone-paid Services Authority on call connection service access to helplines provided by (i) her Department and (ii) other UK Government Departments.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116513","116513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797551","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much public funding has been spent on the schools efficiency taskforce; how many people that taskforce employs; how many schools that taskforce has visited; how much efficiency savings that taskforce has found; what estimate she has made of the savings that taskforce will make in the future; and whether she plans to undertake an assessment of the value for money of that taskforce.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116514","116514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797552","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many early service leavers left the armed forces in the last 12 months; and how many of those had enlisted when below the age of 18.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116515","116515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797553","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding has been provided for Social Fund Budgeting Loans in each of the last 10 years; and how much funding will be provided in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116516","116516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797554","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost of running (a) Phase 1 training at AFC Harrogate including trainee salaries and associated costs and (b) the Combat Infantryman's Course (Phase 1 and 2 training) at ITC Catterick including trainee salaries and associated costs was in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116517","116517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797555","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November to Question 115390,  whether people in receipt of (a) income Support, (b) income-related employment and support allowance or (c) income-related jobseeker's allowance who will in future receive universal credit will be permitted to access Social Fund Budgeting Loans.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116518","116518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797556","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost was of each successfully trained recruit of (a) Phase 1 and 2 training at ITC Catterick, (b) Phase 1 training at ATC Pirbright, (c) Phase 1 training at ATR Bassingbourn and (d) Phase 1 training at AFC Harrogate including trainee salaries and associated costs in the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116519","116519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797557","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the full outturn (a) building maintenance, (b) staffing, (c) training, (d) salaries for recruits and (e) other costs were at Catterick Infantry Training Centre in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116520","116520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797558","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Minister of State for Immigration plans to reply to the correspondence sent by the hon. Member for Nottingham North on 14 November 2017?","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116521","116521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797559","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the anticipated out-turn cost of AFC Harrogate is for financial year 2017-18; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116522","116522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797560","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the anticipated out-turn cost of ITC Catterick is for financial year 2017-18.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116523","116523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797561","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what age group his Department's advertising campaign to encourage people to check the value of their State Pension is intended to target.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116524","116524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797562","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will re-open the Fleetwood to Poulton-le-Fylde rail line as part of the Government's strategic vision for rail.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116525","116525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797563","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Environmental Protection (Microbeads) (England) Regulations 2017 will be subject to the one-in, three-out rule.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116526","116526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797564","2017-12-04","Department for International Trade","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of changes in the number of staff at each grade and salary band which will be needed in his Department after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116527","116527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797565","2017-12-06","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of rail journey times between Nottingham and Derby as a result of High Speed 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116528","116528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797566","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department takes to ensure that it (a) seeks the permission of and (b) notifies in advance bereaved families who are named in its reports.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116529","116529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797567","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to postpone the publication of the report of the non-statutory inquiry established to investigate the notification and after-care of next-of-kin and families of armed forces personnel recently deceased until he has sought permission of the bereaved families named in that report.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116530","116530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797568","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Government has plans to mark the 85th anniversary of the Holodomor.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116531","116531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797569","2017-12-06","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether UK pensioners living in EU countries will continue to get their state pension uprated after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116532","116532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797570","2017-12-06","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) cost and (b) effect on the environment of the development of bi-modal trains?","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116533","116533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797571","2017-12-06","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether all rolling stock on the Midlands Mainline will be compliant with modern accessibility standards by 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116534","116534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797572","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department cannot delay implementation of payments pending the outcome of an incompleted appeal before the Army Board in relation to individuals seeking compensation for having been illegally dismissed from the Armed Forces as a result of a caution.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116535","116535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797573","2017-12-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what her Department's policy is on DBS checks for volunteers in sporting activities.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116536","116536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797574","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to classify fibromyalgia as a long-term condition.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116537","116537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797575","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November to Question 111756, how many staff were employed by a mental health trust at June each year to 2017 who were employed by a primary care trust at June 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116538","116538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797576","2017-12-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to tackle child abuse in sport.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116539","116539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797577","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have received payments in compensation for having been illegally dismissed from the Armed Forces as a result of a caution; and what the cost to the public purse has been of those payments.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116540","116540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797578","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides to healthcare professionals for the diagnosis of fibromyalgia.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116541","116541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797579","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the implications are for the implementation of the provisions of the Military Covenant of not delaying compensation payments when requested to do so for people who have been illegally dismissed from the Armed Forces as a result of a caution.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116542","116542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797580","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support research into fibromyalgia.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116543","116543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797581","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to raise awareness of fibromyalgia among (a) healthcare professionals and (b) members of the public.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116544","116544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797582","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","Whether his Department plans to review the business rates system.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116545","116545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797583","2017-12-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has received about the adequacy of the safeguarding policy of the British Parachute Association.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116546","116546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797584","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date she plans to replace the existing Chief Executive and Chair of the Independent Police Complaints Commission as part of the establishment of the Independent Office for Police Conduct?","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116547","116547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797585","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to review the effectiveness of integration systems for refugees.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116548","116548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797586","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the 12-month grace period to protect individuals from a reduction in housing benefit when someone who lived with them passes away is being implemented effectively.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116549","116549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797588","2017-12-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the cost is to the public purse of the complete Libraries Taskforce dataset?","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116551","116551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797589","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of the total strength of the Army Reserve as at 1 October 2017 are (a) Phase 1 Trained, (b) Phase 2 (or special to arm) Trained and (c) new entrants or recruits.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116552","116552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797590","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the Army Reserve are eligible to (a) deploy on overseas exercises, (b) deploy on overseas operations and (c) be mobilised.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116553","116553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797591","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the Army Reserve qualified for the annual bounty in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116554","116554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797592","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army Reserve Soldiers who received their bounty in April 2017 qualified for (a) Year 1 (£444), (b) Year 2 (£982), (c) Year 3 (£1517), (d) Year 4 (£1517) and (e) Year 5 (£1759).","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116555","116555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797593","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average number of Manned Training Days undertaken by (a) an individual soldier, (b) a Company (or equivalent) and (c) a Battalion (or equivalent) was in the Army Reserve for the training year April 2016 to March 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116556","116556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797594","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average number of Manned Training Days claimed under the Operation Fortify Budget is for (a) individual soldiers, (b) Companies (or equivalent) and (c) Battalions (or equivalent) for the training year April 2016 to March 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116557","116557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797595","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) additional duties contracts, (b) voluntary training other duties agreements and (c) full time reserve soldier contracts are afforded under the Operation Fortify budget?","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116558","116558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797596","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of the strength of the Army Reserve as at 1 October 2017 are (a) Regular Soldiers on fixed term attachments, (b) on a Full Time Reserve Soldier Contract, (c) on an Additional Duties Contract and (d) on a Voluntary Training Other Duties agreement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116559","116559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797597","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how his Department calculated the distribution of the HS2 Road Safety Fund along the Phase One route.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116560","116560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797598","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people on Full Time Reserve Soldier  contracts are eligible (a) to deploy on overseas exercises, (b) to deploy on overseas operations, (c) to be mobilised and (d) for a reduced commitment.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116561","116561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797599","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of Army Reserve Soldiers as of 1 October 2017 are ex-regulars on the Regular to Reserve bonus scheme.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116562","116562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797600","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to High Speed 2's Road Safety Fund, what the current allocations for each council are along the Phase One route.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116563","116563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797601","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of Reserve Soldiers on the Regular to Reserve Bonus scheme have achieved (a) Key Milestone 1, (b) Key Milestone 2, (c) Key Milestone 3 and (d) Key Milestone 4 since the introduction of that Scheme on 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116564","116564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797602","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who carried out the assessment for the allocation of HS2's Road Safety Fund.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116565","116565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797603","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to reduce the number of access refusals of guide dogs owners?","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116566","116566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797604","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much and what proportion of funding made available by NHS England for eating disorders has been allocated to Tier Two providers specialising in early intervention.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116567","116567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797605","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of changes in the level of income of public sector employees since the public sector pay cap was introduced.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116568","116568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797606","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in which locations the additional 2,200 bed spaces funded by his Department’s Domestic Abuse Fund have been created.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116569","116569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797607","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the number the organisations that have received funding from the Department’s Abuse Fund; where those organisations are located; and the number of new refuge bed spaces created by those organisations, in each of the last 2 years.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116570","116570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797608","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Addition Duties Contracts (ADC), (b) Voluntary Training Other Duties (VTOD) agreements and (c) Full Time Reserve Soldier (FTRS) Contracts are affordable under the Operation Fortify Budget.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116571","116571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797609","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November to Question 115565, how much the devolved administrations receive from the Barnett formula arising from the soft drinks industry levy-funded spending package in each financial year of the current spending review period.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116572","116572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797610","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England places a requirement on clinical commissioning groups to consider third sector organisations when commissioning interventions and treatments for eating disorders?","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116573","116573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797611","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much and what proportion of the total spent by the NHS on treating eating disorders has been allocated to the treatment of people aged (a) seventeen and under and (b) eighteen and over in each of the last three years?","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116574","116574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797612","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has a strategy to increase the proportion of male employees in the early years sector.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116575","116575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797613","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which academies in England are currently awaiting a transfer to another trust.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116576","116576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797614","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the longest period is that an academy has waited for a transfer to another trust since 2010.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116577","116577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797615","2017-12-04","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many drug-related deaths there have been by age group in each of the last twelve months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116578","116578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797616","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what work his Department has undertaken in the last two months to protect protected geographical indications?","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116579","116579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797617","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many drug-related deaths there have been where a person previously sought treatment for addiction in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116580","116580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797618","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2017 to Question 114731, if he will publish the name of the 15 mental health places that he has visited since July 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116581","116581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797619","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October to Question 106938 on respiratory system: diseases, if he will make an assessment of the long-term cost to a persons health of living in a cold home.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116582","116582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797620","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of restraint against children in young offenders institutions there have been in each of the last three years, broken down by the role of the person who carried out the restraint technique.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116583","116583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797621","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of  including trusts in the legislative proposal on the beneficial ownership of companies seeking to purchase property,.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116584","116584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797622","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to requiring Scottish Limited Partnerships with offshore partners to file tax returns with Her Majesty's Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116585","116585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797623","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made on the effect of a hard credit check for on the ability of consumers to switch energy suppliers.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116586","116586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797624","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Autumn Budget 2017, Table 1.9, whether the projected effect of the tuition fee cap freeze in financial years 2020-21 to 2022-23 is based on the tuition fee cap freeze ending after financial year 2019-20.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116587","116587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797625","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the average pay in early years settings on their ability to fill vacancies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116588","116588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797626","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits of bringing Scottish Limited Partnerships within the scope of the Persons of Significant Control register.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116589","116589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797627","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Russian counterparts on the detention of Tatars involved in human rights works in Crimea.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116590","116590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797628","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Autumn Budget 2017, paragraph 6.27, what his policy is on public sector pay awards in financial year 2018-19 for employees not covered by an independent Pay Review Body.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116591","116591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797630","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of parents who have successfully applied for tax-free childcare are self-employed.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116593","116593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797631","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department have taken to ensure that patients are not discharged before a care plan has been put in place.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116594","116594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797632","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings that Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116595","116595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797633","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116596","116596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797634","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require Scottish Limited Partnerships to hold a bank account registered in the United Kingdom.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116597","116597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797635","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer on 28 November 2017 to Question 115556, Pre-school education: apprentices, how many and what proportion of apprenticeship starts (a) were completed and (b) remain employed in the early years sector.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116598","116598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797636","2017-12-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings Ministers of her Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116599","116599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797637","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of (a) money laundered and (b) tax avoided by Scottish Limited Partnerships in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116600","116600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797638","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116601","116601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797639","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116602","116602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797640","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 115567 on child minding what proportion of local authorities are paying providers on a monthly basis.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116603","116603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797641","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has plans to require partners of Scottish Limited Partnerships to provide a correspondence address.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116604","116604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797642","2017-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116605","116605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797643","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings Ministers of her Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116606","116606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797644","2017-12-01","Department for International Trade","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116607","116607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797645","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116608","116608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797646","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what meetings Ministers of his Department has had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116609","116609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797647","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 115232, how many claimants of Employment and Support Allowance were subject to payment miscalculations in each (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013, (d) 2014 and (e) 2015, and what the timetable is for those claimant to be reimbursed.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116610","116610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797648","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116611","116611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797649","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for bringing forward legislative proposals to require the publication of details relating to the beneficial ownership of companies buying residential property in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116612","116612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797650","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to check the legality of the tax schemes detailed in the Paradise Papers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116613","116613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797651","2017-12-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Oral Statement of 28 November 2017, Official Report, column 161, on leaving the EU: sectoral impact assessments,  how many pages of material have been withheld in addition to the 850 pages submitted to the Exiting the European Union Committee.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116614","116614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797652","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116615","116615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797653","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish a breakdown of the £8 million investment announced in the Autumn Budget for in-work support for low-paid workers on universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116616","116616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797654","2017-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what meetings that Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116617","116617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797655","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116618","116618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797656","2017-12-01","Attorney General","2017-11-29","To ask the Attorney General, what meetings he has had with representatives of the Legatum Institute in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116619","116619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797657","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners imprisoned for public protection remain imprisioned; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116620","116620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797658","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to bring forward the parole hearings of prisoners imprisonment for public protection who have exceeded their minimum term in prison?","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116621","116621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797659","2017-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of war crimes are detained in the UK; and how many people have been so detained in the last 10 years?","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116622","116622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797660","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle opioid abuse?","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116623","116623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797661","2017-12-04","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on humanitarian aid to the Gaza strip in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116624","116624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797662","2017-12-04","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the UN Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs humanitarian funding appeal to support people in Gaza.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116625","116625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797663","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has plans to increase access to sapropterin for phenylketonuria.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116626","116626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797664","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to support trauma counselling services for child Rohingya refugees?","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116627","116627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797665","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to allow NHS England to negotiate directly with pharmaceutical companies to improve access to treatments for phenylketonuria.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116628","116628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797666","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to support child protection services for Rohingya refugees in Bangladesh?","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116629","116629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797667","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to contribute to funding of the Humanitarian Support Plan for Rohingya refugees?","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116630","116630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797668","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to provide humanitarian support for disabled Rohingya refugees in camps in Bangladesh?","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116631","116631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797669","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department is making in the provision of long-term facilities such as shelters for Rohingya refugees.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116632","116632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797670","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure access to education for child Rohingya refugees in camps in Bangladesh?","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116633","116633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797671","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to ensure safety of unaccompanied Rohingya child refugees in Bangladesh?","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116634","116634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797672","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the early termination of the East Coast rail franchise?","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116635","116635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797673","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps are being taken to ensure counselling services for Rohingya refugees in Bangladesh are provided in their native language.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116636","116636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797674","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 4.24 of the Autumn Budget 2017, how many pupils she estimates will study Maths, Further Maths or Core Maths as a consequence of the payments set out in that paragraph for each year that it is available.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116637","116637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797675","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if it is his Department's policy that the total carbon price should remain at present levels until 2025.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116638","116638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797677","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the sum of the total carbon price is that will remain in place until 2025","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116640","116640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797678","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what components make up the sum of the total carbon price that will remain in place until 2025.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116641","116641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797679","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 6.27 of the Autumn Budget 2017, what plans she has to apply the revised public sector pay policy to school support staff and teaching assistants.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116642","116642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797680","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 4.51 of the Autumn Budget 2017, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Government’s plans for no new low-carbon electricity levies until 2025 on its plans to extend the Energy Company Obligation set out in the Clean Growth Strategy.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116643","116643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797681","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to allow housing associations to increase the number of new homes they build.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116644","116644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797682","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with music educators on the National Plan for Music Education; and whether that Plan should (a) include Early Years, (b) recognise informal pathways for young musicians and (c) continue with universal provision or be focussed on disadvantaged children.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116645","116645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797683","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timetable is to bring forward the secondary legislation  to place an upper limit on the value of public sector exit payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116646","116646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797684","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 7 November 2017, HCWS232 on local government improvement, if he will place in the Library a list of all the material and representations he received before making his announcement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116647","116647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797685","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 7 November 2017, HCWS232, on local government improvement, what further steps are needed to secure local consent.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116648","116648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797686","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for a decision to be made on the authorisation of spinroza as an NHS treatment for people who suffer from spinal muscular atrophy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116649","116649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797687","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reasons are for his decision to (a) award a 12 month franchise extension and (b) offer a potential two year additional direct award to GWR.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116650","116650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797688","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for NICE to begin its evaluation of the spinal muscular atrophy treatment Spinraza.","Biography information for Alberto Costa","Alberto Costa","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116651","116651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797689","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the (a) business case and (b) funding details for wave 2 projects funded through the Industrial Strategy Challenge Fund.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116652","116652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797690","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for publication of his review into improving the productivity and growth of small and medium-sized businesses.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116653","116653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797691","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which UK regulators will be eligible to receive funding from the proposed Regulators' Pioneer Fund.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116654","116654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797692","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful prosecutions have been made for the illegal usage of drones in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116655","116655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797693","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to encourage the commercialisation of UK innovations in (a) cybersecurity, (b) machine learning, (c) microelectronics, (d) compound chip technology and (c) biotechnology.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116656","116656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797694","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what involvement local authorities will have in the development and delivery of the Local Industrial Strategies referred to in the Industrial Strategy White Paper.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116657","116657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797695","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2017 to Question 115216, what changes he proposes to implement for the operation of the Grocery Code Adjudicator (GCA) as a result of the review published on 19 July 2017; and what plans he has to extend the remit of the GCA to cover smaller suppliers in the grocery supply chain.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116658","116658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797696","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2017 to Question 115208 on business premises: valuation, what plans he has to change the amount charged by the Valuation Office Agency to revalue properties for business rates purposes.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116659","116659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797697","2017-12-04","Department for International Trade","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 27 November 2017 on trade matters,  HCWS271, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of appointing the nine Her Britannic Majesty's Trade Commissioners.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116660","116660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797698","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116661","116661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797699","2017-12-01","Attorney General","2017-11-29","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116662","116662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797700","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116663","116663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797701","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116664","116664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797702","2017-12-01","Wales Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116665","116665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797703","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer,  what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116666","116666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797704","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116667","116667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797705","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116668","116668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797706","2017-12-01","Scotland Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116669","116669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797707","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by her Department and (b) her Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116670","116670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797708","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116671","116671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797709","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by 10 Downing Street and (b) that office's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116672","116672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797710","2017-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116673","116673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797711","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116674","116674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797712","2017-12-01","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116675","116675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797713","2017-12-01","Women and Equalities","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what estimate she has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by her Department and (b) her Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116676","116676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797714","2017-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116677","116677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797715","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116678","116678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797716","2017-12-01","Department for International Trade","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116679","116679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797717","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by her Department and (b) her Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116680","116680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797718","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by her Department and (b) her Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116681","116681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797719","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to prevent deaths from pneumonia in developing countries in children under five years old; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116682","116682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797720","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress is being made in ending preventable child deaths by 2030 as set out in the UN Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116683","116683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800731","2017-12-07","Women and Equalities","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many cases of HIV-related workplace discrimination have been reported, in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117352","117352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795433","2017-11-29","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what further steps are being taken to assist employers in encouraging employees to cycle to work.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 115854","115854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795648","2017-11-28","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","What discussions he has had with Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the potential effect of the roll-out of universal credit on levels of household income?","Biography information for Fiona Onasanya","Fiona Onasanya","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902584","902584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795651","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","What discussions he has had with the President of the Board of Trade on the potential merits for future UK trade of better integrating road and rail infrastructure.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902676","902676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795669","2017-11-30","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made on the effects of party political activity on (a) electoral registration and (b) voter engagement in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116023","116023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795670","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will earmark funding to support the recruitment and retention of carers who provide personal homecare visits.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116024","116024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795671","2017-11-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will extend Bereavement Support Payments to people above the state pension age.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116025","116025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795672","2017-11-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing projects on Help to Rent and on a national rent deposit guarantee proposed by Crisis in its report, Crisis Help to Rent programmes.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116026","116026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795673","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of training time for the new nursing associate role is allocated to each specialism.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116027","116027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795674","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 4.24 of Autumn Budget 2017, what funding her Department plans to allocate for (a) expanding the Teaching for Mastery maths programme, (b) the premium for pupils taking maths, further maths or core maths, (c) providing an annual £350,000 for every maths school under the specialist maths school model, (d) the pilot to improve GCSE maths resit outcomes and (e) establishing Further Education Centres of Excellence in each of the next five financial years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116028","116028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795675","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding her Department has made available or plans to make available to secondary schools to increase the range of activities offered to pupils outside the school day; and whether any funding was provided for that purpose from the soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116029","116029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795676","2017-11-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of proportion of premises which have access to fibre and superfast broadband as a result of the implementation of the Digital Scotland Superfast Broadband programme.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116030","116030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795677","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will undertake a review the regulation of employee benefit trusts following representations made on behalf of the Roadchef Employees Benefit Trust.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116031","116031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795678","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evidence his Department has received from the Food Standards Agency on the effect on public health of the mandatory display of hygiene scores at food outlets in Wales.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116032","116032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795679","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2017 to Question 115078, what estimate he has made of the number of disabled children eligible for a tax-free childcare account.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116033","116033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795680","2017-11-30","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister of the Cabinet Office what the total number of Northern Irish workers currently employed by the public sector across the rest of the UK is.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116034","116034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795682","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the revenue raised from the soft drinks industry levy will go to (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, and (c) Northern Ireland as a consequence of the Barnett Formula in the next financial year.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116036","116036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795683","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on the planned lorry holding park in Stanford West in Kent.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116037","116037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795684","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to expand and support the not-for-profit community transport sector.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116038","116038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795685","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reform the bus industry to expand not-for-profit services on commercial routes.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116039","116039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795686","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost will be of his proposed policy on the railcard for ages 26 to 30 years; how that policy proposal will be funded; and when he plans to introduce that railcard on all franchises.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116040","116040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795687","2017-11-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Governments of UK Overseas Territories on creating fully enforced Marine Protected Areas in their waters.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116041","116041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795688","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the rollout of universal credit is not being delayed in Cardiff.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116042","116042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795689","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to undertake a public consultation before the launch of the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116043","116043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795690","2017-12-01","Wales Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what his policy is on the status of West Wales and the Valleys under the Governments new Shared Prosperity Fund; and if he will consider that area's status as eligible to receive the highest level of support under European Structural Funds when allocating funds under that policy.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116044","116044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795691","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of underwriting EU projects in Wales that extend beyond the UK's period of membership of the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116045","116045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795692","2017-12-01","Wales Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether he has had any meetings with the Welsh Government on the future operation of the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116046","116046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795693","2017-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he (a) ordered the drawing up of and (b) received the completed Brexit impact assessments.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116047","116047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795694","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what relationship the Government plans to have with the EU's Permanent Structured Cooperation, known as PESCO, after leaving the EU.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116048","116048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795695","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to Autumn Budget 2017, how much funding has been allocated for the provision of new social housing.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116049","116049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795696","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2017, how many more social housing units will be built in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116050","116050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795697","2017-11-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities have received a) extra borrowing approval and b) the ability to transfer money from the general fund in order to carry out fire safety work on tower blocks.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116051","116051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795698","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to announce voluntary Contracts for Difference auctions for on shore wind in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116052","116052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795699","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the steps needed to develop a carbon capture and storage cluster in Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116053","116053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795700","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that women who know they are expecting a child with disability have access to accurate information about the experiences of families who have raised a child with disability.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116054","116054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795701","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Bus Services Act 2017, when he plans to issue the guidance and regulations on audio-visual next stop announcements.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116055","116055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795702","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of transferring the costs of upgrading or replacing the UK's nuclear deterrent from the Ministry of Defence to another Government accounting department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116056","116056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795703","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the contract awarded in February 2017 to Pale Blue Dot to review business models for carbon dioxide transport and storage, whether this work has been completed.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116057","116057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795704","2017-11-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to protect adults from cyber-bullying on social media.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116058","116058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795705","2017-11-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to protect children from cyber-bullying on social media.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116059","116059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795706","2017-11-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the Government’s policy is on the responsibilities of social media companies relating to cyber-bullying; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116060","116060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795707","2017-11-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has had meetings with social media companies to discuss their responsibilities relating to cyber-bullying in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116061","116061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795708","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the implementation of the Tobacco and Related Products Regulations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116062","116062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795709","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on a) levels of non-compliance with the Tobacco and Related Products Regulations and b) the number of successful prosecutions for non-compliance in the last year for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116063","116063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795710","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training is provided by his Department to local authority trading standards officers on the Tobacco and Related Products Regulations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116064","116064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795711","2017-12-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what her most recent estimate is of the average (a) advertised speed for broadband services, (b) speed received by consumers for broadband services; and if she will make a statement","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116065","116065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795712","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the average number of hours of sport and physical activity undertaken by pupils in primary schools in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116066","116066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795713","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of people employed in the nuclear industry in each year since 2010; and what forecast he has made of the number of people employed in that industry in each year to 2025.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116067","116067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795714","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what funding his Department has allocated to the Green Finance Taskforce in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116068","116068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795715","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse is of (a) installing and (b) subsidising (i) uni-directional and (ii) bi-directional charge points for electric vehicles within the UK.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116069","116069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795716","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to upgrade fuel poor homes to Band C or above.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116070","116070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795717","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the amount of money projected to be invest by 2025 in (a) installing and (b) subsidising (i) uni-directional and (ii) bi-directional charge points for electric vehicles within the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116071","116071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795718","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Government plans to spend on flood and coastal erosion risk management in England in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116072","116072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795719","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department is making on increasing the number of homes to be classified as EPC Band C by 2035.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116073","116073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795720","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) uni-directional and (b) bi-directional charge points for electric vehicles installed in the UK by 2025; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116074","116074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795721","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with the exception of electric vehicles, what policies and options his Department has assessed as feasible routes to decarbonise petrol vehicles before 2040.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116075","116075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795722","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the merits of taxing bioethanol on the basis of energy content rather than volume; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116076","116076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795723","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the proceeds from the sale of the existing Hemel Hempstead hospital site will be used to provide new hospital facilities in Hemel Hempstead.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike  Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116077","116077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795724","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment has she made of the impact of the English Baccalaureate on improving the educational outcomes for children on Free School Meals.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116078","116078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795725","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding per pupil did (a) free (b) academy (c) comprehensive, and (d) grammar schools receive in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116079","116079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795726","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils in receipt of free school meals attend (a) Free Schools, (b) academies, (c) comprehensives and (d) grammar schools.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116080","116080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795727","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of English Baccalaureate students went on to (a) A-levels (b) vocational study and (c) an apprenticeship in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116081","116081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795728","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the budget deficit was in 2010; what his most recent estimate of the budget deficit is; and what forecast he has made of the budget deficit in 2019.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116082","116082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795730","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what NHS services he expects to be available to residents of Hemel Hempstead from the new facilities to be provided by (a) West Hertfordshire Hospitals NHS Trust, (b) Hertfordshire Community NHS Trust,  and (c) Hertfordshire Partnership University NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike  Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116083","116083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795731","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of English Baccalaureate students in receipt of free school meals went on to (a) A-levels, (b) vocational study, and (c) an apprenticeship in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116084","116084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795733","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information has been issued to employers on the English Baccalaureate performance measure.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116085","116085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795734","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information has been issued to Russell Group Universities on the English Baccalaureate performance measure.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116086","116086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795735","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of trends in the proportion of students that obtain the English Baccalaureate in the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116087","116087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795736","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of students who obtain the English Baccalaureate attend (a) state and (b) independent schools.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116088","116088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795738","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the funding arrangements for new pre-registration dental hygiene and dental therapy students starting courses on or after 1 August 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116089","116089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795739","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on funding of Wheels to Work schemes: and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116090","116090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795740","2017-11-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Government's commitments under the Paris Agreement of 2015.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116091","116091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795741","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received from the solar power industry on how rooftop solar power is treated in business rates.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116092","116092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795742","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the difference in business rate liabilities is for rooftop solar power where the majority of the power produced is (a) exported to a third party and (b) consumed onsite.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116093","116093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795743","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what methodology is used to calculate the business rate liabilities of (a) solar power and (b) Good Quality gas CHP; and what the rationale is for that methodology.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116094","116094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795745","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department takes to (a) enforce the Welfare Code for game birds and (b) ensure that cages used for breeding pheasants and partridges meet animal welfare standards.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116095","116095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795746","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how battery storage technologies installed in commercial premises are assessed for business rates.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116096","116096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795747","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the industrial benefits of solar power.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116097","116097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795748","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2017 to Question 7012, on iron and steel, when he plans to publish his Department's paper, Future Capabilities of the UK Steel Sector.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116098","116098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795750","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his oral contribution of 27 November 2017, Official Report, column 45, what specific financial incentives will be available to encourage suppliers to relocate to the UK.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116099","116099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795751","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to develop an evidential roadside test for people who drive under the influence of drugs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116100","116100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795752","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the Pharmacy Integration Fund for 2017-18 has been spent to date; and if he will provide a breakdown of that expenditure.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116101","116101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795753","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the funding allocated to the Pharmacy Integration Fund for 2017-18 remains unspent.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116102","116102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795754","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the amount of funding allocated to the Pharmacy Integration Fund for 2018-19.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116103","116103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795756","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2017 to Question 113095 on buses: tyres, whether the estimated cost of £200,000 for including a check on the age of tyres as part of the annual MOT is estimated on an annual basis.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116104","116104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795757","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people in Garston and Halewood constituency are employed in the pharmaceutical industry.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116105","116105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795758","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 114760, on railways: Leigh, whether his Department will commit to make an assessment of the costs and benefits of a direct train line and station to the town of Leigh.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116106","116106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795759","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November to Question 114760, on railway: Leigh, what criteria his Department uses to commission an assessment into the costs and benefits of a direct train line and station to an area.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116107","116107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795760","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many housing planning applications have been called in by his Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116108","116108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795761","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions  information regarding the immigration status of NHS patients has been shared with the Home Office in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116109","116109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795763","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of landlords' right to immigration checks on the ability of immigrant families to secure accommodation.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116110","116110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795764","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the effect of landlords' rights to immigration checks on discrimination and anti-immigrant sentiment.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116111","116111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795765","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many households have been subject to landlords' immigration checks in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116112","116112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795766","2017-11-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the results of his Department’s consultation on tackling unfair practices in the leasehold market; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116113","116113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795767","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will undertake an annual review of all congenital anomalies with the independent scientific advice of the Commission on Human Medicines, as recommended in the Report of the Commission on Human Medicines Expert Working Group on Hormone Pregnancy Tests, published on 15 November 2017.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116114","116114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795768","2017-11-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support improved energy-efficiency in (a) newbuild homes, and (b) existing properties.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116115","116115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795769","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the provision of care and support available to patients following a stem cell transplant.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116116","116116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795771","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what topics were discussed during the Minister of State for Health's visit to Bournville Care Village on Friday 24 November 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116117","116117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795772","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State plans to respond to the letter of 31 October from the hon. Member for Birmingham Northfield on Premises Cost Directions and Bournville Gardens Health and Wellbeing Centre.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116118","116118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795773","2017-11-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the use of financial assistance provided to Colchester Borough Council to develop proposals for garden settlements.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116119","116119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795774","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what regular assessments have been made by the Government of insurance underwriting trends for offshore helicopter operations since January 2009.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116120","116120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795775","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to require the insurance industry to publish historic cost benefit analyses of under writing commercial helicopter flights in the offshore energy industry since 2009.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116121","116121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795776","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of recent trends in the level of late payments for construction firms on that sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116122","116122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795778","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask The Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of late payments to construction firms on  (a) jobs and (b) insolvencies in that sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116123","116123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795779","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who was present at the oil and gas roundtable attended by the then Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on 12 April 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116124","116124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795780","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who was present at the oil and gas investor roundtable attended by the then Secretary of State for Energy and Climate change on 12 April 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116125","116125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795782","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who was present at the Low Carbon Roundtable attended by the then Secretary of State for Energy and Climate change on 9 May 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116126","116126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795783","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made by Health Education England on developing standards for prescribing that include the risks and benefits of medication, personal preferences, and preventative health support for people with mental health diagnoses.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116127","116127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795784","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to reduce Out of Area Placements in Mental Health Services.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116128","116128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795785","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress is being made on implementing the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health recommendation that NHS England should 9a) define a quantified national reduction in premature mortality among people with severe mental illness, and (b) devise an operational plan for this from 2017/18.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116129","116129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795786","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research his Department is conducting on new diversification schemes for farms.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116130","116130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795788","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote British food produce to domestic consumers.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116131","116131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795789","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Northern Ireland University Air Squadron will reach its capacity of planned student places.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116132","116132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795790","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals living in the UK are currently subject to deportation orders; and how many foreign nationals outside the UK are currently prohibited from entering the UK under the terms of the Immigration Act 1971.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116133","116133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795792","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  with reference to her Department's Special Grant Guidance updated on 28 November 2017, whether Greater Manchester Police will be required to fund costs of up to one per cent of that force's budget before receiving her Department's funding for the Manchester Arena terrorist attack of 22 May 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116134","116134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795793","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals formerly held in immigration removal centres and subsequently released reoffended in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116135","116135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795794","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to encourage primary school students to participate in after-school sports clubs.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116136","116136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795795","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who was present at the Maximising Economic Recovery Roundtable attended by the then Secretary of State for Energy and Climate change on 19 May 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116137","116137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795796","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of average class sizes in Garston and Halewood constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116138","116138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795798","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigrants have been held in immigration removal centres in each of the last 20 quarters; and of those how many have been (a) released and (b) removed from the UK.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116139","116139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795799","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who was present at the CCS Development Forum attended by the then Minister for Energy and Climate change on 5 May 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116140","116140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795800","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national offenders discharged in each of the last five years with convictions for (a) rape, (b) other sexual offences and (c) violence against the person were (i) deported directly from custody, (ii) deported on release from custody, (iii) deported within one month of being released from custody, (iv) deported between one and two months of leaving custody, (v) deported between two and three months of leaving custody, (vi) deported between three and six months of leaving custody, (vii) deported between six and 12 months of leaving custody, (vii) deported 12 months or more after leaving custody, (ix) awaiting deportation in an immigration removal centre and (x) still resident in the UK.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116141","116141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795801","2017-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many compensation orders were issued for each (a) offence and (b) sentence type in each of the last five years; and what the total value of compensation orders was for each offence type.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116142","116142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795802","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who was present at the Infrastructure Forum Roundtable attended by the then Minister for Energy and Climate change on 24 May 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116143","116143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795804","2017-11-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with which companies in the betting industry (a) she and (b) Ministers from her Department have met in the last three months, and what the purpose of each meeting was.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116144","116144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795805","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who was present at the new-gas investors roundtable attended by the then Minister for Energy and Climate change on 25 May 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116145","116145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795806","2017-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the amount was of each of the 20 highest compensation orders issued against offenders in each of the last five years; and to what offence each compensation order was related.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116146","116146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795807","2017-11-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to consult Battersea Dogs and Cats Home and other animal welfare charities on draft legislative proposals to increase the maximum animal cruelty sentence to five years imprisonment.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116147","116147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795808","2017-11-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government what plans he has to supporting Help to Rent projects to enable more people to rent privately.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116148","116148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795809","2017-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the general access times to rape crisis centres in (a) Wandsworth, (b) South London, (c) London and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116149","116149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795811","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if will issue statutory guidance to licensing authorities requiring disability equality training as a license condition for all drivers.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116150","116150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795812","2017-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Mechanised Infantry Vehicle programme will go out to competition at the Prime Contract level.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116151","116151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795813","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the non-payment of vehicle tax.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116152","116152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795814","2017-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether competition is required for all his Department’s procurement programmes?","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116153","116153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795816","2017-11-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the £28m announced in the Autumn Budget for housing first pilot schemes to tackle homelessness will be allocated to Liverpool City Region.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116154","116154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795817","2017-11-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support people entering, returning and staying in the workforce after cancer.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116155","116155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795818","2017-11-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support people with mental ill health entering, returning to and staying in the workforce?","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116156","116156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795819","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people aged (a) 65 and over, (b) 75 and over and (c) 85 and over who visited an NHS dentist in the 24 months to 30 June 2017.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116157","116157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795820","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that dependent older people receiving care in your home services or living in care homes can access NHS dental services.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116158","116158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795822","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the next Adult Dental Health Survey.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116159","116159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795823","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that dental practitioners receive dementia awareness training.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116160","116160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795824","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to set targets for the UK to reduce greenhouse gas emissions in order to limit global warming.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116161","116161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795826","2017-11-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to supporting more sustainable, low emission agriculture.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116162","116162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795827","2017-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to invest in 100 per cent clean energy.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116163","116163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795828","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the Government plans to lay its annual report on progress towards full employment before Parliament as required by the Welfare Reform and Work Act 2016?","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116164","116164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795829","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the Financial Conduct Authority to regulate the rent-to-own sector by capping the total cost of goods bought through rent-to-own.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116165","116165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795830","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to promote better access to affordable credit; and whether his Department has plans to create a national interest-free credit scheme available to people eligible for universal credit.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116166","116166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795831","2017-11-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the implications for government departments of the findings of the report entitled Mapping the Maze: services for women experiencing multiple disadvantage in England and Wales, published by Agenda and Against Violence and Abuse in September 2017.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116167","116167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795833","2017-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to build a women’s prison in Wales.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116168","116168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795834","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of policing fracking sites.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116169","116169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795835","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of policing fracking sites by police force in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116170","116170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795836","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding has been raised by the Welsh police forces from the apprenticeship levy in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116171","116171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795837","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to pass on the funding raised from Welsh police forces from the Apprenticeship Levy to the Welsh Government","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116172","116172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795838","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who was present at the Roundtable energy investors event attended by the then Secretary of State for Energy and Climate change on 31 March 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116173","116173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795839","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who was present at the Roundtable nuclear stakeholders event attended by the then Secretary of State for Energy and Climate change on 31 March 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116174","116174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795841","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 4.46, page 52 of the Autumn Budget 2017, whether his Department will fund discounted rail travel for people aged between 26 and 30.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116175","116175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795842","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of programmes in England providing free meals and activities for children during school holidays; what funding his Department has provided for such programmes in each of the last three years; and what steps his Department is taking to promote such programmes.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116176","116176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795843","2017-11-30","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the oral evidence given by Sir Mark Lyall Grant to the Defence Select Committee on 14 November 2017, HC 556, if he will list the events held ahead of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review with stakeholders in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116177","116177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795844","2017-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will clarify the statement by the Prime Minister of Canada on 18 September 2017 that Canada and the UK will continue to partner in Ukraine to support Defence reform and institutional capacity building.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116178","116178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795845","2017-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what consideration his Department has given to supplying the Government of Ukraine with non-lethal military equipment, which is no longer in operational use but good working order.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116179","116179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795847","2017-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Boeing Poseidon P-8 aircraft his Department plans to buy broken down by year until 2024.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116180","116180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795848","2017-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral evidence given to the Defence Select Committee on Tuesday 17 October 2017, on F35 procurement, HC326, if he will  place in the Library details of the Babel Fish III project.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116181","116181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795849","2017-11-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs,  what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Colombian Government and US Administration on ending child labour in the mining of coal, and other minerals in Columbia.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116182","116182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795850","2017-11-30","Department for International Development","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help end childhood deaths from pneumonia by 2030.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116183","116183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795852","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children looked after by foster carers use the 15 hours of universally available funded childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116184","116184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795853","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost of extending 30 hours of funded childcare to children in foster care.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116185","116185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795854","2017-11-30","Department for International Development","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help achieve the Sustainable Development Goal of ending preventable child deaths by 2030.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116186","116186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795855","2017-11-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of leaving the EU on the operation of the marine and recreational boating sectors.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116187","116187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795857","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 107743, on day care, how many and what proportion of parents who have successfully applied for tax-free childcare are self-employed.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116188","116188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795858","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the number of childcare providers who have successfully signed up for Tax-Free Childcare to date.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116189","116189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795859","2017-11-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the viability of (a) coastal communities and (b) local economies with a significant marine sector of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116190","116190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795860","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the impact assessment for Tax-Free Childcare did not refer to the expenditure on childcare provision by families as set out by the Department of Education.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116191","116191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795862","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria the Government plans to use to measure the success of Tax-Free Childcare.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116192","116192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795863","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what performance indicators and success criteria his Department plan to use to assess the performance of (a) National Savings and Investments and (b) ATOS in delivering Tax-Free Childcare.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116193","116193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795864","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the performance of (a) National Savings & lnvestments  and (b) Atos in the delivery of Tax-Free Childcare since it was launched in April 2017.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116194","116194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795865","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the IT system used by Atos to administer tax-free childcare.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116195","116195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795866","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his (a) Russian, (b) Ukrainian and (c) EU counterparts on the treatment of Ali Feruz.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116196","116196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795868","2017-11-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will undertake a visit to Iran to discuss the case of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe with his Iranian counterpart in advance of her planned court appearance for 10 December 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116197","116197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795869","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the (a) system costs and (b) running costs of tax-free childcare have exceeded the budget allocated to the service by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116198","116198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795870","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to extend the deadline for closing childcare vouchers if the childcare service IT system is not fully operational by April 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116199","116199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795871","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 11 September 2015 to Question 8179 on children: daycare, what assessment he has made of the link between the introduction of tax-free childcare and (a) the cost and (b) demand for childcare.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116200","116200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795872","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff car parking spaces there are  at Shettleston Jobcentre.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116201","116201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795873","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many car parking spaces there are for the use of customers at Shettleston Jobcentre.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116202","116202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795874","2017-11-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the market for second-hand recreational boats of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116203","116203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795876","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many car parking spaces will be available for the use of staff at Shettleston Jobcentre following its merger with Bridgeton, Easterhouse and Parkhead Jobcentres.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116204","116204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795877","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many car parking spaces will be available for the use of customers at Shettleston Jobcentre following its merger with Bridgeton, Easterhouse and Parkhead Jobcentres.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116205","116205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795878","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to ensure that recreational boats placed on the market can attain Union Goods status after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116206","116206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795879","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the Department plans to ensure that recreational boats travelling from the UK to the EU with non-Union goods status can benefit from temporary admission relief on VAT and duty after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116207","116207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795880","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 114582 on General Practitioners: Finance, if he plans to review the performance of the GP at Hand service at regular intervals.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116208","116208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795881","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to  Question 114582 on General Practitioners: finance, what criteria his Department will use to monitor the GP at Hand service.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116209","116209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795883","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to ensure that recreational boaters whose vessels have Union Goods status are able to prove that status when travelling between the UK and EU member states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116210","116210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795884","2017-11-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will list the (a) people and (b) organisations who contributed to informal consultation on implementation of Section 106 of the Digital Economy Act 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116211","116211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795886","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the the amount each university has spent on payments for early retirement in each of the last 3 years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116212","116212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795887","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of the UK leaving the EU on land prices in rural communities.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116213","116213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795888","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients are registered with each General Practitioner in each Clinical Commissioning Group area in Essex.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116214","116214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795890","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to introduce a temporary blue badge scheme for people with short-term medical conditions.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116215","116215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795891","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding he has allocated from the public purse to support the development of new (a) primary care centres and (b) healthcare hubs.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116216","116216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795892","2017-11-30","Department for International Trade","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the number of businesses in Essex that export overseas, which countries those business export to and the value of those exports.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116217","116217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795893","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the reassessment period for people with mental health problems receiving personal independence payments.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116218","116218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795894","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many investigations have been carried out by National Security Vetting in each of the last ten years; and how many of those investigations resulted in the reinstatement of security clearance.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116219","116219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795895","2017-11-30","Attorney General","2017-11-28","To ask the Attorney General, what discussions he has had with the Crown Prosecution Service on applications to the Courts for compensation orders to support victims of crime.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116220","116220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795896","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 106926, on tax-free childcare, for what reasons the figures provided in that Answer differ with those on page 240 of the Office for Budget Responsibility's Economic and Fiscal Outlook 2017.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116221","116221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795898","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the Government has made of the resilience of the UK’s health and social care infrastructure to the effects of climate change.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116222","116222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795899","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government has taken to improve the resilience of NHS and care services to the warming of the UK's climate, the future frequency of adverse weather events and other potential effects of climate change.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116223","116223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795900","2017-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to support victims of crime; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116224","116224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795902","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of progress in reducing the greenhouse gas emissions of NHS Trusts; and what steps he is taking to ensure that the NHS Sustainable Development Unit’s mission to embed and promote the environmental, social and financial elements of sustainable development is being followed through across the NHS in England.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116225","116225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795903","2017-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims of crime in Essex have received the proceeds of compensation orders issued against offenders in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116226","116226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795904","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) disabled adult passengers, (b) adult passengers and (c)  adult passengers with mental health conditions who have used private hire vehicles as a result of living in areas not serviced by buses in each of the last 3 years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116227","116227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795905","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate the Government has made of the number of PHV passengers outside of London in 2015 who were (a) over 75 years old, (b) between 60 and 75 years old, (c) were blind or visually impaired, (d) had other disabilities, and (e) were children travelling without adult supervision.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116228","116228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795906","2017-11-30","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for the Cabinet Office of 22 November 2017, Official Report, c1033, if that Minister will meet with Cambridge Assessment and the hon. Member for Cambridge to discuss the updating of freedom of information arrangements aside from the review of the code of practice.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116229","116229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795907","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits to the economy of (a) Essex and (b) the UK of a passing loop north of Witham on the Great Eastern Main Line.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116230","116230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795909","2017-11-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 October 2017 to Question 105652 (a) how the £30 million made available for relationship support services between April 2017 and March 2020 has been allocated in 2017/18, (b) what the planned total investment in relationship support programmes was for 2018/19 and 2019/20 prior to the November 2017 Budget, (c) what additional funding the November 2017 Budget allocated to relationship support programmes, (d) what the planned total investment in relationship support programmes is for 2018/19 and 2019/20 following the November 2017 Budget and (e) whether government investing in relationship support programmes includes other projects to strengthen families an relationships in addition to the Reducing Parental Conflict Programme.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116231","116231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795910","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the value of the assets for which his Department is responsible.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116232","116232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795911","2017-11-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the planned investment in relationship support programmes was for 2018-19 and 2019-20 prior to any changes announced in Autumn Budget 2017; what additional funding Autumn Budget 2017 allocated to relationship support programmes; what the planned total investment in relationship support programmes is for 2018-19 and 2019-20 as a result of Autumn Budget 2017; and whether that investment in relationship support programmes relates to (a) the Department for Work and Pensions' Reducing Parental Conflict Programme or (b) other programmes or projects intended to strengthen families and relationships.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116233","116233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795913","2017-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the value of the assets for which his Department is responsible.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116234","116234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795914","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to make a decision on upgrading and dualling the A120 between Braintree and the A12; and what the key performance target criteria are for that decision.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116235","116235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795915","2017-11-30","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the value of the assets for which his Department is responsible.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116236","116236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795916","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse has been of the current boundary review (a) up to the date of opening of the third consultation and (b) on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116237","116237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795918","2017-11-30","Scotland Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the value of the assets for which his Department is responsible.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116238","116238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795919","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 114597, what funds her Department allocated to promote that guidance through its social media channels.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116239","116239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795920","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the amount of funding provided by any of the constituent organisations of the EU (a) to specialist violence against women and girls organisations and specialist women’s services and (b) for research relating to those issues.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116240","116240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795921","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 114597, if she will make it her Department's policy to hold data on whether schools have received guidance on their statutory duty towards their pupils' health.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116241","116241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795922","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to provide funding equivalent to that currently provided by the EU for violence against women and girls organisations and specialist women’s services, and research relating to those issues after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116242","116242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795923","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2017 to Question 113317, whether her Department has plans to publish data on the numbers of its case workers who undertook Keeping Children Safe Tier 3 training.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116243","116243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795925","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 109193, where the £500 million in investment in IT has been spent; how that amount compares with the original estimate the Government was given from the providers and on which contracts were signed; and whether there are penalties under those contracts for any overspend.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116244","116244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795926","2017-11-30","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for public service pension schemes of the judgment of the Supreme Court in Walker v. Innospec Limited?","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116245","116245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795927","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training in assessing mental health conditions is available to officials dealing with personal independence claims; and what proportion of such staff have received such training.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116246","116246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795928","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Warrington North constituency who are eligible for inclusion on the electoral register but are not registered.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116247","116247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795929","2017-11-30","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ban vaginal mesh operations.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116248","116248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795930","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received on removing the 50 per cent cap on new Catholic schools; and what plans she has to bring forward legislative proposals on removing that cap.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116249","116249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795932","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to revise and reissue the national guidance document entitled Cycle infrastructure design (LTN 2/08).","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116250","116250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795933","2017-12-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Youth Development Fund grants; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116251","116251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795934","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications have been made for education, health and care plans in (a) the UK, (b) Greater London and (c) the London Borough of Newham in 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116252","116252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795935","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many education, health and care plans have been provided to children in (a) the UK, (b) Greater London and (c) the London Borough of Newham in 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116253","116253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795937","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what  the proportionate change has been in the level of voter registration over the most recent year for which data are available in (a) England, (b) Greater London and (c) London Borough of Newham.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116254","116254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795938","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will require local authorities to produce a strategy for improving disadvantaged children’s outcomes.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116255","116255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795940","2017-11-30","Attorney General","2017-11-28","To ask the Attorney General,  how many successful prosecutions there have been of cyclists riding on pavements in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116256","116256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795941","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to lines 63 and 64 of Table 2.1 of Autumn Budget 2017, what target he has set for the Resource and Accounting Budgetary charge.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116257","116257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795942","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 4.24 of the Autumn Budget 2017, what baseline year will apply for new schools opening in future academic years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116258","116258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795943","2017-11-30","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes to the RAB rate on the Department for Education’s budget in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20, (c) 2020-21, (d) 2021-22, and (e) 2022-23.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116259","116259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795944","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask Secretary of State for Education, what projection his Department has made of the increased cost of each year of graduate debt write-offs following the changes to the student loans repayment threshold proposed in Table 1.9 of Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116260","116260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795945","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to end the upper parameter limit on tuition fees?","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116261","116261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795948","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to set before Parliament the itemised liabilities due for payment by the Government to the EU in respect of the forthcoming withdrawal agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Mr Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116263","116263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795949","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding the Government plans to allocate to the PE and Sport Premium in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21, (e) 2021-22, and (f) 2022-23.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116264","116264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795950","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the revenue projections for the soft drinks industry levy in the Autumn Budget 2017, Table C.5, what assessment he has made of the potential effect the fall in projected revenue will have on the total revenue funding allocated to the Department for Education in each year of the forecast period.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116265","116265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795951","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much the Government has allocated to the healthy pupil capital fund in the next two financial years; and what proportion of that funding is ring-fenced from the soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116266","116266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795953","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much government funding was allocated to the Union Learning Fund in each financial year from 2009-2010 to 2014-2015.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116267","116267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795954","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether funding for the planned £26 million contract to provide breakfast clubs will be allocated from revenue raised from the soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116268","116268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795955","2017-11-30","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in the UK have been fined for failing to complete a Household Enquiry Form for voter registration in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116269","116269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795956","2017-11-30","Cabinet Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that people who identify as transgender can register to vote.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116270","116270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795957","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were admitted to Accident and Emergency departments for self-harm in each NHS trust in England, in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116271","116271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795958","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of management training opportunities provided to (a) junior doctors and (b) nurses for working in A&E departments.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116272","116272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795959","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of never events in NHS trusts.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116273","116273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795961","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the net change has been in the number of in-patient perinatal mental health beds since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116274","116274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795962","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people born on 3 May 2000 or earlier are in possession of an Oyster Photocard registered in (a) Woking, (b) Gosport, (c) Bromley or (d) Watford local authority who are aged (i) under 24, (ii) 25 to 49, (iii) 50 to 64 and (iv) 65 or older.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116275","116275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795963","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people born on 3 May 2000 or earlier are in possession of a Proof of Age Standards Scheme card registered in (a) Woking, (b) Gosport, (c) Bromley or (d) Watford local authority who are aged (i) under 24, (ii) 25 to 49, (iii) 50 to 64 and (iv) 65 or older.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116276","116276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795965","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people born on 3 May 2000 or earlier are in possession of a provisional or permanent driving licence registered in (a) Woking, (b) Gosport, (c) Bromley or (d) Watford local authority who are aged (i) under 24, (ii) 25 to 49, (iii) 50 to 64 and (iv) 65 or older.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116277","116277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795966","2017-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people born on 3 May 2000 or earlier are in possession of a military identification card registered in (a) Woking, (b) Gosport, (c) Bromley or (d) Watford local authority who are aged (i) under 24, (ii) 25 to 49, (iii) 50 to 64 and (iv) 65 or older.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116278","116278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795967","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people born on 3 May 2000 or earlier are in possession of a police identification card registered in (a) Woking, (b) Gosport, (c) Bromley or (d) Watford local authority who are aged (i) under 24, (ii) 25 to 49, (iii) 50 to 64 and (iv) 65 or older.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116279","116279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795968","2017-11-30","Home Office","2017-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people born on 3 May 2000 or earlier are in possession of a passport registered in (a) Woking, (b) Gosport, (c) Bromley or (d) Watford local authority who are aged (i) under 24, (ii) 25 to 49, (iii) 50 to 64 and (iv) 65 or older.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116280","116280"
