"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147165","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292148","292148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147166","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal from the Verify scheme of service providers on people in (a) Walsall North constituency that have enrolled with that service and are required to re-enrol with another service provider.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292335","292335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147167","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292149","292149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147168","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Ministerial Statement of  9 September 2019 on Local Government update, HCWS 1830, if he will place in the Library a copy of the selection criteria by which the 100 places invited to develop proposals for town deals were decided.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292121","292121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147169","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the Towns Fund prospectus.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292122","292122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147170","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many meetings she had with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292150","292150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147171","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of (a) sanctions and (b) conditionality on the (i) health and well-being of claimants and (ii) the ability of claimants to enter employment.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292336","292336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147172","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292151","292151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147173","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on trends in the level of referrals to food banks.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292337","292337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147174","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of trends in the level of child poverty.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292338","292338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147175","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of patients that waited longer than four hours in A&E in (a) 2009-10 and (b) 2018-19.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292123","292123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147176","2019-10-02","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292152","292152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147177","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of the NHS mental health nursing workforce in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292124","292124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147178","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people on NHS waiting lists in England in (a) 2010 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292125","292125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147179","2019-10-02","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292153","292153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147180","2019-10-02","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292154","292154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147181","2019-10-02","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he he has taken to ensure the preparedness of the British Army for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292270","292270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147182","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292155","292155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147183","2019-10-02","Department for International Trade","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many meetings she had with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292156","292156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147184","2019-10-02","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292157","292157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147185","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 290705 on Civil Disorder, on what dates Ministers of her Department have met with the (a) National Police Chiefs Council and (b) the National Police Coordination Centre since July 2019; and what were the outcomes of those meetings.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292126","292126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147186","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of the Government's proposal to develop and build a commercially viable fusion power plant by 2040.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292339","292339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147187","2019-10-02","Wales Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292158","292158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147188","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of leaving Euratom on the (a) cost to the public purse of developing and (b) ability of the UK to develop commercially viable fusion power plants.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292340","292340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147189","2019-10-02","Prime Minister","2019-09-30","To ask the Prime Minister, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292159","292159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147190","2019-10-02","Northern Ireland Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292160","292160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147191","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292161","292161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147192","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 290704 which states that there is no intelligence to suggest widespread public disorder, what the evidential basis was for the statement in paragraph 13 of the Yellowhammer document suggesting there may be a rise in public disorder and community tensions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292127","292127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147193","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) the Chinese Government's compliance with the Sino-British Declaration and (b) the effect of that declaration under international law.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292079","292079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147194","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made on (a) human rights, (b) police violence and (c) repression in Hong Kong to (i) his Chinese counterpart, (ii) the Chinese Ambassador to the UK and (iii) the Government in Hong Kong; and what response has been received to those representations.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292080","292080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147195","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have plans to hold meetings with the delegation from Fight for Freedom Stand With Hong Kong to discuss the recent events in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292081","292081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147196","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many GPs were recruited to the NHS under the GP International recruitment scheme in (a) 2018 and (b) 2019; and what the cost to the public purse has been of that scheme.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292341","292341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147197","2019-10-03","Department for International Trade","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if she will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of her Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292342","292342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147198","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of her Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292343","292343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147199","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of her Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292344","292344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147200","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of her Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292345","292345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147201","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of her Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292346","292346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147202","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of her Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292347","292347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147203","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the application Hacker House made to her Department for funding from the Cyber Security Immediate Impact Fund included information on previous funding received by (a) Directors in London and (b) Partners of that company.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292163","292163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147204","2019-10-03","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292348","292348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147205","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292349","292349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147206","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's policy is on political advertising in schools.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292164","292164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147207","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292350","292350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147208","2019-10-03","Prime Minister","2019-09-30","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between his office and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292351","292351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147209","2019-10-02","Wales Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292352","292352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147210","2019-10-02","Scotland Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292353","292353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147211","2019-10-02","Leader of the House","2019-09-30","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his office and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292354","292354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147212","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many and what proportion of organisations in receipt of funds through the Cyber Security Immediate Impact Fund were awarded the maximum sum available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292165","292165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147213","2019-10-02","Northern Ireland Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292355","292355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147214","2019-10-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292356","292356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147215","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292357","292357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147216","2019-10-02","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292358","292358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147217","2019-10-02","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292359","292359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147218","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292360","292360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147219","2019-10-02","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292361","292361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147220","2019-10-02","Attorney General","2019-09-30","To ask the Attorney General,  if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292362","292362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147221","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish (a) the outcome of all meetings and (b) all call logs between Ministers of his Department and Mr Crispin Odey.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292363","292363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147222","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 290970 on Brexit, when he plans to publish the costs of the Get Ready for Brexit campaign for (a) August and (b) September 2019.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292179","292179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147223","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what procedures are in place to record the number of patients  offered (a) evening and (b) weekend appointments at GP surgeries.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292364","292364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147224","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps is he taking to strengthen protections for shop workers that face (a) abusive, (b) threatening and (c) violent behaviour.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292365","292365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147225","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse has been on advertising in schools in relation to the UK leaving the EU in the last six months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292166","292166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147226","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the Healthy Starts Voucher Scheme to include the purchase of fortified plant milks.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292141","292141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147227","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is his policy to retain a safety critical guard on each train on the First Trenitalia West Coast franchise.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292224","292224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147228","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the existing locations of (a) train crew and (b) catering depots will be retained on the First Trenitalia West Coast franchise.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292225","292225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147229","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the buffet car will be retained on all trains, including the new and updated fleet, on the First Trenitalia West Coast franchise.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292226","292226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147230","2019-10-02","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether there there are plans to change the operational models for supplying train catering store supplies on the First Trenitalia West Coast franchise.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292227","292227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147231","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether all ticket offices on the First Trenitalia West Coast franchise will remain open with existing staffing levels and opening hours maintained.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292228","292228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147232","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) despatch staff, (b) shunters, (c) directly employed cleaners (d) customer service staff and (e) other front-line station staffing levels will be maintained on the First Trenitalia West Coast franchise.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292229","292229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147233","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number of deaths related to opioid usage and (b) rates of opioid addiction.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292366","292366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147234","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the provision of treatment for (a) opioid and (b) other prescription drug addiction.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292367","292367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147235","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of regulations on the (a) sale, (b) marketing and (c) proscribing of opioids and other extra strong pain relief medication.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292368","292368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147236","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has his Department made of the effectiveness of regulations on (a) donations from and (b) lobbying by pharmaceutical companies.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292369","292369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147237","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the cost to schools of increasing starting salaries for teachers to £30,000.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292252","292252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147238","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to apply national pay settlements to teachers working in academy schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292253","292253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147239","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to implement a schools level national funding formula; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292254","292254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147240","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will allocate additional funding to Ofsted to carry out additional inspections when schools previously rated Outstanding are no longer exempt from routine inspection.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292255","292255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147241","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his oral contribution of 3 September 2019, Official Report, column 65, on education funding, which courses will be eligible for funding from the £120 million for high-cost subjects; and how that funding will be distributed.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292256","292256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147242","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 2.10 of Spending Round 2019, how the £66 million will be distributed between (a) state maintained nurseries and (b) private, voluntary, and independent childcare settings.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292257","292257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147243","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 2.10 of Spending Round 2019 published on 4 September 2019, what the average hourly funding rate for delivering the Government's free hours offers (a) was in 2018-19 and (b) will be in 2019-20.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292258","292258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147244","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce plastic waste in oceans.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292370","292370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147245","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 May 2019 to Question 246545 on Green Deal Scheme: Appeals, how many of the 107 outstanding cases referred to her have been with her office for (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five, (f) six, (g) seven, (h) eight, (i) nine, (j) 10, (k) 11 and (l) 12 months or longer without a final decision having been made.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292371","292371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147246","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the financial effect on the housing sector of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292372","292372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147247","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 May 2019 to Question 246545 on Green Deal Scheme: Appeals, how many Intention Notices have been (a) issued and (b) agreed.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292373","292373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147248","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 May 2019 to Question 246545 on Green Deal Scheme: Appeals, how many cases from Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency that were referred to her have been with her office for (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five, (f) six, (g) seven, (h) eight, (i) nine, (j) 10, (k) 11 and (l) 12 months or longer without a final decision having been made.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292374","292374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147249","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has contingency plans to second police officers to alternative territorial police forces in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292128","292128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147250","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Health of 30 September 2019, on the Health Infrastructure Plan, what increase in capital funding will be delivered by the Health Infrastructure Plan; what the subsequent additional Barnett Consequential Funding to Scotland for that plan will be; and if he will provide the spend profile on a year by year projection for the additional funding for that plan to Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292375","292375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147251","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to Question 286311, tabled on 3 September 2019 by the hon. Member for Ilford North.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292376","292376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147252","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to Question 286312, tabled on 3 September 2019 by the hon. Member for Ilford North.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292377","292377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147253","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to Question 286313, tabled on 3 September 2019 by the hon. Member for Ilford North.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292378","292378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147254","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the £25 million funding for T levels announced in the Spending Round 2019 will be allocated.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292259","292259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147255","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to Question 286314, tabled on 3 September 2019 by the hon. Member for Ilford North.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292379","292379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147256","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy for NHS England to require (a) Clinical Commissioning Groups and (b) NHS trusts that have formularies which do not list all of the medical devices available on Part IX of the Drug Tariff to issue guidance to clinicians on their ability to prescribe the most appropriate medical device available through that tariff and to include a link to that tariff online.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292263","292263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147257","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure pension funds consider the impact of climate change when taking investment decisions.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292199","292199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147258","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress has been made on ensuring the smooth flow of medical devices in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with a deal and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292264","292264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147259","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the capacity of Notified Bodies under the terms of the Medical Devices Regulation to meet the demand for their services.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292265","292265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147260","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to Question 286315, tabled on 3 September by the hon. Member for Ilford North.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292380","292380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147261","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent research she has commissioned on the safety of (a) milk and (b) meat that enters the human food chain of cattle slaughtered as a result of bovine TB incidence.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292082","292082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147262","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions has she had with the Welsh Government on strategies for the eradication of bovine TB.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292083","292083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147263","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to publish its response to the Godray Report on bovine TB.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292084","292084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147264","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of (a) restoring sections of and (b) extending the Sankey Canal to join the main canal system through the Leeds and Liverpool Canal.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292280","292280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147265","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers he plans to recruit in (a) St Helens, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year until 2024-25.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292381","292381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147266","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of police officers that will leave the service in (a) St Helens, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year until 2024-25.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292382","292382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147267","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of women affected by changes to the stage pension age, in (a) St Helens, (b) Liverpool City Region and (c) the UK in each year until 2029-30.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292383","292383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147268","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 290458 on A34, if his Department will take steps to ensure that the environmental impact assessment for the A34 improvement works conducted by the Highways Agency is published.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292384","292384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147269","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many organisations receive funding from his Department through the Asylum, Migration and Integration Fund.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292230","292230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147270","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on (a) refugees and (b) people seeking asylum in the UK in the event that UK (i) charities and (ii) organisations no longer receive funding through the Asylum, Migration and Integration Fund.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292231","292231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147271","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the memorandum of understanding sent from the Cabinet Office to his Department governing the sharing of GOV.UK user data with the Government Digital Service.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292180","292180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147272","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the Memorandum of Understanding sent by the Cabinet Office to his Department on the sharing of GOV.UK user data with the Government Digital Service.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292181","292181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147273","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the Memorandum of Understanding sent by the Cabinet Office to his Department on the sharing of GOV.UK user data with the Government Digital Service.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292182","292182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147274","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the (a) bidders and (b) successful candidates for tender for the Get Ready for Brexit campaign; and what the value of each successful tender was for both (i) external advertising and (ii) analytics.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292242","292242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147275","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, by what date his Department plans for the 20,000 new police officers to have completed training at the National College of Policing at Hendon.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292243","292243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147276","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers from (a) England and Wales, (b) Scotland and (c) non-geographic forces were deployed to support the Police Service of Northern Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292244","292244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147277","2019-10-02","Wales Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on the Wales economy of the UK leaving EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292385","292385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147278","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many complaints in relation to the conduct of Special Advisers in each government department were submitted to the (a) Ethics and Propriety team and (b) the Cabinet Secretary since the formation of the Government in 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292245","292245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147279","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many waste incineration plants burning (a) residential, (b) commercial and (c) industrial waste were licensed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292246","292246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147280","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 208368 on Renewable Heat Incentive Scheme: Scotland, how many outstanding decision notices there are for applications under the renewable heat incentive scheme for the installation of a biomass boiler for (a) non-domestic properties and (b) domestic applications.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292386","292386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147281","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reason Stornoway Wind Farm was unsuccessful in the third Contracts for Difference round.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292387","292387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147282","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timeframe is for the conclusion of the review of evidence on levelised costs of electricity generation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292388","292388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147283","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications made to the seasonal workers pilot scheme were (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292389","292389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147284","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for the seasonal workers pilot scheme from businesses operating in Scotland were (a) made and (b) successful.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292390","292390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147285","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment has been made of the effectiveness of the financial assistance scheme for pensioners affected by occupational pension scheme looses.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292247","292247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147286","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much money has been spent from the public purse on placing the Government's Brexit notifications in newspapers.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292391","292391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147287","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how money has been spent from the public purse on radio campaigns for the Government's Get ready for Brexit campaign.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292392","292392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147288","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have been convicted of a serious assault on a prison officer in each of the last five years; and what additional sentence those prisoners were given as a result those assaults.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292171","292171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147289","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how money has been spent from the public purse on TV adverts for the Government's Get ready for Brexit campaign.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292393","292393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147290","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how money has been spent from the public purse on social media in relation to the Government's Get ready for Brexit campaign.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292394","292394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147291","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of homicide did not receive a custodial sentence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292172","292172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147292","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders released from prison following a murder conviction have been on life licence in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292173","292173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147293","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications under the seasonal workers pilot scheme were allocated but not filled with a seasonal worker.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292395","292395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147294","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria his Department plans to use to evaluate the seasonal workers pilot scheme.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292396","292396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147295","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders serving a life sentence for murder have been released on licence since 2007; and how many of those people were subsequently convicted of (a) another murder, (b) violence against the person and (c) another offence.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292174","292174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147296","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the answer of 8 April 2019 to Question 240591 on Energy: storage, when the Government plans to amend the Electricity Act 1989 to define electricity storage as a distinct subset of generation.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292397","292397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147297","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders serving life sentences for murder that were released on licence did not commit another offence in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292175","292175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147298","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment she has made of the effect of Stornoway wind farm being unsuccessful in the third Contracts for Difference auction on the proposed interconnector to the Western Isles; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292398","292398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147299","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places on the seasonal workers pilot scheme were allocated to (a) operators and (b) businesses in (i) Angus (ii) Perth and North Perthshire, (iii) Stirling, (iv) Ochil and South Perthshire and (v) North East Fife.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292399","292399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147300","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places on the seasonal workers pilot scheme were allocated to (a) operators and (b) businesses in (i) Ayr Carrick and Cumnock, (ii) Dumfries and Galloway, (iii) Dumfriesshire, Clydesdale and Tweedale, (iv) Berwickshire, Roxburgh and Selkirk and (v) East Lothian.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292400","292400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147301","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places on the seasonal workers pilot scheme were allocated to (a) operators and (b) businesses in (i) Mcray, (ii) Inverness, Nairn, Badenoch and Strathspey, (iii) Banff and Buchan (iv) Gordon and (v) West Aberdeenshire and Kincardine constituencies.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292401","292401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147302","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timescale is for the launch of the public consultation on milk supply contracts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292402","292402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147303","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of mandatory contracts for milk supply contracts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292403","292403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147304","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292404","292404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147305","2019-10-02","Attorney General","2019-09-30","To ask the Attorney General, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292405","292405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147306","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292406","292406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147307","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292407","292407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147308","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292408","292408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147309","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292409","292409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147310","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292410","292410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147311","2019-10-02","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292411","292411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147312","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292412","292412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147313","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292413","292413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147314","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292414","292414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147315","2019-10-02","Attorney General","2019-09-30","To ask the Attorney General, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292415","292415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147316","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292416","292416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147317","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292417","292417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147318","2019-10-03","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will commission a review of the conditions attached to Official Development Assistance to ensure that aid recipients follow accepted best practice in relation to (a) the disposal of plastic waste and (b) other environmental procedures.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292129","292129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147319","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292418","292418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147320","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292419","292419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147321","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the (a) level of use and (b) ward occupation rate of NHS hospitals in advance of new NHS hospitals being built; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292130","292130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147322","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the level of risk to the health of children posed by wi-fi systems in the home; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292131","292131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147323","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292420","292420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147324","2019-10-02","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292421","292421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147325","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292422","292422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147326","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292423","292423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147327","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Prime Minister's office spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292424","292424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147328","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Prime Minister's office spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292425","292425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147329","2019-10-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292426","292426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147330","2019-10-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on ministerial travel by (a) first class, (b) second class and (c) in total in 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292427","292427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147331","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on refreshments in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292428","292428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147332","2019-10-02","Attorney General","2019-09-30","To ask the Attorney General, how much his Department spent on refreshments in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292429","292429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147333","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department spent on refreshments in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292430","292430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147334","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department spent on refreshments in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292431","292431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147335","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on refreshments in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292432","292432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147346","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government what steps he is taking to support the digitalisation of high streets in small towns and villages.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912534","912534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146755","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish the performance indicators and metrics for the grant funding awarded to Hacker House; and what assessment she has made of whether those performance indicators have been met.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291558","291558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146756","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing councils with the power to manage properties currently owned by housing associations.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291556","291556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146757","2019-10-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps she is taking to help ensure households who (a) don't want and (b) are unable to have a smart meter installed can access the cheapest available energy deals.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291596","291596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146758","2019-10-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with the President of the Supreme Court.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291537","291537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146759","2019-10-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the adequacy of the guidance issued to Ministers on relations with the judiciary.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291538","291538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146760","2019-10-01","Prime Minister","2019-09-27","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with with (a) President Trump, (b) President Rouhani and (c) his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291539","291539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146761","2019-10-01","Department for International Trade","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the financial value was of arms exports to each member of the Saudi Arabian-led intervention in Yemen since 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291540","291540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146762","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of buses in England (a) meet and (b) exceed Euro VI emission standards.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291560","291560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146763","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how he plans to allocate the £200 million of increased funding to transform bus services announced in the Spending Round 2019.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291561","291561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146764","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will introduce a vehicle labelling scheme for new and second-hand cars and vans detailing the real world nitrogen dioxide and particulate matter emissions of vehicles.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291562","291562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146765","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the National Audit Office's report, Exiting the EU: supplying the health and social care sectors, published on 27 September 2019, what assessment he has made of the effect on medical supplies in the event that government freight capacity is not adequate by 30 November 2019.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291520","291520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146766","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the National Audit Office's report, Exiting the EU: supplying the health and social care sectors, published on 27 September 2019, (a) for how long and (b) at what cost his Department is procuring a dedicated courier service for urgent medicines and supplies secured from manufacturers in the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291521","291521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146767","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for his policies of the report entitled, Exiting the EU: supplying the health and social care sectors, published by the National Audit Office in September 2019.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291522","291522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146769","2019-10-02","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason was the Government's procurement of additional freight capacity delayed.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291524","291524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146770","2019-10-02","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of freight capacity for priority goods will be in place by 31 October 2019; and what assessment he has made of the effect on the supply of priority goods in the event that that capacity is not made available until 30 November 2019.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291525","291525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146771","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) cost to the public purse of and (b) length of time required for Government-secured freight capacity in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291526","291526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146772","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) availability and (b) adequacy of stockpiles of (i) medicines, (ii) medical equipment and (iii) medical devices held by suppliers to prepare for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291527","291527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146773","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of (a) nursing homes and (b) providers of domiciliary care have made preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and what support his Department has provided to those organisation to ensure that preparedness.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291528","291528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146774","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to introduce a ban on the sale of plastic tea bags.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291557","291557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146775","2019-10-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the report entitled, Attitudes to Animal Research 2018 published in May 2019, what her policy is on the use of dogs in medical research.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291517","291517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146776","2019-10-01","Home Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report entitled, Attitudes to Animal Research 2018, published in May 2019, whether she plans to undertake a review of the use of a second non-rodent species in regulatory toxicity testing.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291518","291518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146777","2019-10-01","Home Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to stop toxicity testing on mammals by 2035.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291519","291519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146778","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether it is her policy to lay before Parliament the statutory instruments required to give legal effect to the regulations on age verification for commercial pornography sites by 3 October 2019.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291559","291559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146779","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve road connectivity between South Yorkshire and Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291576","291576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146780","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of (a) regulation of purpose-built student accommodation providers and (b) safeguards for students affected by properties not being built in time for university starting dates.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291607","291607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146781","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of delays in the provision of new purpose-built student accommodation beyond the start date of students' courses  on (a) student well-being, (b) academic achievement of students and (c) taxpayer value for money.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291608","291608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146782","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether it remains the policy of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence that intermittent self-catheterisation is the gold standard approach to safe and effective catheterisation.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291563","291563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146783","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the most common cause of unplanned admissions to hospitals in England is; and what steps he is taking to reduce the need for those admissions.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291564","291564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146784","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether any funds are being made available from the public purse for Southampton University's trial to compare mixed multi/single-use catheter management with single-use catheter management by intermittent catheter uses.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291565","291565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146785","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the responses to the survey of local authorities undertaken by his Department in September 2019 on schools' preparedness for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291609","291609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146786","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which ethical committee gave consent to the Multicath study undertaken into reusable catheters by Professor Mandy Fader of Southampton University.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291566","291566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146787","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have been enrolled to use reusable catheters on the Multicath study undertaken by Professor Mandy Fader of Southampton University; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291567","291567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146788","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Section 20 rules to apply to stay in the UK under the EU Settlement Scheme, what support her Department is providing to local authorities to enable them to work with looked-after children that are EU nationals.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291577","291577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146789","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many non-disclosure agreements in relation to preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal his Department has signed with (a) private organisations and (b) public organisations from (i) 23 June 2016 to 22 August 2019 and (ii) since 22 August 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291545","291545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146790","2019-10-02","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many non-disclosure agreements in relation to preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal his Department has signed with (a) private organisations and (b) public organisations between (i) 23 June 2016 and  22 August 2019 and (ii) since 22 August 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291546","291546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146791","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many non disclosure agreements in relation to preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal her Department has signed with (a) private organisations and (b) public organisations between (i) 23 June 2016 and  22 August 2019 and (ii) since 22 August 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291547","291547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146792","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that children in care that are EU nationals are informed of the potential requirement to apply to secure their status in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291578","291578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146793","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the take-up of dancing in schools to help tackle childhood obesity.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291588","291588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146794","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what criteria the Healthcare Safety Investigation Branch is required to meet in order to start an investigation.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291586","291586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146795","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's consultation entitled, Building a safer future: proposals for reform of the building safety regulatory system, whether he plans to lower the threshold at which combustible materials are banned for use on new high-rise residential buildings from 18 metres to 11 metres.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291579","291579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146796","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the National Audit Office's report, Exiting the EU: supplying the health and social care sectors, published on 27 October 2019, what discussions he has had with healthcare providers to assess the adequacy of (a) medicines, (b) medical supplies, (c) freight capacity for securing continued supplies in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291598","291598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146797","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's consultation entitled, Building a safer future: proposals for reform of the building safety regulatory system, whether he plans to undertake a consultation on banning the use of combustible materials on the external walls of (a) hospitals, (b) care homes and (c) sheltered housing.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291580","291580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146798","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of (a) nursing homes and (b) other social care providers have complied with his advice on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU; and what discussions officials of his Department have had with providers that have not complied with that advice.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291599","291599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146799","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with representatives of NHS England on the reintroduction of financial incentives to attract people into nursing careers.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291600","291600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146800","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with representatives of healthcare providers on nursing vacancies in NHS trusts.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291601","291601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146801","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the length of time  for nursing applications to reach pre-2015 levels in the event of the reintroduction of financial incentives for people entering the nursing profession.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291602","291602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146802","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's data release entitled, Building Safety Programme: Monthly Data Release for August 2019, what steps his Department is taking to confirm the cladding status of the four private sector residential buildings for which such status is still to be confirmed.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291581","291581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146803","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of trends in level of people living in temporary accommodation in the last three years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291589","291589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146804","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support individuals and families in temporary accommodation to move into long-term housing.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291590","291590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146805","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of funding allocated to local authorities to implement the Homelessness Reduction Act 2017.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291591","291591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146806","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 April 2019 to Question 239278 on Sleeping Rough, when he plans to publish the impact and process evaluation of the rough sleeping initiative.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291592","291592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146807","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to increase the provision of (a) affordable housing and (b) social housing in (i) London and (ii) England.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291593","291593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146808","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's data release entitled, Building Safety Programme: Monthly Data Release for August 2019, published on 12 September 2019, how many of the 1,494 non-ACM cladding samples held at the Building Research Establishment contain combustible materials.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291582","291582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146809","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's data release entitled, Building Safety Programme: Monthly Data Release for August 2019, published on 12 September 2019, how many of the 1,494 non-ACM cladding samples held at the Building Research Establishment are timber cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291583","291583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146810","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's data release entitled, Building Safety Programme: Monthly Data Release for August 2019, published on 12 September 2019, if his Department will publish a full analysis of the 1,494 non-ACM cladding samples held at the Building Research Establishment.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291584","291584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146811","2019-10-02","Department for International Development","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding allocated by his Department to consultancy services to support its preparations for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291603","291603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146812","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to introduce safety tests on the proposed 5G pilot projects.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291573","291573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146813","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the level of risk to health posed by 5G connectivity.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291574","291574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146814","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Independent Press Standards Organisation on improving the conduct of the press intruding into the private lives of non-political public figures.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291587","291587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146815","2019-10-02","Department for International Development","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer to ensure that Official Development Assistance expenditure by other Departments contributes to poverty reduction.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291604","291604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146816","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to support pupils with SEND.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291605","291605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146817","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli Government on the alleged shooting by the Israeli Defence Force of a 9 year old Palestinian boy, Abd a-Rahman a-Shteiwi on 12 July 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291575","291575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146818","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the finding by the Children's Commissioner for England in her report, Growing Up North, published in March 2018, that pupils from London who have had free school meals are twice as likely to go to university than equivalent children in the north.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291571","291571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146819","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the finding by the Northern Powerhouse Project in its 2018 report, Educating the North, that  disadvantaged pupils in the north achieve attainment levels 1.3 percentage points less than the national disadvantaged average and 6.5 percentage points less than their disadvantaged peers in London.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291572","291572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146820","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent advice he has received from the Director General of the Propriety and Ethics Team on the (a) standards and ethics and (b) corporate governance of government departments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291541","291541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146821","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many requests for investigations into the conduct of ministers has the Director General of the Propriety and Ethics Team received in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291542","291542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146822","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the preparedness of the Import of Products, Animals, Food and Feed System (IPAFFS) to replace the EU’s Trade Control and Expert System; and what discussions the Government has had with representatives of port health authorities on contingency planning for IPAFFS after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291548","291548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146823","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the capacity of UK Border Force to manage high risk food and feed that does not enter through a Border Inspection Post or Designated Point of Entry in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291549","291549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146824","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) financial and (b) logistical support (i) has been and (ii) will be provided to port operators and port health authorities for potential changes in (A) throughput and (B) volume of trade at UK border control posts after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291550","291550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146825","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Government's announcement of 21 August 2019 that ports and local areas will receive £9 million of funding to prepare for the UK leaving the EU, how much funding will be allocated to the London Port Health Authority.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291551","291551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146826","2019-10-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions officials in his Department have had with (a) state government officials, (b) state government ministers (c) union government officials and (d) union government ministers in the Indian state of Assam on the implementation of the National Register of Citizens in that state.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291568","291568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146827","2019-10-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2019 to Question 169229 on India: Politics and Government, if he will make an estimate of the number of people living in the Indian state of Assam who are at risk of being confined in detention camps in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291569","291569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146828","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the UK will be a listed country for animal health in relation to (a) ungulates, (b) equines (c) dogs, (e) cats and (f) ferrets in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291552","291552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146829","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to EU Official Control Regulation 2017/625 due to come into force on 14 December 2019, whether the Government has contingency plans to process consignments of live animals in the event that they are returned to the UK after being refused entry into the EU if the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291553","291553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146830","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has plans to implement EU Official Control Regulation 2017/625 on the application of food and feed law, rules on animal health and welfare, plant health and plant protection products.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291554","291554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146831","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether live animal consignments designated under the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species (CITES) or non-CITES will be permitted to enter the UK using (a) the Port of Dover (b) Eurotunnel, (c) Harwich and (d) Portsmouth.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291555","291555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146832","2019-10-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 11 September 2019 to Question 169229 on India: Politics and Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the implementation of the National Register of Citizens in the Indian state of Assam on (a) the level of risk of mass deprivation of liberty, (b) the level of risk of mass statelessness, (c) rights of active and passive suffrage, (d) freedoms of speech and assembly, in particular of local religious and political leaders, (e) religious freedoms, and (f) incidents of suicide.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291570","291570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146833","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who the directors will be of the company limited by guarantee to run the National College of Creative Industries.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291543","291543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146834","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the funding allocated to the National College of Creative Industries will be subject to the same grant agreements after the establishment of the private company to replace that organisation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291544","291544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146835","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to require vet practices to scan and check microchip registration of dogs and cats on their first appointment to ensure that pet and owner match.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291606","291606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146836","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department has spent on the proposed Abacus Free School project in Hampstead and Kilburn constituency.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291594","291594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146837","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the (a) potential merits, (b) affordability (c) feasibility of the redevelopment of Hampstead Police Station for Abacus Primary School.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291595","291595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146838","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the proportion of HGV operations that that will be prepared for new border processes on 31 October 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291529","291529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146839","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the improvements to port infrastructure on the UK side of channel since June 2019 on potential goods disruption after the UK leaves the EU; and what comparative assessment he has made of the effect of those improvements and the improvements made on the French side of the English Channel.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291530","291530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146840","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what contingency plans his Department has put in place to mitigate disruption to air travel in the event of a large Icelandic volcanic eruption.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291531","291531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146841","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the level of disruption to air travel as a result of the potential for an Icelandic volcanic eruption.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291532","291532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146842","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to reduce the level of disruption to air travel since the Eyjafjallajokull eruption in 2010.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291533","291533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146843","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with his Icelandic counterpart on the risk of a volcanic eruption in that region.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291534","291534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146844","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to introduce a requirement for  buses to have audio visual (a) next stop and (b) final destination announcements.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291597","291597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146845","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the environment in the UK of a large volcanic eruption in Iceland.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291610","291610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146846","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps she has taken to reduce gambling related harm.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291536","291536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146847","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has reviewed on potential Icelandic volcanic activity and the effect of such activity on the UK.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291535","291535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146421","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the National Funding Formula on (a) the number of school places, (b) spending per pupil, (c) school spending reserves and (d) the sustainability of school funding in Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291242","291242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146422","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the reduction in funding for high needs support on mainstream SEND provision in the Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291243","291243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146423","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department allocated to (a) Liverpool City Council and (b) Knowsley Borough Council to support children with SEND needs in each year since April 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291244","291244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146424","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that young people with SEND who are (a) in full-time further education and (b) aged 20 or above have sufficient financial support to complete their studies.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291245","291245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146425","2019-10-01","Northern Ireland Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Northern Ireland Office will make it its policy to support Invest NI in hosting visits by Ambassadors to the UK to the Causeway Coast.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291277","291277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146426","2019-10-01","Northern Ireland Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of adopting the system used in England and Wales by which businesses can make claims against debtors who refuse to pay outstanding debts.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291278","291278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146427","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Cabinet Office's transparency data on ministerial gifts, what estimate he has made of the total value of all gifts given to the Prime Minister between July 2016 and July 2019.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291369","291369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146428","2019-10-01","Northern Ireland Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department made a cash payment to a civil servant as a result of offence allegedly caused by a royal portrait on display in the Northern Ireland Office.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291279","291279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146429","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Severn Power Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291370","291370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146430","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Glanford Brigg Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291371","291371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146431","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Peterborough Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291372","291372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146432","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Blackburn Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291373","291373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146433","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Enfield Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291374","291374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146434","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Cottam Development Centre Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291375","291375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146435","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Grain CHP Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291376","291376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146436","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Killingholme Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291377","291377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146437","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of VPI Immingham Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291378","291378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146438","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Rye House Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291379","291379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146439","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Sandbach Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291380","291380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146440","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Thornhill Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291381","291381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146441","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of London Heat and Power Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291382","291382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146442","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Langage Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291383","291383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146443","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Coryton Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291384","291384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146444","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what is the generation capacity of what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Rocksavage Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291385","291385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146445","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Marchwood Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291386","291386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146446","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Little Barford Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291387","291387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146447","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Staythorpe C Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291388","291388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146448","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Chickerell Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291389","291389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146449","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 217589, for what reasons his Department did not include timber building materials in the bespoke fire safety testing commissioned by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291390","291390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146450","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September to Question 286248, whether his Department attempted to procure (a) non-fire retardant zinc composite material and (b) copper composite material cladding with a polyethylene core from outside the UK for testing as part of the Building Research Establishment testing programme commissioned by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291391","291391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146451","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the letter from Lord O’Shaughnessy to the hon. Member for Sheffield Central on 21 December 2017, what progress the Government has made on its review of upfront charging and extending charges to out-of-hospital care and care providers by non-NHS organisations.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291392","291392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146452","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department provides to schools on preventing pupils vaping on school premises; and what estimate his Department has made of the number of schools that have written to parents on the prevalence of vaping.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291393","291393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146453","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 9 September 2019, HCWS1828, what estimate his Department has made of the additional funding that schools in North East Hampshire will collectively receive in comparison to funding received in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291394","291394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146454","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will publish data on rates of criminalisation among looked after young people by type of care placement in its annual report, Children looked after in England including adoption.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291395","291395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146455","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the review of the UK Protection of civilians strategy will consider the distinct vulnerabilities faced by children in conflict zones.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291336","291336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146456","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether EU citizens will have the right to vote in the May 2020 local elections in the event that the UK has left the EU (a) with or (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291396","291396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146457","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of ensuring that data held by her Department that would qualify a person's child for free school meals also captures (a) how many children that person is the main carer of and b) the school year of each qualifying child.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291347","291347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146458","2019-10-01","Prime Minister","2019-09-26","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on the grant of £100,000 made to Hacker House in 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291368","291368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146459","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what sanctions apply to civil servants on the offence of misconduct in public office.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291397","291397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146460","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the (a) effectiveness of the discard ban in reducing discards of quoata species of fish and (b) the levels of fishermen complying with that ban.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291398","291398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146461","2019-10-01","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ensure that the Be a Force for All campaign complies with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR); and whether a data protection impact assessment has been produced in accordance with Article 35 and 36 of the GDPR.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291338","291338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146462","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how information and data in the Cabinet Office or Government Digital Service which is collected centrally or shared by Departments is held; what the security clearance required to access such data is; who has access to such data; and what measures are in place to ensure such data does not leave the Cabinet Office.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291339","291339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146463","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment his Department has made of rent levels on household income.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291399","291399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146464","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the UK regains its measles free status.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291400","291400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146465","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his timescale is for tackling the issue of taxi drivers licensing in a local authority with less stringent standards to the local authority for their main area of trade.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291401","291401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146466","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to introduce minimum standards for taxis and private hire vehicles in England and Wales in accordance with the Government’s response to Report of the Task and Finish Group on Taxi and Private Hire Vehicle Licensing.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291402","291402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146467","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Government’s response to the Report of the Task and Finish Group on Taxi and Private Hire Vehicle Licencing, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislation on restricting cross-border and out of area journeys by taxis.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291403","291403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146469","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government Communications Service is taking to ensure that (a) transparency and (b) the values of the civil service code are maintained through effective governance of communications on the UK's departure from the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291340","291340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146470","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has (a) awarded a commercial contract to and (b) purchased digital services from (i) Anomaly LLP and (ii) Anomaly UK London Ltd in the last six months.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291341","291341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146471","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what amount his Department has spent on the Getting Ready for Brexit campaign since 23 July 2019; which companies have been awarded contracts by his Department as part of the Getting Ready for Brexit campaign; whether (a) Ministers and (b) civil servants including special advisers declared any interests in relation to those contracts; and what steps he is taking to ensure that the civil service code values of transparency and impartiality are maintained through the effective governance of communications on the UK's departure from the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291342","291342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146472","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what is (a) the nature of services purchased by the Government from CDL Group, (b) the value of the contract, (c) the length of the contract, (d) the process by which the contract was awarded and (e) whether any interests were declared by Ministers and civil servants, including special advisers, in relation to the award of the contract.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291343","291343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146473","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the length of prorogation required in order for the Government to prepare for a Queen's speech.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291405","291405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146474","2019-10-01","Department for International Development","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the humanitarian situation in Kashmir following the earthquake on 24 September 2019.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291406","291406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146475","2019-10-01","Department for International Development","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to reports of the army expelling international NGOs from Nigeria, what assessment he has made of the ability of humanitarian organisations to carry out their activities in Nigeria.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291407","291407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146476","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support he can provide to charities and other organisations who have not been paid money owed to them as a result of Working Links going into administration.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291408","291408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146477","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of Sikhs who did not identify themselves as either religious or ethnically Sikh in the 2011 census.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291409","291409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146478","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which dry dock facilities in the UK are under consideration for future refits for the Prince of Wales aircraft carrier.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291410","291410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146479","2019-10-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2019 to Question 285165 on Children: Maintenance, for what reasons she has not made an assessment of the effect on equality of calculating child maintenance liabilities using gross income due to different tax liabilities in the constituent parts of the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291411","291411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146480","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the competition for contracts under the Freight Capacity Framework Agreement will be completed and the winning bidders announced.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291366","291366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146481","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which (a) ports, (b) airports and (c) rail freight terminals could provide additional freight capacity under the Freight Capacity Framework Agreement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291367","291367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146482","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the supply of factor concentrates for haemophiliacs will not be affected in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291412","291412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146483","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on extending the Cycle to Work scheme to include bus travel.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291413","291413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146484","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to make an assessment of the feasibility of extending the Borders railway to Carlisle.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291414","291414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146485","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve rail connectivity between South Yorkshire and Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291415","291415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146486","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on the capacity improvement scheme planned for the Hope Valley Line; and what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail to ensure that work is completed as quickly as possible.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291416","291416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146487","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Timpson review of school exclusion: Government response, published in May 2019, what progress his Department has made on establishing the practice programme to embed effective partnership working to better equip schools to intervene early for children at risk of exclusion.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291417","291417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146488","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Timpson review of school exclusion: Government response, published in May 2019, what progress his Department has made on providing guidance on the use of in-school units and managed moves; and what the timetable is for his Department's consultation on that guidance.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291418","291418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146489","2019-10-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many requests have been made for consular assistance by UK citizens since 2014.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291419","291419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146490","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Timpson review of school exclusions, when his Department plans to issue updated guidance on school exclusions to schools.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291420","291420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146491","2019-10-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether customers will have the right to refuse the installation of smart meters in their homes after 2024.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291286","291286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146492","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that visa-free travel is maintained between the UK and the EU for short visits to work in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291421","291421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146493","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether a new immigration system will be in place from 1 November 2019 for people working in the UK and not under visiting or settled status.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291422","291422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146494","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there will be a transition immigration system in place from 1 November 2019 for people working in the UK and not under visiting or settled status.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291423","291423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146495","2019-09-30","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on work permits for British musicians living and working in the EU on 1 November 2019.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291424","291424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146496","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to ensure that British musicians will be able to apply for work permits that will be valid from 1 November 2019 in the event that an agreement is not reached before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291425","291425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146497","2019-10-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Indian counterpart on reports that 13,000 boys have been detained in Kashmir since its autonomous status was revoked on 5 August 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291426","291426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146498","2019-09-30","Women and Equalities","2019-09-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much the Government have spent on celebrations for International Women's day in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291337","291337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146499","2019-10-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to work towards the de-escalation of tensions over the situation in Kashmir; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291427","291427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146500","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons the Government has not responded to the letter of the hon. Member for Kingston Upon Hull North dated the 1 August 2019 on compensation for victims of the contaminated blood scandal.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291428","291428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146501","2019-10-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had with his international counterparts on the situation in Yemen at the UN General Assembly.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291429","291429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146502","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on establishing the Centre of Excellence for Human Security announced by his Department on 4 April 2019.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291356","291356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146503","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the mandate of the UN Special Representative for Children and Armed Conflict, created by the UN General Assembly in December 1996, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that allied forces receive training on children affected by armed conflict.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291357","291357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146504","2019-10-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to reform the process for making judicial appointments, including to the Supreme Court.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291430","291430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146505","2019-10-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the Government's policy is on politically appointed judges.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291431","291431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146506","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the working relationship will be between the Chief Digital Information Officer and the Chief Data Officer.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291432","291432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146507","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of testing for the use of Gamma-hydroxybutyrate in postmortems when the cause of death is unclear.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291433","291433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146508","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the perpetrators of attacks on civilians in conflict zones are not supplied with arms, material or financial services by the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291358","291358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146509","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding the NHS has contributed to the Apprenticeship Levy since its introduction in 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291359","291359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146510","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of crime have been received by Action Fraud; how many of those reports led to (a) an investigation and (b) a prosecution; and how many of these prosecutions were successful in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291216","291216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146511","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much Apprenticeship Levy funding was drawn down by the NHS on a monthly basis in the financial years (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20 to date.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291360","291360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146512","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to answer Question 287463 tabled on 5 September 2019 by the hon. Member for Halton.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291237","291237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146514","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the average time it takes for Action Fraud call centre operators to answer calls from the public; and what is Action Fraud's target time is for answering such calls.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291217","291217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146515","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much Apprenticeship Levy funding was not used within the 24 month period by NHS organisations in each month in the financial years (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, and (c) 2019-20 to date.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291361","291361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146516","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria must reports submitted to Action Fraud meet in order to be investigated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291218","291218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146517","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people employed by Action Fraud as (a) call centre operators, (b) investigators and (c) other staff.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291219","291219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146518","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the average time taken to investigate cases at Action Fraud; and what steps she is taking to ensure Action Fraud has the resources necessary to investigate such cases.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291220","291220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146519","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of Action Fraud's performance.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291221","291221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146520","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of reports of fraud made to Action Fraud that were not recorded as crimes.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291222","291222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146521","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to support fraud victims whose cases do not meet Action Fraud's criteria for investigation.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291223","291223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146522","2019-10-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with her Department’s officials about the circumstances of the award of a £100,000 grant to the company Hacker House in January 2019.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291434","291434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146523","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) people from Twickenham who attempted to make reports of fraud to Action Fraud, (b) those reports that were investigated, (c) prosecutions that followed those reports, (d) telephone calls made to Action Fraud and (e) telephone calls answered by Action Fraud over the latest 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291224","291224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146524","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve ophthalmology services.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291435","291435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146525","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish data relating to the final two quarters of 2018-19 of Annual Accounts Surplus or Deficit for London Clinical Commissioning Groups; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291212","291212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146526","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to extend the ban on combustible building materials to high-rise hotels.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291436","291436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146527","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to extend the ban on combustible building materials to high-rise offices.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291437","291437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146528","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for eye care appointments.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291238","291238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146529","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's plan is for supporting new woodland establishment and tree planting during the transition period from the existing Countryside Stewardship scheme to the new Environmental Land Management Schemes being fully established by 2024.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291292","291292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146530","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Committee on Climate Change scenario is being used to calculate any costs associated with afforestation and tree planting outside of woodlands to meet the UK’s net zero target.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291293","291293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146531","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many Environmental Land Management scheme test and trials projects will (a) incorporate an objective to increase tree cover through woodland creation, agroforestry or increased hedgerows and (b) undertake to investigate carbon storage and mitigation.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291294","291294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146532","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to enable the natural regeneration of trees and shrubs to support achieving the UK's 2050 net zero target.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291295","291295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146533","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Department has to prioritise the role of agroecological farming systems including agroforestry in future farming and environmental payments.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291296","291296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146534","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to ensure that (a) silvo-arable and (b) silvo-pastoral systems are included in Environmental Land Management Scheme trials.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291297","291297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146535","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Department is taking to encourage farmers to engage with the tests and trials phase of Environmental Land Management Scheme.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291298","291298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146536","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings her Department has had with Liverpool City Council to discuss preparations for leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291246","291246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146537","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings her Department has had with Knowsley Borough Council to discuss preparations for leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291247","291247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146538","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what meetings his Department has had with Liverpool City Council on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291248","291248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146539","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what meetings his Department has had with Knowsley Borough Council on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291249","291249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146540","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions officials in his Department have had with representatives from NHS providers in Cheshire and Merseyside on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291250","291250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146541","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions officials in his Department have had with representatives from Liverpool City Council on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291251","291251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146542","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions officials in his Department have had with representatives from Knowsley Borough Council on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291252","291252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146543","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of whole farm agroecological systems.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291299","291299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146544","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of secondary school teachers that have taken on private tuition outside school in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291227","291227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146545","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been purchased through the Help to Buy scheme in the East Hampshire constituency in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291362","291362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146546","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many enquiries have been conducted on the tax returns of self-assessment taxpayers excluding trusts, partnerships, charities in each financial year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291350","291350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146547","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of secondary school children who receive private tuition.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291228","291228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146548","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate she has made of the number of business start-ups in (a) East Hampshire constituency and (b) Hampshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291363","291363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146549","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the feasibility of (a) the United Nations and (b) another independent observer to report on alleged human rights abuses in Kashmir.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291316","291316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146550","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Indian counterpart on the actions of Indian security forces in Kashmir.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291317","291317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146551","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to increase public awareness of the effect of the beef and leather industry on deforestation in the Amazon.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291318","291318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146552","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what evidence base his Department used for the guidance issued on (a) vaping, (b) heat-not-burn and (c) other non-smoke nicotine products.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291364","291364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146553","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what evidence base his Department used to produce guidance on the relative merits of breastfeeding and bottle feeding; and what changes have been made to that guidance in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291365","291365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146554","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote measures to prevent deforestation in the Amazon at (a) the UN and (b) other multilateral institutions.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291319","291319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146555","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent diplomatic steps he has taken to ensure that the Chinese government complies with the terms of the 1984 Sino-British Agreement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291320","291320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146556","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in Hong Kong on the conduct of the Hong Kong police force during recent demonstrations in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291321","291321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146557","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the British consulate in Zimbabwe is taking to compile accurate inflation data on the price of goods in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291322","291322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146558","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the amount of time it will take to cross the border between Spain and Gibraltar in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291323","291323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146559","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions officials in his Department have had with trades unions in Gibraltar on the effect on (a) jobs and (b) the economy in Gibraltar of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291324","291324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146560","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessments he has made of the potential (a) merits and (b) risks of allowing Huawei to access the UK’s 5G network.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291325","291325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146561","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the detention of Uighur Muslims in China.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291326","291326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146562","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the persecution of Christians in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291327","291327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146563","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on the detention of Pastor Wang Yi.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291328","291328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146564","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made on preparations to table a UN resolution demanding an immediate ceasefire by all parties in the conflict in Yemen throughout that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291329","291329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146565","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the Saudi-led Coalition's compliance with international law in relation to the recent attack on a detention centre in Sana’a.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291330","291330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146566","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the involvement in the recent air strikes on a detention centre in Sana’a of UK (a) planes and (b) weapons sold to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291331","291331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146567","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made on the effectiveness of the Saudi-led coalition’s procedures for investigating airstrikes on civilian targets.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291332","291332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146568","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to support a full, independent UN-led inquiry into alleged war crimes committed by all sides in the Yemeni conflict.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291333","291333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146569","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential merits holding a debate on UK support for the war in Yemen.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291334","291334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146570","2019-10-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage other countries to support greater accountability for violations of (a) international humanitarian and (b) human rights law.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291304","291304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146571","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Report No. 1016 of the WHO Technical Report Series, what the timeframe is for the publication of Report No. 1015 to be published; and if he will place an interim copy of that report in the Library.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291305","291305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146572","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the postcodes where adverts for the Get Ready for Brexit campaign have been placed.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291438","291438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146573","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was paid into the Civil Aviation Authority administered ATOL scheme by UK airlines in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291439","291439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146574","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Government's policies of the report entitled, The UK strategy on protection of civilians, published by RUSI and Save the Children in September 2019.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291306","291306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146575","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on which dates the 100 towns invited to develop proposals for the £3.6 billion Towns Fund were allocated funding.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291440","291440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146576","2019-10-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether her Department plans to include carbon emissions from UK Overseas Territories in its carbon accounting processes for the Paris Agreement.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291441","291441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146577","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what criteria his Department used to identify the 100 towns invited to develop proposals for the £3.6 billion towns fund.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291442","291442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146578","2019-10-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if her Department will work with the UK Overseas Territories to reduce their carbon emissions as part of the UK’s (a) contribution towards the Paris Agreement and (b) Net Zero commitment.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291443","291443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146579","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what criteria were used to select the 100 towns that will receive funding from the Towns Fund.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291444","291444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146580","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what criteria was used to select successful bids under the Future High Streets Fund; and if he will publish the scoring matrix used for each application to that fund.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291445","291445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146581","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to prevent food insecurity after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291446","291446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146582","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment she has made of the average length of time for a claimant to receive their first (a) legacy benefit payment and (b) universal credit payment in the each of the last two years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291447","291447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146583","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of whether households have reduced their expenditure on non-essential items in order to avoid debt while waiting for their first payment of universal credit.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291448","291448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146584","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing a policy of backdating universal credit payments.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291449","291449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146585","2019-10-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect of ending the five week wait for the first universal credit payment on (a) levels of poverty and (b) the public purse.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291450","291450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146586","2019-10-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the merits of replicating the policy of the Scottish Government to require full medical records to be available for disability benefit assessments.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291451","291451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146587","2019-10-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the merits of only having face-to-face medical assessments for disability benefits if that is requested by the claimant.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291452","291452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146588","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the supply of medicines to NHS (a) providers and (b) hospitals in the Cheshire and Merseyside area in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291253","291253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146589","2019-10-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information her Department holds on Hacker House's presence in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291287","291287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146590","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Timpson Review of School Exclusion, what progress has been made on updating guidance for head teachers on their powers to exclude pupils; and when a consultation on that revised guidance will be published.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291453","291453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146591","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children aged five-years old and under with a special educational need arising from autism or autism spectrum disorder had (a) an Education, Health and Care Plan and (b) received SEN support in each English region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291454","291454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146592","2019-10-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish the dates and minutes of meetings held between her Department and representatives of Hacker House.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291288","291288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146593","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) discussions his Department had with and (b) representations his Department made to the National Cyber Security Council on (i) the Cyber Security Immediate Impact Fund and (ii) the decision to provide grant funding to Hacker House.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291289","291289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146594","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Bahraini counterpart on reports of violence at the Bahraini Embassy in the UK on 26 July 2019.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291291","291291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146595","2019-10-01","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will undertake an inquiry into delays in resolving the dispute between HMRC and the Roadchef Employee Benefits Trust.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291335","291335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146596","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received on the need to redevelop Whipps Cross Hospital.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291455","291455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146597","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when a decision will be made on the capital investment bid submitted to NHSI by Barts Health NHS Trust for the redevelopment of Whipps Cross Hospital.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291456","291456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146598","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 249189 on Regulator of Social Housing, how many respondents to the consultation on the Social Housing Green Paper in 2018 (a) supported and (b) rejected the proposal to consider removing the serious detriment test used to determine compliance with the Home Standard if it is a bar to a more proactive approach by the Regulator of Social Housing.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291213","291213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146599","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many applicants were interviewed for the post of Housing Ombudsman.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291214","291214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146600","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department supports the transition to agroecological farming by 2030 as recommended by the Royal Society of Arts Food, Farming and Countryside Commission report published on 16 July 2019.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291300","291300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146601","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to reverse the declining trend in Official Development Assistance spending on education.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291209","291209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146602","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average length of time was for the Housing Ombudsman Service to determine case complaints in the first three months of 2019-20; and how many complaints were dealt with within the six month target during that period.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291215","291215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146603","2019-10-01","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to reduce excise duty on UK produced petroleum.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291457","291457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146604","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department will maintain rural development funding for (a) community farms, (b) processing, (c) marketing and (d) local food should the UK leave the EU.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291301","291301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146605","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the findings in the IPCC’s Special Report entitled the Ocean and Cryosphere in a Changing Climate.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291458","291458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146606","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to improve flood defences in (a) rural, (b) coastal and (c) urban areas in response to rising sea levels.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291459","291459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146607","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of creating a community supported agriculture start-up fund.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291302","291302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146608","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the contribution of the aviation industry to carbon emissions; and what plans his Department has to reduce emissions from the aviation industry.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291460","291460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146609","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the findings from the Government’s research into homelessness in the LGBT community, as announced in the Rough Sleepers Strategy and the LGBT Action Plan.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291461","291461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146610","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate has been made of the cost to the public purse of the Get ready for Brexit advertising campaign (a) online and (b) in other forms in (i) the UK, (ii) England, (iii) Wales, (iv) Scotland, and (v) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291462","291462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146611","2019-10-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether she has made an assessment of the potential risk to the UK's future fuel security should the UK become reliant on Russian or Middle Eastern petrol in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291463","291463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146612","2019-10-01","Department for International Development","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the announcement on education funding at the UN General Assembly, what steps he is taking to ensure that the most marginalised (a) girls and (b) adolescents are able to access a good standard of education.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291464","291464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146613","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to increase tourism in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291307","291307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146614","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to improve the GP to patient ratio in the London Borough of Redbridge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291465","291465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146615","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department has made an assessment of the potential benefits of reducing pools duty to 10 per cent to the industry and local economy in the North West.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Sir George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291239","291239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146616","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many women have started courses in STEM subjects at colleges in Dudley in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291308","291308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146617","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will undertake a review of the effectiveness of the pools duty rate.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Sir George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291240","291240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146618","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to increase literacy rates of primary school students from lower income households in Dudley.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291309","291309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146619","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to increase the take-up of apprenticeships through university technical colleges.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291310","291310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146620","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the effect on (a) Stockton-on-Tees and (b) Teesside of the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291466","291466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146621","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on food prices in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291467","291467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146622","2019-10-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate she has made of the potential effect on fuel prices of the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291468","291468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146623","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will (a) implement the recommendation of housing association Habinteg and make accessible and adaptable (M4(2) Category 2) the mandatory baseline for all new housing and (b) issue detailed guidance to local planning authorities on how they should reflect the housing needs of older and disabled people in their plans as required by the Neighbourhood Planning Act 2017.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291469","291469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146624","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to prevent a potential rise in hate crime in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291470","291470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146625","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on food prices in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291471","291471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146626","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that routine decision making for a foster child is delegated to their carers as set out in The Children Act 1989, Guidance and Regulations: Section 3.188 which was revised in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291472","291472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146627","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to remove the VAT on all digital publications.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291311","291311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146628","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure children who are educated outside the school setting can access Relationships, Health and Sex Education (RSE).","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291473","291473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146629","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to reduce the tax on the football pools to bring it in line with taxation rates applying to bingo.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Sir George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291241","291241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146630","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate has been made of the cost to the public purse of the Get Ready for Brexit advertising campaign (a) online and (b) in other forms in (i) the North East, (ii) the North West, (iii) Yorkshire and the Humber, (iv) the West Midlands, (v) the East Midlands, (vi) East Anglia, (vii) the South West, (viii) the South East and (ix) London.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291474","291474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146631","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of shortages of foster carers by region.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291475","291475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146632","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to share innovative practices in foster carer recruitment among local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291476","291476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146633","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support homeless migrants from the EU apply for settled status.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291281","291281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146634","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps her Department is taking to protect animals from the effects of fireworks.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291312","291312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146635","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds in relation to perpetrators of crimes using sharp objects and (a) time spent in Pupil Referral Units, (b) housing status and (c) employment status.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291477","291477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146636","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps her Department has taken to tackle the anti-social use of fireworks.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291313","291313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146637","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to help meet Sustainable Development Goal 2 on zero hunger.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291210","291210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146638","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions he has had with his German counterpart on an international alliance for achieving Sustainable Development Goal 2 on hunger.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291211","291211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146639","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate her Department has made of the level of support for a ban on the public sale of fireworks.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291314","291314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146640","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has had from Suffolk County Council on the proposed North Ipswich Route in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291478","291478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146641","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when a new children’s commissioner will be appointed to the Northamptonshire children’s social services department.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291479","291479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146642","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on creating financial incentives for local authorities to invest county farms estates.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291303","291303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146643","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on disruptions to freight traffic on the A14; and what estimate he has made of the cost of those disruptions to (a) hauliers and (b) other vehicles.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291480","291480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146644","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Suffolk county council on the Ipswich northern route since 1 January 2019.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291481","291481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146645","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of women with a disability attended cervical cancer screening in the NHS in the last period for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291229","291229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146646","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average length of time was for his Department to respond to funding requests for new roads from local authorities.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291482","291482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146647","2019-10-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Bahraini counterpart on reports of violent incidents at the British Embassy in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291230","291230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146648","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with Highways England on the Ipswich northern route.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291483","291483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146649","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September to Question 286636 on HIV infection, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of people diagnosed with HIV at a late stage of infection.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291231","291231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146650","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many cases have been prosecuted by the Serious Fraud Office in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291351","291351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146651","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of ensuring that universities throughout the UK adopt system-wide planning process in addition to controls on numbers.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291282","291282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146652","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many unexplained wealth orders the Serious Fraud Office has (a) applied for and (b) been granted in each of the last 10 financial years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291352","291352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146653","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many Deferred Prosecution Agreements (DPAs) the Serious Fraud Office has entered into in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291353","291353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146654","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, how many Deferred Prosecution Agreements (DPAs) the Serious Fraud Office has entered into in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291354","291354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146655","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-26","To ask the Attorney General, what the total value is of all assets confiscated by the Serious Fraud Office in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291355","291355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146656","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to ban tyres aged 10 years and over on (a) public service and (b) other vehicles.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291254","291254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146657","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the outcome is of his Department’s recent consultation on banning tyres aged 10 years and older on PSVs and other vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291255","291255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146658","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Egyptian counterpart on strengthening protections for the human rights of non-Muslims in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291272","291272"
