"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43046","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 223W, on Sandymoor school, what funding will be allocated to Sandymoor Free School in the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192123","192123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43047","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to offer compensation to initial teacher training applicants who have been wrongly advised that they failed the professional skills test and denied the opportunity to train as teachers.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192133","192133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43048","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which contractors will be responsible for the professional skills test for initial teacher training entrants for the 2014-15 academic year.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192131","192131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43049","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what further information he will give to initial teacher training providers about candidates who were incorrectly notified that they had failed the professional skills test.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192132","192132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43050","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils in (a) Denton and Reddish constituency, (b) Stockport Metropolitan Borough and (c) Tameside Metropolitan Borough Council continued into (i) further education, (ii) higher education and (ii) apprenticeships in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192141","192141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43051","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many service leavers (a) applied to and (b) were accepted on initial teacher training in (i) 2008-09, (ii) 2009-10, (iii) 2010-11, (iv) 2011-12, (v) 2012-13 and (vi) the current academic year to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192173","192173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43052","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of initial teacher trainees were service leavers in (a) 2008-09, (b) 2009-10, (c) 2010-11, (d) 2011-12, (e) 2012-13 and (f) the current academic year to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192174","192174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43053","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of service leavers (a) applied to and (b) were accepted on initial teacher training in (i) 2008-09, (ii) 2009-10, (iii) 2010-11, (iv) 2011-12, (v) 2012-13 and (vi) the current academic year to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192175","192175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43054","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding has been allocated to the Troops to Teachers programme to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192171","192171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43055","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many service leavers have (a) applied to and (b) been accepted on the Troops to Teachers programme to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192172","192172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43056","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools proposed to open in September 2014 have yet to secure a (a) permanent and (b) temporary site; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192053","192053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43057","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, by which criteria the Education Funding Agency will prioritise the allocation of capital resources to secondary schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192054","192054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43058","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will meet the Never Such Innocence campaign to discuss educational material relating to the commemoration of the First World War.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191989","191989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43059","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Statement of 13 March 2014 by the Minister for Schools, how much of the funding announced will come from (a) his Department's budget and (b) the Treasury.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192041","192041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43060","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Statement of 13 March 2014 by the Minister for Schools, Official Report, columns 427-42, on school funding, whether any of the funding announced will generate a Barnett consequential.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192042","192042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43061","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total expected value is of the parent body contracts to be awarded to (a) Magnox Limited and (b) Research Sites Restoration Limited; and what the basis for valuing each contract was.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192039","192039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43062","2014-03-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which recommendations of the Maitland Review he has not implemented due to an alternative approach being adopted; and what the alternative approach is in each such case.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192052","192052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43063","2014-03-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much onshore wind capacity (a) received planning approval and (b) was rejected in each month in 2013; and how many planning applications for onshore wind farms were (i) approved and (ii) rejected in each such month.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191992","191992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43064","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what value-for-money audit procedure will apply the parent body organisation contracts planned for (a) Magnox Limited and (b) Research Sites Restoration Limited.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191939","191939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43065","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what aspects of the proposed parent body organisation contracts planned for (a) Magnox Limited and (b) Research Sites Restoration Limited will be covered by commercial confientiality restrictions on disclosure; and for what reasons each such aspect will be so covered.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191940","191940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43066","2014-03-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many families with children receive the warm home discount.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191921","191921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43067","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will suspend co-operation between his Department and the Russian state nuclear company Rosatom on planning for a new nuclear plant.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191901","191901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43068","2014-03-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department plans to consult on changes to the warm home discount for the period from 2015-16.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191920","191920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43069","2014-03-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to mitigate the impact of bats on churches; if he will set out a timetable for such steps; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191918","191918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43070","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward proposals to re-introduce the National Rivers Authority staffed with civil and flood engineers.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191925","191925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43071","2014-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which responsibilities for tackling animal welfare crimes are handled by (a) his Department and (b) non-governmental organisations.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191995","191995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43072","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the leakage rate for the United Utilities Water Company was in the latest period for which figures are available; and what change there has been in that rate in the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192140","192140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43073","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made towards bringing the standard of air quality in those parts of Denton and Reddish constituency designated as an air quality management area to within the guideline limits.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192137","192137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43074","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 7 February 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton regarding Mr J Rossi-Stephenson.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192112","192112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43075","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance he has given to the UK delegation to the Parliamentary Assembly of the Council of Europe on political groupings and other associations with United Russia.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192130","192130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43076","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the publication of the UN Commission of Inquiry's report and the UN Human Rights Council resolution on North Korea, what mechanisms will be implemented to ensure ongoing monitoring, investigation and reporting on human rights in North Korea by the UN, including violations of women's rights as a result of sexual violence and human trafficking; and if he will make representations that the mandate and resources of the UN Special Rapporteur on Human Rights in North Korea should be strengthened and increased and that a database of evidence and testimonies to support a process of justice and accountability should be established.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192048","192048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43077","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to improve trade relations between Commonwealth members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191961","191961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43078","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times his Department met the Commonwealth Secretariat to discuss trade relations in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191960","191960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43079","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of British intervention on the level of opium production in Helmand Province, Afghanistan, since 2001.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191930","191930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43080","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Minister for the Middle East and North Africa discussed Western Sahara with (a) Abdelilah Benkirane, Head of Government and (b) Salaheddine Mezouar, Minister for Foreign Affairs and Cooperation, during his recent visit to Rabat.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191942","191942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43081","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the levels of opium cultivation in the area within a 10-mile radius of Camp Bastion, Afghanistan, in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191931","191931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43082","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the US Secretary of State on  Ukraine.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191948","191948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43083","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made in recovering any Ukrainian assets held in the UK that have been improperly acquired.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191949","191949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43084","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many women human rights defenders staff in the UK embassy in Kabul has met in the last six months; and what direct intervention the UK has recently made on their behalf in relation to their security needs.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191941","191941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43085","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts on Ukraine.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191946","191946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43086","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the NATO Parliamentary Assembly on Ukraine.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191947","191947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43087","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department plans to take to support human rights in Uganda in response to the passing of the Anti-Homosexuality Act and the Anti-Pornography Act.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191898","191898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43088","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has any planned diplomatic engagements with the government of Uganda.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191899","191899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43089","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has identified any threat to British LGBTI citizens travelling to Uganda.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191900","191900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43090","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he or officials in his Department have had with the Israeli government about recent deaths of Palestinians following encounters with Israeli forces.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191897","191897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43091","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met Uganda's High Commissioner in London.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191912","191912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43092","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in Commonwealth governments on Uganda's Anti-Homosexuality Act and Anti-Pornography Act.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191913","191913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43093","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential change in the number of health visitors working with children as a result of the transfer of funding for health visitors from the NHS to local authorities in 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191911","191911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43094","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency to carry out a consultation with patients and professionals on the effect of switching between brands of anti-epileptic drugs.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191970","191970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43095","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on mental health issues in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191945","191945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43096","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on suicide prevention in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191924","191924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43097","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the allocation of donor lungs to cystic fibrosis patients in England; and what steps he is taking to ensure the allocation of donor lungs is based on need and not location.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191929","191929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43098","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the effects of switching between different versions of levetiracetam and other anti-epileptic drugs.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191971","191971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43099","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency took to consult with patients before issuing new guidance on switching between different manufacturers' versions of anti-epileptic drugs.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191974","191974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43100","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of local authorities currently planning to close homes offering respite care to severely disabled children and adults.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191978","191978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43101","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to ensure that children who need mental health interventions are placed in facilities as close to their homes as possible.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191994","191994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43102","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what budget was allocated to the National Institute for Health Research in each of the last three years; and how much of that budget was spent in each such year.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191967","191967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43103","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on that body's policy for payment of senior staff after leaving NHS jobs for a period of secondment.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191975","191975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43104","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what services are given in support of NHS nurses reporting cases of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191991","191991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43105","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will estimate the average cost to the public purse of placing a severely disabled child in full-time residential care.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191976","191976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43106","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has given to local authorities on the provision of respite care to severely disabled children and adults.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191977","191977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43107","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Salisbury of 28 February 2014, Official Report, column 569W, on abortion, what process the Chief Medical Officer follows to detect discrepancies in abortion notifications; and what resources the Chief Medical Officer has for that task.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192050","192050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43108","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of doctors and nurses participated in clinical audit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192120","192120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43109","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS funding has been spent on clinical audit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192121","192121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43110","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what powers the Care Quality Commission has to carry out spot checks of all wards of a hospital without seeking the permission of the relevant commissioner beforehand.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192040","192040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43111","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients NHS England plans to fund for treatment for each of the technologies within its Commissioning through Evaluation programme in the year beginning April 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Heather Wheeler","Heather Wheeler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192002","192002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43112","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to promote innovation in specialised services following the indefinite suspension of the Specialised Services Commissioning Innovation Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Heather Wheeler","Heather Wheeler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192003","192003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43113","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many alert notices have been issued in respect of healthcare professionals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192122","192122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43114","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the chair of the food network of the responsibility deal has received (a) paid employment, (b) funding for research and (c) hospitality from the food industry.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192170","192170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43115","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the commitments made in the outcome document of the UN Commission on the Status of Women 2013 outcome document have been met and implemented to date; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192128","192128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43116","2014-03-18","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to make the reporting of female genital mutilation cases mandatory for all public sector workers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191984","191984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43117","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the decision to cancel the e-borders programme was taken.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192028","192028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43118","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people held in immigration removal centres on 13 March 2014 had been held for (a) between 28 and 60 days, (b) between 60 and 365 days, (c) more than 12 months and (d) more than 18 months.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192038","192038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43119","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of how many (a) private and (b) public sector properties will be used for the vulnerable persons relocation scheme in 2014-15.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192036","192036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43120","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which local authorities are participating in the vulnerable persons relocation scheme.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192037","192037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43121","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to implement changes as a result of the Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration report Exporting the border?: An inspection of e-Borders.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192034","192034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43122","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people from Syria who will relocate through the vulnerable persons relocation scheme between 29 January 2014 and 30 May 2015.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192035","192035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43123","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of report by the Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration of the critical system vulnerabilities in Semaphore and Warnings Index; and what steps she took in response to that report.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192032","192032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43124","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many exit checks were performed on passengers leaving the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192033","192033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43125","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent officials in her Department of each grade have worked on the e-borders programme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192030","192030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43126","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of merging the e-borders programme into the border system programme.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192031","192031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43127","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what commercial tenders have been received for a new system to introduce exit checks and replace the e-borders programme.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192029","192029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43128","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what arrangements he has put in place to mitigate the effects of planned reductions to legal aid under the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 on (a) unaccompanied migrant children who have made Article 8 right to private life and family claims, (b) unaccompanied migrant children who have mixed claims and (c) trafficked children who are seeking leave to remain from his Department and have Article 8 claims; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192051","192051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43129","2014-03-18","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to make conspiring to perform female genital mutilation a criminal offence.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191986","191986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43130","2014-03-18","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the proportion of calls made to the NSPCC reporting female genital mutilation cases that have been passed on to the police.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191987","191987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43131","2014-03-26","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which responsibilities for tackling animal welfare crimes are managed by (a) her Department and (b) non-governmental organisations.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191996","191996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43132","2014-03-18","Department for International Development","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many full-time equivalent officials in her Department have responsibility for helping developing countries improve education systems.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191990","191990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43133","2014-03-17","Department for International Development","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy that demonstrable humanitarian access to Myanmar, including in Rakhine state, is a condition for the increased development aid budget for that country.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191937","191937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43134","2014-03-17","Department for International Development","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with the Burmese government on its commitment to release Rohingya political prisoners held in Buthidaung and Maungdaw prisons.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191938","191938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43135","2014-03-18","Department for International Development","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funds her Department has made available to the Inter-Religious Council of Ugunda in each year from 2010-11 to 2013-14.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191914","191914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43136","2014-03-17","Department for International Development","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with the Burmese government about resolving the issue of the statelessness of the Rohingya population in Myanmar.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191922","191922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43137","2014-03-17","Department for International Development","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department directly or indirectly contributed (a) financially and (b) in other ways to the work of the Committee on Human Rights Affairs of the Parliament of Uganda in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191907","191907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43138","2014-03-18","Department for International Development","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many full-time equivalent officials in her Department have responsibility for helping developing countries improve their tax collection systems.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191988","191988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43139","2014-03-18","Department for International Development","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many full-time officials in her Department have responsibility for helping developing countries improve their healthcare systems.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191985","191985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43140","2014-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many defendants in homicide cases have pleaded the partial defence of diminished responsibility in each year since 2010; and how many defendants have been convicted with diminished responsibility in each of those years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192012","192012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43141","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the circumstances under which an offender should stay with a particular team or probation officer and not be transferred will change as a result of the introduction of the National Probation Service and the 21 community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192014","192014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43142","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he expects the rehabilitation activity requirement to reduce unit costs in the courts and the community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192044","192044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43143","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was levied in fines by each magistrates court in Greater Manchester in each of the last five years; what proportion of such fines were written off by each court; and what proportion of such fines were collected.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192142","192142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43144","2014-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to negotiate compulsory prisoner transfer agreements with (a) Jamaica and (b) Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191919","191919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43145","2014-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of attempted murder have been granted permission to enter exclusion zones in the Liverpool City Region which form part of their license arrangements since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191982","191982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43146","2014-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will initiate a review into the reasons why Mr Edward McEvilly was permitted to enter an exclusion zone in which his victim lives within one week of his release from prison.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191983","191983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43147","2014-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the Youth Justice Board's budget has been spent on research in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191980","191980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43148","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offender cases will be transferred from one officer to another following the creation of the National Probation Service and community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191964","191964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43149","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much in victim surcharge has been imposed by adult courts since October 2012; and how much of that figure has been collected to date.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191969","191969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43150","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of rates of prosecutions in North Belfast for public order offences.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191943","191943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43151","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with (a) the Northern Ireland Justice Minister, (b) the Director of Public Prosecutions and (c) the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland on the prosecution of public order offences in Belfast.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191944","191944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43152","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-13","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he has taken to restrict access to departmental meetings by lobbyists since 2011.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191955","191955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43153","2014-03-17","Prime Minister","2014-03-13","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the possibility of Israel (a) disarming its nuclear weapons capability and (b) joining the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty was discussed with (i) his Israeli counterpart, (ii) other Israeli ministers and (iii) members of the Knesset during his visit to Israel on 12 and 13 March 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192110","192110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43154","2014-03-18","Scotland Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how Scottish soldiers and their families posted on accompanied tours elsewhere in the UK can register to vote in the Scottish Referendum.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192169","192169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43155","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the differential turnout was between the highest and lowest income group in each general election for which such data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191926","191926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43156","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if he will list the registration rates for students in higher education institutions in the UK in ranked order for the most recent period available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191927","191927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43157","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if he will list the local authority databases used by electoral registration officers in the dry run for individual electoral registration for the 10 authorities with the (a) best and (b) worst registration rates.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191928","191928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43158","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the future propensity to vote of those electors who (a) use and (b) do not use their vote in the first general election after reaching the age of 18 years old.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191932","191932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43159","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Student Loans Company database has been used for purposes of maximising student registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192114","192114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43160","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what discussions the Electoral Commission has had with the Office for National Statistics and other Government departments on the size of the UK population eligible to vote but not registered (a) before and (b) after the publication of its report, Great Britain's Electoral Registers 2011.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192109","192109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43161","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if he will list each local authority database used by electoral registration offices in the dry run for individual electoral registration (IER) for the 10 local authorities with the (a) best and (b) worst registration rates during the IER dry run.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192119","192119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43162","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent assessment the Electoral Commission has made of reasons for differential turnout between socio-economic groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191999","191999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43163","2014-03-18","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in East Lothian constituency.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192011","192011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43164","2014-03-20","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 27 February 2012, Official Report, column 151W, on bus services: disability, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that operators comply with the Public Service Vehicles Accessibility Regulations 2000.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192043","192043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43165","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of obstructive sleep apnoea among lorry drivers.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192111","192111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43166","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of road accidents resulting in a (a) serious injury and (b) fataity involved people driving for business purposes in each of the last four quarters.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192047","192047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43167","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many employees of the Driver and Vehicle Agency in Northern Ireland have been employed there for (a) five years or fewer, (b) six to 10 years, (c) 11 to 15 years, (d) 16 to 20 years and (e) more than 20 years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192125","192125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43168","2014-03-19","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many employees of the Driver and Vehicle Agency in Northern Ireland are (a) under 30, (b) 31 to 40, (c) 41 to 50, (d) 51 to 60 and (e) over 60 years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192126","192126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43169","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the role of the Health and Safety Executive in reducing accidents by people who drive as part of their employment.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192113","192113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43170","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many bus operators in Greater Manchester have been reported to the Transport Commissioner in each year since 2005; and how many bus operators lost their operational licence as a result of subsequent investigations in each such year.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192139","192139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43171","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many near-miss aircraft incidents have occurred under 7,000ft with aircraft (a) arriving at and (b) taking off from Heathrow Airport in the last five years.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191936","191936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43172","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many aircraft have had to land due to (a) engine problems, (b) fuel shortages and (c) other technical problems at Heathrow Airport in the last five years.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191935","191935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43173","2014-03-18","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the electrification of the Windemere to Oxenholme railway line.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191981","191981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43174","2014-03-18","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has made to the European Commission on the state aid judgement on the Merseyside cruise terminal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191979","191979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43175","2014-03-17","Women and Equalities","2014-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will place in the Library a list of expenses which were (a) claimed by and (b) paid to (i) Equality and Human Rights Commission (EHRC) Board members, (ii) members of the EHRC Senior Management team and (iii) all staff employed via off-payroll arrangements in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191968","191968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43176","2014-03-17","Women and Equalities","2014-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what estimate she has made of the number of staff working for the Equality and Human Rights Commission who are employed through off-payroll arrangements in each of the last six financial years; and how long each such individual had been so employed by the Commission.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191965","191965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43177","2014-03-17","Women and Equalities","2014-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what estimate she has made of pay gaps in respect of (a) gender, (b) race and (c) disability amongst employees of the Equality and Human Rights Commission in each of the last five financial years; and whether such estimates take account of salaries of staff employed through off-payroll arrangements.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191966","191966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43178","2014-03-17","Women and Equalities","2014-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many members of staff working for the Equality and Human Rights Commission who are employed through off-payroll arrangements were remunerated by payment to a personal services company; and what the total value of any such payments was in each of the last six financial years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191998","191998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43179","2014-03-17","Women and Equalities","2014-03-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the (a) average and (b) highest daily rate paid to staff working for the Equality and Human Rights Commission employed through off-payroll arrangements in each of the last six financial years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191997","191997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43180","2014-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he received the Work Programme Evaluation: Interim meta-report; what his plans are for its publication; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192009","192009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43181","2014-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the operation of the Work Programme in rural areas.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192007","192007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43182","2014-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received from (a) providers and (b) customers on the effectiveness of the Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192008","192008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43183","2014-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to introduce statutory time limits on claims for personal independence payments.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191993","191993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43184","2014-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people referred by Jobcentre Plus to the Work Programme in each month since June 2011 failed to start on the Programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192006","192006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43185","2014-03-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to highlight the importance of women in the workplace at the forthcoming discussions on decent work at the UN Commission on the Status of Women 2014.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192127","192127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43186","2014-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2012, Official Report, column 1032W, on Work Programme, when he expects to publish the independent evaluation of the Work Programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192005","192005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43187","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the additional cost to small businesses of abolishing the percentage threshold scheme for recovering statutory sick pay.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192168","192168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43188","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on alternative models of compensating small businesses for sickness absence after the abolition of the percentage threshold scheme for recovering statutory sick pay.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192167","192167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43189","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list by sector the amount of revenue received by the Exchequer as a result of tariffs on US imports in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192182","192182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43190","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on the ability of small businesses to manage sickness absence of abolishing the Percentage Threshold Scheme for recovering statutory sick pay.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192158","192158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43191","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the benefits and disbenefits of extending the Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme to the charity and social enterprise sector.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192183","192183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43192","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Rentcharge payers his Department has arranged to receive Rentcharge redemption in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Greater Manchester in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192166","192166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43193","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local planning authorities do not have an (a) adopted local development framework or (b) extant development plan in place.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192155","192155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43194","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect (a) green belt and (b) open green spaces in (i) the county of Greater Manchester, (ii) Tameside Metropolitan Borough and (iii) Stockport Metropolitan Borough.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192152","192152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43195","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of planning applications to build on sites in (a) Greater Manchester, (b) Tameside Metropolitan Borough and (c) Stockport Metropolitan Borough involved building on designated Green Belt land in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192153","192153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43196","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on housing benefit for tenants in (a) council property, (b) housing association and registered social landlord property and (c) private sector housing in (i) Tameside and (ii) Stockport in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192149","192149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43197","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much and what proportion of (a) council tax and (b) business rates was uncollected by each of the metropolitan districts in the county of Greater Manchester in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192150","192150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43198","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of freehold properties in Greater Manchester subject to chief rents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192151","192151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43199","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, columns 14-15W, on military bases: Yorkshire and the Humber, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters and emails sent by his Department, the CDS, the CGS, or officers or officials working for them to, or received from the officer commanding 15 Brigade or from officers or officials working in 15 Brigade headquarters about the proposal to merge 15 Brigade into a new Adaptive Force Brigade and about where the new Adaptive Force Brigade headquarters should be based.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192160","192160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43200","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the applicants of the contracts for the professional skills test for ITT entrants will be assessed; and how often Ministers have received reports relating to the quality or otherwise of the contractors.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192184","192184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43201","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received from the UK Ambassador in Rabat on the arrest of the journalists Lafkir Laghdaf and Khaled Rouhi.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192176","192176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43202","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will raise with the Moroccan Ambassador to the UK the arrests of the journalists Lafkir Laghdaf and Khaled Rouhi.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192177","192177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43203","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2014, Official Report, column 527W, on Gibraltar, what subjects were discussed at the meetings referred to in the Answer.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192180","192180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43204","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold discussions with the Polisario Front on security in the parts of Western Sahara under its control.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192178","192178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43205","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that GPs are aware of the warning signs of obstructive sleep apnoea and are screening for that condition using (a) the Epworth sleepiness test and (b) other recognised tests.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192181","192181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43206","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases leading to ground E abortions of cleft lip were diagnosed by (a) ultrasound and (b) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what those other methods of diagnosis were; and how many such diagnoses which did not result in abortion were recorded in that period.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192162","192162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43207","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ground E abortions for anencephaly were diagnosed by (a) ultrasound and (b) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what other methods of diagnosis were listed under other; and how many such diagnoses which did not result in abortion were recorded in the same period.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192163","192163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43208","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases leading to ground E abortions of congenital malformations of the musculoskeletal system were diagnosed by (a) ultrasound and (b) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what those other methods of diagnosis were; and how many such diagnoses which did not result in abortion were recorded in that period.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192161","192161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43209","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ground E abortions for spina bifida were diagnosed by (a) ultrasound and (b) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what other methods of diagnosis were listed under other; and how many such diagnoses which did not result in abortion were recorded in the same period.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192164","192164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43210","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases leading to ground E abortions of club foot were diagnosed by (a) ultrasound and (b) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what those other methods of diagnosis were; and how many such diagnoses which did not result in abortion were recorded in that period.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192165","192165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43211","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how trafficked children will be identified and referred to the Government's new personal advocates trial for child victims of trafficking; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192159","192159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43212","2014-03-17","Department for International Development","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to Answer to the hon. Member for Foyle of 10 March 2014, Official Report, column 42W, on developing countries: family planning, what empirical bases and methodologies her Department uses in its annual assessment of the extent to which the Government is achieving value for money from its Programme Partnership Arrangement funding to Marie Stopes International and the International Planned Parenthood Federation; how the estimate of 715,929 abortions was arrived at; what meaning is given to unsafe when describing such abortions; and how her Department arrives at an evidence-based understanding of what constitutes an unsafe abortion when no data is collected on the abortions performed by partner organisations.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192156","192156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43214","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with (a) metropolitan local authorities and (b) passenger transport executives on the introduction of red route measures to principal transport corridors in cities and conurbations.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192147","192147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43215","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has for the roll-out of smartcard technology for travel on (a) buses, (b) trams and (c) metro systems outside London.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192148","192148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43216","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on the ability of older and disabled workers to find work as a result of the abolition of the Percentage Threshold Scheme for recovering statutory sick pay.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192157","192157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43217","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in (a) Denton and Reddish constituency, (b) Tameside Metropolitan Borough and (c) Stockport Metropolitan Borough are (i) entitled to and (ii) receiving council tax relief.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 192154","192154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42682","2014-03-17","Attorney General","2014-03-12","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been (a) charged and (b) prosecuted under sections 2A and 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191735","191735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42683","2014-03-17","Attorney General","2014-03-12","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been charged under (a) section 2A and (b) section 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997 in each police force in England and Wales since those sections came into force.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191736","191736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42684","2014-03-17","Attorney General","2014-03-12","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of the Law Officers' Departments in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191801","191801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42685","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191800","191800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42686","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his assessment is of the potential financial and commercial implications for the UK information techology industry of the release of classified material relating to the operation of the intelligence and security services by Edward Snowden; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191824","191824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42687","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much UK Trade & Investment has spent in the (a) production and (b) postage of promotional materials to hon. Members in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191749","191749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42688","2014-03-18","Cabinet Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the average weekly hours worked since the first quarter of 2008 to date.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191752","191752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42689","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2014, Official Report, columns 170-1W, on public sector: food, how much funding is provided by his Department to strengthen supply chains.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191715","191715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42690","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what representations he has received from (a) the Electoral Commission, (b) the Welsh Government and (c) Carmarthenshire County Council on the Chief Executive of Carmarthenshire County Council and his responsibilities as Returning Officer.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191697","191697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42691","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the suitability of the chief executives of Carmarthenshire County Council and Pembrokeshire County Council acting as returning officers in future elections.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191698","191698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42692","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will meet the Electoral Commission to discuss the suitability of the chief executives of Carmarthenshire County Council and Pembrokeshire County Council for their roles as returning officers at the forthcoming European election.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191699","191699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42693","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what discussions he has had with the Electoral Commission on returning officer responsibilities in Carmarthenshire at the forthcoming European elections.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191701","191701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42694","2014-03-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will amend the guidance given to the Electoral Commission on whether prohibiting public officials who are suspended or under criminal investigation retain their responsibilities as returning officers.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191700","191700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42695","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged 18 to 24 years old in Scotland have been unemployed for (a) six months, (b) one year, (c) two years and (d) more than two years.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191751","191751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42696","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which statistics identified as high impact outputs with less widespread support by the Office for National Statistics in consultation on statistical products 2013 have had funding secured for their compilation in 2014-15.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191785","191785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42697","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much each Government department has allocated to charitable, benevolent or philanthropic institutions to deliver programmes through the Charities Act 2006 to date.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191743","191743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42698","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191802","191802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42699","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to ensure that all statistics identified as high impact outputs with less widespread support by the Office for National Statistics in its consultation on statistical products 2013 will continue to be funded for 2014-15.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191818","191818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42700","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change there has been in (a) gross and (b) net immigration into Northern Ireland in the last three years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191872","191872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42701","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the loss of tax revenue arising from fuel laundering across the land border with the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191890","191890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42702","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the loss of revenue arising from cigarette smuggling across the land border with the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191891","191891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42703","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many fines have been imposed to employers in Northern Ireland since 2012 for not paying the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191892","191892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42704","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how much air passenger duty revenue is lost annually as a result of passengers multi-ticketing via foreign hub airports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191851","191851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42705","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that the tax system does not disadvantage families with stay-at-home mothers.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191887","191887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42706","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will include in his Budget 2014 measures included in the wine and spirit trade association submission.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191799","191799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42707","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191814","191814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42708","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much air passenger duty revenue he expects will not accrue to the Exchequer in 2013-14 as a result of multi-ticketing via foreign hubs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191852","191852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42709","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the number of individual taxpayers in each 1,000 band of gross income between 40,000 and 70,000.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191879","191879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42710","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the potential cost to the public purse of raising the income tax personal allowance for 2014-15 from 10,000, (a) 10,550, (b) 11,000, (c) 11,500, (d) 12,000, (e) 12,500 and (f) 13,000.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191880","191880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42711","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had on the effects of Shared Appreciation Mortgage schemes on the status of estates left behind after the death of the loan applicant.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191780","191780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42712","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to ensure greater transparency in credit scoring procedures.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191704","191704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42713","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what proportion of occasions when a fire engine was despatched in response to a 999 call (a) a police vehicle and (b) an ambulance was also sent to the same incident in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191786","191786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42714","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have included in their development plans requirements for (a) higher energy efficiency standards than those required by Building Regulations and (b) onsite generation of energy.","Biography information for Martin Caton","Martin Caton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191849","191849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42715","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191803","191803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42716","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to discourage the setting up of illegal Traveller caravan sites and associated anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191888","191888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42717","2014-03-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) her Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of her Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191804","191804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42720","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the protocols required between the UK and Welsh Governments pertaining to environmental protection in the Cleddau estuary should Trident be moved from its current base in Scotland.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191695","191695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42721","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on relocating Trident to the Cleddau in the event of Scottish independence.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191696","191696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42722","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what financial contribution would be requested from the Welsh Government in relocation costs if Trident were moved to the Cleddau in the event of Scottish independence.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191692","191692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42723","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the (a) cost and (b) timescale on relocating Trident to the Cleddau in the event of Scottish independence.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191693","191693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42724","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost was of the provision of functional skills training for MoD St Athan by Bridgend College in each year since 2008; what the projected costs of the provision of functional skills training by a private contractor in future years; whether an assessment of the business case for the transfer of that training to a contracted provider was carried out prior to the decision to make that transfer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191784","191784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42725","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191805","191805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42726","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value of each asset under contraction valued at 1 million or more held on Air Command's balance sheet is.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191821","191821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42727","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) quantity and (b) value of all information technology tangible fixed assets items valued at 1 million or over held on Air Command's balance sheet is.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191822","191822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42728","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans there are for (a) Russian attendance and (b) Russian dialogues in the margins of the NATO Summit to be held in Wales in September 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191881","191881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42729","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) army applications and (b) successful army applications from Northern Ireland there have been in the last three years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191855","191855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42730","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people from Northern Ireland have joined the Royal Marines in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191867","191867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42731","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) quantity and (b) value of all single use military equipment tangible fixed asset items valued at 1 million or over held on Air Command's balance sheet is.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191823","191823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42732","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of teachers teaching in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) London, (d) Lambeth and (e) Streatham parliamentary constituency have undertook specialist training on educational provision for children and young people on the autism spectrum in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191882","191882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42733","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of school governing bodies in holding head teachers to account; and what plans he has to review the guidance his Department issues to school governors.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191825","191825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42734","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191806","191806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42735","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many available school places there are at schools that provide specialist support for children and young people on the atuism spectrum in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) London, (d) Lambeth and (e) Streatham parliamentary constituency; and how many such places will be available in each of the next 15 years.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191883","191883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42736","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in reception, year one and year two will be provided with a hot, nutritious meal at lunchtime from September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191776","191776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42737","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he will publish the Statistical First Release Admission appeals in maintained primary and secondary schools in England: academic year 2011 to 2012.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191777","191777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42738","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the application process will (a) open and (b) close for the Champions League of Head Teachers scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191778","191778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42739","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's target is for the number of (a) applications and (b) recruits to the Champions League of Head Teachers scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191779","191779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42740","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had on introducing compulsory sex and relationship education in schools with (a) teachers, (b) parents, (c) religious bodies and (d) organisations with an interest in young people's welfare; and if he will publish the results of those discussions.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191787","191787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42741","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy trusts (a) met the deadline to submit, (b) missed the deadline of 31 January 2014 for submitting and (c) are yet to submit their 2012-13 accounts return.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191775","191775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42742","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of children's centre closures on the long-term development of children from disadvantaged families.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191750","191750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42743","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations he has received on the importance of the morale of teachers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191762","191762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42744","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to assess the morale of teachers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191763","191763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42745","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has given on the proportion of the questions in the revised Key Stage 2 Mathematics tests which should be (a) real life problems and (b) abstract arithmetical calculations.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191746","191746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42746","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, by what means the National College for Teaching and Leadership agency gathers information on child protection issues in independent schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191691","191691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42747","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is his policy immediately to close schools which refer themselves to the National College for Teaching Leadership on the grounds of suspicions of child abuse.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191703","191703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42748","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Liverpool, Wavertree of 16 October 2014, Official Report, column 754W, on the Green Deal scheme, to what the remainder of the funding allocated to the Green Deal in November 2011 which has not yet been spent has been allocated.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191708","191708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42749","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the European Commission has reached a conclusion in its consideration of the state aid case for the compensation scheme for the carbon floor price.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191709","191709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42750","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the economic viability of oil and gas extraction from the UK Contintental Shelf in the next decade.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191720","191720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42751","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191807","191807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42752","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what reductions in carbon dioxide emissions have resulted in the last five years from local authorities putting requirements in their development plans for (a) higher energy efficiency standards than those required by Building Regulations and (b) onsite generation of energy in new developments.","Biography information for Martin Caton","Martin Caton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191848","191848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42753","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of people in each region of the UK are in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191865","191865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42754","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on fuel poverty.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191864","191864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42755","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191808","191808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42756","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many enforcement cases run by the Environment Agency were (a) under investigation, (b) proceeding, having been issued in the courts and (c) completed on 26 February 2014.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191771","191771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42757","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the current staffing complement is in the Environment Agency's legal services and operations departments; and how many staff have applied to leave under such staff reduction plans.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191772","191772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42758","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many legal and enforcement cases there were in each geographic area of the Environment Agency on 26 February 2014; and how many such cases were (a) under investigation, (b) being considered for enforcement action, (c) being considered for legal action by the legal services department and (d) issued and proceeding through the courts.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191773","191773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42759","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cases being investigated for enforcement action or issued and proceeding in the courts have (a) been discontinued completely, (b) been enforced using a lower level of action and (c) ceased to be investigated in each geographic area of the Environment Agency since 26 February 2014.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191774","191774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42760","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps each area of the Environment Agency is taking to reduce its enforcement and legal caseload by 31 March 2014; and by how many and what proportion of existing cases each area plans to reduce its caseload.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191850","191850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42761","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consideration he has given to conducting a national soil survey to assess the effects of recent flood damage on the future productivity of farmland.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191717","191717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42762","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will undertake a review of the proposal by the Environment Agency to disband the three West Sussex internal drainage boards; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191747","191747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42763","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will assess the impact of agricultural policies in the UK on the level of flooding in recent years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191711","191711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42764","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage local communities to plant trees.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191712","191712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42765","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to determine whether wild animals being imported into the UK are being sourced (a) illegally from the wild and (b) from legal captive-breeding facilities; what estimate he made of the number of animals so imported in the last three years; and what steps he takes to ensure good animal welfare standards in captive-breeding facilities in the UK.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191702","191702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42766","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken or is supporting at the United Nations to diminish tensions in Ukraine.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191738","191738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42767","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the convictions of Khalifa Rabeiah and Othman al-Shehhi in the United Arab Emirates.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191767","191767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42768","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with which countries the EU acting as a legal personality has concluded co-operation agreements in the field of justice and home affairs.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191707","191707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42769","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent Swiss referendum result on the free movement of people in the EU on the long-term validity of that policy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191759","191759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42770","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy that there be a UK refendum on the principle of free movement of people within the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191760","191760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42771","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to prevent further acts of aggression by Russia.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191862","191862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42772","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the UN sanctions regime against the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191845","191845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42773","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191809","191809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42774","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress of Bosnia and Herzegovina towards EU accession.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191834","191834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42775","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the UK will (a) review and (b) suspend security assistance to the government of Uganda following the passage of the recent anti-homosexuality law in that country.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191847","191847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42776","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support an African-led solution to problems of maritime insecurity in the Gulf of Guinea.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191846","191846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42777","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the improvement of human rights in Vietnam.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191842","191842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42778","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191810","191810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42779","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2014, Official Report, column 196W, on Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme, for what reasons his Department considers that the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme does not affect the operation of Government accounting and borrowing rules; to which organisations his Department has communicated this; whether he has discussed with the Chancellor of the Exchequer the possibility of allowing an exemption to Government accounting and borrowing rules in this instance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191833","191833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42780","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice his Department offers to patients requiring deep brain stimulation treatment, in cases where extra funding is required.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191793","191793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42781","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the report by Breast Cancer Campaign entitled Finding the cures, improving the care, published on 11 March 2014, what assessment he has made of claims in that report that patients are being failed by insensitive NHS doctors and nurses.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191884","191884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42782","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will hold discussions with the Northern Ireland Minister of Health to discuss the recent rise in the incidence of scarlet fever in England and its implications for Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191885","191885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42783","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with North West Ambulance Service Trust about delays in attending call-outs.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191789","191789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42784","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulances have taken longer than (a) 30 minutes and (b) one hour to arrive at the patient in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191796","191796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42785","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many taxis have been used by ambulance trusts to collect urgent or emergency patients in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191797","191797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42786","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what proportion of occasions when a fire engine was despatched in response to a 999 call an ambulance was sent to the same incident in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191794","191794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42787","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the contribution by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 11 March 2014, Official Report, column 267, on Care Bill, whether the chair of the committee looking at draft guidance on Clause 119 of the Bill will be remunerated.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191716","191716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42788","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the Nursing and Midwifery Council's proposal to raise nurse registration fees.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191765","191765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42789","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the NHS Annual Report to be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191748","191748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42790","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to contribute to the consultation by the Nursing and Midwifery Council on its proposals to increase its compulsory annual fee.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191764","191764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42791","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether a joint PHE-JCVI-DH-NICE working group to examine how the impact of vaccination programmes could best be assessed has been established and has yet met.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191706","191706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42792","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department takes in ensuring that CITES-listed animals have their welfare needs met from when they are prepared and shipped for (a) import to and (b) export from the UK.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191705","191705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42793","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what amount of (a) tobacco and cigar products, (b) Class A and B drugs and (c) alcohol products were recovered by the Border Agency or its predecessor (i) in total value and (ii) from all ports and airports in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191690","191690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42794","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce a pre-consideration eligibility test for visas and immigration applications where the associated fees exceed 500.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191740","191740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42795","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much revenue the UK Visas and Immigration Service received from application fees where the application is not processed due to reasons of eligibility in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191741","191741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42796","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the administrative costs associated with visa and immigration applications received by the UK Visas and Immigration Service which are not processed due to reasons of eligibility were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191742","191742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42797","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints of alleged stalking behaviour were received by each police force in England and Wales in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191739","191739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42798","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to extend sections 2A and 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997 to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191737","191737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42799","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which countries the EU is acting as a legal personality currently negotiating co-operation agreements in the field of justice and home affairs.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191745","191745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42800","2014-03-18","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of police staff in each police area in England and Wales have received training in sections 2A and 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191757","191757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42801","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Minister of Justice on counter-terrorism issues.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191875","191875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42802","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the devolved administration in Northern Ireland on a minimum unit price for alcohol.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191871","191871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42803","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what change in spending there has been in the security and intelligence agencies in the last three years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191873","191873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42804","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2014, Official Report, column 819W, on human trafficking, on what date the terms of reference for the review of the National Referral Mechanism will be finalised; when the review of the National Referral Mechanism will commence; when the review of the National Referral Mechanism will be (a) completed and (b) published; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191817","191817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42805","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the vulnerability of the UK to a terrorist cyber-attack is; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191819","191819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42806","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) her Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of her Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191811","191811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42807","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the likelihood of a terrorist cyber-attack on the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191820","191820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42808","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the change in the number of non-EU students issued visas to study at UK universities in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191829","191829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42809","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many non-EU students (a) came to the UK and (b) departed the UK in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191830","191830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42810","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to introduce a ban on the sale of alcohol below the cost of duty plus VAT.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191869","191869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42811","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to introduce a minimum unit price for alcohol in England and Wales.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191870","191870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42812","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to record the departure of non-EU students as they leave the UK at the end of their studies.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191828","191828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42813","2014-03-17","Department for International Development","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, to what use has past UK aid to Ukraine been put.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191868","191868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42814","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191812","191812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42815","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many individuals convicted of (a) murder or (b) attempted murder in each of the last 10 years have been released with exclusion zones forming a part of their licence arrangements.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191826","191826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42816","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that the sentencing of foreign criminals in British courts is in accordance with the relevant sentencing guidelines.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191886","191886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42817","2014-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what treatment is available for persons convicted of stalking (a) in prisons and (b) as a condition of a community order.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191758","191758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42818","2014-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of probation staff have received training in sections 2A and 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191756","191756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42819","2014-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress he has made on implementing the Third Parties (Rights against Insurers) Act 2010; and when he will take steps to bring this Act into force.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191783","191783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42820","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions an individual on licence for an attempted murder conviction has been granted permission to enter an exclusion zone which has been formed as part of their licence arrangement in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191781","191781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42821","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times a convicted attempted murderer released on licence has been allowed to enter an exclusion zone formed as part of their licence arrangement within one week of their release in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191795","191795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42822","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of (a) magistrates' courts, (b) County courts and (c) County Court money claims centres use higher-rate telephone numbers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191689","191689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42823","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what provision there will be for members of the public to contribute to the independent inquiry into the on-the-run scheme announced by the Prime Minister on 27 February 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191761","191761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42824","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the change was in the number of Post Office Card accounts in Northern Ireland between 1 January 2012 and 1 January 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191769","191769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42825","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on providing older workers in Northern Ireland with adequate skills training.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191854","191854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42826","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Social Democratic and Labour Party on the introduction of the National Crime Agency for Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191874","191874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42827","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what reports she has received on whether the Provisional IRA is still involved in criminal and illegal activity.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191861","191861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42828","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she last met the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland to discuss terrorist activity.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191876","191876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42829","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many terrorist acts by alleged (a) republicans and (b) loyalists have been recorded by the Police Service of Northern Ireland in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191877","191877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42830","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the devolution of responsibility for levying of corporation tax to the Northern Ireland Assembly.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191889","191889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42831","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many successful prosecutions of alleged republican terrorists there have been in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191857","191857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42832","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what funding has been made available to the Police Service of Northern Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191858","191858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42833","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many prosecutions have been brought forward against those dealing in illegal fuel laundering in the last five years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191859","191859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42834","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the role of alleged dissident republicans in illegal fuel laundering.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191860","191860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42835","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many young people from Northern Ireland have joined the (a) Army cadets, (b) RAF cadets and (c) Royal Navy cadets in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191866","191866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42836","2014-03-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the voter registration effects in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191856","191856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42837","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he was first informed of increased levels of radioactivity in the cooling waters in the reactor at the Vulcan Nuclear Reactor Test Establishment.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191838","191838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42838","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many people aged 18 to 24 years in Scotland have been unemployed for (a) six months, (b) one year, (c) two years and (d) more than two years.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191839","191839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42839","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the change to average wages in Scotland since 2010.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191840","191840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42840","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the change in average household energy bills in Scotland since 2010.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191827","191827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42841","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he last met the Chancellor of the Exchequer to discuss income tax in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191831","191831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42842","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he was first informed about the increased levels of radioactivity in the cooling waters in the reactor at the Vulcan Nuclear Reactor Test Establishment.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191753","191753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42843","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what steps are being taken by the Electoral Commission in Northern Ireland to promote electoral registration in rural areas where residents live some distance from permanent electoral offices.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191770","191770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42844","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were for each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Luton Borough Council.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191733","191733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42845","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Telford and Wrekin.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191714","191714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42846","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Aberdeen City Council and (b) Aberdeenshire County Council.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191721","191721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42847","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-12","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which local authorities (a) did and (b) did not complete local data matching after the confirmation dry run with the Department for Work and Pensions' database and electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191816","191816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42848","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191813","191813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42849","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the Government has spent on rail services per head of population in each region of England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191841","191841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42850","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the size of pension received by employees of the General Lighthouse Authority of the transfer of pensions from that authority's scheme to the Principal Civil Service pension scheme.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191835","191835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42851","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 March 2014, Official Report, columns 64-5WS, what estimate he has made of (a) the cost to the General Lighthouse Fund (GLF) and (b) effect on the GLF's reserves of reducing light dues by one penny in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191836","191836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42852","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the savings that will be made in (a) financial year 2015-16 and (b) succeeding years as a result of the work of the Commissioners of Irish Lights in the Republic of Ireland being met fully from Irish sources.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191837","191837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42853","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what rail spending per head will be in each region of England in each year of Control Period 5.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191878","191878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42854","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all trains operated by the Northern Rail franchise will be compliant with the Equality Act 2010 by 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191843","191843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42855","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average age of rolling stock used by the Northern Rail franchise has been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191853","191853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42856","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the station usage figures were for each railway station in Copeland in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191844","191844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42857","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Abellio on potential improvements to rolling stock on the Great Eastern Main Line.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191766","191766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42858","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, column 387W, on First Capital Connect, what the (a) net franchise payment and (b) revenue support are for the extension of the Essex Thameside franchise from May 2013 to September 2014.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191754","191754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42859","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 March 2014, Official Report, columns 64-5WS, on light dues 2014-15, what estimate he has made of the total revenue foregone by the Exchequer by reducing the light dues rate by one penny to 40p per net registered tonne in 2014-15; and what estimate he has made of the total revenue so foregone through a further reduction in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191782","191782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42860","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what is the (a) principal value, (b) annual interest rate and (c) estimated total cost of the loan provided by his Department to facilitate the transfer of the General Lighthouse Authorities' pension schemes to the Principal Civil Service Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191755","191755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42861","2014-03-17","Wales Office","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on relocating Trident to the Cleddau in the event of Scottish independence.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191694","191694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42862","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will rank how many homeless households were placed in each London local authority by other local authorities since 2010; and how many homeless households each London local authority has placed in authorities other than their own since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191726","191726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42863","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the actual and percentage change was in the number of households from each London local authority provided with temporary accommodation outside their home borough between March 2010 and December 2013.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191727","191727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42864","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the actual and percentage change was in the number of homeless households in temporary accommodation in each London local authority between March 2010 and December 2013.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191728","191728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42865","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households have been placed in temporary accommodation in each London local authority by councils other than their own since March 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191729","191729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42866","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homeless households have been placed in temporary accommodation in each London local authority by councils other than their own in each of the last eight quarters.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191730","191730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42867","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households have been placed in temporary accommodation by London councils in each local authority area outside London since March 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191731","191731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42868","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in Scotland have (a) received a sanction and (b) received a sanction and disputed it in each of the last five years; and how many such claimants had a sanction overturned as a result of it being reconsidered or appealed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191732","191732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42869","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have received sanctions of their jobseeker's allowance for non-attendance in (a) Portsmouth South constituency, (b) Portsmouth, (c) Hampshire and (d) England to date.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191713","191713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42870","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Darlington constituency currently receive independent living fund payments.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191710","191710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42871","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect (a) generally and (b) on ease of comparisons with previous years of collecting work-related ill-health data through the Labour Force Survey biennially instead of annually.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191798","191798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42872","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which Health and Safety Executive Approved Codes of Practice (a) have been reviewed since May 2010, (b) are scheduled for review or amendment and (c) are not currently scheduled for review.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191791","191791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42873","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has for the future use of Post Office card accounts.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191790","191790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42874","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to promote small business entrepreneurial skills for people who are currently unemployed.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191768","191768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42875","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Warrington currently have benefits of which type paid into a Post Office card account.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191788","191788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42876","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many, and what number per 1,000, of the adult population received social care in each English local authority in (a) 2009-10 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191725","191725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42877","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the effect of the removal of the under-occupancy penalty on the number of children living in relative income poverty.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191718","191718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42878","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to reply to the email correspondence from the hon. Member for Denton and Reddish dated 10 January 2014 (reference 7648/Jan14) on Atos Healthcare.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191734","191734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42879","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2014, Official Report, column 848W, on incapacity benefit, what estimate his Department originally made of the number of Incapacity Benefit claimants who would be migrated to employment and support allowance; what his Department's latest estimate of the number of such claimants is; and what proportion of such claimants are still to be migrated.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191719","191719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42880","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which 30 local authority areas have received the largest number of homeless households in temporary accommodation placed by London local authorities since March 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191722","191722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42881","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of adults received social care in each English local authority in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191724","191724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42882","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce long term unemployment in Peterborough constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191744","191744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42883","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there has been in the number and proportion of homeless households in nightly booked temporary accommodation in London since March 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191723","191723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42884","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to review his Department's Fee for Intervention policy.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191832","191832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42885","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the empty property business rates for the vacant properties recorded on the e-PIMS database owned by (a) his Department and (b) any executive agencies or non-departmental public bodies of his Department in the current financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191815","191815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42886","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has issued on the requirement to have 16,000 or less in savings for eligibility for income-based jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191792","191792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43567","2014-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress he has made on his reforms to rehabilitation aimed at reducing reoffending.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903108","903108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42356","2014-03-13","Attorney General","2014-03-11","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the effects on prosecutions of the Court of Appeal judgement in the case of Pace and another v R on 18 February 2014, EWCA Crim 186.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191677","191677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42357","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what amount the Government has spent on research on type one diabetes in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191682","191682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42358","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the Government's objectives are in the work of the Doha Development Agenda.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191482","191482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42359","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress he has made on developing a global standard of financial transparency in the extractive industry.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191496","191496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42360","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) Post Office Limited, (b) the National Federation of Sub Postmasters, (c) the Department for Work and Pensions and (d) the Treasury on the future of the Post Office card account.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191517","191517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42361","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber employed an apprentice in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191636","191636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42362","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to publish the report of the independent project review of the Counter Fraud Checking Service once it is completed.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191593","191593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42363","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the change in numbers of civil servants working less than 20 hours per week was between January 2010 and January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191685","191685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42364","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what (a) amount and (b) percentage per average bottle alcohol excise duty increased between (i) 1997 and 2010 and (ii) 2010 and 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191676","191676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42365","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department made before the 2012 Budget of the number of properties valued at more than (a) 2 million and (b) 5 million.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191427","191427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42366","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department made before the 2012 Budget of the average annual payment required from each property valued above 2 million in order to raise a net sum of 2 billion per annum.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191429","191429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42367","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department made before the 2012 Budget of the effect on stamp duty land tax and inheritance tax receipts of the introduction of a so-called mansion tax designed to raise a net sum of 2 billion per annum.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191430","191430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42368","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what savings have accrued to the Exchequer as a result of lowering the Low Value Consignment Relief threshold in the 2011 Finance Bill from 18 to 15.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191497","191497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42369","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to address levels of negative equity and home repossessions in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191505","191505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42370","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which consumer goods products sold in the UK are subject to the highest levels of tax per product; what the level of tax is on each such product; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191591","191591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42371","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the average UK consumer pays per year in (a) fuel duty and (b) alcohol excise duty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191592","191592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42372","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consumer goods products sold in the UK attract the highest levels of tax per product; and what level of tax is so levied.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191559","191559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42373","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many women have been short-listed for positions on the Monetary Policy Committee since 2010; how many of those on each (a) short-listing panel and (b) appointments panel were women; and what steps he has taken to identify qualified female candidates and encourage them to apply.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191539","191539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42374","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid in working tax credits payments to recipients in (a) Glasgow, (b) Edinburgh, (c) Dundee and (d) Aberdeen in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191622","191622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42375","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of small businesses in Brigg and Goole constituency which will be affected by the extension of the small business rate relief scheme to March 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191639","191639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42376","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the cost to the Exchequer of introducing a business rates holiday for investment in new plant and machinery in 2015-16.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191657","191657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42377","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many fines have been issued to employers in (a) Portsmouth South constituency, (b) Hampshire and (c) the South East for non-payment of the national minimum wage in each year since 2010; and what the total value of such fines was in each such area.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191668","191668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42378","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the effects of changes to tax and benefits on the number of children living in relative income poverty in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191659","191659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42379","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of manufacturing businesses that are currently liable for business rates.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191660","191660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42380","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the cost to the Exchequer of extending 1,000 retail sector business rates relief to manufacturers.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191661","191661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42381","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many women were short-listed for the position of Deputy Governor of the Bank of England; how many of those on the (a) short-listing panel and (b) appointments panel were women; and what steps he took to identify qualified female candidates and encourage them to apply for that position.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191680","191680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42382","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the benefits of self-help housing schemes for Newcastle upon Tyne's housing stock.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191644","191644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42383","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what value of grants has been issued in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber under the New Homes Bonus Scheme since that scheme's introduction.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191637","191637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42384","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of London households in temporary accommodation were in (a) private sector leased properties, (b) hotels, (c) bed and breakfast, (d) local authority registered social landlord property and (e) other accommodation (i) at the most recent date for which figures are available and (ii) at 31 March 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191531","191531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42385","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has given to each (a) local authority and (b) other organisation to deliver the Gold Standard homelessness initiative.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191532","191532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42386","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the governance arrangements of the London Fire and Emergency Planning Authority to make its members more accountable to the Mayor of London.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191587","191587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42387","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish Birmingham City Council's bid for funding for a weekly refuse collection.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191552","191552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42388","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people have been employed to work on the Gold Standard homelessness initiative; and where they are based.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191518","191518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42389","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of the Gold Standard homelessness initiative funding had been spent on staffing by 31 December 2013.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191519","191519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42390","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities had taken part in the Gold Standard homelessness initiative as of 31 December 2013.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191520","191520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42391","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the National Housing Advice Service has spent on training to deliver the Homelessness Gold Standard; and how many councils had trained staff as of 31 December 2013.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191521","191521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42392","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) change and (b) percentage change in homelessness (i) applications and (ii) admissions was in each (A) London local authority area and (B) English region between March 2010 and December 2013.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191522","191522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42393","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) change and (b) percentage change was in the number of homelessness acceptances arising from the end of a private sector tenancy in each (i) London local authority and (ii) English region between March 2010 and December 2013.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191523","191523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42394","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the number of single adults who have applied for social housing in (a) England and (b) the London Borough of Havering since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191473","191473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42398","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if her Department will authorise the release as a spreadsheet of the postcode data used for the Cumbria County Council broadband coverage map.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191438","191438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42399","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to encourage citizens of the Commonwealth who are studying at UK conservatoires to pursue careers in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191476","191476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42400","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on which occasions the flags of the Commonwealth are flown on Parliament Square.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191478","191478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42401","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to increase and support participation in grassroots football.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191582","191582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42402","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on how many occasions she has met representatives of the (a) Premier League and (b) Football Association to discuss access to grassroots football.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191549","191549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42403","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the potential cost of implementing the recommendations of the Veterans' Transition Review, published on 11 February 2014.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191553","191553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42404","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service prosecutors there were in the service prosecution authority of each branch of the armed forces in each year since 2006, what the length of their service in each authority was; how many have received specialist training in the investigation of sexual offences; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191530","191530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42405","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the UK's gross domestic product the Government spend on defence; and what steps he is taking to encourage the UK's NATO allies to match this proportion.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191555","191555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42406","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many serving members in each branch of the armed forces were deemed to have lost out on promotion following receiving a police caution in the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191525","191525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42407","2014-03-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will place in the Library copies of the memoranda of understanding underpinning the 2010 sale of 12 VIP AgustaWestland AW 101 helicopters to the Indian government.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191543","191543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42408","2014-03-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Jackie Callcutt was involved in the negotiations for the AgustaWestland deal with India which collapsed earlier this year.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191544","191544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42409","2014-03-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the name was of each official in his Department who took part in negotiations prior to the 2010 sale of 12 VIP AgustaWestland AW 101 helicopters to the Indian government.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191545","191545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42410","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the military prosecutor who made the decsion not to bring any charges in relation to the rape allegation brought by Corporal Anne-Marie Ellement had undertaken the specialist training on rape and sexual offences compulsory for CPS prosecutors who work on rape cases at the time of that decision.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191580","191580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42411","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when Ministers in his Department were first made aware of problems with the reactor cooling systems at the Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment; and which Minister was so informed.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191631","191631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42412","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date in January 2012 the problem with the reactor cooling systems at the Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment was detected.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191632","191632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42413","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on legal costs relating to International Military Sales Ltd in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191575","191575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42414","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department first became aware of the increase in discharges of noble gases from the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment as a result of the incident in January 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191600","191600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42415","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of how many veterans of the D-Day landings will travel to Normandy for the 70th anniversary of those landings.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191645","191645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42416","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons representatives of his Department did not mention the incident at the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment in January 2012 in any of their oral or written reports to the Dounreay Stakeholder Group in 2012 and 2013.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191599","191599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42417","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets and how many personnel are taking part in Exercise Saber Strike; what the cost to the public purse is of the exercise; and what assets and how many personnel took part in each of the last five Saber Strike exercises.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191598","191598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42418","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which NATO member states have sent maritime patrol aircraft to (a) RAF Lossiemouth and (b) RAF Leuchars since September 2013; which aircraft were so sent; and what the purpose was of each visit.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191596","191596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42419","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what conditions have to apply in order to prevent the release of a Service Inquiry report to the general public.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191597","191597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42420","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department informed (a) the Defence Nuclear Safety Regulator, (b) the Office for Nuclear Regulation and (c) the Scottish Environmental Protection Agency of the incident at the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment in January 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191604","191604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42421","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what revisions his Department has made to the projected future demand for highly enriched uranium for the Naval Nuclear Propulsion Programme.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191605","191605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42422","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he instructed his officials not to make public the problem with the reactor cooling system at Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment at the Dounreay Stakeholder Group meetings of 19 January, 25 April, 18 July and 7 November 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191603","191603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42423","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to hold a national event in London to mark the 70th anniversary of the D-Day landings.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191647","191647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42424","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has measured the dimensions of the fracture in the cladding of the fuel core of the reactor in the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191601","191601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42425","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department has received about holding a national event in London to mark the 70th anniversary of the D-Day landings.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191648","191648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42426","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with its US counterpart on revisions to the future demand for highly enriched uranium for the Naval Nuclear Propulsion Programme.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191602","191602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42427","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to assist veterans of the D-Day landings to take part in the Normandy 70 commemorations.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191646","191646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42428","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there is a NATO communications installation at RAF Croughton.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191666","191666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42429","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his statement of 6 March 2014, Official Report, columns 1077-9, on nuclear submarines, what work will be carried out at (a) Devonport and (b) Raynesway as a result of the 150 million investment.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191673","191673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42430","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 39 of the final report of UN Special Rapporteur on human rights and counter-terrorism dated 28 February 2014, if he will publish the investigations report on civilian casualties through use of remotely piloted aircraft by the UK in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191671","191671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42431","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of potential effects of the five additional Reaper remotely-piloted aircraft systems procured under an urgent operational requirement on the final part of the armed forces redundancy programme.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191662","191662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42432","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether US C-17 aircraft carrying MQ-1 Predators refuel at RAF Mildenhall.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191667","191667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42433","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish and place in the Library a copy of the advice from the Defence Nuclear Safety Regulator on the incident at the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment in January 2012 and its implications for the Naval Nuclear Propulsion Programme.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191606","191606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42434","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value is of the break clauses in each contract his Department currently holds with Capita.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191617","191617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42435","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) length and (b) value is of each contract his Department currently holds with Capita.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191618","191618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42436","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has identified the exact location of the fracture in the cladding of the fuel core of the reactor in the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191608","191608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42437","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria his Department used in its decision on to whom to award the contract to manage the Defence Infrastructure Organisation.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191619","191619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42438","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the role of the new strategic partner taking over the Defence Infrastructure Organisation will be in the statutory planning process; and whether his Department will be the final arbiter in planning matters relating to local plans regarding his Department's land and property following that new partner assuming its role.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191620","191620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42439","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the Defence Nuclear Safety Regulator did not mention the incident at the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment in January 2012 in (a) his quarterly reports to the Dounreay Stakeholder Group and (b) his 2012 annual report.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191607","191607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42440","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons (a) the Scottish Environment Protection Agency and (b) the  Office for Nuclear Regulation were told to keep the information regarding the problem with the reactor cooling system at Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment on a need to know basis for security reasons.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191609","191609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42441","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a lessons-learnt exercise has been carried out following the discovery of problems with reactor cooling systems at the Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the report from any such exercise.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191610","191610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42442","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what advice was given to Ministers by (a) the Defence Nuclear Safety Regulator, (b) the Head of Nuclear Propulsion and (c) the Naval Superintendent, Vulcan relating to potential risks to submarine safety following the discovery of problems with reactor cooling systems at the Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the relevant correspondence.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191611","191611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42443","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which periods the reactor at the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment was shut down between 1 January 2012 and 11 March 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191612","191612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42444","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many vessels were (a) intercepted and (b) boarded by the Royal Navy in UK territorial waters in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191613","191613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42445","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what investigations were conducted to establish the safety of reactors on board the Royal Navy's nuclear powered submarines following the discovery of problems with reactor cooling systems at the Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment; which submarines were investigated; on what dates investigations (a) commenced and (b) were concluded; and whether any implications for reactor safety were identified for any vessel following such investigations.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191614","191614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42446","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many days the reactor at the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment was shut down between 1 January 2012 and 6 March 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191615","191615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42447","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what types of vessels are assigned to UK contingency operations; and at what notice each such type of vessel is held.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191492","191492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42448","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) serving and (b) ex-serving members of each branch of the armed forces were out of time to make an official complaint following their being wrongly disciplined following receipt of a police caution; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191501","191501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42449","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) serving and (b) former members of each branch of the armed forces received compensation following the end of the previous policy of disciplining personnel who received a police caution; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191502","191502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42450","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much compensation has been paid to (a) serving and (b) former members of each branch of the armed forces who were disciplined following receipt of a police caution; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191503","191503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42451","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to reverse sanctions still having an effect after November 2008 on serving members of each of the armed forces who were disciplined following receipt of a police caution; how many serving members of the armed forces were so involved; and if he will make a statement","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191504","191504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42452","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many visitors there were at the (a) National Army Museum, (b) Royal Air Force Museum, (c) National Museum of the Royal Navy and (d) National Memorial Arboretum in the last year for which figures are available; and what the planned grant-in-aid is for each such attraction in 2014-15.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191425","191425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42453","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service police there were in (a) each branch of the armed forces and (b) the Special Investigations Branch in the last year for which data is available; how many such police have received specialist training in the investigation of sexual offences; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191443","191443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42454","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times civilian counsel have been briefed by the service prosecution authority in each year since 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191444","191444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42455","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many cases were taken to summary appeal courts in each year since 2006 by members of each branch of the armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191445","191445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42456","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how long (a) HMS Westminster, (b) HMS Brocklesby and (c) HMS Daring will be stationed in Gibraltar.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191471","191471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42457","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons there are no Royal Navy vessels on duty in the Far East.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191479","191479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42458","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what type of ships are held for Maritime Security Operations in Gibraltar.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191480","191480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42459","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) serial number and (b) date of entry into service is for each (i) C-17A Globemaster, (ii) Hercules C1/C3 (K), (iii) C4/C5 (J), (iv) Tristar and (v) VC10 airframe.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191418","191418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42460","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) serial number and (b) date of entry into service is for each (i) BAE 125, (ii) BAE 146, (iii) Agusta and (iv) Islander BN2T CC Mk2 airframe.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191419","191419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42461","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the date of entry into service is for each (a) Chinook, (b) Griffin HAR2, (c) Puma, (d) Puma HC2, (e) Merlin and (f) Sea King airframe.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191420","191420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42462","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the date of entry into service is for each (a) Griffin HT1, (b) Hawk T2, (c) Hawk T1, (d) King Air, (e) Tucano, (f) Tutor T Mark 1, (g) Squirrel HT1, (h) Vigilant T1 and (i) Viking T1 airframe.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191421","191421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42463","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) serial number and (b) date of entry into service is for each (i) Typhoon, (ii) Tornado GR4 and (iii) Sentinel R1 airframe.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191422","191422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42464","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions military personnel were deployed on the streets of Northern Ireland to deal with explosive devices in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191686","191686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42465","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2014, Official Report, column 33W, on unmanned air vehicles, if he will publish a complete list of countries to which his Department has sent pilots to operate unmanned aircraft. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191683","191683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42466","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any restrictions have been placed on the operation of reactors onboard Royal Navy submarines as a result of the incident at the Vulcan Naval Reactor Test Establishment in January 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191674","191674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42467","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his statement of 6 March 2014, Official Report, columns 1077-9, on nuclear submarines, how much of the additional 150 million investment announced on 6 March 2014 is for (a) Devonport and (b) Raynesway.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191672","191672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42468","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost is of the fuel core which will be loaded onto HMS Vanguard in the refuelling announced on 6 March 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191675","191675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42469","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that a higher proportion of religious education lessons are taught by fully qualified subject specialists.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191441","191441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42470","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many specialist religious education teachers there were in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191442","191442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42471","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of pre-school education on attainment during school years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191474","191474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42472","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children aged three or four in (a) England and (b) the London Borough of Havering are in pre-school education.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191475","191475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42473","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of religious education lessons were taught by non-subject specialists in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191439","191439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42474","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the study of a musical instrument in both (a) primary and (b) secondary schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191477","191477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42475","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will continue to provide additional funding for the security requirements of Jewish faith schools after 2015.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191586","191586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42476","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools he and other Ministers in his Department have visited since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191588","191588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42477","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools officials in his Department have visited in connection with finding (a) permanent and (b) temporary sites for free schools due to open in September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191589","191589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42478","2014-03-17","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the names are of the free school projects proposed to open in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15 that have been cancelled or withdrawn; and what the pre-opening expenditure was for each of those projects.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191590","191590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42479","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to implement the recommendations of the Ofsted report RE: Realising the Potential, published in October 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191527","191527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42480","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2014, Official Report, column 914W, on teachers: training, how many bursaries for initial teacher training were offered for each subject where there was not a shortage of fully qualified subject specialists in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191526","191526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42481","2014-03-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department will be taking to implement the findings of the second State of Natural Capital report by the Natural Capital Committee.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191585","191585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42482","2014-03-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what solar geo-engineering his Department (a) has conducted, (b) has permitted and (c) is aware of in the airspace above Britain.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191581","191581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42483","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the change in energy costs for the average household of pensionable age since May 2010.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191514","191514"
