"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765807","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the attainment gap between disadvantaged and other students in (a) A-levels, (b) vocational qualifications and (c) all Level 3 qualifications by age 19 in each region of England.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105746","105746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765808","2017-10-11","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of demand for digital skills in London.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106168","106168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765809","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of 16 to 19-year olds participate in (a) A-levels and (b) a technical or vocational pathway in each region of England.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105745","105745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765810","2017-10-11","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of adults in London who do not have core digital skills.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105989","105989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765811","2017-10-11","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the criteria will be for eligibility for free training in basic digital skills for adults lacking relevant qualifications under the new digital strategy.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105990","105990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765812","2017-10-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many countries his Department currently provides military aid to.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105974","105974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765813","2017-10-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much financial aid the Government gave foreign militaries in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106311","106311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765814","2017-10-11","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings the Chief Secretary to the Treasury has had since her appointment; and whom she has met with.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106306","106306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765815","2017-10-11","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs staff currently work in UK customs.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106307","106307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765816","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how may people received (a) statutory paternity and (b) shared parental pay in the financial year 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106314","106314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765817","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Deer Act 1991 in each police force area in 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106094","106094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765818","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage supermarkets to publish food waste data and audited annual breakdowns of food waste.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106368","106368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765819","2017-10-11","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of withdrawal from the European Medicines Agency on access to new treatments for people with dementia.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106147","106147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765820","2017-10-11","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure parity of funding between research into dementia care and bio-medical research on dementia.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106247","106247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765821","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department had made of the potential effect on the UK organic milk industry's trade with the US of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106424","106424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765822","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8580, on Ministry of Defence: Brexit, which stages of the contingency plans have so far been implemented.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106423","106423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765823","2017-10-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how he will maintain co-operation between the Republic of Ireland and Northern Ireland as required by the Good Friday Agreement when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106298","106298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765824","2017-10-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions he has had with (a) cross-border bodies established under the Good Friday Agreement and (b) community and other third-sector organisations involved in cross-border co-operation on funding to maintain effective cross-border co-operation.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106297","106297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765825","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress the Department is making on an equivalency agreement for trade in organic products with the US after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106070","106070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765826","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2017 to Question 10092, on UK membership of the EU, what steps his Department will need to take to confirm formally withdrawal from the EEA agreement as a matter of international law.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106266","106266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765827","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the gender split is in University Technical Colleges in (a) Sheffield and (b) England and Wales among students.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106320","106320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765828","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an assessment of the outcome of the gluten free product prescribing trial undertaken by the Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group in 2016.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106217","106217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765829","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many screened interview rooms are being lost in jobcentres in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106236","106236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765830","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many screened interview rooms are being lost in jobcentres in Sheffield.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106237","106237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765831","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the date for Eastern Avenue Jobcentre's closure will be confirmed.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106231","106231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765832","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of Jobcentre closures on the planned roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106232","106232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765833","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the cost-benefit analysis of Eastern Avenue Jobcentre closure.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106233","106233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765834","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assistance is being provided to staff of jobcentres selected for closure who are unable to relocate to alternative sites and maintain their current working hours due to family commitments.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106234","106234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765835","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of potential risks to staff and other customers of the location of screened rooms in Cavendish Court Jobcentre.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106235","106235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765836","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to make further announcements on funding awards for character education under the character grants programme.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106296","106296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765837","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the causes of the reduction in the number of further applications to ensure adequate numbers of foster carers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105865","105865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765838","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to ensure that the subject focus in the EBacc does not discourage schools from promoting the uptake of creative subjects.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105888","105888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765839","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for the publication of the Government response to the National Fostering Stocktake consultation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105879","105879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765840","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to review support for the Children in Need campaign; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105720","105720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765841","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of extending pupil premium to cover children from overseas adopted in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105719","105719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765842","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of children in the UK who are waiting to be adopted.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105729","105729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765843","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to assess the condition of John Henry Cantlie and to secure his release.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105994","105994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765844","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that landlords do not avoid compliance with the minimum energy standards for rented homes.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105993","105993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765845","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied minors have arrived in the UK under the Vulnerable Children Resettlement Scheme; how many of those minors went into foster care; and how many have been sponsored or hosted by communities.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106316","106316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765846","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that section 41 of the Youth Justice Crime and Evidence Act 1999 which protects victims of alleged rape or sexual assault from being questioned about their sexual history during trial is properly upheld.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106390","106390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765847","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure equality in funding for rail services between the north and south.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105876","105876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765848","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department collects on people whose appeal rights have been exhausted and then become missing.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105718","105718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765849","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of compensating women who have reached state pension age for losses caused by changes introduced in the Pension Acts 1995 and 2011 to their state pensions.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106071","106071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765850","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to achieve equitable transitional state pension arrangements for all women born in the 1950s affected by changes to state pensions introduced buy the Pensions Act 1995 and 2011.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106072","106072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765851","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the equitable distribution of child benefits and tax credits between divorced parents.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105992","105992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765852","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of extending statutory adoption leave to the self-employed.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105717","105717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765853","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to maximise take-up from low-carbon energy sources.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105887","105887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765854","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many family residential centres there are for each court area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106289","106289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765855","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children per court area have been removed from their parents via a care order having (a) had and (b) not had a residential assessment.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106288","106288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765856","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department holds any information on the number of benefit recipients who have (a) monthly contract or (b) pay-as-you-go mobile phones; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106414","106414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765857","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many energy champions have been funded in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106198","106198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765859","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of sanctioned benefits claimants who are (a) illiterate, (b) innumerate and (c) IT illiterate.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105799","105799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765860","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) what the average waiting time is for callers wanting to speak to an advisor calling the 0345 benefit advice line, (b) what the average time is that a caller spends speaking with an advisor and (c) what the average cost is for the caller of such a call.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106196","106196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765861","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support his Department provides to the Third Sector to assist those people seeking benefit advice.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106195","106195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765862","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been put in the employment and support allowance support group after completing a work capability assessment by (a) region, (b) parliamentary constituency and (c) local authority area in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106300","106300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765863","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what percentage of those who are sanctioned are (a) illiterate, (b) innumerate and (c) IT illiterate.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106197","106197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765864","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 7 February 2017, Official Report, column 214, whether the Government plans to introduce (a) a remedial order or (b) an urgent remedial order to allow single parents to apply for parental orders.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106127","106127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765865","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make a statement on surrogacy.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106125","106125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765866","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to review legislation on surrogacy.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106124","106124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765867","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has a serious intention to pursue its request to the Law Commission to include a project on surrogacy in the 13th programme of law reform.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106126","106126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765868","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have applied for a gender recognition certificate in each of the last three years for which figures are available; and how many of the applications have been (a) accepted and (b) refused.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105995","105995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765869","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many gender recognition certificates have been granted to transgender women who posses male genitalia.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105996","105996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765870","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is necessary for a transgender women to have female genitalia in order to receive a gender recognition certificate.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105997","105997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765871","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many freedom of information requests from Mr Giles Sheldrick of the Daily Express are outstanding.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106073","106073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765872","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate he has made of how many serving prisoners are transgender.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106000","106000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765873","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many female to male transgender offenders in the prison system are serving their sentences in male prisons.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105998","105998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765874","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many male to female transgender offenders in the prison system are serving their sentences in female prisons.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105999","105999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765875","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect on GDP of high levels of personal private debt.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105754","105754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765876","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of retail crime to (a) businesses, (b) local authorities and (c) the police in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105751","105751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765877","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of dentistry services by the NHS.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105753","105753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765878","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of raising to 35-years the age threshold of the shared accommodation rates since January 2012.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105755","105755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765879","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with trades union representatives on high temperatures in the workplace.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105756","105756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765880","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the number of Citizens Advice Bureau offices which have closed since 2012-13.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105763","105763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765881","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households in (a) England, (b) Bolton Metropolitan Borough and (c) Bolton North East constituency spend more than 10 per cent of their income on fuel bills.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105752","105752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765882","2017-10-11","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many child tax credit applications by reunited refugee families have been approved through fast track procedures.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105979","105979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765883","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the benefit of using multilateral forums to resolve disagreements with the Government of Mauritius about the Chagos Islands.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105948","105948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765884","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Treasury and HM Revenue and Customs on fast track access to child tax credits for families who have been through the refugee family reunion process.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105980","105980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765885","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that changes in the level of funding for schools do not result in the reduction of pastoral or other child support services.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106054","106054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765886","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support the film industry in (a) the North East and (b) Northumberland.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105952","105952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765887","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has made to the BBC on its gender pay gap.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106055","106055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765888","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in (a) HM Prison Northumberland, (b) the North East and (c) the UK have died by suicide whilst incarcerated in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105953","105953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765889","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for how long a conviction or criminal offence is required to be shown a Disclosure and Barring Service check; and whether children and young people under the age of 18 are required to carry forward convictions into adulthood on such a check.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106056","106056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765890","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current waiting time is for (a) a personal independence payment application to be processed, (b) an appeal against a decision to be actioned and (c) an appointment for a work capability assessment.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105950","105950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765891","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if his Department still plans to complete negotiations on the UK leaving the EU by April 2019.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105951","105951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765892","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assistance the Government is providing to Jewish people seeking to leave Yemen.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106269","106269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765893","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will review the decision not to release any new funding for schools.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105874","105874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765894","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations her Department has received from the Association of School and College Leaders on the new national funding formula.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105875","105875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765895","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when last he had discussions with (a) his Libyan counterpart, (b) the British Ambassador to Libya and (c) the Mayor of Sirte.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106426","106426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765896","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed the UN Human Rights Council Resolution condemning the use of the death penalty as a means of punishment for consensual same-sex relations with (a) his US counterpart and (b) the UK Permanent representative at the UN.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106026","106026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765897","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether a family visit for Andy Tsege has been (a) secured and (b) scheduled.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106027","106027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765898","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the UN and (b) his counterpart in Cyprus on the UN-Cyprus talks.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106024","106024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765899","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to support UN-Cyprus talks.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106025","106025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765900","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her Cypriot counterpart in the Government about its golden visa schemes.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106136","106136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765901","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the operation of the UK Tier 1 investor visa scheme.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106135","106135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765902","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what checks are conducted on those who apply for a UK Tier 1 investor visa.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106134","106134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765903","2017-10-10","Prime Minister","2017-10-06","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions she has had with President Anastasiades; and whether she plans to visit Cyprus in this parliamentary session.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106023","106023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765904","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is providing to Anguilla, British Virgin Islands, Montserrat and the Turks Caicos Islands to repair the damage caused by hurricanes Irma and Maria.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106028","106028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765905","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government's duty to provide assistance to British Overseas Territories is separate to its commitment to meet its UN 0.7 per cent target under the International Development Act 2015.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106020","106020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765906","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to visit Cyprus during the current parliamentary session.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106021","106021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765907","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the Government's policy is on the use of funds intended to meet its UN 0.7 per cent target under the International Development Act 2015 on assistance for British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106416","106416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765908","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his Cypriot counterpart on increasing (a) imports to and (b) exports from Cyprus after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106022","106022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765909","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of psychological support on offer to stem cell transplant patients after they leave hospital.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106240","106240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765910","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on care arrangements for stem cell transplant patients after they leave hospital.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106242","106242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765911","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to clinical nurse specialists for patients recovering from a stem cell transplant.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106241","106241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765912","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to carry out a review of the family courts system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106014","106014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765913","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the transparency of the family courts system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106013","106013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765914","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of the robustness and transparency of the UK's arms export licensing system.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106015","106015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765915","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of measures to prevent the illegal export of electronic waste to developing countries.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105894","105894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765916","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of employment and support allowance and personal independence payment assessments in dealing with issues experienced by those suffering from mental illnesses.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106329","106329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765917","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Myanmar Government on allowing access for human rights observers to Rakhine State.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105749","105749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765918","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with his foreign counterparts on the imposition of sanctions against the Myanmar Government.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105748","105748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765919","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what requirements his Department has set for the re-establishment of military assistance provided by the UK to Myanmar.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106277","106277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765920","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department maintains a list of books and other written materials which have been banned by each prison.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106001","106001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765921","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has provided to prison governors on rules permitting books to be handed on to prisoners.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106002","106002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765922","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders who took part in programmes on drug recovery wings in prisons have reoffended in each year since those wings were introduced.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106263","106263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765923","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that drug users receive (a) suitable accommodation and (b) access to addiction support services after they leave prison.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106254","106254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765924","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the capacity is of drug recovery wings in each prison in which they operate.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106255","106255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765925","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to extend the use of drug recovery wings to prisons that do not have them.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106256","106256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765926","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have taken part in programmes on drug recovery wings in prisons in each year since they were introduced.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106252","106252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765927","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of drug recovery wings on reducing drug addiction in prisons.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106253","106253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765928","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders who took part in programmes on drug recovery wings in prisons have reoffended for drug-related offences in each year since those wings were introduced.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106262","106262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765929","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the speed with which books are passed to prisoners by means of designated providers.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106003","106003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765930","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that prisoners do not face delays in receiving books sent by means of designated providers.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106004","106004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765931","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the ease and speed with which prisons provide books to prisoners.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106005","106005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765932","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what funding his Department provides to assist offenders who have taken part in programmes on drug recovery wings in prisons after their release.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106257","106257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765933","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have taken part in programmes on drug recovery wings, by offence.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106258","106258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765934","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what non-financial support is provided to offenders taking part in programmes on drug recovery wings in prisons upon release.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106260","106260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765935","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders who took part in programmes on drug recovery wings in prisons have reoffended for burglary in each year since those wings were introduced.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106261","106261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765936","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders who took part in programmes on drug recovery wings in prisons were serving sentences of (a) less than six months, (b) six to 12 months, (c) 12 months to two years and (d) more than two years.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106259","106259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765937","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposals for smart ticketing for public transport in the North on the number of station staff employed in that region.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106279","106279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765938","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to guarantee interoperability between smart ticketing systems for public transport provided by different franchise operators.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106280","106280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765939","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what financial contribution his Department expects local government and private business to make towards the introduction of smart ticketing for public transport in the North.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106281","106281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765940","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in which regions smart ticketing for public transport in the North will be introduced during (a) a trial period and (b) full roll-out.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106282","106282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765941","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department plans to spend on introducing smart ticketing for public transport in the North.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106285","106285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765942","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of rolling out smart ticketing for public transport in the North.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106283","106283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765943","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of smart ticketing on the number of journeys undertaken on public transport in the North.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106284","106284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765944","2017-10-10","Department for International Trade","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the value was of trade between the UK and Myanmar in each year from 2008.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106278","106278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765945","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on introducing a new statutory entitlement to carer's leave for working people.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105863","105863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765947","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for the publication of the responses to the call for views by the Intellectual Property Office on IPTV set-top boxes.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106175","106175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765948","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the National Health Service (Charges to Overseas Visitors) (Amendment) Regulations 2017 on public health.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105932","105932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765949","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what requirements she has placed on the NHS to report on patients' immigration status.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105896","105896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765950","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to extend the Immigration Skills charge to EU citizens when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106290","106290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765951","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of up-front charges for healthcare on people not seeking early medical help due to their immigration status or the cost of healthcare.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106403","106403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765952","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason her Department has started contacting asylum seekers asking them to sign a consent form that would give her Department access to their personal medical records.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106402","106402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765953","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to introduce minimum unit pricing for alcohol sales to reduce the effects of cheap alcohol on public health and crime levels.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106096","106096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765954","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs has the discretion to reimburse the Roadchef Employee Benefits Trust's fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106294","106294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765955","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) how many extradition requests have been made, (b) how many of those have been refused and (c) what the cost to the public purse for legal aid is for such requests made by the UAE in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106085","106085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765956","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy and (b) Scottish Government on tackling problems with tumble dryer safety in Scotland.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106293","106293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765957","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to reduce the drink-drive limit to 50mg.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106315","106315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765958","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the report by STOPAIDS entitled A Stocktake Review of DFID's Work on HIV and AIDS, published in September 2017.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106030","106030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765959","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department monitors and assesses the effectiveness of HIV and AIDS awareness campaigns and training as part of their integration into wider health programmes funded by her Department; and how her Department measures reducing the incidence of HIV and AIDS.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106295","106295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765960","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps have been taken since the Westminster Hall debate on faulty electrical imports in March 2016 to review consumer protection against internet sales of faulty or counterfeit mobile telephone chargers, tablets and similar goods.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106380","106380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765961","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on (a) regulating the import of electrical goods such as mobile phone chargers and (b) consumer protection and redress with trading partners for faulty of sub-standard goods after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106095","106095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765962","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to remove the process of constraint payments whereby wind turbine operators are recompensed at times of surplus generation and attempted stabilisation of the grid.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106308","106308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765963","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many full-time disabled students were registered on higher education courses in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106239","106239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765964","2017-10-11","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the level of geographical variation of IVF funding; and whether it is his Department's policy that clinical commissioning groups implement NICE recommendations to commission funding for three cycles of IVF.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106243","106243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765965","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy of 12 September 2017, Official Report, column 635, if he will provide an update on the Government's monitoring of the effect on human health of wind turbine low-frequency sound and infrasound; and what assessment his Department has made of those findings.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106244","106244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765966","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on raising the threshold for repayment of student loans for graduates who started their course before 2012.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106238","106238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765967","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding has been allocated from the public purse to local authorities to support steps to establish air quality plans.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106213","106213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765968","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any funding has been allocated from the public purse to support Sheffield Council in establishing its air quality plans.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106214","106214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765969","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department plans to provide to schools in areas of high air pollution hotspots to help them protect children's health.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106215","106215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765970","2017-10-11","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of arrears identified by national minimum wage investigations in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17 have been subsequently repaid to workers to whom they are owed.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106370","106370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765971","2017-10-11","Women and Equalities","2017-10-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2017 to Question 6824, when the Government Equalities Office next plans to update her on reports of discrimination against non-UK EU nationals seeking employment.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105981","105981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765972","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will place in the Library copies of written evidence submitted to the Taylor review of modern working practices published on 11 July 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106151","106151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765973","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many meetings were held by officials of his Department on the Taylor review of modern working practices between 30 November 2016 and 11 July 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106377","106377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765974","2017-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the cost to the public purse was of the Taylor review of modern working practices.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106376","106376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765975","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the promotion of credit unions as an alternative to pay day lenders.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105873","105873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765976","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the Government is promoting the uptake of the tax-free childcare scheme to workers and parents in (a) the UK and (b) East Renfrewshire.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105869","105869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765977","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what joint working the Government is undertaking with the Scottish Government to promote racial tolerance and interfaith dialogue.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106206","106206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765978","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of post office counter services on vulnerable older customers; and what alternatives are available to those customers.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105870","105870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765979","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how (a) many employers in East Renfrewshire signed up to the Disability Confident Scheme and (b) that scheme is promoted to employers.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105868","105868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765980","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many East Renfrewshire residents (a) are eligible to receive and (b) claim pension credit.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105867","105867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765981","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when officials of his Department last met representatives of the Post Office to discuss the provision of local post offices.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105872","105872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765982","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on the retention of local post office services in East Renfrewshire.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105871","105871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765983","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has given assistance to British American Tobacco in its challenge to the claim for unpaid VAT brought against it by the Government of Bangladesh; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105750","105750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765984","2017-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Law Commission on including a review of whether the UK's corporate laws are fit for purpose in its 13th programme of law reform.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106310","106310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765985","2017-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many times he has visited (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland since his appointment as Secretary of State.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106149","106149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765986","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what percentage of Child Support Agency Arrears are deemed uncollectable in (a) Aberdeen City (b) Aberdeenshire and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106321","106321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765987","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle constituency who have received trans vaginal mesh implants as part of their treatment for (a) pelvic organ prolapse repair or (b) stress urinary incontinence attend clinics for pain caused by that treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106031","106031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765988","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle constituency have received trans vaginal mesh implants as part of their treatment for (a) pelvic organ prolapse repair and (b) stress urinary incontinence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106032","106032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765989","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2017 to Question 3811, how much of her Department's budget allocated to 16 to 19-year old education was reallocated to other budgets in the financial year 2016-17.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106098","106098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765990","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the costs of the renewal of the Trident submarine programme (a) with and (b) without (i) construction of the Hinkley Point C nuclear power station and (ii) the full projected 18 GWe UK civil nuclear power new build programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105861","105861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765991","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on monitoring the contribution of UK personnel, intelligence and assets including British bases to US-led counter-terror operations that result in casualties.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106342","106342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765992","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether an estimate has been made of how many people have been killed in UK counter-terror operations outside of armed conflict since January 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106340","106340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765993","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many casualties have occurred as a result of joint US-UK counter-terror activities in Yemen since January 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106341","106341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765994","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK personnel, intelligence, or assets including British bases were used in US raids which took place in the Yemeni villages of Yakla and Al Jubah in January and May 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106343","106343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765995","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on reports that the US is adopting new standards relating to the use of force outside of armed conflict.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106344","106344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765996","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will provide breakdowns of UK (a) exports to and (b) imports from the top five countries, as published in HM Revenue and Customs' Overseas Trade Statistics for each month since June 2012 adjusted to remove exports and imports of non-monetary gold from the data.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106286","106286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765997","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the GP to patient ratio for (a) Brighton and Hove Clinical Commissioning Group, (b) other clinical commissioning groups and (c) the UK; what recent assessment he has made of the safe ratio of patients to doctors in GP practices; what steps he is taking to increase the number of GPs in Brighton and Hove; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106089","106089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765998","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to immediately take steps to prepare for a publicly-owned organisation to take over the Govia Thameslink Railway franchise on an agreed date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105831","105831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/765999","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on the implications of the section entitled Advantages to the UK's nuclear deterrent programme on page 22 of the Rolls Royce document UK SMR: A National Endeavour; what information his Department holds on the relevance of the UK's civil nuclear programme to the UK's naval nuclear weapons programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106041","106041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766000","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications made by transgender prisoners for transfer to a prison of their chosen gender have been approved since the provisions of the Equality Act 2010 relating to gender reassignment came into force.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106216","106216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766001","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to monitor proper and effective implementation of section 41 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999 in sexual violence cases.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106412","106412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766002","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to tackle the involvement of sex trafficking in the sex and prostitution industries; what assessment she has made of regional disparities in the quantom of that involvement; and what steps she is taking to help protect female sex workers.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106413","106413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766003","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, at what time of the day the main use of electricity in domestic homes was by (a) day and (b) month in 2015-16.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106410","106410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766004","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that suppliers of second-hand electrical goods do not sell unsafe electrical goods.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106411","106411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766005","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much electricity was consumed in each month in 2015-16.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106271","106271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766006","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will guarantee a six year funding period for the Shared Prosperity Fund to provide disadvantaged communities with funding equivalent in real-terms to that currently provided by means of the European Social Fund.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106033","106033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766007","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the UK can maintain access to EU data, intelligence, training, research and security infrastructure for the purposes of child protection.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106081","106081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766008","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether children and young people resident in the UK are able to apply for settled status in their own right.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106080","106080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766009","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has set performance targets to expedite the advanced assurance application process for social investment tax relief.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106230","106230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766010","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many social investment tax relief advanced assurance applications are pending.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106228","106228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766011","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how long on average it takes his Department to process advanced assurance applications for social investment tax relief.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106229","106229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766012","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how long on average it takes his Department to process advanced assurance applications to the Enterprise Investment Scheme.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106227","106227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766013","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate access to private rented housing for homeless people.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106226","106226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766014","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measures are available to support those with limited (a) mental capacity, (b) literacy or (c) language skills to apply for universal credit on line.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105807","105807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766015","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to respond to the report published on 6 September 2017 by the Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs entitled Commissioning impact on drug treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105811","105811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766016","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the implications for her policies are of the Office for National Statistics' statistical bulletin entitled Deaths related to drug poisoning in England and Wales: 2016 registrations, published in August 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105812","105812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766017","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons National Savings and Investments is closing applications to new customers for its five-year children's bonds.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105741","105741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766018","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to introduce a saving scheme to enable grandparents to save for their grandchildren.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105740","105740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766019","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what preparations his Department has made to replicate the relevant functions of  the European Food Safety Authority after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106118","106118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766020","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the cost to the public purse of replicating the relevant functions of the European Environment Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106119","106119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766021","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the number of staff required to replicate the relevant functions of the European Chemicals Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106114","106114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766022","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to replicate the relevant functions of the European Chemicals Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106115","106115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766023","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the cost to the public purse of replicating the relevant functions of the European Food Safety Authority after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106116","106116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766024","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the number of staff required to replicate the relevant functions of the European Food Safety Authority after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106117","106117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766025","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the cost to the public purse of replicating the relevant functions of the European Chemicals Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106113","106113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766026","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the number of staff required to replicate the relevant functions of the European Environment Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106106","106106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766027","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of replicating the relevant functions of the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106100","106100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766028","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the number of staff required to replicate the relevant functions of the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106101","106101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766029","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of replicating the relevant functions of the European Medicines Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106103","106103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766030","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what preparations his Department has made to replicate the relevant functions of the European Medicines Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106105","106105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766031","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the number of staff required to replicate the relevant functions of the European Medicines Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106104","106104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766032","2017-10-10","Department of Health","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what preparations his Department has made to replicate the relevant functions of the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106102","106102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766033","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the length of queues at the Port of Dover.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106084","106084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766034","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of replicating the relevant functions of the European Maritime Safety Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106107","106107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766035","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of replicating the relevant functions of the European Aviation Safety Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106108","106108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766036","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the number of staff required to replicate the relevant functions of the European Aviation Safety Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106109","106109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766037","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to replicate the relevant functions of the European Aviation Safety Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106110","106110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766038","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the number of staff required to replicate the relevant functions of the European Maritime Safety Agency after the UK leaves the EU","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106111","106111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766039","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to replicate the relevant functions of the European Maritime Safety Agency after the UK leaves the EU","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106112","106112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766040","2017-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applicants for universal credit have requested split payments on (a) any grounds and (b) the grounds of domestic abuse since the launch of universal credit in the pilot areas; and what proportion of the total number of applicants have so requested such split payments in each category.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106034","106034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766041","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent representations he has made to coalition partners on trends in the number of civilian deaths caused by coalition airstrikes.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106006","106006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766042","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the number of civilians killed by coalition airstrikes in Syria.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106007","106007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766043","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the number of civilians killed by UK airstrikes in Syria.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106008","106008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766044","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many applicants for wind farm accreditation between July and October 2016 were on request accordingly afforded an extension of time or grace period by Ofgem to allow for successful conversion to full accreditation.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106076","106076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766045","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many certificated G59 commissioning engineers who were not embedded within power supply companies and district network operations were available to sign off wind farm accreditation between July and November 2016.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106077","106077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766046","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many unsuccessful applications for full onshore wind farm accreditation there were between July and October 2016.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106075","106075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766047","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many applicants for full onshore wind farm accreditation there were between July and October 2016.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106074","106074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766048","2017-10-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's policy is on a ban on the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106440","106440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766049","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the Government decided to locate the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre on none of the sites recommended in the Prime Minister's Holocaust Commission report of January 2015; which organisations were consulted before the decision was made to use none of those sites; and what sites were considered after that decision was taken.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106036","106036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766050","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what cost estimates underlay the decision to allocate 50 million of public funds towards the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre; and whether funding is also to be raised from non-government sources.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106189","106189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766051","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what date Victoria Tower Gardens was first considered by the Government as a possible site for the Holocaust Memorial; and by whom that proposal was made.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106178","106178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766052","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation was formed; what resources were used to create that foundation; and how much funding that foundation has received from the public purse to date.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106188","106188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766053","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what dates the Government decided that the (a) Holocaust Memorial and (b) Holocaust Learning Centre would be located in Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106179","106179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766054","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment the Government has made of the compatibility of locating the proposed Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens with the requirements for space for works and parking at the south end of the Palace of Westminster during the  Restoration and Renewal programme; and what guidance has been received from the authorities in both Houses of Parliament on that matter.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106190","106190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766055","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the Government did not hold a public consultation on the proposal to locate the Holocaust Memorial and Holocaust Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens before making its decision.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106180","106180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766056","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what dates the Royal Parks agency was informed that Victoria Tower Gardens (a) was being considered and (b) had been chosen as a site for the Holocaust Memorial; and on what date the Royal Parks agency was informed that the Holocaust Learning Centre would also be located in those gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106181","106181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766057","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment the Government has made of the compatibility of locating the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens with maintaining the present level of security at the Palace of Westminster.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106191","106191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766058","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government obtained advice on the security implications for the Palace of Westminster before deciding to locate the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106192","106192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766059","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Government has made of the annual cost of maintenance and security for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens after construction; and which organisation will bear those costs.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106193","106193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766060","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations the Government has received from the Royal Parks agency's (a) Board and (b) officials on the plan to site the Holocaust Memorial and Holocaust Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106182","106182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766061","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Government made (a) prior to and (b) after making the decision to locate the Holocaust Memorial and Holocaust Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens of the (i) number of visitors per year and (ii) volume of additional road traffic.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106183","106183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766062","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions the Government has had with Westminster City Council on the proposal to locate the Holocaust Memorial in Victoria Tower Gardens (a) before the site was announced and (b) subsequently; and on what dates those discussions were held.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106184","106184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766063","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment the Government has made of the compatibility  of the planned Holocaust Memorial in Victoria Tower Gardens with Westminster City Council's statues and monuments policy; and when that policy was first brought to the attention of the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106185","106185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766064","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment the Government has made of the compatibility of the planned Holocaust Memorial in Victoria Tower Gardens with the Royal Parks' memorials policy.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106186","106186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766065","2017-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions the Government had with Historic England on the proposal to build the Holocaust Memorial and Holocaust Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens (a) before the site was announced and (b) subsequently; on what dates those discussions were held; and what observations Historic England has made of that proposal.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106187","106187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766066","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the Government's Overseas Justice and Security Assistance guidelines are being applied consistently across government.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106396","106396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766067","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the Joint Doctrine Publication, entitled UK Joint Targeting Policy, on the Departmental website.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106064","106064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766068","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Departmental policy, as outlined in Joint Doctrine Publication 0-30.2 unmanned aircraft systems of August 2017 includes targeting conducted (a) jointly by the different armed forces or (b) with allied nations.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106065","106065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766069","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Departmental policy, as outlined in Joint Doctrine Publication 0-30.2 unmanned aircraft systems of August 2017 applies to strikes outside of war zones.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106066","106066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766070","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made on the effectiveness of its implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105778","105778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766071","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to publish how it ensures the adequate implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105785","105785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766072","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure its provision of overseas assistance is in accordance with the Government's human rights obligations.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105786","105786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766073","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department received on its implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105780","105780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766074","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments his Department has made in the last three calendar years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105791","105791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766075","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for which countries his Department has made Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments in the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105768","105768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766076","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what representations he has received from the food and drink sector on the creation of an equivalent definition to Regulation 178/2002 on market placement during negotiations with the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106417","106417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766077","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the creation of an equivalent definition to Regulation 178/2002 on market placement during negotiations with the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106418","106418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766078","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Scotland on the creation of an equivalent definition to Regulation 178/2002 on market placement during negotiations with the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106419","106419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766079","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what assessment he has made of the economic effect on industry of negotiations with the EU not resulting in the creation of an equivalent definition to Regulation 178/2002 on market placement.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106420","106420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766080","2017-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what plans he has to support industry in the event that negotiations with the EU do not result in the creation of an equivalent definition to Regulation 178/2002 on market placement.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106421","106421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766081","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK: Position Paper, published on 21 August 2017, whether it is his policy that EU compliance responsible persons in UK private sector companies must be EU-based; and what assessment his Department has made on the effect of such a policy on employment levels.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106422","106422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766082","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of its implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105774","105774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766083","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to publish how it ensures the adequate implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105787","105787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766084","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received on its implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105773","105773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766085","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure its provision of overseas assistance is in accordance with the Government's human rights obligations.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105770","105770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766086","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments his Department has made in the last three calendar years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105771","105771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766087","2017-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for which countries his Department has made Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments in the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105772","105772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766088","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the position paper, Confidentiality and Access to Documents, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions the Government has had with the Scottish Government on the handling by the EU of information produced while the UK was an EU member state after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105889","105889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766089","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the status of British National Overseas passport holders in EU member states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105897","105897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766090","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many British National Overseas passports have been issued in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105898","105898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766091","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many British National Overseas passport holders are resident in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) other EU member states, (d) Hong Kong and (e) the People's Republic of China.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105900","105900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766092","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many valid British National Overseas passports are currently in issue.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105901","105901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766093","2017-10-11","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of refugees and asylum seekers who have died as a result of suicide or who have attempted suicide while in the process of being deported from the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105976","105976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766094","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations her Department has received on its implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105781","105781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766095","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, for which countries her Department has made Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments in the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105782","105782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766096","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments her Department has made in the last three calendar years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105783","105783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766097","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to publish how it ensures the adequate implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105788","105788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766098","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure its provision of overseas assistance is in accordance with the Government's human rights obligations.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105789","105789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766099","2017-10-10","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of its implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105790","105790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766100","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership, published on 24 August 2017, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Scotland on the proposed UK-EU model for exchanging and protecting personal data.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106398","106398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766101","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure its provision of overseas assistance is in accordance with the Government's human rights obligations.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105769","105769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766102","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of its implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105784","105784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766103","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations her Department has received on its implementation of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105779","105779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766104","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to publish how it ensures the adequate implementation of the Overseas Security Justice Assistance framework.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105777","105777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766105","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments her Department has made in the last three calendar years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105775","105775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766106","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for which countries her Department has made Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessments in the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105776","105776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766107","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, whether it is her policy to maintain the UK's alignment with EU data protection law after the UK leaves the EU irrespective of how EU data protection law changes in the future.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106394","106394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766108","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, whether it is her policy to secure a UK-EU model for exchanging and protecting personal data which can not in the future be declared invalid by the European Court of Justice.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106391","106391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766109","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, what discussions the Government has had with the Scottish Government on the proposed UK-EU model for exchanging and protecting personal data.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106397","106397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766110","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on UK GDP of UK-EU data flows being disrupted by the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106385","106385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766111","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, what plans her Department has made to address the effect on UK GDP of UK-EU data flows being disrupted by the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106386","106386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766112","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, what representations the Government (a) has made and (b) received from EU data protection adequate countries on retaining free data transference between those countries and the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106388","106388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766113","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, what economic assessment the Government has made on the removal of free data transference between the UK and EU data protection adequate countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106389","106389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766114","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, whether the Government plans to grant all third counties designated by the EU as data protection adequate the same status from the UK; and on what basis such a decision will be made.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106392","106392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766115","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, what plans her Department has to keep UK data protection rules aligned with those of the EU following withdrawal beyond Convention 108.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106393","106393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766116","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, what plans the Government has to support industry in the event of the removal of free data transference between the UK and EU data protection adequate countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106395","106395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766117","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, what economic assessment has been made of the effect on UK firms and consumers of negotiations with the EU failing to provide a UK-EU model for exchanging and protecting personal data.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106384","106384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766118","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, what representations she has received from civil society organisations on the proposed UK-EU model for exchanging and protecting personal data.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106382","106382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766119","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what formal role he plans to give to the devolved administrations during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU on the matter of continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105910","105910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766120","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what formal role he plans to give to the overseas territories during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU on the matter of continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105911","105911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766121","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what formal role he plans to give to the Crown Dependencies during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU on the matter of continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105912","105912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766122","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the position paper, Confidentiality and Access to Documents, published on 21 August 2017, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of EU institutions refusing to provide guarantees on the use by the EU of information produced while the UK was an EU member state after the UK leaves the EU in the event that there is no deal.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105890","105890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766123","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the position paper, Confidentiality and Access to Documents, published on 21 August 2017, what representations the Government has made to EU member states on the handling by the EU of information produced while the UK was an EU member state after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105891","105891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766124","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the position paper, Confidentiality and Access to Documents, published on 21 August 2017, what contingency planning there has been in the event that EU institutions refuse to provide guarantees about the use by the EU of information produced while the UK was an EU member state after the UK leaves the EU in the event that there is no deal.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105892","105892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766125","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the position paper, Confidentiality and Access to Documents, published on 21 August 2017, what representations the Government has received from civil society on the handling by the EU of information produced while the UK was an EU member state after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105893","105893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766126","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has through negotiations with the EU to ensure that British National Overseas passport holders continue to hold the same rights as they do now after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105899","105899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766127","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what representations he has made to other EU member states on the contents of that position paper.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105907","105907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766128","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what assessment his Department has made of the economic effect of potential trade frictions in the event that the Government fails to reach an agreement during negotiations with the EU on continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105908","105908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766129","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what plans his Department has made to support UK industry in the event that the Government fails to reach an agreement during its negotiations with the EU on continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105909","105909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766130","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Scotland on the withdrawal agreement with the EU potentially resulting in the invalidity of EU compliance activities before withdrawal day for goods placed on the market after withdrawal day.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105919","105919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766131","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the withdrawal agreement with the EU potentially resulting in the invalidity of EU compliance activities before withdrawal day for goods placed on the market after withdrawal day.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105920","105920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766132","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what representations he has received from industry on the withdrawal agreement with the EU potentially resulting in the invalidity of EU compliance activities before withdrawal day for goods placed on the market after withdrawal day.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105921","105921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766133","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what representations he has received from trade unions on the withdrawal agreement with the EU potentially resulting in the invalidity of EU compliance activities before withdrawal day for goods placed on the market after withdrawal day.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105922","105922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766134","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, if his Department will set out the possible issues affecting the continuity of service provision at the point of exit which would result in economic disruption.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105923","105923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766135","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what economic assessment he has made of the effect on industry in the event that the withdrawal agreement with the EU results in the invalidity of EU compliance activities before withdrawal day for goods placed on the market after withdrawal day.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105917","105917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766136","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK, published on 21 August 2017, what plans he has to support industry in the event that the withdrawal agreement with the EU results in the invalidity of EU compliance activities before withdrawal day for goods placed on the market after withdrawal day.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105918","105918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766137","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Scotland on the contents of that position paper.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105902","105902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766138","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the contents of that position paper.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105903","105903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766139","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions he has had with representatives of Scottish industry on the contents of that position paper.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105904","105904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766140","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions he has had with representatives of trades unions in Scotland on the contents of that position paper.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105905","105905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766141","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what discussions he has had with other EU member states on the contents of that position paper.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105906","105906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766142","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, whether it is the Government's policy to allow EU institutions oversight over the Government's proposals to ensure continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the UK; and whether it is the Government's policy to have such arrangements fall within the jurisdiction of the European Court of Justice.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105915","105915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766143","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what assessment his Department has made of the potential economic effect on UK businesses of their compliance activities having to be duplicated in the EU as a result of the outcome of negotiations with the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105913","105913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766144","2017-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the position paper, Continuity in the availability of goods for the EU and the EU, published on 21 August 2017, what plans his Department has to support industry in the event that UK businesses' compliance activities have to be duplicated in the EU as a result of the outcome of negotiations with the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105914","105914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766145","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, whether he plans to use negotiations with the EU to retain the UK's ability to shape the future direction of EU data protection law.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106387","106387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766146","2017-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the policy paper, The exchange and protection of personal data: a future partnership paper, published on 24 August 2017, whether it is his policy to refrain from entering any UK-EU model for exchanging and protecting personal data if the framework requires oversight from the European Court of Justice.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106383","106383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766147","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 9663, if he will set out the measures that his Department has implemented to improve access to benefits and employment for former members of the armed services.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105983","105983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766148","2017-10-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2017 to Question HL1415, when the report of the working group on electrical safety in the private rented sector will be published.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105975","105975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766149","2017-10-11","Department for International Development","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the work of Robert Carr Civil Society Networks Fund.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106174","106174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766150","2017-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on a formal appeal process for decisions on early advances for universal credit.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105991","105991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766151","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she expects the Residential Care Leadership Board to report on progress in implementing Sir Martin Narey's recommendations in his report Residential Care in England.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106317","106317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766152","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2017 to Question 6504, what assessment she has made of the reasons why the number of looked after children placed in care homes, secure units and hostels outside their council boundary in England increased from 2,610 in March 2012 to 4,020 in March 2016.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106132","106132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766153","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2017 to Question 6504, what assessment she has made of the reasons why 50 per cent of looked after children who are reported missing are children placed in residential accommodation.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106133","106133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766154","2017-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 9902, on Witnesses: Video Recordings, which courts will be in the first phase of the rollout nationally of section 28 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999 in Autumn 2017.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106318","106318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766155","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department collects on the nationality of people spot-checked by immigration officers and subsequently (a) arrested and (b) not arrested.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105809","105809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766156","2017-10-10","Department for Education","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department hold on how much and what proportion of outstanding student loan debt owed by students attributable to tuition fee payments.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105792","105792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766157","2017-10-10","HM Treasury","2017-10-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether trainee clinical psychologists are eligible for tax and national insurance relief under the NHS Widening Access Training scheme.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106220","106220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766158","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to prevent the illegal trapping of migratory songbirds in sovereign base areas of Cyprus.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105956","105956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766159","2017-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) global and (b) per capita spend from his Department's Regional Expenditure with the UK Industry and Commerce and Supported Employment for 2015-16 is with spend on the construction of aircraft carriers excluded.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106209","106209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766160","2017-10-10","Home Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to respond to the House of Lords Select Committee's post-legislative scrutiny report on the Licensing Act 2003, published on 4 April 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106287","106287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766161","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the costs were to the public purse of his recent visits to (a) Paraguay and (b) Argentina, by heading.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106265","106265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766162","2017-10-10","Scotland Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the costs to the public purse of his visits to Singapore and Myanmar were, by heading.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106268","106268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766163","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the expected response time is of a coastguard search and rescue helicopter to an incident in the Firth of Forth.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106273","106273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766164","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fatalities occurred around the UK coastline in each of the last five years to which coastguard services were called.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106274","106274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766165","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to review the location and number of HM Coastguard (a) employees and (b) search and rescue helicopters serving the Firth of Forth and south-east Scotland.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106276","106276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766166","2017-10-10","Department for Transport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many incidents in the Firth of Forth required a response from coastguard services in the last three years; and what the time was from callout to arrival for each incident.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106275","106275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766167","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many businesses have benefited from the Better Broadband Scheme in (a) Scotland and (b) each local authority area.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106140","106140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766168","2017-10-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of EU workers in the technology, culture and heritage sectors classed as low skilled.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106303","106303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766169","2017-10-11","Wales Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will take steps to place in the Library an estimate of the number of non-UK EU citizens employed by each sector in Wales.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105965","105965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/766170","2017-10-11","Wales Office","2017-10-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on its proposed changes to the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105964","105964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760620","2017-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data the UK Statistics Authority holds on the level of (a) poverty and (b) in-work poverty in Hemsworth constituency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105073","105073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760621","2017-10-09","Cabinet Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to facilitate whistleblowing in his Department and its arm-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105075","105075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760622","2017-10-09","Cabinet Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2017 to Question 8205, on Government Departments: buildings, what the total cost to the public purse is of the move to 10 South Colonade; and what estimate he has made of savings in property costs of that move in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105078","105078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760623","2017-10-09","Cabinet Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect on UK data privacy legislation of not incorporating into UK law, Article 8 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105171","105171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760624","2017-10-09","Cabinet Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings he has had with the Government Chief Scientific Adviser in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105176","105176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760625","2017-10-09","Cabinet Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward proposals to provide for the appointment of sub-agents at any future national referendum.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105239","105239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760626","2017-10-09","Cabinet Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward proposals to extend the option for candidates to restrict publication of their home address to all polls.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105240","105240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760627","2017-10-09","Cabinet Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 7591, on civil servants: recruitment, whether any workers or firms from outside the Government have been involved in any of the work surrounding the pilots.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105236","105236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760628","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to base customs officials in Scotland after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105159","105159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760629","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employees received national insurance relief for employment allowance in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105169","105169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760630","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to appoint a Chief Scientific Adviser.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105178","105178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760631","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much VAT has been refunded to visitors to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105217","105217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760632","2017-10-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the role of Companies House is in combatting money laundering.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105218","105218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760633","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much and to who the annual tax reliefs have been granted under the Patent-Box scheme.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105219","105219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760634","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on employers of increasing the immigration skills charge levied on migrant workers.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105096","105096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760635","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department will appoint a Chief Science Adviser.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105128","105128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760636","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consideration the Government has given to bringing forward legislative proposals to protect customers who use payment initiation services under the revised Payment Services Directive in the event that a product ordered online does not (a) arrive or (b) meet the customer's expectations.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105118","105118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760637","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has to allow HM Opposition access to the Office for Budget Responsibility.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105133","105133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760638","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the cost to the Exchequer of removing the public sector pay cap.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105134","105134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760639","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to end the public sector pay cap for (a) firefighters, (b) police, (c) teachers, (d) nurses and (e) doctors.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105071","105071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760640","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether social rents will revert to the previously agreed settlement of Consumer Price Index plus one per cent from 1 April 2020.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105097","105097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760641","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of landlords in each local authority area who are registered for self-assessment with HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105116","105116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760642","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make a statement about the outcomes of HM Revenue and Customs' Let Property Campaign to date and the plans for the Let Property Campaign until 2020.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105117","105117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760643","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which local authorities in England share the names and addresses of landlords with HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105115","105115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760644","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to allow local authorities to keep more than 30 per cent of the money generated from the sale of a council home under the Right to Buy scheme to help fund the building of replacement homes.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105080","105080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760645","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the replacement rate of social housing stock sold under Right to Buy since 2012.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105081","105081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760646","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will take steps to assist residential leaseholders whose ground rents have risen substantially.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105084","105084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760647","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in his Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105202","105202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760648","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2017 to Question 7880, what steps his Department takes to assess what proportion of prospective tenants receive information as to (a) whether an energy certificate has been acquired and (b) what rating the property they are considering renting or leasing has been given; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105187","105187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760649","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether an election will take place in 2018 to elect a Mayor for the Sheffield City Region.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105136","105136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760650","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that local housing authorities make homeless families aware that they are (a) entitled to compensation if they are unlawfully placed in bed and breakfast accommodation for longer than six weeks and (b) able to escalate a formal complaint to the Local Government Ombudsman in the event that such financial redress is not offered in compensation.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105186","105186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760651","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that the Local Government Ombudsman publishes details of compensation award guidance in cases where homeless families are unlawfully placed in bed and breakfast accommodation for more than six weeks.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105185","105185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760652","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he or officials of his Department first consulted (a) local authorities and (b) software suppliers on the implementation timetable changes to business rates and business rates relief in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105160","105160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760653","2017-10-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on the intended start time for the six-week period specified in the Homelessness (Suitability of Accommodation)(England) Order 2003 (No.3326) in respect of the date on which (a) a homeless family accepts a placement in bed and breakfast and (b) that family moves into that accommodation.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105243","105243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760654","2017-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to appoint a Chief Scientific Adviser.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105175","105175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760655","2017-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the merits of allocating funding from the Government and Heritage Lottery Fund to commemorate Hedd Wynn in Ceredigion as part of the Government's First World War commemorations programme.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105110","105110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760656","2017-10-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which projects are receiving funding from the Government and Heritage Lottery Fund to commemorate the centenary of the First World War.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105111","105111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760657","2017-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role shipyards in Jarrow will play in the National Shipbuilding Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105072","105072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760658","2017-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department will appoint a Chief Science Advisor.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105120","105120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760659","2017-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total salary commitment of each service of the armed forces is by country and region.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105100","105100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760660","2017-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, whether and how National Security Objective 3 is taken into account in single-source procurements.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105139","105139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760661","2017-10-09","Cabinet Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to review the Government's redactions of the Intelligence and Security Committee's April 2017 UK Lethal Drone Strikes in Syria report; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105094","105094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760662","2017-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Royal Navy's decision to withdraw the Harpoon anti-ship missile by the end of 2018 on the capabilities of the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105167","105167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760663","2017-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, what weight is attached to National Security Objective 3 in the marking criteria for competitive procurements.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105137","105137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760664","2017-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, whether National Security Objective 3 applies to all competitive procurements.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105138","105138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760665","2017-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel are deployed in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105188","105188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760666","2017-10-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to appoint a Chief Scientific Adviser.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105179","105179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760667","2017-10-09","Department for International Trade","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what information his Department receives on the end use of UK arms exports.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105242","105242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760668","2017-10-09","Department for Education","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings (a) she and (b) Ministers of her Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in her Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105203","105203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760669","2017-10-09","HM Treasury","2017-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether universities will have access to European Investment Bank loans to finance large-scale innovative projects after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105108","105108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760670","2017-10-09","Department for Education","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the Department's definition is of a children's centre linked site.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105083","105083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760671","2017-10-09","Department for Education","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children's centre linked sites there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105082","105082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760672","2017-10-09","Department for Education","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the new school funding formula on the level of funding for each school in Jarrow constituency.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105069","105069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760673","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to ensure that EU nationals applying for a place on a UK university course will not face additional migration barriers throughout any transitional period after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105074","105074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760674","2017-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in his Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105204","105204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760675","2017-10-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimates he has made of the costs to the recreational bass fishery of recent conservation measures affecting sea anglers.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105168","105168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760676","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which departments contributed to the 32 million allocated to relief and support following Hurricane Irma; and how much each such Department contributed to that sum.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105158","105158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760677","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of further financial support which will be required in the current financial year by British Overseas Territories following Hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105157","105157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760678","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what EU sanctions the UK is applying to (a) Venezuela or (b) Venezuelan citizens.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105163","105163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760679","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 4381, what events his Department is supporting in Africa to commemorate contribution of African soldiers to the First World War.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105161","105161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760680","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the 32 million allocated to relief and support following Hurricane Irma will be spent.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105172","105172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760681","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8242, on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: arms length external organisations, what the timetable is for the estimate of the number of arms-lengths bodies that will be established after the UK leaves the EU to be made and published.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105200","105200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760682","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in his Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105205","105205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760683","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will undertake an assessment of the effectiveness of the Government's response to Hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105089","105089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760684","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to publish an assessment of the reconstruction needs of British Overseas Territories affected by Hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105092","105092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760685","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Malaysia on that government's treatment of atheists and apostates.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105105","105105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760686","2017-10-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking  to help de-escalate the conflict in Yemen; and whether the Government supports a UN-led independent investigation into alleged violations of human rights by all sides of that conflict.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105107","105107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760687","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has plans to introduce an opt-out system for organ donation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105088","105088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760688","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracted units of dental activity were not delivered through National Health Service dental contracts in England in each year from 2012 to 2017.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105149","105149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760689","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2017 to question 8038, how many and what proportion of (a) permanent staff, (b) contractors and (c) agency staff who have worked in his Department for more than three months have completed the Responsible for Information training course.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105077","105077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760690","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the forecast year-end position of (a) Alder Hey and (b) Merseycare is in 2017-18; whether NHS England or any other funding body provide financial support to (i) Alder Hey and (ii) Merseycare to help those organisations manage underlying financial pressures; what plans those organisations have to manage such pressures; and how much cash those organisations currently hold.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105141","105141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760691","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount spent by (a) Alder Hey and (b) Merseycare on the bid to run Liverpool Community Trust; and whether any consultants were involved in that process.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105142","105142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760692","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many alternative provider medical services contracts were issued in England and Wales in each of the last 10 years; how many of those contracts have been (a) tendered or (b) retendered; and how many tenders did not result in a new provider being appointed.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105121","105121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760693","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the quality of care homes since the publication of the report of the Care Quality Commission, The state of adult social care services 2014 to 2017, on 6 July 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105123","105123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760694","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) general medical services and (b) personal medical services contracts have been cancelled by the contractor in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105122","105122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760695","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8038, on Department of Health: cybercrime, whether his Department requires contractors to have obtained a certificate from the Government Cyber Essentials scheme; and how many and what proportion of contractors doing work for his Department have obtained such a certificate.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105229","105229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760696","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether a clinical and financial risk analysis has been carried out on the proposal to restrict patient access to blue-light filtering intraocular lenses in the NICE draft clinical guideline on cataracts in adults: management.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105216","105216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760697","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints have been submitted to the National Guardian's Office in each year since it was established.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105180","105180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760698","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the operating budget has been of the National Guardian's Office in each year since it was established.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105181","105181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760699","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many case reviews have been undertaken by the National Guardian's Office in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105182","105182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760700","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health visitors were employed in (a) Greater London and (b) the London Borough of Newham in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105170","105170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760701","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total value of undelivered contracted units of dental activity in NNS dental contracts in England was in each year from 2012 to 2017.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105147","105147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760702","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to award the contract to appoint a provider of Liverpool community trust services; and what steps his Department is taking to monitor the application of NHS improvement rules relating to the (a) voting system used by Liverpool Community Health (LCH) staff members and (b) number of interim LCH posts created by Alder Hey since it was awarded the interim management contract for LCH.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105135","105135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760703","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for how many NHS dental contracts in England were not all contracted units of dental activity delivered in each year from 2012 to 2017.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105148","105148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760704","2017-10-09","Department for International Trade","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the revenue accrued to the public purse of UK hospitals operating branches in India for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105165","105165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760705","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8799, on genetics: screening, in what locations other than Cambridge NHS genome testing will take place.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105166","105166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760706","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent staff are employed in the National Guardian's Office.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105183","105183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760707","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the final scope of the NICE draft clinical guideline on cataracts in adults: management.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105215","105215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760708","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide a list of IT exemplar trusts.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105184","105184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760709","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in his Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105206","105206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760710","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Act of Parliament enables Border Force officers to access social media of people presenting at the UK border.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105164","105164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760711","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU nationals living in the UK were incorrectly sent notifications after 26 June 2017 that they would be deported; what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of reimbursing costs incurred by those people in response to such letters; and whether there is an upper limit for compensation claims for people affected by those notifications.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105241","105241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760712","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings (a) she and (b) Ministers of her Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in her Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105207","105207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760713","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) visa refusal decisions, (b) visa curtailment decisions and (c) removals have been made in respect of overseas students whose Test of English for International Communication certificates were cancelled by Educational Training Services since February 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105152","105152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760714","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of Tier 5 (Temporary Worker - Creative and Sporting) visas were granted to applicants of each nationality in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105102","105102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760715","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of visitor visas were granted to applicants of each nationality in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105103","105103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760716","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what has been the cost to her Department of the legal action arising from (a) visa curtailments and (b) removals of overseas students whose Test of English for International Communication certificates have been cancelled by the Educational Testing Services since February 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105154","105154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760717","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the powers available to take action against illegal encampments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105130","105130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760718","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of visitor visas were granted to applicants of each country in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105101","105101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760719","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of re-testing overseas students whose certificates for the Test of English for International Communication were cancelled by Educational Testing Services since February  2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105153","105153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760720","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refusals of indefinite leave to remain were overturned on appeal between March 2016 and March 2017; how many of these appeals were not challenged by her Department; how many of those cases have been processed; and how many of those cases have been processed where her Department offered no challenge.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105140","105140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760721","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many protesters arrested at the shale gas exploration site off the A583 Preston New Road during 2017 were (a) permanently resident in Lancashire, (b) resident at a protester camp and (c) permanently resident outside of Lancashire.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105150","105150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760722","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to Lancashire Police has been for operations in relation to the activities of protesters at the shale gas exploration site off the A583 Preston New Road in 2017.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105151","105151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760723","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the extent of call transference between call handling centres in different police service areas as part of overflow procedures for calls to (a) 101 and (b) 999.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105076","105076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760724","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate the Government has made of the amount which accrues to the public purse of telephone calls made to the UK Border Agency.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105124","105124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760725","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of (b) Tier 5 (Temporary Work Visas - Creative and Sporting) were granted to applicants of each country in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105106","105106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760726","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets are in place for the production of (a) visitor and (b) Tier 5 (Temporary Work) visas to be granted from overseas visa application centres; and whether such targets differ by country of application.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105104","105104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760727","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the enforcement of rules to prevent metal recycling operators from making cash payments for scrap metal.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105126","105126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760728","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to prevent metal thefts from (a) communications and transport networks and (b) heritage sites.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105127","105127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760729","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that her policies are informed by independent scientific advice.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105125","105125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760730","2017-10-09","Department for International Development","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many meetings (a) she and (b) Ministers of her Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in her Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105208","105208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760731","2017-10-09","Department for International Development","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment has been made of the trend in the humanitarian situation in Rakhine State; and what steps she is taking to support refugees fleeing violence in that area.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105191","105191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760732","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the value of British steel to be used in the prisons building programme.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105156","105156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760733","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in his Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105209","105209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760734","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reimburse people who have paid employment tribunal fees.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105070","105070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760735","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent by HM Prison and Probation Service on recruitment in each month since September 2016.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105091","105091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760736","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff are employed under each community rehabilitation company contract; and how many staff were employed under each contract when it began operating.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105090","105090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760737","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Service Credits each community rehabilitation company has had to pay in compensation for the minimum level of loss or damage as a result of a reduced provision of services.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105085","105085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760738","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment tribunal claimants in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency (a) paid fees and (b) have had fees refunded since 2013; what the total sum of fees still to be so refunded to claimants is; and when he intends that refund process to be completed.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105112","105112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760739","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment tribunal claimants there were in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency in the year (a) before and (b) after the introduction of tribunal fees.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105113","105113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760740","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much and what proportion of steel used in the construction of HM Prison Berwyn was sourced from British (a) manufacturers and (b) suppliers.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105155","105155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760741","2017-10-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers his Department plans to recruit in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105129","105129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760742","2017-10-09","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8744, Northern Ireland Office: buildings, from who the sub-let income in 2016-17 was from; and for what length of time that part of his Department's estate was sub-let.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105237","105237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760743","2017-10-09","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 7938, on Northern Ireland Office: consultants, to who and for what work the daily rate contracts were awarded; to who the other contract referred to in that Answer was awarded; what payment system was used for that other contract; and what work that other contract involved.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105190","105190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760744","2017-10-09","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8763, on Northern Ireland Office: procurement, if he will provide details of the procurement that took more than one year to complete.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105199","105199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760745","2017-10-09","Prime Minister","2017-09-14","To ask the Prime Minister, how many meetings she has had with the Government Chief Scientific Adviser in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105177","105177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760746","2017-10-09","Home Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to publish previously unpublished reviews, studies and reports into the effects of EU migration on UK wages and the UK economy.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105099","105099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760747","2017-10-09","Scotland Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in his Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105210","105210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760748","2017-10-09","Scotland Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8745, on Scotland Office: buildings, if his Department will publish the Memorandum of Terms of Occupation referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105230","105230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760749","2017-10-09","Department for Transport","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in his Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105211","105211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760750","2017-10-09","Department for Transport","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding Network Rail has allocated to ensure that its projects are biodiversity net positive.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105079","105079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760751","2017-10-09","Department for Transport","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8716, on Government Communications Service: staff, what the payscales are of the two members of staff who work solely on High Speed 2 (HS2); at what payscales the two vacancies were advertised; and what the payscales are for the two members of staff who work part-time on HS2 communications.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105146","105146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760752","2017-10-09","Department for Transport","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding Highways England has allocated to ensure that projects are biodiversity net positive.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105093","105093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760753","2017-10-09","Department for Transport","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will review road safety on the A19.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105114","105114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760754","2017-10-09","Wales Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether he has had discussions with the Welsh Government on the possibility of utilising the site occupied by No. 4 School of Technical Training at St. Athan in the event that school is relocated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105109","105109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760755","2017-10-09","Wales Office","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in his Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105212","105212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760756","2017-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with the Chief Scientific Adviser in his Department in the last three months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105213","105213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/760757","2017-10-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8045, on Department for Work and Pensions: cybercrime, how many and what proportion of firms have a Cyber Essentials qualification; and whether that qualification is a requirement for delivering work procured by his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105232","105232"
