"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654362","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria her Department uses to allocate funding to the voluntary and charitable sector; and if she will publish those criteria and any scoring system that they support.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56625","56625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654363","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which voluntary and charitable sector organisations are funded by her Department; how much each such organisation received in 2015-16; and how much each such organisation is due to receive in 2016-17.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56626","56626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654364","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has for the future staffing of the Student Loans Company.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56673","56673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654365","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has for the future staffing of the Skills Funding Agency.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56674","56674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654366","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2016 to Question 50659, what data from the National Pupil Database her Department shares with (a) the Home Office for immigration purposes, (b) media bodies and (c) other parties.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56640","56640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654367","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to answer Question 54886, tabled on 24 November 2016 by the hon. Member for Copeland.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56550","56550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654368","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56600","56600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654369","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what underspends there have been on the Youth Contract scheme in each of the last four years; and how any such underspends have been (a) allocated and (b) published.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56576","56576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654370","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the consultation on accelerated courses and switching university or degree is due to report; and whether there will be a debate in the House on the findings of that consultation.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56680","56680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654371","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the recommendations of the New Economics Foundation's Blue New Deal Action Plan, published in November 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56581","56581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654372","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's consultation on the review of animal establishments licensing in England, which closed on 12 March 2016, when she plans to publish draft regulations on the licensing of animal establishments, and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56617","56617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654373","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many reindeer in how many consignments and from which countries have been imported into the UK in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56616","56616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654374","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56601","56601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654375","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the cap is on the turnover of businesses to be covered by the Groceries Adjudicator.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56557","56557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654376","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) legal status is and (b) statutory powers are of the Groceries Adjudicator.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56556","56556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654377","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what legal requirements govern the importation, movement and keeping of reindeer in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56614","56614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654378","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many reindeer imported into the UK in the last five years have survived for longer than two years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56615","56615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654379","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to ensure that farmers are provided with detailed breakdowns of the claims paid to them when they receive basic farm payments.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56555","56555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654380","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made in implementing the recommendations of the report, Salmon five point approach - restoring salmon in England, published in May 2016.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56672","56672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654381","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment her Department has made of future levels of fish stocks in the North Sea.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56465","56465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654382","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much liquid milk was imported into the UK in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56461","56461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654383","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55821, if she will make it her policy to provide support to farmers who are experiencing depression or anxiety related to delayed single payments and other financial issues.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56464","56464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654384","2016-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) flood prevention work has taken place in areas prone to flooding by the River (i) Ribble, (ii) Lune, (iii) Darwen, (iv) Wyre and (v) Yarrow, (b) flood prevention work is planned in 2017, 2018 and 2019 at those locations and (c) the cost is to the public purse of such work in those locations in (A) 2016, (B) 2017, (C) 2018 and (D) 2019.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56532","56532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654385","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the low levels of rainfall in the South of England in the last six months, what discussions she has had with (a) the Environment Agency and (b) water utility companies on drought preparedness and water resilience planning; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56508","56508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654386","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a maximum price for bass landed as allowable by catch which is linked to the price on the dock of pollock with that price calculated over the average price paid for pollock over the immediate three-month period; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56503","56503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654387","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that there is no shortfall in the number of people will adequate skills to take up jobs in agriculture after the UK leaves the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56473","56473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654388","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to identify the country of origin of lion trophies imported into the UK in 2015 and 2016.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56690","56690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654389","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what types of lion trophies were imported into the UK in 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56691","56691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654390","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of persecution and displacement of religious minorities in (a) Syria and (b) Iraq; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56689","56689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654391","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he or his Department had with representatives of the Serbian newspaper Danas on his visit to Serbia on 11 November 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56506","56506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654392","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British ex-patriots residing in EU countries have contacted (a) UK embassies and (b) the Foreign and Commonwealth Office regarding visa rights since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56536","56536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654393","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55856, what length of time he spent at the Geca Kon bookstore, Serbia on 11 November 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56528","56528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654394","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55856, if he will publish any record made of discussions held during his visit to the Geca Kon bookstore, Serbia, on 11 November 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56531","56531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654395","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he held discussions on the future of the UK fishing industry with the Norwegian Foreign Minister during his recent visit to the UK.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56447","56447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654396","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he held discussions on the potential effect of tariffs on the seafood trade between Britain and Norway with the Norwegian Foreign Minister during his recent visit to the UK.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56448","56448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654397","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the number of refugees who have left Syria since conflict in that country began; how many such refugees now reside in each other country; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56635","56635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654398","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 48999, what estimate she has made of the number of civilians injured during the coalition forces' attack on Mosul; and how many children have been protected by the humanitarian assistance provided by the £40 million of extra funding announced on 21 September 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56660","56660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654399","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to mark the centenary of the Balfour Declaration.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56622","56622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654400","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55857, what the cost to the public purse was of the official government car used during the state visit to Serbia on 11 November 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56560","56560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654401","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56603","56603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654402","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56604","56604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654403","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase psychology support for adults with muscle-wasting conditions in south Yorkshire.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56618","56618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654404","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to develop a national hepatitis C elimination strategy.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56558","56558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654405","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency planning his Department is undertaking on the recruitment of (a) EU and (b) non-EU health services staff prior to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56538","56538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654406","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information (a) his Department and (b) NHS England holds on plans for community hospitals to relieve pressures on acute hospitals over the winter 2016 period.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56539","56539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654407","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 47601, whether NICE's planned review of its processes and systems in 2017 will include its methodology for assessing combination therapies.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56561","56561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654408","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms there are to ensure that local authorities and clinical commissioning groups meet their statutory duty to provide free aftercare under Section 117 of the Mental Health Act 1983.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56589","56589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654409","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there is a care adviser to support adults in the neuromuscular service at Salford Royal NHS Trust.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56577","56577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654410","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase specialist neuromuscular consultant support for children attending Royal Manchester Children's Hospital NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56578","56578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654411","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase psychological support for adults with muscle-wasting conditions in south Yorkshire.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56593","56593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654412","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital bed days there were for people with a (a) primary and (b) secondary diagnosis of dementia in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56652","56652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654413","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital bed days there were for people with a (a) primary and (b) secondary diagnosis of malnutrition in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56653","56653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654414","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital bed days there were for people with a primary diagnosis of malnutrition and a secondary diagnosis of dementia in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56654","56654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654415","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many emergency hospital admissions there were of people with a (a) primary and (b) secondary diagnosis of dementia in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56655","56655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654416","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what agreements have been reached between the Royal Free Hospital and Google's DeepMind on intellectual property matters in the implementation of the Streams app which shares patient data with third parties.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56639","56639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654417","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for antidepressants by (a) drug and (b) dose have been dispensed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56694","56694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654418","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2016 to Question 54960, what the outturn was for specialist commissioning of tier four child and adolescent mental health services in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56692","56692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654419","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2016 to Question 54960, what the outturn was for specialist commissioning of eating disorder units in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56693","56693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654420","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require the Care Quality Commission to notify (a) hon. Members and (b) local councillors of ratings of inadequate or requires improvement in care homes.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56438","56438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654421","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to allow the abolition of bursaries for students attending degree courses in nursing, midwifery and allied health professions; and what the timetable for implementation of such proposals will be.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56452","56452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654422","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many specialist neuromuscular consultants were employed by the NHS in each period from 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56518","56518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654423","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to promote a national awareness campaign on stop smoking services.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56527","56527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654424","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his Department's policy to ensure that there is a care adviser to support adults in neuromuscular services at all NHS trusts that provide those services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56511","56511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654425","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase specialist neuromuscular consultant support for children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56512","56512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654426","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many specialist paediatric neuromuscular consultants were employed by the NHS in each period from 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56519","56519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654427","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 8 November 2016 to Questions 51400, 51421 and 51422, how his Department is measuring the performance of Capita in providing a more efficient administration of the National Dental Performers List.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56525","56525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654428","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of reasons why quit rates for smoking have declined in recent years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56501","56501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654429","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of stop smoking services in England.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56502","56502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654430","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will take steps to ensure that the proceeds of fines imposed by the Competition and Markets Authority on pharmaceutical companies will be invested in the NHS.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56488","56488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654431","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2016 to Question 55779, what areas of funding in the bespoke data collection contributed to the £3.4 billion difference between NHS England's estimate of mental health spending in 2014-15 and the outturn; and if he will correct the record.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56695","56695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654432","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 49945, how the police are funding their legal representation in connection with the resumed inquests into the Birmingham pub bombings of November 1974.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56696","56696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654433","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the nationalities are of each of the people granted indefinite leave to remain in the Peterborough City Council area since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56491","56491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654434","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for indefinite leave to remain have been received for people who gave a residential address within the Peterborough City Council area in each year since 2010; how many of those applications were (a) granted and (b) appealed after being declined; of those applications that were appealed, how many were (i) successful and (ii) unsuccessful; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56492","56492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654435","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2016 to Question 51383, what steps her Department is taking to collect statistics on the speed of UK Visas and Immigration's implementation of decisions made by the First Tier Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum).","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56497","56497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654436","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list the main reasons why UK Visas and Immigration rejected visa applications in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56479","56479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654437","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa applications were processed by UK Visas and Immigration in the last five years; and what proportion of those applications were rejected the first time each such application was submitted.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56480","56480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654438","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the reliability of information contained in the International Passenger Survey for the purpose of migration control; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56467","56467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654439","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussion she or her Department has had with the (a) incoming and (b) outgoing US administrations on the possibility of banning certain groups of British citizens from travel to the US.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56429","56429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654440","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2016 to Question 51510, on criminal proceedings: mental illness, if she will ensure that appropriate places of safety are extended to people with autism.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56458","56458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654441","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to end the adults at risk in immigration detention policy.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56463","56463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654442","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the proportion of women affected by domestic abuse; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56455","56455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654443","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to Question 50684, tabled by the hon. Member for North Swindon on 27 October 2016.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56677","56677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654444","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 49635, on Travellers: caravan sites, in what circumstances she would not expect the police to use their powers to remove Travellers from an unauthorised site.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56663","56663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654445","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the total amount spent by her Department in each of the last five years on ending domestic violence; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56659","56659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654446","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the prevalence of domestic violence over the last decade; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56658","56658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654447","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 49635, on Travellers: caravan sites, what guidance her Department provides to the police on use of their powers to remove Travellers from a site.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56662","56662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654448","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on evaluation of the Domestic Violence Disclosure Scheme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56656","56656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654449","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil servants are working on the Violence against Women and Girls Strategy 2016-20; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56657","56657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654450","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential implication for her Department's policies on the cyber security of nuclear facilities of the Stuxnet cyber attacks.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56541","56541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654451","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56605","56605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654452","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in which (a) local authority areas and (b) Parliamentary constituencies asylum hostels are located.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56678","56678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654453","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in which (a) local authority areas and (b) Parliamentary constituencies new asylum hostels are planned to open in the next six months.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56679","56679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654454","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56606","56606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654456","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support Yazidis, Christians and other vulnerable minorities in Iraq.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56651","56651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654457","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the availability within Yemen of diesel oil for the (a) generation of electricity and (b) functioning of water pumps used as wells.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56435","56435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654458","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate her Department has made of the number of Yemenis who are at risk of malnutrition; and what proportion of those people are children.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56436","56436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654459","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what changes her Department plans to make to the list of priority countries as a result of the Bilateral Development Review 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56484","56484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654460","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to open any new country programmes as a result of the Bilateral Development Review 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56478","56478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654461","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to exit or transition from any country programmes as a result of the Bilateral Development Review 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56534","56534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654462","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims of trafficking were witnesses or accused in criminal proceedings in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56516","56516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654463","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many restraining orders imposed in England and Wales in 2014 and 2015 explicitly restricted online contact.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56514","56514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654464","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many restraining orders imposed in England and Wales in 2014 and 2015 restricted contact through the use of legal processes.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56515","56515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654465","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many restraining orders were imposed as a result of stalking and harassment in England and Wales in 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56513","56513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654466","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Legal Aid Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 on access to justice for the most vulnerable people in society.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56494","56494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654467","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions appeal cases for hearing at tribunals have been adjourned as a result of the Department for Work and Pensions not providing sufficient information on universal credit in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56468","56468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654468","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the problem-solving courts pilot programme announced by her Department in May 2016 will begin.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56475","56475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654469","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much (a) the National Offender Management Service (NOMS) and (b) her Department spent on external consultancy fees relating to NOMS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56476","56476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654470","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of the offence of throwing any article or substance into a prison without authorisation since that offence came into force; and how many such people have received the maximum sentence for that offence.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56477","56477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654471","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to incentivise employers to recruit ex-offenders.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56433","56433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654472","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of First-tier Tribunal users represented themselves as litigants in person; and what proportion of those tribunals found in favour of the appellant for each (a) chamber and jurisdiction as defined by the Courts and Tribunals Judiciary in September 2016 and (b) quarter in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56444","56444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654473","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Government's press release, entitled Killer drivers to face life sentences, published on 4 December 2016, if she will take further steps to improve the enforcement of offences related to dangerous driving.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56460","56460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654474","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers are employed in England and Wales.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56466","56466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654475","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding her Department provided to the Survivors Trust in each year since 2009-10; and if she will publish all files related to that funding allocation held by her Department.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56450","56450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654476","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding her Department provided to Survivors (Hull and East Riding) in each year since 2009-10; and if she will publish all files related to that funding allocation held by her Department.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56451","56451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654477","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans her Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56608","56608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654478","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate her Department has made of how frequently perpetrators of harassment or stalking seek indirectly to contact their victim through (a) civil and (b) family court action.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56620","56620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654479","2016-12-12","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56609","56609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654480","2016-12-12","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Government of the Irish Republic on ownership of Lough Foyle.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56613","56613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654481","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans 10 Downing Street has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56610","56610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654482","2016-12-12","Prime Minister","2016-12-07","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she has had with King Salman on her visit to the Gulf in December 2016 on the situation in Yemen; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56583","56583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654483","2016-12-12","Scotland Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56611","56611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654484","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Transport of 17 November 2016, Official Report, column 376, when the review of the application of national minimum wage legislation to seafarers in UK waters will commence; and if he will take steps to ensure that that review applies to seafarers working in all sectors of the UK shipping industry.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56565","56565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654485","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to encourage the retro-fitting of fuel additive LoNOx to diesel vehicles.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56568","56568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654486","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Minister of State for Transport of 17 November 2016, Official Report, column 364, on car manufacturers: emissions, whether he has received the pledged payment from Volkswagen; and what plans he has to have further discussions with Volkswagen on payments as a result of its manipulation of emissions tests in 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56574","56574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654487","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Transport of 17 November 2016, Official Report, column 376, if he will detail the existing working arrangements between the Maritime and Coastguard Agency and HM Revenue and Customs' National Minimum Wage (NMW) Enforcement Team in the event of a complaint of (a) nationality-based pay discrimination and (b) non-payment of the NMW for seafarers employed on vessels working from and between UK ports.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56562","56562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654488","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Transport of 17 November 2016, Official Report, column 376, if he will take steps to establish formal working arrangements between the Maritime and Coastguard Agency and HM Revenue and Customs' National Minimum Wage (NMW) Enforcement Team to ensure that all complaints of (a) nationality-based pay discrimination or (b) non-payment of the NMW for seafarers employed on vessels working from and between UK ports are fully investigated.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56563","56563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654489","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Transport of 17 November 2016, Official Report, column 376, if he will list the (a) Government departments, (b) maritime trade unions, (c) shipping companies and (d) other stakeholders who will participate in the review of the application of national minimum wage legislation to seafarers in UK waters; and when the first meeting of the legal review group is planned to take place.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56564","56564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654490","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which local authorities his Department has consulted on the progress of plans for the construction of High Speed 2 since May 2015.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56540","56540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654491","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2016, HCWS 322, Rail update, what discussions he has had with the Rail Delivery Group on his proposals to change the operation of Network Rail.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56587","56587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654492","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2016, HCWS 322, Rail update, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposals in that Statement.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56588","56588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654493","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the causes of signal and power failures on the South West main line between Woking and Eastleigh on 6 December 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56634","56634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654494","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria he used to decide whether or not to extend Transport for London's remit to cover the London suburban rail network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56667","56667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654495","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of trends in the number of Merchant Navy ratings and the long-term effects of such trends on the UK shipping industry.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56668","56668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654496","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to ensure that after changes to Network Rail are made the national rail network is maintained in a suitable condition for rail freight.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56453","56453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654497","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which parts of the East-West Growth Corridor railway lines will be electrified; and what the total cost to the public purse will be of that electrification.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56449","56449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654498","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions (a) his Department and (b) Network Rail has with local authorities ahead of major rail maintenance work in the areas covered by those authorities.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56495","56495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654499","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what procedures his Department has agreed with Network Rail on the avoidance of major weekend rail maintenance works on lines serving locations where events likely to attract substantial numbers of people are scheduled.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56496","56496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654500","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has considered taking steps to prevent the overselling of seats on commercial flights.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56498","56498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654501","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans the Government has to encourage more young people to take up careers as Merchant Navy ratings.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56670","56670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654502","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the time taken to ratify the Istanbul Convention on women who have experienced domestic, sexual, emotional and financial violence in the last four years.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56493","56493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654503","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will harmonise the eligibility rules for civilian and non-civilian widows entitlement to Bereaved Parents Allowance if a widower decides to (a) remarry and (b) enter a civil partnership.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56439","56439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654504","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to promote Marriage Week in February 2017.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56459","56459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654505","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55851, on universal credit, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of reductions to universal credit on the number of children in (a) relative and (b) absolute child poverty in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56487","56487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654506","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure sufficient information relating to claimants is provided for appeal cases for hearing at tribunals relating to universal credit.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56469","56469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654507","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support vulnerable claimants with mental health issues sanctioned during the Christmas period when job centres are closed.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56470","56470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654508","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Garston and Halewood constituency have received sanctions on their benefit payments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56509","56509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654509","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Garston and Halewood constituency have had more than one sanction in their benefit payments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56510","56510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654510","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Garston and Halewood constituency who were in receipt of disability living allowance (DLA) have had their application for personal independence payment (PIP) (a) refused completely and (b) approved at a lower level of need than the DLA claim it superseded in each year since the introduction of PIP as a replacement for DLA began.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56535","56535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654511","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2016 to Question 51735, on housing benefit: hotels, whether the reference in that Answer to current levels means real terms levels or current cash levels.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56661","56661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654512","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Garston and Halewood constituency have had a Motability vehicle in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56552","56552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654513","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Garston and Halewood constituency have been in receipt of disability living allowance each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56553","56553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654514","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Garston and Halewood constituency have had their  disability living allowance claims converted to personal independence payments in each year since those payments were introduced","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56554","56554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654515","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people of working age in Garston and Halewood constituency have had a work capability assessment in each year since 2010; and how many of those people have been passed fit for work and placed (a)  on jobseeker's allowance, (b) in a work-related activity group and (c) in the support group.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56551","56551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654516","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that companies comply with UK regulations when importing potentially hazardous products for the construction sector.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56575","56575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654517","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the (a) lowest, (b) average and (c) largest loss of household income under the lower benefit cap for families (i) in receipt of universal credit and (ii) in receipt of legacy benefits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56569","56569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654518","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2016 to Question 55467, if he will make it his policy that carers who are in school and college and do not qualify for loans and grants in the educational maintenance system receive Carer's Allowance.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56619","56619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654519","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 55219, for what reason he has not made an assessment of trends in the incidence of pension fraud in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK since the introduction of the pension freedoms announced in the Budget 2014.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56585","56585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654520","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Garston and Halewood constituency have had mobility components stopped which enable access to the Motability Scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56582","56582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654522","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Scotland claiming (a) disability living allowance and (b) carer's  allowance have been affected by the 84-day rule in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56586","56586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654523","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the Hendry Review of Tidal Lagoons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56681","56681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654524","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which (a) workers' representatives groups and (b) trade unions were consulted by his Department during the drawing up of the shortlist for Director of Labour Market Enforcement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56566","56566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654525","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of workers employed within sectors of the economy that the Government has identified as at risk of labour market abuse and exploitation.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56567","56567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654526","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56594","56594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654527","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many businesses are operating within the (a) construction, (b) care homes, (c) hotels and (d) catering sectors in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56559","56559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654528","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been spent on providing ESOL courses in the city of Hull in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56647","56647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654529","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will take steps to prevent recruitment firms advertising for jobs exclusively abroad before they have advertised locally.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56648","56648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654530","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to conduct a regional analysis of levels of unskilled migration and its effect on local wages.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56666","56666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654531","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what safeguards his Department has to ensure that rules on mergers and acquisitions do not damage foreign direct investment.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56537","56537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654532","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2016 to Question 44312, what the total sum of arrears was that was recovered by HM Revenue and Customs for non-compliance with the national minimum wage in the first half of 2016-17; how many (a) workers and (b) employers those arrears relate to; how much of that total sum of arrears was recovered through the self-correction mechanism introduced in 2015; and how many (i) workers and (ii) employers those self-corrected arrears relate to.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56533","56533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654533","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to calculate the cost to (a) consumers and (b) the environment of planned obsolescence of electronic products manufactured in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56543","56543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654534","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to develop a coastal industrial strategy with regard to (a) renewable energy, (b) small-scale fishing, (c) aquaculture and (d) tourism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56481","56481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654535","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support sustainable economic regeneration in coastal communities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56482","56482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654536","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with charities on the financial effect of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56440","56440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654537","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support business growth in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56685","56685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654538","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the governance arrangements will be for UK Research and Innovation.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56686","56686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654539","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he discussed the future of the UK fishing industry with the Norwegian Foreign Minister during his recent visit to the UK.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56430","56430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654540","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he held discussions on the potential effect of tariffs on the seafood trade between Britain and Norway with the Norwegian Foreign Minister during his recent visit to the UK.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56446","56446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654541","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to his oral evidence to the European Scrutiny Committee on 26 October 2016, on Parliamentary Scrutiny of EU Trade Deal: Canada/EU Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement, HC 792, for what reasons a debate on that agreement did not take place in the House in November 2016.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56676","56676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654542","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of reverting to default World Trade Organisation tariffs on UK businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56684","56684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654543","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many representatives of businesses in the West Midlands he has met since his Department was created; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56636","56636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654544","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many specialist trade negotiators are employed by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56637","56637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654545","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many civil servants in his Department are working full-time with the World Trade Organisation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56584","56584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654546","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many third party (a) consultants and (b) consultancy companies his Department plans to commission; and what the cost to the public purse of such commissioning will be in (i) 2017, (ii) 2018, (iii) 2019 and (iv) 2020.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56644","56644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654547","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many third party (a) consultants and (b) consulting companies have been commissioned by his Department since it was established; and what the cost to the public purse of such commissioning has been.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56642","56642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654548","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56607","56607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654549","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56602","56602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654550","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many third party (a) consultants and (b) consultancy companies his Department plans to commission; and what the cost to the public purse of such commissioning will be in (i) 2017, (ii) 2018, (iii) 2019 and (iv) 2020.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56645","56645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654551","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many third party (a) consultants and (b) consultancy companies have been commissioned by his Department since it was established; and what the cost to the public purse of such commissioning has been.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56643","56643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654552","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment the Government has made of the transitional support that would be required for exporting companies based in the UK for a future outside the (a) Single Market and (b) customs union.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56638","56638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654553","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he discussed the future of the UK fishing industry with the Norwegian Foreign Minister during his recent visit to the UK.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56445","56445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654554","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on European mobile data roaming charges for UK citizens of the UK leaving the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56454","56454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654555","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he had discussions on the potential effect of tariffs on the seafood trade between Britain and Norway with the Norwegian Foreign Minister during his recent visit to the UK.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56431","56431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654556","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the extra resources needed at ports to process the arrival of EU citizens following the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56432","56432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654557","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the Government's policy is on whether Article 127 of the EEA agreement should be triggered.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56529","56529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654924","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has assessed the potential merits of developing magnetic levitation trains as part of the Government's industrial strategy.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907831","907831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657460","2016-12-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to support business growth in the north of England.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907839","907839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657461","2016-12-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent representations he has received on the status and rights of agency workers.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907835","907835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657462","2016-12-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support businesses as part of the Northern Powerhouse.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907832","907832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652577","2016-12-08","Attorney General","2016-12-06","To ask the Attorney General, how many unpaid internships there are in the Law Officers' Departments.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56300","56300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652578","2016-12-08","Cabinet Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to relocate civil servants outside of central London as part of the 2018 move to 10 South Colonnade.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56338","56338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652579","2016-12-08","Cabinet Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what meetings have taken place between officials of his Department and Barclays representatives on the proposed move of 5,700 civil and public service posts to 10 South Colonnade.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56349","56349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652580","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons the Cabinet Office List of Ministerial Responsibilities published in October 2016 does not have Ministers' Private Office email addresses in all cases but rather generic email addresses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Sir Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56412","56412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652581","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department plans to correct contact detail inaccuracies in the List of Ministerial Responsibilities published in October 2016.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Sir Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56410","56410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652583","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons the Cabinet Office List of Ministerial Responsibilities published in October 2016 does not have Ministers' Private Office telephone numbers in all cases but rather switchboard numbers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Sir Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56411","56411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652584","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an estimate of the potential effect of businesses paying the adult minimum wage rate to people under 25 years of age who are not in training but carrying out the same work as those 25 years of age or over on (a) rates of poverty and (b) levels of disposable income for people under 25 years of age.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56280","56280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652585","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an estimate of the cost to businesses of their paying the adult minimum wage rate to people under 25 years of age who are not in training but are doing the same job as people 25 years of age or older.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56281","56281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652586","2016-12-08","HM Treasury","2016-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56314","56314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652587","2016-12-08","HM Treasury","2016-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56237","56237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652588","2016-12-08","HM Treasury","2016-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of income tax is estimated to come from the top one per cent of earners in the UK in 2020.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56250","56250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652589","2016-12-08","HM Treasury","2016-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's policy paper, entitled Soft Drinks Industry Levy, published on 5 December 2016, what the alternative levy free options are for people with Type 1 or Type 2 diabetes affected by the proposed soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56251","56251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652590","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2016 to Question 54118, what assessment his Department has made of the net benefit to the UK economy of Jersey and Guernsey setting independent economic and taxation policies.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56258","56258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652591","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether, when making the decision to withdraw the direction for Birmingham City Council not to take any step in connection with the adoption of the Birmingham Development Plan 2031, his Department (a) received any submissions, whether oral or in writing, from third parties, (b) received any submissions from parties interested in or connected to the Peddimore Employment Site and Langley Sustainable Urban Extension and (c) held any meetings with third parties in relation to the decision to withdraw the Holding Direction.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56249","56249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652592","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made on enabling local authorities to retain 100 per cent of business rates.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56271","56271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652593","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56226","56226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652594","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many hours of learning were provided on average to people undertaking lessons in English as a second language as a result of courses funded by his Department in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56334","56334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652595","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people his Department has helped to learn English as a second language as a result of courses funded by his Department in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56335","56335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652596","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on programmes which promote the use of the (a) Cornish and (b) English language in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56336","56336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652597","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56301","56301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652598","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to encourage people from C2DE families to participate in programmes funded by the Youth Social Action Fund.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56351","56351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652599","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate she has made of the number of people working in the creative industries whose jobs are linked to Channel 4, but who are not employed by that channel.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56422","56422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652600","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on the wider creative industries of any change to the structure of Channel 4.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56423","56423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652601","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her plans are for the future of Channel 4; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56424","56424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652602","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answers of 6 December 2016 to Questions 55206 and 55161, for what reasons the advisers were named in only one of those Answers.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56384","56384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652603","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2016 to Question 40504, whether she has held any meetings with her Ministerial colleagues on options for the future of Channel 4 since her appointment.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56417","56417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652604","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made by National Trust and National Parks England in providing proposals to her Department that outline better engagement with communications providers to assist in tackling mobile not sports since February 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56388","56388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652605","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings her Department and the Prime Minister's Office have had on the future of Channel 4 in the last six months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56421","56421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652606","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many unpaid internships there are in her Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56302","56302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652607","2016-12-08","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to make available a list of planned, publicly-funded sites for the Emergency Services Network to other mobile network operators to allow for site sharing.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56337","56337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652608","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56227","56227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652609","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with non-governmental organisations on children's access to pornographic material.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56266","56266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652610","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to enable parents and guardians to ensure children access age-appropriate materials on the internet.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56267","56267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652611","2016-12-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56228","56228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652612","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the UK's capability to deploy (a) the Joint Precision Airdrop System and (b) comparable unmanned equipment for making deliveries from the air.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56346","56346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652613","2016-12-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which of the Astute class submarines are (a) available for operations, (b) being used for training, (c) preparing to deploy and (d) being refitted.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56322","56322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652614","2016-12-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many incursions by Russian submarines into UK waters there have been since 1 January 2016; and what the location was of such submarines.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56330","56330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652615","2016-12-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the Single Service Regulations Office report on wage inflation to be published.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56331","56331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652616","2016-12-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56303","56303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652617","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to increase parliamentary accountability of Defence Equipment and Support.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56296","56296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652618","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what commemorations her Department (a) has held and (b) plans to hold to mark the centenary of First World War and the participation of Muslim soldiers from the Indian subcontinent who fought alongside British and French troops on the Western Front.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56289","56289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652619","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research her Department has conducted on the reasons for exclusions of children from early years settings.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56293","56293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652621","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many unpaid internships there are in her Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56304","56304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652622","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications of the Social Mobility Commission's evaluation of the quality of apprenticeships as set out in its report, State of the Nation 2016, published in November 2016, for the (a) quality of new and existing apprenticeship standards and (b) guidance on the design of such standards; and if she will establish a robust quality criteria for apprenticeships.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56282","56282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652623","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship standards relate to skills for which there are shortages in the green economy.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56283","56283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652624","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to make anonymised ward level data on post-16 student work, education and training destinations, as reported by local authorities to the National Client Information System, open data and available through the data.gov.uk website.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56347","56347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652625","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52226, for what reason there is no requirement to outline a typical career progression or career path for apprenticeships past the end of an apprenticeship in the guidance criteria.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56344","56344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652626","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how she plans to measure the effect of the new Primary PE and Sport Premium on children's activity levels.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56333","56333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652627","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56229","56229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652628","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to introduce guidelines on nutritional standards for packed lunches in schools.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56268","56268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652629","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department offers to schools making applications to the Regional Academies Growth Fund.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56265","56265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652630","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consideration her Department has given to (a) travel time and (b) the availability of public transport for pupils travelling to secondary school when making decisions on (i) opening new and (ii) closing existing schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56244","56244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652631","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful prosecutions Ofsted have brought against early years providers who did not take the action required in a welfare requirements notice in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56370","56370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652632","2016-12-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of farm-related deaths from (a) slurry, (b) machinery, (c) disease and (d) collapsing buildings in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56383","56383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652633","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of proposals to limit emissions from diesel generators on the bio power sector.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56401","56401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652634","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many Article 10 certificates for ivory items have been (a) applied for and (b) issued in the last 10 years for which records are available.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56363","56363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652635","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential benefits of used cooking oil in generating carbon-neutral electricity.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56381","56381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652636","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to increase take-up by supermarkets of the Red Tractor Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56420","56420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652637","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with Natural England on the level of resources needed for the roll-out of trial badger culls.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56408","56408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652638","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons Natural England requires a breakdown of spending from companies set up by farmers to carry out trial badger culls.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56425","56425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652639","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56230","56230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652640","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the (a) number and (b) type of animal furs and skins which were seized after being imported illegally in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56343","56343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652641","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of import permits granted in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56341","56341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652642","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how her Department plans to monitor implementation of the guidance set out in the Code of Practice on the use of snares; and when her Department plans to review or revise that code.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56325","56325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652643","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the (a) number and (b) type of animal furs and skins which were imported for sale in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56342","56342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652644","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many unpaid internships there are in her Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56305","56305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652645","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to introduce food labelling for pasture-based milk and dairy products.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56276","56276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652646","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the proportion of packaging waste which will be recycled or recovered in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56277","56277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652647","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of packaging waste was recycled or recovered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56278","56278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652648","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with representatives of the insurance industry on creating a flood insurance scheme for businesses.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56279","56279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652649","2016-12-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56307","56307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652650","2016-12-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56231","56231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652651","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2016 to Question 49936, what the names are of the six projects funded through the Conflict, Security and Stability Fund during the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56246","56246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652652","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his Department's news story on plans to demolish a Bedouin village in Israel, published on 23 November 2016, whether he has raised concerns on behalf of the Government with the Israeli ambassador in addition to the concerns he has raised on behalf of the House; and what the outcome of such discussions have been.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56402","56402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652653","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed as having chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56376","56376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652654","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to produce an occupational health strategy for the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56377","56377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652656","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to produce a strategy for healthy living for the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56378","56378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652657","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will issue guidance to GPs on seeking information on a patient's employment during appointments.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56379","56379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652658","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will produce a respiratory strategy for the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56380","56380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652659","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many care home providers the Care Quality Commission has held risk assessment meetings with since April 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56405","56405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652660","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the ambit of the Health Service Medical Supplies (Costs) Bill 2016 was changed to include medical supplies other than pharmaceuticals during the drafting stage of that Bill.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56382","56382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652661","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many care home providers have been referred to local authorities by the Care Quality Commission as being at risk of financial failure since April 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56406","56406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652662","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the Kalydeco form of Ivacaftor has been deemed unsuitable for use by children aged between two and five in England; what assessment he has made of its use by children in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56385","56385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652663","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many regulated care home providers have handed back contracts to local authorities in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56407","56407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652664","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the public consultation announced in 2015 on the availability of homeopathic products through NHS prescriptions.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56390","56390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652665","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many care homes inspected by the Care Quality Commission in 2015-16 did not meet the requirements as set out in Regulation 13 of the Care Quality Commission (Registration) Regulations 2014.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56418","56418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652666","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and which hospitals inspected by the Care Quality Commission in 2015-16 did not meet the requirements set out in Regulation 14 of the Health and Social Care Act 2008 (Regulation Activities) Regulations 2014.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56391","56391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652667","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he intends to bring forward legislative proposals making it compulsory for restaurants and catering outlets to publicly display their food hygiene rating on their premises, websites and menus.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56419","56419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652668","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2016 to Question 55033, what steps his Department takes to recover outstanding fees from private patients.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56392","56392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652669","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to encourage leaders of local health and care systems to work together with local services to deliver good-quality end of life care for LGBT and other people.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56396","56396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652670","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost to the public purse per day is of agency staff employed through (a) NHS Professionals Ltd. and (b) the private sector.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56360","56360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652671","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the needs of LGBT people are recognised when planning and commissioning health and social care services; and how his Department plans to monitor its progress in recognising such needs.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56397","56397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652673","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve palliative and end-of-life care for LGBT people.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56399","56399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652674","2016-12-08","HM Treasury","2016-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to use the revenue raised from the soft drinks industry levy to fund oral health improvement programmes for children.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56362","56362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652675","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department will take to ensure that clinical commissioning groups follow criteria for surgical interventions in the NICE clinical guideline CG189, on obesity: identification, assessment and management of obesity in children, young people and adults.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56365","56365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652676","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for all clinical commissioning groups to be responsible for commissioning Tier 4 Specialised Complex Obesity Services after the transfer of such services from NHS England.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56366","56366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652677","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to (a) better diagnose and (b) reduce the incidence of sepsis in hospitals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56373","56373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652678","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with clinical bodies on the potential connection between levels of alcohol consumption and prostate cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56374","56374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652679","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which clinical commissioning groups are responsible for commissioning Tier 4 Specialised Complex Obesity Services after the transfer of such services from NHS England.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56367","56367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652680","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the relative increase in the number of people dying as a result of dementia as opposed to heart disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56375","56375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652681","2016-12-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many pharmaceutical companies have been referred to the Competition and Markets Authority in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56359","56359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652682","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2016 to Question 53369, if he will estimate the number of medical records which are missing.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56394","56394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652683","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the forecast net profit of NHS Professionals Ltd in each of the next three financial years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56353","56353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652684","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the annual cost to the public purse of exempting undergraduate students from (a) dental charges and (b) prescription charges.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56354","56354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652685","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the annual cost to the public purse of administering exemptions for eligible students from (a) dental charges and (b) prescription charges.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56355","56355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652686","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of NHS paediatric bed availability.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56356","56356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652687","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the rate of NHS-specific inflation in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56357","56357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652688","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2016 to Question 55033, if he will collect and publish figures for outstanding fees from private patients.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56393","56393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652689","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the average cost to the NHS of each day of delayed discharge.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56358","56358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652690","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Bradford Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust on ensuring that patients with muscle-wasting conditions who are served by that Trust have access to a neuromuscular care advisor.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56350","56350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652691","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many care home providers have been required by the Care Quality Commission to develop Risk Mitigation Plans since April 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56416","56416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652692","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the extent to which clinical commissioning groups are rationing treatments by restricting access to routine surgery for patients who smoke or are clinically obese.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56247","56247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652693","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the use of portable surgical health centres to support (a) the delivery of care in a community setting, (b) system transformation and efficiency within the NHS and (c) improving patient outcomes.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56252","56252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652694","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of hospital admission for a child having teeth extracted under general anaesthetic.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56269","56269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652695","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the factors that limit children's access to NHS dental services; whether those factors differ in different parts of the UK; and what steps his Department is taking to increase such access.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56272","56272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652696","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to bring forward legislative proposals related to the Law Commission's final report and draft Bill on the regulation of health and social care professionals, published in April 2014.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56253","56253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652698","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the General Medical Council guidance for doctors providing cosmetic surgery which came into force in June 2016.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56254","56254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652699","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the findings of its consultation on the expansion of Care Quality Commission ratings to include independent healthcare providers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56255","56255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652700","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many residents of care homes had an emergency admission to a hospital in 2015-16.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56243","56243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652701","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56232","56232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652702","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to abolish student bursaries for degree courses in the nursing, midwifery and allied health professions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56218","56218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652703","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of NHS England's General Practice Resilience Programme.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56219","56219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652704","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of General Practice Resilience Programme funding has been granted to vulnerable GP practices in London.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56220","56220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652705","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP practices in Enfield have received financial assistance from the General Practice Resilience Programme.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56221","56221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652706","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2016 to Question 51648, what recent estimate he has made of the number of GP practices that require assistance from the General Practice Resilience Programme in (a) Enfield and (b) London.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56222","56222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652707","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56308","56308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652708","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current position of NICE is on the funding of energy psychology as a psychological treatment available through the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56316","56316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652709","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what analysis his Department has undertaken of the effectiveness of energy psychology; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56317","56317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652710","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) reviewed independent research on the efficacy of energy psychology; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56318","56318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652711","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52227, whether the level of reported incidents has increased in the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56327","56327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652712","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2016 to Question 51861, what the current GP to patient ratio is in England; how many more patients he estimates there will be by 2021; and what estimate he has made of the expected GP to patient ratio by 2021.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56319","56319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652713","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2016 to Question 51861, what the average amount is that each GP practice will receive from GP Resilience Programme funding; and what those GP practices are expected to achieve with that funding.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56320","56320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652714","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2016 to Question 51861, how many GP practices in (a) Birmingham and (b) the West Midlands will receive financial support from the GP Resilience Programme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56321","56321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652715","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52227, what discussions he has had with his Ministerial colleagues about increasing litigation fees; what plans he has to support GP practices in dealing with those increased fees; and what steps he plans to take across Government to reduce the number of compensation claims.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56328","56328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652716","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49729, what changes there were in the level of capacity available between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56329","56329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652717","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place a list of NHS providers with whom NHS England holds contracts to provide specialist dermatology services in the Library.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56284","56284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652718","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what NHS England's policy is on the approval of Individual Funding Requests for an unlicensed indication where there is a licensed NICE-recommended alternative.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56285","56285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652719","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the transaction costs of the (a) internal and (b) external market to health services in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56286","56286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652720","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the expenditure on competition and corporate lawyers by health services in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56287","56287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652721","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the expenditure on tendering and bidding processes by health services in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56288","56288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652722","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of inactivity on children's academic performance.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56290","56290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652723","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to introduce the gold-standard framework, developed by Dr Keri Thomas, for detecting group B streptococcus infection.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56291","56291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652724","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the differences are between the Cold Weather Plan 2016 and the Cold Weather Plan 2015.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56273","56273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652725","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the differences are between the Cold Weather Plan 2015 and the Cold Weather Plan 2014.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56274","56274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652726","2016-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Prison Reform Trust briefing, Prison: the facts, Summer 2016, what assessment the Government has made of the rate of self-harm among prisoners serving sentences for public protection; and what steps her Department is taking to reduce that rate.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56256","56256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652727","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Gangmasters Licensing Authority Annual Report and Accounts 2015-16 will be laid before the House.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56295","56295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652728","2016-12-19","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied and separated children have been (a) identified, (b) assessed and (c) transferred under sub-section 1 of section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56298","56298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652729","2016-12-20","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) refugee children and (b) families or carers of such children have been resettled under the Vulnerable Children's Resettlement Programme since that programme began.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56332","56332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652730","2016-12-08","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the trialled fast track scheme for permanent residency applications from EU migrants; (b) what progress has been made to extend that programme to all eligible EU migrants; and when the roll-out of that programme will be completed.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56326","56326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652731","2016-12-08","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unpaid internships there are in her Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56309","56309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652732","2016-12-08","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56233","56233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652733","2016-12-08","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of allocating a proportion of funding from the National and International Capital City Grant for the policing of Cardiff.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56224","56224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652734","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made, or modelling her Department has carried out, of the potential effect of achieving the Government's net migration target on the economy and public finances of (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) the other nations and regions of the UK.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56241","56241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652735","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made, or modelling her Department has carried out, of the potential effect of achieving the Government's net migration target on the demographics and migration levels of (a) Scotland and (b) the other nations and regions of the UK.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56242","56242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652736","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total value of fees charged by each constabulary in the North West of England under the Removal, Storage and Disposal of Vehicles (Prescribed Sums and Changes) Regulations 2008 was in 2015; and on how many occasions each of those constabularies waived such fees for victims of crime in that year.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56371","56371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652737","2016-12-08","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress the Government has made on reforming pre-charge bail.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56340","56340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652738","2016-12-19","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been (a) identified, (b) assessed and (c) transferred under the family unity provisions of the Dublin III Regulation from Greece to the UK since January 2016.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56372","56372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652739","2016-12-08","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to answer Questions 47283 and 47284 tabled on 7 October 2016 by the right hon. Member for Slough.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56361","56361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652740","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55224, how many incidents of hate crime were recorded in 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56415","56415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652741","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce rural crime.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56403","56403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652742","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions in each month between 1 January 2015 and 30 November 2016 UK Visas and Immigration placed visas in the wrong passports; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure that no visas are placed in the wrong passports in future.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56369","56369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652743","2016-12-08","Department for International Development","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department ensures that aid finance is predictable and reliable for recipient countries.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Dame Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56339","56339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652744","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much overseas development aid funding was provided to the British Council in each of the last six years by country.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56257","56257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652745","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what financial contribution her Department has made to UNAIDS in each of the last five years; and what financial contribution her Department plans to make in 2016-17.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56248","56248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652746","2016-12-08","Department for International Development","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56234","56234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652747","2016-12-08","Department for International Development","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many unpaid internships there are in her Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56310","56310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652748","2016-12-08","Department for International Development","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which organisations her Department is working with to end modern day slavery.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56323","56323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652749","2016-12-08","Department for International Development","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on anti-human trafficking programmes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56324","56324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652750","2016-12-16","Department for International Development","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department has provided to the UN Trust Fund to End Violence Against Women in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56297","56297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652751","2016-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many unpaid internships there are in her Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56312","56312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652752","2016-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much her Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56235","56235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652753","2016-12-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56313","56313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652755","2016-12-08","Prime Minister","2016-12-06","To ask the Prime Minister, what meetings she has held with ministerial colleagues on the options for the future of Channel 4 since her appointment.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56395","56395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652756","2016-12-08","Prime Minister","2016-12-06","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she has had on the future of Channel 4 since her appointment.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56400","56400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652757","2016-12-08","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much extra money his Department has made available for the establishment of the Market Surveillance Unit in the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56398","56398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652758","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the DVLA on the recommendations of the report Driven to Despair, published by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman in October 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56413","56413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652759","2016-12-08","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency assesses people's fitness to drive within the targets set by the Government.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56386","56386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652760","2016-12-08","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency on resolving the grievances raised in the eight complaints investigated by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman in October 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56387","56387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652761","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department had with Volkswagen while considering its response to the Transport Select Committee's Third Report, Volkswagen emissions scandal and vehicle type approval, HC69.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56409","56409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652762","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2016 to Question 52776, and with reference to the letter of the same date from the Under-Secretary of State for Transport to the Chair of the Transport Committee, what the reasons are for the difference on whether Govia Thameslink Railway is able or not able to separate claims for force majeure from official and alleged unofficial action.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56345","56345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652763","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the top three main causes of late-running trains on the rail network were in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56263","56263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652764","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's forecast expenditure on smart ticketing schemes in the rail industry is in each year from 2015-16 to 2019-20; and what estimated completion dates there are for smart ticketing projects during that period.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56275","56275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652765","2016-12-08","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56236","56236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652766","2016-12-08","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average amount of CO2, in grammes, emitted per metric tonne of freight coming into or leaving the UK was, per kilometre of transportation, for (a) air freight, (b) road transport via the Channel tunnel, (c) rail via the Channel tunnel and (d) sea freight for the most recent 10 years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56223","56223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652767","2016-12-08","Department for Transport","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to accelerate access for train-operating companies delivering services (a) to the South West and (b) nationally to new passenger rolling stock.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56270","56270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652768","2016-12-08","Wales Office","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56315","56315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652769","2016-12-12","Women and Equalities","2016-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the expected budget is of the Equality and Human Rights Commission for each of the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56260","56260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652770","2016-12-12","Women and Equalities","2016-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much her Department spent on advertising the services provided by the Equality and Human Rights Commission in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56261","56261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652771","2016-12-12","Women and Equalities","2016-12-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent steps the Government has taken to tackle homophobic, biphobic and transphobic bullying; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56245","56245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652773","2016-12-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56238","56238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652774","2016-12-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what analysis the Government has conducted into the effect of the childcare costs element of universal credit on the household income of those who receive that credit.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56292","56292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652775","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55470, if he will (a) make it his Department's policy to make regular contact with people who are subject to a benefit sanction in order to discern whether they have used food banks at any time over the duration of the sanction, (b) make it his Department's policy to offer assistance with an application for a hardship payment to individuals who are identified as food bank users and (c) regularly publish data related to the use of food banks by people subject to benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56414","56414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652776","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55887, how many full-time equivalent members of staff his Department has employed to work on the design and implementation of universal credit in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15 and (f) 2015-16.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56404","56404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652777","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in the UK have had their eligibility for the motability scheme revoked before (a) mandatory reconsideration and (b) final appeal stage since April 2013.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56364","56364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652778","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was of the independent review into drug and alcohol addiction, and obesity; effects on employment outcomes, the report from which was published on 5 December 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56368","56368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652779","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the ruling of the Employment Tribunal on Aslam and others vs Uber of 28 October 2016, case number 2202550/2015, relating to the employment classification of Uber drivers, if he will estimate how many other such subordinate workers there are in the UK who are classified with a different legal status.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56428","56428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652780","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the ruling of the Employment Tribunal on Aslam and others vs Uber of 28 October 2016, case number 2202550/2015, relating to the employment classification of Uber drivers, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that workers so misclassified are receiving (a) the national living wage, (b) paid holidays and (c) other employee rights.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56426","56426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652781","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the ruling of the Employment Tribunal on Aslam and others vs Uber of 28 October 2016, case number 2202550/2015, relating to the employment classification of Uber drivers, if he will estimate the effect on national insurance tax receipts of the misclassification of workers in the gig economy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56427","56427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652782","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government plans to take to bring forward new gas generation in the event that no new combined cycle gas turbine capacity clears the capacity market auction in December 2016.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56262","56262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652783","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate the Government has made of the proportion that gas-fired generation will form of the new proposed 14GW of electricity interconnection to be developed by 2023.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56264","56264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652784","2016-12-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56299","56299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652785","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Director for Labour Market Enforcement will be appointed.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56294","56294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652786","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the annual costs to charities of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56239","56239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652787","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the proportion of medical research charities she expects to incur costs as a result of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56240","56240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652788","2016-12-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department spent on travel that was not standard class in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56225","56225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652789","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2016 to Question 55692, for what reasons his Department did not consult small and medium-sized businesses on the effect of a rise in the national living wage on productivity.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56259","56259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652790","2016-12-08","Department for International Trade","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56311","56311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652791","2016-12-08","Department for International Trade","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations his Department has received from the transition team of President-elect Donald Trump on future trade relations between the US and the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56348","56348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652792","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the effect on the NHS of the UK leaving the EU is not adverse.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56352","56352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652793","2016-12-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2016 to Question 55030, on health services and social services, if he will publish the findings of his Department's work with the Department for Health prior to the submission of notice of intention to leave the EU under Article 50 of the Lisbon Treaty.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56389","56389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652794","2016-12-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many unpaid internships there are in his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56306","56306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/656592","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to deter Russian expansion in eastern Europe; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907790","907790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/656593","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts on the commitment to spend at least two per cent of GDP on defence.","Biography information for Claire Perry","Claire Perry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907784","907784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/656594","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the Boeing P-8 Poseidon aircraft to be brought into operational service.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907788","907788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/656595","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to encourage innovation by defence suppliers.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907793","907793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/656596","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take to improve accommodation at RAF Odiham in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907787","907787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/656597","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department is providing to the UN and other aid agencies to deliver humanitarian aid to people in Aleppo.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907789","907789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/656598","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the UK is taking to defend NATO's eastern flank.","Biography information for Lord Davies of Gower","Byron Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907791","907791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652260","2016-12-07","Department for Transport","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the British Road Safety Statement, published in December 2015, what progress has been made on the revision of government buying guidelines to promote the uptake of procuring safer vehicles.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56093","56093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652261","2016-12-07","Cabinet Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many safer vehicles have been procured by each government department since the adoption of the Road Safety Statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56094","56094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652262","2016-12-08","Cabinet Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have verified their identity using the gov.uk Verify system since its inception.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56146","56146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652263","2016-12-08","Cabinet Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he expects the gov.uk Verify to be in use by the 19 local authorities participating in proposed local government trials of that service.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56147","56147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652264","2016-12-07","HM Treasury","2016-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the reported dash for cash policy relating to senior managers at the Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56156","56156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652265","2016-12-07","HM Treasury","2016-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 55190, what estimate he has made of the proportion of spending from the National Productivity Investment Fund to be allocated to projects outside London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56178","56178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652266","2016-12-07","HM Treasury","2016-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people employed in human resources roles in his Department have (a) prior experience and (b) qualifications in human resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56120","56120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652267","2016-12-07","HM Treasury","2016-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the change required in the (a) cost and (b) number of personnel required for customs administration if the UK departs the (i) EU single market and (ii) EU customs union.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56122","56122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652268","2016-12-07","HM Treasury","2016-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to increase duty paid on white cider products.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56138","56138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652269","2016-12-07","HM Treasury","2016-12-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made in recovering unpaid taxes following publication of the Panama papers.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56060","56060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652270","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has allocated as part of the settlement for contaminated land activities to each local authority in England in 2016-17.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56066","56066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652271","2016-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people employed in human resources roles in his Department have (a) prior experience and (b) qualifications in human resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56110","56110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652272","2016-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many young people in Merseyside and Halton have benefited from the Government's Help to Buy scheme.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56135","56135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652273","2016-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department offers to countries of the Western Balkans that seek membership of the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56127","56127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652274","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the means of accountability are to central government of the Coast to Capital Local Enterprise Partnership.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56101","56101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652275","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he last met the Chairman and Chief Executive of the Coast to Capital Local Enterprise Partnership.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56102","56102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652276","2016-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for the announcement of individual allocations for each Local Enterprise Partnership under the third round of growth deals.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56155","56155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652277","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the exceptional circumstances were in relation to his decision to permit building on greenbelt land in Sutton Coldfield.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56197","56197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652278","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the difference in price between houses built on (a) greenbelt and (b) non-greenbelt land.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56198","56198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652279","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he took to prioritise the development of brownfield sites in Birmingham prior to his decision to permit building on greenbelt land in Sutton Coldfield.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56199","56199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652280","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what alternative options he considered  prior to his decision to permit building on greenbelt land in Sutton Coldfield.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56200","56200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652281","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps were taken to identify sites of brownfield land under 600 square metres in size suitable for housing development in Birmingham prior to his decision to permit building on greenbelt land in Sutton Coldfield.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56201","56201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652282","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to support people in care homes who receive unexpected (a) telephone and (b) management fees bills.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56207","56207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652283","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Gambling Commission report, Young People and Gambling, published in November 2016, what steps her Department is taking to prevent children aged 11 to 16 from participating in gambling.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56206","56206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652284","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the oral evidence by the Chair of Ofcom to the Culture, Media and Sport Committee on 22 November 2016, on the outstanding range of recommendations made for appointment to the board of Channel 4, for what reason she rejected one of those recommendations.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56196","56196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652285","2016-12-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many people employed in human resources roles in her Department have (a) prior experience and (b) qualifications in human resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56111","56111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652286","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 1.20 of the Autumn Statement 2016, what proportion of that investment in broadband will be allocated to projects in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56067","56067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652287","2016-12-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 1.20 of the Autumn Statement 2016, how her Department plans to determine the allocation of broadband investment.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56068","56068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652288","2016-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2016 to Question 52667, if he will provide a breakdown of expenses claimed by the 127 investigators employed by Red Snapper.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56054","56054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652289","2016-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people employed in human resources roles in his Department have (a) prior experience and (b) qualifications in human resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56112","56112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652290","2016-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which of the UK's international allies have procured P-8 Poseidon aircraft; and what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the number of the UK's allies which have procured such aircraft on the way in which the UK operates its maritime patrol aircraft.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56098","56098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652291","2016-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the UK's allies on the interoperability potential between the UK's new maritime patrol aircraft and international fleets.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56099","56099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652292","2016-12-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what capacity exists in the UK armed forces to (a) use and (b) deploy Joint Precision Airdrop Systems.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56104","56104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652293","2016-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Government's plans are for the number of Iraq Historic Allegations Team investigators when the number of cases of that team is reduced to the planned 60 active investigations in 2017.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56187","56187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652294","2016-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much legal aid has been paid to (a) Public Interest Lawyers and (b) Leigh Day for cases related to (i) the Iraq Historic Allegations Team and (ii) Operation Northmoor.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56186","56186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652295","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 55124, whether her Department communicated the decision on the transfer of ownership of the former Glenburn Sports College site in Skelmersdale from her Department to Lancashire County Council to bodies other than Lancashire County Council.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56194","56194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652296","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start centres have closed in Yorkshire and the Humber since 2010; and where such centres were located.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56193","56193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652297","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2016 to Question 54109, on Institute for Apprenticeships, whether any of the potential sites under consideration is in Sheffield.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56129","56129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652298","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Equality and Human Rights Commission report, Religion or belief - is the law working, published in December 2016, if she will obtain independent legal advice to establish whether sections 60 (4) and (5) of the School Standards Framework Act (SSFA) comply with the EU Employment Equality Directive Article 4 (2) and whether exceptions allowed under the SSFA are legitimate and proportionate.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56128","56128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652299","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many three and four year old children in England have a disability; and how many of those children are benefiting from free childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56140","56140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652300","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Ofqual's Vocational Qualifications Dataset published in October 2016, how many level 3 childcare certificates were awarded in each year from 2012 to 2016 by region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56163","56163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652301","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to improve regional inequalities in early years provision; and if she will make it her policy to include measures to improve such inequalities in the Northern Powerhouse schools strategy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56164","56164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652302","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the number of (a) Russell Group graduates and (b) graduates with a first class degree working in primary education in deprived communities.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56159","56159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652303","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of school-based early years providers in (a) academies and (b) free schools had staff with (i) Early Years Professional Status, (ii) Early Years Teacher Status or (iii) Qualified Teacher Status in each year from 2014 to 2016.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56160","56160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652304","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much public funding the Education Funding Agency expects to (a) successfully claw back and (b) fail to claw back from free schools which have failed to attract the number of students initially planned for the current academic year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56161","56161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652305","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department allocated from the public purse for the (a) London Schools Challenge and (b) Northern Powerhouse Schools Strategy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56152","56152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652306","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost of closure of Baverstock Academy in Druids Heath, Birmingham.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56149","56149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652307","2016-12-08","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average cost is of a new (a) academy secondary, (b) secondary free and (c) maintained secondary school.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56150","56150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652308","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much the Education Funding Agency identified as needing to be clawed back from new free schools which failed to attract the planned number of students in each academic year since 2009-10; and how many free schools were identified as having funds which needed to be clawed back in each of those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56173","56173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652309","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding the Education Funding Agency has clawed back from free schools due to such schools admitting fewer pupils than planned in each academic year since 2009-10; and how much such funding has not yet been clawed back from such schools relating to each of those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56162","56162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652310","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial assistance is available from the public purse to secondary schools seeking to run a summer school programme for disadvantaged pupils.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56180","56180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652311","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial support her Department plans to offer secondary schools which provide summer school programmes for pupils transitioning from primary school to secondary school for September 2017.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56181","56181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652312","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people employed in human resources roles in her Department have (a) prior experience and (b) qualifications in human resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56113","56113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652313","2016-12-07","Department for Education","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish all the submissions to her Department's consultation, Early years funding: changes to funding for three and four-year olds.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56058","56058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652314","2016-12-08","Department for Transport","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what mobilisation of the UK's national resources took place during Storm Angus; which bridges were so protected during that Storm; what infrastructure was so protected during that Storm; and whether the Army was called to provide assistance during that Storm.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56063","56063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652315","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to bring forward proposals to amend the Pet Animals Act 1951 to prohibit repeat breeding and sale from the family cat or cats.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56069","56069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652316","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether temporary flood barriers, mobile water pumps and incident command vehicles were deployed during Storm Angus.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56064","56064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652317","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to ensure that the UK meets the EU target to reuse and recycle 50 per cent of household waste by 2020.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56065","56065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652318","2016-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people employed in human resources roles in her Department have (a) prior experience and (b) qualifications in human resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56114","56114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652319","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much each of the top 50 recipients of funding from the Common Agricultural Policy received in 2015.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56079","56079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652320","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will establish a Land Reform Review Group for England.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56080","56080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652321","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what definition her Department uses of the term grass-fed; and what guidance her Department issues to farmers on the use of the term grass-fed when marketing meat.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56081","56081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652322","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding has been allocated to (a) St Helens, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK for flood prevention and remediation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56073","56073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652323","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding for flood prevention her Department has allocated to each local authority in 2016-17.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56074","56074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652324","2016-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to improve enforcement of (a) paragraph 15 on environmental enrichment for pigs of Schedule 8 to the Aftercare of Farmed Animals (England) Regulations 2007 and (b) paragraph 5 on tail docking of pigs of Schedule 3 to the Mutilations (Permitted Procedures) (England) Regulations 2007.","Biography information for Sir Alan Meale","Sir Alan Meale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56158","56158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652325","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2016 to Question 55450, if she will publish the reasons why the Animal and Plant Health Agency refused to grant import permits in those cases; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56145","56145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652326","2016-12-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to prevent diamondback moths from destroying seasonal Brussels sprouts crops.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56210","56210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652327","2016-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information the Government holds on whether any UK nationals sit as judges in Israeli military courts.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56157","56157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652328","2016-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to Early Day Motion (EDM) 504 of Session 2015-16, Prisoners of Conscience in Eritrea, if he will meet with the Eritrean Ambassador to the UK to discuss the cases of Dawit Isaal, Aster Fissehatsion and the other political prisoners referred to in that EDM.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56143","56143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652329","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to raise reports of human rights violations in the United Arab Emirates during the 2017 UK-UAE Year of Culture.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56107","56107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652330","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British women were arrested for reporting rape in the United Arab Emirates (a) between 2011 and 2016 and (b) during 2016.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56108","56108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652331","2016-12-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) his US counterpart and (b) the UN on the potential use of the Joint Precision Airdrop System to deliver humanitarian relief supplies to (i) Aleppo and (ii) elsewhere in Syria.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56103","56103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652332","2016-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2016 to Question 54666, how many fines have been issued to those caught damaging buildings in the British Indian Ocean Territory for each year in the last 30 years for which records are available; and what the (a) individual and (b) total amount of such fines was in each such year.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56089","56089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652333","2016-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2016 to Question 54664, when the contract between Sure telecoms and the British Indian Ocean Territory Administration was agreed; when that contract will next be tendered for; and what the value is of that contract.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56090","56090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652334","2016-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the risk of piracy in the waters of the British Indian Ocean Territory.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56091","56091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652335","2016-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many people employed in human resources roles in his Department have (a) prior experience and (b) qualifications in human resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56115","56115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652336","2016-12-07","Department of Health","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to fund the expansion of the NHS graduate management scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56061","56061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652337","2016-12-07","Department of Health","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many paediatric intensive care beds were free and available for use on 3 and 4 December 2016 in NHS hospitals in England.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56059","56059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652338","2016-12-07","Department of Health","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were admitted to hospital for obesity-related illnesses in each calendar year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56055","56055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652339","2016-12-07","Department of Health","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people admitted to accident and emergency departments for flu were (a) pregnant, (b) suffering from a long-term health condition and (c) 65 years and over in each calendar year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56056","56056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652340","2016-12-07","Department of Health","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people employed in human resources roles in his Department have (a) prior experience and (b) qualifications in human resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56116","56116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652341","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to require tobacco manufacturers to publish sales data at a local level; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56082","56082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652342","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to reduce the smoking rate in people under the age of 16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56083","56083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/652343","2016-12-08","Department of Health","2016-12-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the role of sustainability and transformation plans is in (a) promoting the use of Stop Smoking Services and (b) implementing a more integrated approach between public health teams on smoking cessation and local efforts on tobacco control.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56084","56084"
